<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Scott Walker - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRFIwZW0xMEVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-CA&amp;gl=CA&amp;ceid=CA:en</link><language>en-CA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:35:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Wisconsin Senate Passes Bill Limiting Governor's Powers - TIME</title><link>http://time.com/5471065/wisconsin-senate-governor-bill/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780122510226</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 20:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://time.com/5471065/wisconsin-senate-governor-bill/" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Senate Passes Bill Limiting Governor's Powers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TIME&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com/news/world/2018/12/03/wisconsin-republicans-forge-ahead-with-power-stripping-bills.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Republicans forge ahead with power-stripping bills&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Toronto Star&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/world/wisconsin-repoublicans-weaken-governor-attorney-general-1.4933168" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Republicans OK bills to weaken incoming Democratic governor, attorney general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC.ca&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com/news/world/2018/12/05/wisconsin-republicans-approve-bills-stripping-power-from-incoming-democratic-governor.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Republicans approve bills stripping power from incoming Democratic governor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Toronto Star&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/republican-wisconsin-lame-duck-vote-majority-early-voting-attorney-general-governor-tony-evers-josh-a8668636.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lame-duck Wisconsin Republicans pass vote to restrict incoming Democrats in controversial 'power grab'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqhQEICiJ_Q0JJU1dUb0pjM1J2Y25rdE16WXdTa3dLRVFpU3A5Q2pqWUFNRWZsMXBCZEc0VVRkRWpkWGFYTmpiMjV6YVc0Z1VtVndkV0pzYVdOaGJuTWdiVzkyWlNCMGJ5QjNaV0ZyWlc0Z2FXNWpiMjFwYm1jZ1JHVnRiMk55WVhSektBQVAB?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="http://time.com">TIME</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/6FMRzlLYFIVkz-E2DI2QDqfhOAa3wGPzyLR3NKYQNS7pZ55qD3z7r1ZVrpD8i5U1pGIUvUYjLve55O_1SALbYvwxxIUpInya6r2aB46vhS7Q5RIRjZb1CJk4_YSDzWV9blZfKA=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Appeals to Scott Walker: Don't stain legacy, veto bills - National Post</title><link>https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/democrat-says-hell-appeal-to-walker-to-veto-gop-power-play</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYGh0dHBzOi8vbmF0aW9uYWxwb3N0LmNvbS9wbW4vbmV3cy1wbW4vZGVtb2NyYXQtc2F5cy1oZWxsLWFwcGVhbC10by13YWxrZXItdG8tdmV0by1nb3AtcG93ZXItcGxhedIBrQFodHRwczovL25hdGlvbmFscG9zdC1jb20uY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy9uYXRpb25hbHBvc3QuY29tL3Btbi9uZXdzLXBtbi9kZW1vY3JhdC1zYXlzLWhlbGwtYXBwZWFsLXRvLXdhbGtlci10by12ZXRvLWdvcC1wb3dlci1wbGF5L2FtcD9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/democrat-says-hell-appeal-to-walker-to-veto-gop-power-play" target="_blank"&gt;Appeals to Scott Walker: Don't stain legacy, veto bills&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;National Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. — A bipartisan group of political figures appealed to Gov. Scott Walker to avoid staining his legacy and behaving like a sore loser by signing ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://nationalpost.com">National Post</source></item><item><title>What are the risks of the Amazon deal? Ask Scott Walker. - POLITICO</title><link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/14/amazon-new-headquarters-reaction-foxconn-scott-walker-966375</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFKADzT-sXvRwlfDHnJsc7sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4Zn5CjCu8uACMLTRlgY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/14/amazon-new-headquarters-reaction-foxconn-scott-walker-966375" target="_blank"&gt;What are the risks of the Amazon deal? Ask Scott Walker.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;POLITICO&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opponents of Amazon's public giveaways say those governing Virginia and New York should take heed.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.politico.com">POLITICO</source></item><item><title>Behind the Scenes in Wisconsin: A Republican Power Play, Months in the Making - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/07/us/wisconsin-republicans-power.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEs2EN-68ZTQoIyes6z6SG8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:35:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/07/us/wisconsin-republicans-power.html" target="_blank"&gt;Behind the Scenes in Wisconsin: A Republican Power Play, Months in the Making&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. — Last spring, after Wisconsin Democrats seized a state legislative seat long held by Republicans and sent a liberal justice to the State Supreme Court, Republicans began to worry. Gov. Scott Walker, preparing to seek a third term, warned his fellow Republicans on Twitter of the “risk of a blue wave” and publicly urged them not to be complacent with fall elections ahead. During the same period, an aggressive and methodical alternate strategy was emerging behind the scenes. Over the summer, Robin Vos, the speaker of the Wisconsin Assembly, sought a detailed analysis from the st...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Effort to weaken governors stirs separation-of-powers debate - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/20a04ae0546d487881bb77a6d97b74ba</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFFsX13uI6SWWV_JTGtheBgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:14:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/20a04ae0546d487881bb77a6d97b74ba" target="_blank"&gt;Effort to weaken governors stirs separation-of-powers debate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MILWAUKEE (AP) — If Democrats sue to prevent Republicans from diluting the powers of newly elected governors and attorneys general in Wisconsin and Michigan, the lawsuits will probably center on one question: Are lawmakers usurping authority that belongs to the executive branch? The legal threat arose after Republicans passed bills Wednesday that would give lawmakers leverage over actions previous governors and attorneys general could carry out on their own. If the bills are signed by outgoing GOP Gov. Scott Walker, lawmakers will decide when the state can withdraw from lawsuits, and the ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Appeals to Scott Walker: Don't stain legacy, veto bills - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/7b001b3a2c6547b4b334bd26c9d146ad</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbmv9UpbURxleCgZESTLWcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:16:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/7b001b3a2c6547b4b334bd26c9d146ad" target="_blank"&gt;Appeals to Scott Walker: Don't stain legacy, veto bills&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — A bipartisan group of political figures appealed to Gov. Scott Walker to avoid staining his legacy and behaving like a sore loser by signing legislation that would weaken the powers of the Democrat who defeated him. Rather than notching another partisan victory in his final weeks in office, they said, Walker should think bigger. Think of your recently deceased father, they pleaded. Think of former President George H.W. Bush. Think of Christ. "You can have a long, successful career ahead," longtime Republican and major GOP donor Sheldon Lubar wrote to Walker in a deeply ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The Hawk That’s Helping China - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/07/opinion/trump-china-trade-war.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDfWhQmrAwMmqC4_Db89DfcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwpoIY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:08:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/07/opinion/trump-china-trade-war.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Hawk That’s Helping China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article is part of the Opinion Today newsletter. You can sign up here to receive the newsletter each weekday. First, China: Tensions keep rising between the United States and China, which isn’t an altogether bad thing. For too long, American leaders have failed to respond adequately to China’s increasing assertiveness — its theft of intellectual property, hostility to foreign companies, aggression in Asia and imperial ambitions around the world. A more hawkish policy toward China makes sense. Unfortunately, President Trump is pursuing a version of clueless hawkishness. His administrati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin and Michigan Republicans try to curb incoming Democratic attorneys general - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/wisconsin-and-michigan-republicans-try-to-curb-incoming-democratic-attorneys-general-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFbMkNqpzDhASYQAxaw_G4wqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/wisconsin-and-michigan-republicans-try-to-curb-incoming-democratic-attorneys-general-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin and Michigan Republicans try to curb incoming Democratic attorneys general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASSOCIATED PRESS By Associated Press Efforts also afoot to rein in governors’ powers after election of Democrats State Sen. Tim Carpenter, a Democrat from Milwaukee, questions a list of appointment referrals submitted to the State Senate during its lame-duck session this week. Associated Press MADISON, Wis. (AP) — Republicans pushing to hang on to power in Wisconsin and Michigan aren’t stopping at curbing the authority of incoming Democratic governors. They’re also trying to hamstring Democrats who are about to take over as attorneys general. The moves underscore how attorneys general have ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Lame-Duck Republicans Stick It To The Poor In Wisconsin - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/lame-duck-republicans-stick-it-to-the-poor-in-wisconsin_us_5c080567e4b069028dc5eb62</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF2alK8nrjsHf83Fd5NicOUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/lame-duck-republicans-stick-it-to-the-poor-in-wisconsin_us_5c080567e4b069028dc5eb62" target="_blank"&gt;Lame-Duck Republicans Stick It To The Poor In Wisconsin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wisconsin Republicans are about to lose a governor who supports their policies to limit assistance to the poor, so they just locked them in before a newly elected Democrat takes office. In the early morning hours of a lame-duck session Wednesday, state lawmakers approved legislation that would prevent Governor-elect Tony Evers and Attorney General-elect Josh Kaul from carrying out their campaign promises to protect and expand food, medical and unemployment assistance for low-income Wisconsinites. Specifically, the bills curtail the governor’s ability to make administrative changes to joint ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Correction: Wisconsin-Legislature-Lame-Duck story - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/02dd4f5766da4c9a955c3a6ac47398fe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKP6Lx12uRNAQF3celZUpLsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:48:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/02dd4f5766da4c9a955c3a6ac47398fe" target="_blank"&gt;Correction: Wisconsin-Legislature-Lame-Duck story&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — In a story Dec. 5 about lame-duck legislation approved by Wisconsin lawmakers that would curtail powers of the incoming Democratic governor and attorney general, The Associated Press reported erroneously that Gov. Scott Walker would have 10 days from the date the bills reach his desk to sign or veto them. Walker would have six days to act. A corrected version of the story is below: Next governor will ask Walker to veto lame-duck legislation Next Wisconsin governor will ask Walker to veto GOP legislation to weaken new administration By SCOTT BAUER and TODD RICHMOND Assoc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Republicans in Wisconsin, Michigan move to curb Democrats' power - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/republicans-wisconsin-michigan-move-curb-democrats-power-181207171032406.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAZnkkB3KghsMs3nuaekFnkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:41:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/republicans-wisconsin-michigan-move-curb-democrats-power-181207171032406.html" target="_blank"&gt;Republicans in Wisconsin, Michigan move to curb Democrats' power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican-controlled legislatures in Wisconsin and Michigan this week sought to curb the power of recently-elected Democratic governors and others, eliciting howls of protest from critics who called it a power grab after President Donald Trump's party lost ground in November's midterm elections. The Republican efforts, which echoed actions taken by politicians in North Carolina in 2016, threatened to further deepen political rancor in the key Midwestern battleground states. "While you can find isolated incidents where legislatures have tried to hamstring governors before, there has been no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Michigan G.O.P. Starts Limiting Power of Incoming Democratic Leaders - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/us/politics/michigan-republicans-power.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZkpceOymTqSP8zeA_7oJkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloEY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:22:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/us/politics/michigan-republicans-power.html" target="_blank"&gt;Michigan G.O.P. Starts Limiting Power of Incoming Democratic Leaders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LANSING, Mich. — Michigan Republicans, following the tactics of conservative lawmakers in Wisconsin, moved on Thursday to start limiting the power of the incoming Democratic secretary of state and set the stage for additional curbs on the Democrats who will take over as governor and attorney general in January. The G.O.P.-led State Senate in Michigan, voting largely along party lines, passed a bill that strips the incoming secretary of state of the authority to oversee campaign finance issues and hands it to a new bipartisan commission. Other bills, which are likely to be approved next week...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Foxconn or Foxgone? Tariffs, Wisconsin, and iPhone fires - TechCrunch</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/12/05/foxconn-or-foxgone-tariffs-wisconsin-and-iphone-fires/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENPYT2ghU7sPRfC5zP0BrpoqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowlIEBMLEXMOc_</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:13:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://techcrunch.com/2018/12/05/foxconn-or-foxgone-tariffs-wisconsin-and-iphone-fires/" target="_blank"&gt;Foxconn or Foxgone? Tariffs, Wisconsin, and iPhone fires&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TechCrunch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TOPSHOT - Wisconsin Governor Scott Walker (2nd L), US President Donald Trump (C), Foxconn Chairman Terry Gou (2nd R), Speaker of the House Paul Ryan (R) and an unidetified official (L) participate in a groundbreaking for a Foxconn facility at the Wisconsin Valley Science and Technology Park on June 28, 2018 in Mount Pleasant, Wisconsin. (Photo by Brendan Smialowski / AFP) (Photo credit should read BRENDAN SMIALOWSKI/AFP/Getty Images) First some notes on SoftBank’s rumored expansion into China and its weird fund math, then Foxconn, and then quick notes on tech depression, Huawei, and more. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://techcrunch.com">TechCrunch</source></item><item><title>This Is What It Looks Like to Steal Power From Your Voters - Jezebel</title><link>https://theslot.jezebel.com/this-is-what-it-looks-like-to-steal-power-from-your-vot-1830881192</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDESVxMM7Uk8iZ2I8qUrzoAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlYECMLFMMOKjHg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://theslot.jezebel.com/this-is-what-it-looks-like-to-steal-power-from-your-vot-1830881192" target="_blank"&gt;This Is What It Looks Like to Steal Power From Your Voters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Jezebel&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image: AP Before the sun came up on Wednesday morning, Wisconsin’s lame-duck Republican-controlled state Senate passed a bill by a one-vote margin that would limit early voting and the power of the state’s incoming Democratic governor and attorney general. It was a last-minute power grab, an attempt by state Republicans to instill a de-facto permanent majority and override the will of the voters who kicked them out of power. A few hours after it passed the state Senate, the Republican-controlled state Assembly sent it to Governor Scott Walker’s desk on a 56-27 vote. More on the legislation ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://theslot.jezebel.com">Jezebel</source></item><item><title>Michigan's Lame-Duck Republicans Waddle Away from Democracy - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michigans-lame-duck-republicans-waddle-away-from-democracy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAvrmBzEFpwKPI-UuReCVowqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:07:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/michigans-lame-duck-republicans-waddle-away-from-democracy" target="_blank"&gt;Michigan's Lame-Duck Republicans Waddle Away from Democracy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast You’ve read about what Republicans are doing in Wisconsin, North Carolina, and Michigan, where GOP-held legislatures are to varying degrees trying to undo things the voters did on Nov. 6 that don’t suit them. Wisconsin has attracted national attention because outgoing Governor Scott Walker is a man liberals love to hate, and North Carolina because the state’s Moral Monday protests have enjoyed national attention for two years now. But what’s happening in Michigan may be the most egregious of the three. Consider: On one front, the Repu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin Republicans Are Shooting Themselves In the Foot - The Atlantic</title><link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2018/12/wisconsin-debacle-wasnt-worth-it-gop/577522/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMoZs8thzqWcFu6vBOeU6oMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowm_EEMKAiMJXamQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2018/12/wisconsin-debacle-wasnt-worth-it-gop/577522/" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Republicans Are Shooting Themselves In the Foot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Atlantic&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Wisconsin GOP’s lame-duck power play was not the death of democracy. But it was bad enough: petty, vindictive, and self-destructive. It was, as the saying goes, worse than a crime. It was a blunder. And for what? In its arrogant insularity, the Wisconsin GOP became a national symbol of win-at-all-costs, norms-be-damned politics. Cut through the overwrought rhetoric and what did the Republican legislators actually accomplish? Not really a whole lot; certainly not enough to justify the political damage they’ve inflicted on themselves. They have managed to energize the progressive base, ex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theatlantic.com">The Atlantic</source></item><item><title>Here's how Wisconsin Republicans want to strip power from incoming Democrats - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/wisconsin-republicans-strip-power-democrats/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC230c2vgMqLifF9S2YriHkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:12:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/wisconsin-republicans-strip-power-democrats/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Here's how Wisconsin Republicans want to strip power from incoming Democrats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker is on his way out, defeated in November by Democratic Gov.-elect Tony Evers. But with an assist from his GOP allies in the state legislature, Walker appear poised to sign off on a suite of measures designed to strip power from his successor. The bills on Walker's desk would weaken the state's executive branch at precisely the time Democrats are set to reclaim it after nearly a decade on the outs. The legislation also targets the authorities of incoming Democratic Attorney General Josh Kaul, who, like Evers, campaigned heavily on promises to expand heal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Republicans are staging mini-coups across the US - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/republicans-are-staging-mini-coups-across-the-us</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPUubWmuFFVPl4ZUHPCA2c0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:01:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/republicans-are-staging-mini-coups-across-the-us" target="_blank"&gt;Republicans are staging mini-coups across the US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democracies empower the will of majorities. In the US, Republican lawmakers on both the state and national level have rejected that basic principle. In a lame-duck session in the wee hours of Wednesday morning, Republican legislators in the state of Wisconsin passed a sweeping bill designed to radically check the powers of the incoming governor. The result of this 11th-hour tactic is an attack on progressive causes, the integrity of the electoral process, and democratic accountability. Last month, Democrat Tony Evers won the state gubernatorial race, unseating Republican incumbent Scott Wal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Lone Wisconsin Republican Who Opposed Stealing Democrats’ Power Explains Why - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/robert-cowles-wisconsin_us_5c0959b1e4b0844cda511aed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwtOrPj3ovXJe1DJYfNH9QqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:59:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/robert-cowles-wisconsin_us_5c0959b1e4b0844cda511aed" target="_blank"&gt;Lone Wisconsin Republican Who Opposed Stealing Democrats’ Power Explains Why&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The vote by the Republican-controlled Wisconsin Legislature to strip power away from the incoming governor and attorney general split for the most part along predictable partisan lines. Not surprisingly, Democrats didn’t go along with weakening those positions just as members of their own party are set to take the offices. In the state Assembly, the measure passed on a party-line vote, 56-27. In the Senate, it passed 17-16, with every Democrat opposed. One Republican notably broke ranks and also voted against it. State Sen. Robert Cowles (R), who represents Green Bay, released a statement T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Are Rural Voters the ‘Real’ Voters? Wisconsin Republicans Seem to Think So - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/upshot/wisconsin-republicans-rural-urban-voters.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBPePssHkkDHXFd1l1VP43oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:54:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/upshot/wisconsin-republicans-rural-urban-voters.html" target="_blank"&gt;Are Rural Voters the ‘Real’ Voters? Wisconsin Republicans Seem to Think So&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In much of Wisconsin, “Madison and Milwaukee” are code words (to some, dog whistles) for the parts of the state that are nonwhite, elite, different: The cities are where people don’t have to work hard with their hands, because they’re collecting welfare or public-sector paychecks. That stereotype updates a very old idea in American politics, one pervading Wisconsin’s bitter Statehouse fights today and increasingly those in other states: Urban voters are an exception. If you discount them, you get a truer picture of the politics — and the will of voters — in a state. Thomas Jefferson believe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin Republicans are trying to erase their 2018 loss - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/wisconsin-2018-state-legislature-tony-evers-scott-walker/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPCGWU0_wA_Bbf7Ml12osl8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:12:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/wisconsin-2018-state-legislature-tony-evers-scott-walker/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Republicans are trying to erase their 2018 loss&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elections have consequences. That adage, which has long been part of the bedrock of our democracy, doesn't appear to be the case anymore -- at least in Wisconsin. Earlier this week, the Republican-held state legislature passed a series of measures aimed at tying the hands of the incoming Democratic governor and attorney general. Among them, from CNN's report: "Wisconsin is now expected to reduce its number of early voting days, restrict gubernatorial influence over a powerful economic agency [Democratic Gov-elect Tony] Evers sought to disband, and require legislative backing for certain dec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Michigan Republicans vote to strip power from incoming Democrat - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/06/republicans-michigan-wisconsin-strip-power-incoming-democrats</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDK4XCV9mP5s1Ezc-G-eixIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:53:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/06/republicans-michigan-wisconsin-strip-power-incoming-democrats" target="_blank"&gt;Michigan Republicans vote to strip power from incoming Democrat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Republican-led Michigan senate has voted to bar the incoming Democratic secretary of state from enforcing campaign finance law, one day after Republicans in Wisconsin similarly took action to restrict the power of newly elected Democrats. The 25-11 vote, which fell along party lines, was the latest salvo by Republicans seeking to capitalize on a lame-duck session before handing control of the state’s top elected offices to Democrats. Related: Wisconsin Republicans approve bill to weaken incoming Democratic governor The measure is among several that opponents say ignore voters who spoke ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin Republicans Approve 82 Scott Walker Appointees In 1 Day - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/scott-walker-82-appointees_us_5c084080e4b0844cda4f9959</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAi2zCtfUw95iNpPIJoMk7cqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:27:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/scott-walker-82-appointees_us_5c084080e4b0844cda4f9959" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Republicans Approve 82 Scott Walker Appointees In 1 Day&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republicans in the Wisconsin state Senate rushed to approve 82 of Gov. Scott Walker’s appointees, a month after voters chose not to reelect the Republican. The GOP-controlled Legislature has been working with Walker to make sure that the incoming governor and attorney general, who are both Democrats, won’t have as much power as their Republican predecessors. They’ve passed a series of bills in a lame-duck session that amount to nothing less than a brazen partisan power grab, taking responsibilities away from the governor and attorney general and giving them to the heavily gerrymandered Wisc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Evers to appeal to Walker to veto GOP power play - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/dbded03c16ce4c3c8609d01b403e57d9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHZ6AM9I5Y0PkSFiuTXPc3EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:05:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/dbded03c16ce4c3c8609d01b403e57d9" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Evers to appeal to Walker to veto GOP power play&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — The Latest on Wisconsin Republican lawmakers moving to limit the powers of the incoming Democratic governor and attorney general (all times local): 4 p.m. The incoming Democratic governor of Wisconsin says he will make a personal appeal to outgoing Republican Gov. Scott Walker to veto legislation that weakens the new administration's powers. Gov.-elect Tony Evers said Wednesday that he also wants Wisconsin residents to urge Walker not to sign the bills. If the bills are signed, Evers says, he will explore litigation or other ideas to ensure the legislation "does not get...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Ron Johnson Dismisses Uproar Over Wisconsin GOP Power Grab As 'Way Overblown' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/wisconsin-ron-johnson-evers-power_us_5c084e24e4b069028dc644e1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGN0UCcgoa0py00OO1n2IoQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:02:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/wisconsin-ron-johnson-evers-power_us_5c084e24e4b069028dc644e1" target="_blank"&gt;Ron Johnson Dismisses Uproar Over Wisconsin GOP Power Grab As 'Way Overblown'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― Sen. Ron Johnson (R-Wis.) says the uproar over the extraordinary proposals aimed at reducing the power of incoming Gov. Tony Evers and other Democrats in Wisconsin is “way overblown.” The Republican-controlled state legislature in Wisconsin passed a series of proposals shortly before dawn on Wednesday that would cut early voting in the state, give Republicans full control of a state economic development agency, block the governor’s ability to write regulations and allow the legislature to hire its own lawyers to file lawsuits on behalf of the state. The GOP measures are being w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Republican Businessman Sheldon Lubar Calls Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker 'Conniving' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sheldon-lubar-scott-walker-wisconsin_us_5c07ef92e4b0fc2361125f52</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJUpFN6fKg_9GRXeUjC_bd8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:01:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sheldon-lubar-scott-walker-wisconsin_us_5c07ef92e4b0fc2361125f52" target="_blank"&gt;Republican Businessman Sheldon Lubar Calls Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker 'Conniving'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A top Republican businessman in Wisconsin is urging Gov. Scott Walker (R) and other lawmakers to stop what he called their “conniving” to quell early voting measures and diminish the powers of recently elected Democrats. Millionaire Sheldon Lubar was voted one of the most influential businessmen in Milwaukee in 2015, and had previously donated to one of Walker’s campaigns. But he called out the state’s conservative leadership Tuesday after Republican lawmakers moved ahead with a striking power grab against incoming Democrats, including Gov.-elect Tony Evers, who defeated Walker last month. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin Republicans Defiantly Move to Limit the Power of Incoming Democrats - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/05/us/wisconsin-power-republicans.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIx8JaU8M6djZIfPoajPK3AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:46:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/05/us/wisconsin-power-republicans.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Republicans Defiantly Move to Limit the Power of Incoming Democrats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. — When Wisconsin Republicans pushed through a sweeping set of bills Wednesday to limit the power of the state’s newly elected Democrats, it was another hardball maneuver by a man who has played a key role in driving the state sharply to the right. In the days after the Republican governor’s stunning loss last month — the end of eight years of one-party control of the state’s government — Robin Vos, the Republican speaker of the Assembly, was defiant. “We are going to stand like bedrock to guarantee that Wisconsin does not go back,” Mr. Vos told local reporters after the midter...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Michigan Republicans following Wisconsin's lead in curbing Democrats' power - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-states/michigan-republicans-following-wisconsins-lead-in-curbing-democrats-power-idUSKBN1O5289</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECjGhR0uhlP6X14PLhjwXkkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:00:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-states/michigan-republicans-following-wisconsins-lead-in-curbing-democrats-power-idUSKBN1O5289" target="_blank"&gt;Michigan Republicans following Wisconsin's lead in curbing Democrats' power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A day after Wisconsin Republicans approved a package of bills intended to restrict the powers of incoming Democratic leaders, Republican lawmakers in Michigan advanced a similar effort despite an outcry from Democrats. The Michigan state Senate voted on Thursday to strip the power to oversee campaign finance from the newly elected Democratic secretary of state, Jocelyn Benson, instead handing the authority to a bipartisan commission. The vote came after the state House of Representatives on Wednesday passed a bill that would allow lawmakers to sidestep the attorney general in litigation inv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin Democrats look at legal options on lame-duck bills - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/wisconsin-democratic-lawsuits/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGxhmryjyrFd1xjpy6GoxSIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:16:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/wisconsin-democratic-lawsuits/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Democrats look at legal options on lame-duck bills&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democrats in Wisconsin are carefully considering legal options after an extraordinary lame-duck session produced a flurry of GOP-led legislation Tuesday night aimed at diminishing the power of the state's incoming Democratic governor. If outgoing Republican Gov. Scott Walker signs the measures, expect immediate court action. The measures range from efforts to reduce early voting days to restrict the governor's influence over a powerful government agency that Democratic Gov.-elect Tony Evers promised to disband. Other pieces are aimed at insisting on legislative backing for certain decisions...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin Republicans pass lame-duck bills to strip governor of powers after Democrat wins office - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/wisconsin-republicans-pass-lame-duck-bills-to-strip-governor-of-powers-after-democrat-wins-office-2018-12-05</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKe0ImlsLN6E-lit8h8sbUkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 20:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/wisconsin-republicans-pass-lame-duck-bills-to-strip-governor-of-powers-after-democrat-wins-office-2018-12-05" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Republicans pass lame-duck bills to strip governor of powers after Democrat wins office&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASSOCIATED PRESS By Scott Bauer, Todd Richmond Republican Scott Walker jeered during Christmas-tree lighting Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker was heckled as he spoke at the lighting of the state Christmas Tree in the state capitol’s rotunda by voters incensed at Republican eleventh-hour efforts to strip Walker’s successor, Tony Evers, of some powers of the executive office. Associated Press/Steve Epps MADISON, Wis. (AP) — Wisconsin Republicans pushed through protests, internal disagreement and Democratic opposition Wednesday to pass far-reaching legislation that would shift power to the GOP-cont...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>The Wisconsin power grab is part of a bigger Republican attack on democracy - Vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/12/6/18127332/wisconsin-state-republican-power-grab-democracy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF6iOGgRtVSIXVuwA_UX2zUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowlOzSATCaiDUwo9dy</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:10:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/12/6/18127332/wisconsin-state-republican-power-grab-democracy" target="_blank"&gt;The Wisconsin power grab is part of a bigger Republican attack on democracy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker. Scott Olson/Getty Images The GOP’s turn against democracy may be a greater threat to the American experiment than President Trump. The Wisconsin Republican Party is nullifying the results of the 2018 election. On Wednesday morning, the Republican-controlled state legislature passed a bill that would seize key powers from incoming Democratic Gov. Tony Evers, who defeated incumbent Gov. Scott Walker in November. Walker is expected to sign it in the coming days. The bill blocks Evers’s ability to change state welfare policy and withdraw from a lawsuit against the A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.vox.com">Vox.com</source></item><item><title>Paul Ryan Silent On GOP Power Grab In Wisconsin - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/wisconsin-paul-ryan-scott-walker-tony-evers_us_5c07eebae4b0a6e4ebdacf24</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBxomSEenuDRS9KSNrQ6GV8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:24:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/wisconsin-paul-ryan-scott-walker-tony-evers_us_5c07eebae4b0a6e4ebdacf24" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Ryan Silent On GOP Power Grab In Wisconsin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― The extraordinary proposals aimed at reducing the power of incoming Gov. Tony Evers and other Democrats in Wisconsin was met with silence this week by one of the state’s top officials: House Speaker Paul Ryan (R). The measures, which were passed by the Republican-controlled state Legislature on Tuesday, would cut early voting in the state, give Republicans full control of a state economic development agency, block the governor’s ability to write regulations and allow the Legislature to hire its own lawyers to file lawsuits on behalf of the state. Current Gov. Scott Walker, who ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>‘Wisconsin Has Never Seen Anything Like This’ - The Atlantic</title><link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/12/wisconsin-gop-seeks-to-limit-democrat-everss-powers/577411/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED7uWIkk4JQwW-njd08qxpMqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowm_EEMKAiMPtZ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 20:08:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/12/wisconsin-gop-seeks-to-limit-democrat-everss-powers/577411/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Wisconsin Has Never Seen Anything Like This’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Atlantic&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the early-morning hours Wednesday, Republicans in control of the Wisconsin legislature carried out their plan to neuter the Democrats whom the state’s voters elected to lead them scarcely a month ago. In party-line votes, Republicans passed legislation to limit the ability of the incoming governor, Tony Evers, and attorney general, Josh Kaul, to deliver on their campaign promises to protect the Affordable Care Act, expand infrastructure spending, and overhaul the state’s economic-development agency. They dramatically scaled back early voting in Wisconsin, and across a range of areas, the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theatlantic.com">The Atlantic</source></item><item><title>'Star Trek' and Godzilla: Meet the colorful judge at the center of Florida's recount lawsuits - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/politics/florida-recount-judge-mark-walker-lawsuits/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHdDqzQy5A1IxXk7i8_flkQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:04:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/politics/florida-recount-judge-mark-walker-lawsuits/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Star Trek' and Godzilla: Meet the colorful judge at the center of Florida's recount lawsuits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A federal courthouse is rarely a place for "Star Trek" references. But Chief US District Judge Mark Walker isn't a normal jurist. Walker, a colorful and relaxed judge who was nominated to his post by President Barack Obama in 2012, now finds himself at the center of Florida's election recount, hearing at least eight cases on the matter. In a quiet, monotone courthouse not known for abundant color, he stands out. RELATED: Florida's Senate race heads to a hand recount Sporting a bow tie over his black robes during marathon hearings on Wednesday and Thursday, Walker played devil's advocate wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Wisconsin Senate's Move To Undermine An Incoming Democratic Governor, Explained - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/wisconsin-senate-republicans-block-governor-elect_us_5c07f06fe4b0680a7ecb5953</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIZQJYjNXYEO5N-HosxAV0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:37:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/wisconsin-senate-republicans-block-governor-elect_us_5c07f06fe4b0680a7ecb5953" target="_blank"&gt;The Wisconsin Senate's Move To Undermine An Incoming Democratic Governor, Explained&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wisconsin’s Republican-controlled state Legislature passed a number of measures Wednesday to cripple the authority of the state’s incoming Democratic leaders, including Gov.-elect Tony Evers and Attorney General-elect Josh Kaul. Two-term Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker (R), who narrowly lost his re-election bid last month, is expected to sign the package into law before he leaves office in January. So... how did this happen and what does it mean? Evers, the state schools superintendent, defeated Walker by a razor-thin margin in the midterm election on Nov. 6, securing what appeared to be a majo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Gov. Scott Walker On Students Who Gave Nazi Salute: 'They're Idiots.' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/gov-scott-walker-wisconsin-students-nazi-salute_us_5bede8d6e4b0510a1f2f0b57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIaTXRwe0o9deH7HYvRnQFYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 22:45:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/gov-scott-walker-wisconsin-students-nazi-salute_us_5bede8d6e4b0510a1f2f0b57" target="_blank"&gt;Gov. Scott Walker On Students Who Gave Nazi Salute: 'They're Idiots.'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker mustered a lukewarm response when asked about a group of high school students in his state who were photographed giving a Nazi salute. “I think they’re just stupid,” Walker ― who will be out of a job in January ― told reporters Thursday. “I think they’re idiots. It’s as simple as that. I don’t know that it’s any more complicated than that. They’re just a bunch of idiots.” .@ScottWalker on photo of Baraboo high school students giving Nazi salute: "I think they’re just stupid. I think they’re idiots. It’s as simple as that. They’re just a bunch of idiots." Some try...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>On Politics: Trump Calls Trade Truce a Success, but Doubts Linger - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/04/us/politics/trump-china-trade.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFFSl-nkAc8grmDS0IgaW2YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:22:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/04/us/politics/trump-china-trade.html" target="_blank"&gt;On Politics: Trump Calls Trade Truce a Success, but Doubts Linger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good Tuesday morning. Here are some of the stories making news in Washington and politics today. _____________________ • President Trump on Monday cast his trade truce with President Xi Jinping of China as a success, promising rapid benefits for American farmers and automakers. But the deal includes no concrete commitments, deep divisions remain and a staunch China skeptic, Robert Lighthizer, will lead the American negotiating team. • Paul Manafort, Mr. Trump’s former campaign chairman, went to Ecuador in 2017 to talk to the incoming president about Chinese investment. Then talk turned to t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Scott Walker Leaves As He Came, With Extreme Partisan Power Grabs - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/scott-walker-partisan-power-grab_us_5c06b35ae4b066b5cfa68297</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDoyEr3ZqLDgMilmVaVMp4IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 19:58:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/scott-walker-partisan-power-grab_us_5c06b35ae4b066b5cfa68297" target="_blank"&gt;Scott Walker Leaves As He Came, With Extreme Partisan Power Grabs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his final days as Wisconsin’s governor, Scott Walker is working with the GOP-controlled state legislature to strip power away from the governor and the attorney general and shift it over to lawmakers. The motivation for their plan isn’t secret: Walker lost his re-election, and the incoming governor and attorney general are Democrats. The state legislature, however, will remain overwhelmingly Republican. What Walker and his Republican allies are doing shouldn’t be a surprise. From the time he took office, he has steadily amassed control for the GOP and quietly taken over state functions. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin GOP uses rare session to weaken incoming governor - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/27a08a42972b484fa0590264bee43b57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHk4gvo19ID13dAgdTEocFoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:47:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/27a08a42972b484fa0590264bee43b57" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin GOP uses rare session to weaken incoming governor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — Still stinging from an election loss, Wisconsin Republicans on Monday tried to push through measures that would weaken the incoming Democratic administration and allow outgoing Republican Gov. Scott Walker to make one last major mark on the state's political landscape after his defeat in November. They backed down, for now, on changing the 2020 presidential primary date at a cost of millions of dollars to benefit a conservative state Supreme Court justice. That had been introduced but did not win approval in committee, meaning it is likely dead. Angry opponents filled t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Most Americans will have Democratic governors after the 2018 midterms - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/politics/americans-democratic-governor-2018-midterms/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBoMOOfkFBj6TCYQqGZg7jUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:04:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/politics/americans-democratic-governor-2018-midterms/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Most Americans will have Democratic governors after the 2018 midterms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most Americans will live under Democratic governors come next year. In the 2018 midterms, Democrats picked up seven governorships, to bring their nationwide total to 23. Republicans picked up one from an independent in Alaska, giving them control of 27 governorships. But those numbers don't tell the whole story. Democrats won where a lot of people live. Before the election, just 42% of Americans were represented by Democratic governors. Come January, it will be 53%. That 11-point jump is greater than the 9-point increase Democrats saw in the percentage of House seats they controlled pre- an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Republicans’ Midwest ‘Power Grab’ - The Atlantic</title><link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/12/gop-power-grab-wisconsin-and-michigan/577246/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG55J-di0k2FtKFL9kR5XK4qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowm_EEMKAiMPtZ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 12:26:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/12/gop-power-grab-wisconsin-and-michigan/577246/" target="_blank"&gt;The Republicans’ Midwest ‘Power Grab’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Atlantic&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Wisconsin and Michigan, Republicans are responding to their loss of top statewide offices in last month’s elections by rapidly trying to undercut the Democrats about to take office. The gambit seems straight out of North Carolina, where Republicans used the lame-duck session after the 2016 elections to limit the power of the incoming Democratic governor in what one top Democrat called a “legislative coup”—and largely got away with it. The Wisconsin legislature could vote as soon as Tuesday to limit the ability of Tony Evers, the incoming Democratic governor, to run state agencies and int...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theatlantic.com">The Atlantic</source></item><item><title>Midwestern Republicans Try To Kneecap New Democratic Governors - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/midwestern-republicans-try-to-kneecap-new-democratic-governors_us_5c05acebe4b0cd916faefc3e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdBE_rOivpplyn1QujIWU4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:23:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/midwestern-republicans-try-to-kneecap-new-democratic-governors_us_5c05acebe4b0cd916faefc3e" target="_blank"&gt;Midwestern Republicans Try To Kneecap New Democratic Governors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lame-duck Republican legislatures in two Midwestern states where Democrats seized key state offices in November are trying to kneecap the incoming leaders and change election rules, aiming to consolidate GOP power despite the election results. In Wisconsin, Republicans aim to limit early voting, change the date of the state’s presidential primary to help a conservative member of the Wisconsin Supreme Court win re-election, limit the governor’s ability to make certain appointments and block Gov.-elect Tony Evers from eliminating a state economic development agency. To the east, Michigan’s GO...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Did Minority Voters Dethrone Scott Walker? - The Atlantic</title><link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/11/black-and-latino-turnout-helped-defeat-scott-walker/575818/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMi4Y4w4TdtmmrFixjY9zxYqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowm_EEMKAiMPtZ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/11/black-and-latino-turnout-helped-defeat-scott-walker/575818/" target="_blank"&gt;Did Minority Voters Dethrone Scott Walker?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Atlantic&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Walker was elected governor of Wisconsin eight years ago. He’s survived a recall attempt, a reelection bid, a brief flirtation with running for the GOP nomination for president, and years of bitter opposition from Wisconsinites who fought against his hard-line policies on voting rights, health care, education, and the state safety net. He’s led what might be considered the model of a Republican state takeover in the era of Trumpism. And he lost the 2018 election to his Democratic challenger, Tony Evers, by a margin of 1.2 points, a total of just over 30,000 votes. As the dust settles ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theatlantic.com">The Atlantic</source></item><item><title>How Republicans are trying to strip power from Democratic governors-elect - Vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/12/4/18123784/gop-legislature-wisconsin-michigan-power-grab-lame-duck</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFLxA-QzYHp2dcIGClMAqNYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowlOzSATCaiDUwmcT7BQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:54:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/12/4/18123784/gop-legislature-wisconsin-michigan-power-grab-lame-duck" target="_blank"&gt;How Republicans are trying to strip power from Democratic governors-elect&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker and the GOP-led state legislature are pushing changes that would curb Tony Evers’s power in office. Scott Olson/Getty Images Republicans are suddenly pushing “good governance” in states they lost power in. Republicans, about to lose their grip on power in a number of states, are trying their hardest to sour Democrats’ election wins — and Wisconsin is taking charge. In Wisconsin, Republican Gov. Scott Walker will have to pass the baton to Democrat Tony Evers come January, but before he does, the state’s GOP-controlled legislature is passing bills to curb Evers’s p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.vox.com">Vox.com</source></item><item><title>Stung by Election Losses, Republicans in the States Seek a Way to Neutralize Democrats - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/03/us/wisconsin-lawmakers-republicans-power.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPUzlhe08ZDZ1CxwYG9MZBUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:08:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/03/us/wisconsin-lawmakers-republicans-power.html" target="_blank"&gt;Stung by Election Losses, Republicans in the States Seek a Way to Neutralize Democrats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. — When Democrats won the governor’s office in Wisconsin, it was one of the party’s most celebrated midterm successes in regaining power in the states. Now Republicans are striking back, moving to slash the power of the new governor even before he takes the oath of office. Democrats reacted with fury, crowding the halls of the State Capitol in Madison on Monday and accusing the Republicans of trying to undo an election they had lost. It was only the latest such Republican effort across the country to try to use legislative action to counter blows the party suffered at the polls...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin Is About to Make a Huge Mistake - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/03/opinion/wisconsin-legislature-republicans-evers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcmj_0ln7udvYgvk7kKUp0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwpoIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 19:44:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/03/opinion/wisconsin-legislature-republicans-evers.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Is About to Make a Huge Mistake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Late Friday afternoon, less than a month after a Democrat, Tony Evers, defeated Scott Walker, the incumbent Republican governor, Robin Vos, the Republican Speaker of the Wisconsin State Assembly, followed through on his threat to strip the new governor of some of his power. That day, an assembly committee released five bills that grant sweeping new authority to the Legislature at the expense of both Mr. Evers and Wisconsin’s new attorney general, Josh Kaul, who also happens to be a Democrat. Drafted in secret, the legislation was rushed to the Joint Finance Committee on Monday for its only ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Walker shouted down over GOP attempt to weaken his successor - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/d95d1190247b4bc6a611c053214cf77e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJqDnw02GDpR_s-WT2z_maIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:14:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/d95d1190247b4bc6a611c053214cf77e" target="_blank"&gt;Walker shouted down over GOP attempt to weaken his successor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — Demonstrators booed outgoing Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker on Tuesday during a Christmas tree-lighting ceremony, a sign of tumult as Republicans in the Legislature met to push through measures to gut the powers of his Democratic successor. The Legislature met deep into the night Tuesday to pass a series of bills, first unveiled Friday, that would weaken the governor's office and transfer power away from the Democratic-elect attorney general and give it to the Legislature. The Legislature wasn't expected to complete its work until early Wednesday morning. Walker has signal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin Republicans move to undercut incoming Democratic governor - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-states/wisconsin-republicans-move-to-undercut-incoming-democratic-governor-idUSKBN1O411E</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPk1C-pC7Euq5rJ9co7X0kEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 20:38:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-states/wisconsin-republicans-move-to-undercut-incoming-democratic-governor-idUSKBN1O411E" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin Republicans move to undercut incoming Democratic governor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facing the loss of complete control of state government next month, Wisconsin Republicans passed legislation on Wednesday to weaken the powers of the newly elected Democratic governor and attorney general. The final votes in the state Senate and Assembly came around dawn, following hours of debate during which Democrats accused Republicans of a naked last-minute power grab that ignores the results of the Nov. 6 election. Republicans defended the legislation as a good-faith effort to ensure the legislative and executive branches remain equals. Republican Governor Scott Walker, who was heckle...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin GOP Senate Passes Bill to Hobble Democratic Successors - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/wisconsin-gop-senate-passes-bill-to-hobble-democratic-successors</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGKtYiHu9FfUMgzBuhH59bUqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:01:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/wisconsin-gop-senate-passes-bill-to-hobble-democratic-successors" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin GOP Senate Passes Bill to Hobble Democratic Successors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andy Manis/Getty, Republicans in the Wisconsin Senate followed through on their threat to use the last days of their session to pass sweeping measures to hobble the state’s incoming Democratic governor and attorney general, and the state Assembly is expected to follow their lead later today. The assembly and senate are considering a number of bills designed to effectively prevent Governor-elect Tony Evers and incoming Attorney General Josh Kaul from delivering on their campaign promises. Both approved bills would then go to Republican Gov. Scott Walker, who lost his bid for re-election in N...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>North Carolina wrote the playbook other states are using to undermine democracy - Vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/12/5/18125544/north-carolina-power-grab-wisconsin-michigan-lame-duck</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG6_AqCve5BWNCs0iWmdMiMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowlOzSATCaiDUwg7tz</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:10:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/12/5/18125544/north-carolina-power-grab-wisconsin-michigan-lame-duck" target="_blank"&gt;North Carolina wrote the playbook other states are using to undermine democracy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Wisconsin, Gov. Scott Walker and Republican lawmakers are using the lame duck session of the state legislature to undermine incoming Democratic leadership’s power. Darren Hauck/Getty Images Two years ago, North Carolina Republicans decided to make Democrats’ lives hell. Democrat Roy Cooper was weeks away from being sworn in as the new governor of North Carolina, when outgoing Republican Gov. Pat McCrory called a special session of the legislature under the guise of helping the victims of natural disasters. Instead, he was orchestrating a plan to severely limit the incoming Democratic gov...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.vox.com">Vox.com</source></item><item><title>Republicans plan lame-duck power grab ‘denying the will of voters’ just weeks before Democrats take control - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/lame-duck-wisconsin-power-grab-scott-walker-republicans-demcorats-house-tony-evers-josh-kaul-a8667601.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC9v_c3qdrAs13QhaFFp-ZEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 23:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/lame-duck-wisconsin-power-grab-scott-walker-republicans-demcorats-house-tony-evers-josh-kaul-a8667601.html" target="_blank"&gt;Republicans plan lame-duck power grab ‘denying the will of voters’ just weeks before Democrats take control&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wisconsin Republicans are attempting a dramatic re-shifting of power in the state that would undermine the incoming Democratic administration even before they even start their first day. A slew of bills were planned to be voted on in the Republican-controlled state legislature on Tuesday, where they were expected to pass and be sent on to Republican Governor Scott Walker’s desk just weeks before he leaves office. The bills would limit the powers of the incoming Democrats in what opponents have described as a blatant last minute power grab that would effectively invalidate the will of the pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Lawmakers Clash and Protesters Chant Amid Fight Over Wisconsin Governor’s Power - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/04/us/wisconsin-republicans-power.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELj9dQf1MsjdzjrC8QIALUoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloEY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:46:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/04/us/wisconsin-republicans-power.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lawmakers Clash and Protesters Chant Amid Fight Over Wisconsin Governor’s Power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Update: The Wisconsin State Legislature passed measures limiting the governor’s power on Wednesday. Read about the latest developments here. MADISON, Wis. — Lawmakers sparred in sharp, angry tones. Furious demonstrators drowned out cheery Christmas carols being sung by schoolchildren. Visitors were cleared from a Capitol gallery, escorted away as they chanted: “Shame! Shame! Shame!” So went a long and tumultuous day in Wisconsin, as Republicans who control this state’s Legislature pushed forward an extensive list of measures aimed at limiting the power of a newly elected governor and attorn...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Wisconsin and Michigan Republicans try to undermine Democratic election wins - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/politics/wisconsin-michigan-republican-post-election-power-grabs/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDXwIZ7c58DME1WvYtm2m8sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 23:17:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/politics/wisconsin-michigan-republican-post-election-power-grabs/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wisconsin and Michigan Republicans try to undermine Democratic election wins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republicans in Wisconsin and Michigan were wiped out of their states' top offices in November. But before Democrats can take their place next year, GOP lawmakers in both states are moving to strip the incoming leaders of key powers. Most of the attention has centered on Wisconsin, where Republicans are in the midst of an "extraordinary session" designed to effectively prevent Democratic Gov.-elect Tony Evers and incoming Attorney General Josh Kaul from delivering on their campaign promises. If the bills pass Wisconsin's Republican-led Assembly and Senate, and lame-duck Gov. Scott Walker sig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Will Scott Walker Get Away with One Final Power Grab in Wisconsin? - The New Yorker</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/current/will-scott-walker-get-away-with-one-final-power-grab-in-wisconsin</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENvSjikMZIwEh94X_Y0FsCoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowjMqjCjCJhZwBMNWYrQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:31:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/news/current/will-scott-walker-get-away-with-one-final-power-grab-in-wisconsin" target="_blank"&gt;Will Scott Walker Get Away with One Final Power Grab in Wisconsin?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New Yorker&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eight years ago, Scott Walker came into office as Wisconsin’s governor and executed one of the most dramatic power grabs in recent American history. Now, he’s trying for another one on his way out. Last month, the Wisconsin governor—who famously eviscerated public-sector workers’ collective-bargaining rights in 2011, during the first months of his administration—lost his reëlection bid to the Democrat Tony Evers, the state’s superintendent of schools. Since Walker’s win in 2010, the year of the Tea Party, Republicans had maintained nearly complete control of Wisconsin’s government. The stat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newyorker.com">The New Yorker</source></item><item><title>'This is not democracy': Republicans try to shrink power of incoming Democrats - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/04/republicans-democrats-michigan-wisconsin-voting-midterms</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGwODVZ4JkLm0n-cTuQgR7IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:00:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/04/republicans-democrats-michigan-wisconsin-voting-midterms" target="_blank"&gt;'This is not democracy': Republicans try to shrink power of incoming Democrats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A month after the midterm elections on 6 November, several states continue to be convulsed by bitter partisan fighting in which Republicans are being accused of flagrantly undemocratic attempts to steal victory from the clutches of their Democratic rivals. The most intense battle is playing out in Wisconsin, where Republican lawmakers are attempting a power grab that would strip key functions from the state’s incoming Democratic governor and attorney general. Opponents are denouncing the move, which sparked protests on Monday, as a blatantly undemocratic negation of the November election re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>California Takes Its Time Counting Ballots. Paul Ryan Thinks That's Really Weird. - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/paul-ryan-california-elections_us_5c004a8ae4b027f1097be7a7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHCxko4fE9LytARquguDVBIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ3knAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 22:13:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/paul-ryan-california-elections_us_5c004a8ae4b027f1097be7a7" target="_blank"&gt;California Takes Its Time Counting Ballots. Paul Ryan Thinks That's Really Weird.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;House Speaker Paul Ryan (R-Wis.) said he did not understand why California's vote tallies changed after Election Day. House Speaker Paul Ryan (R-Wis.) said Thursday it was “bizarre” that Republicans lost House races in California in races they appeared to be winning on election night, saying the state’s election processes were “very strange” and he did not understand how vote totals could change after Election Day. This year, Democrats flipped six seats in California, including several by very narrow margins. Democrats could flip a seventh: As ballots continued to be counted, The Associated...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Stunning state power grabs expose a GOP uneasy with democracy itself - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/opinions/wisconsin-michigan-north-carolina-gop-power-grab-avlon/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAHu_D6LGSfbpo7x1CBBFWgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:00:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/opinions/wisconsin-michigan-north-carolina-gop-power-grab-avlon/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Stunning state power grabs expose a GOP uneasy with democracy itself&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Avlon is a CNN senior political analyst and anchor. The opinions expressed in this commentary are his own. View more opinion articles on CNN. Sometimes in politics, if you're not angry it's because you're not paying attention. Or you're just a hyper-partisan hack. Because after an election that saw the highest voter turnout for a midterm election in 100 years, we are witnessing an effort to roll back election results in big swing states. In Michigan and Wisconsin, Republicans who control the state legislatures are trying to use year-end "lame duck" sessions to rein in the governors' po...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>GOP governors minimize Trump impact on midterm losses - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/b4eb9c9b4df14c30929994c8385431bc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDF-WP8d6iB0iio-X6n3uc8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 21:24:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/b4eb9c9b4df14c30929994c8385431bc" target="_blank"&gt;GOP governors minimize Trump impact on midterm losses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SCOTTSDALE, Ariz. (AP) — Republican governors are minimizing any suggestion that voter discontent with President Donald Trump played a role in the midterm elections, where Democrats flipped seven governorships, took control of the U.S. House and picked up hundreds of state legislative seats. "I don't think what you saw in this electoral cycle was any different that would you see" in any midterm, said Nebraska Gov. Pete Ricketts during the Republican Governors Association meeting Wednesday in suburban Phoenix. Ricketts noted that two years after Democrat Barack Obama was elected president, t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Republican-led Wisconsin legislature approves bills to diminish executive power after Democratic election wins - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/wisconsin-legislature-power/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHbvxMQFqnULPzl6iQAZjIUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:23:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/wisconsin-legislature-power/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Republican-led Wisconsin legislature approves bills to diminish executive power after Democratic election wins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wisconsin Republicans moved overnight to strip power from newly elected Democratic leaders, advancing legislation that would limit early voting, enact Medicaid work requirements and potentially block the incoming attorney general from withdrawing the state from a lawsuit over Obamacare. The measures are all expected to be signed by lame-duck Republican Gov. Scott Walker, effectively preventing his successor, Gov.-elect Tony Evers, and Attorney General-elect Josh Kaul from delivering on the promises that lifted them to victory in November. Nearly a day after the legislature's "extraordinary ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Florida starts painstaking hand recount in US Senate race - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/797e56eb5f694a0787cbebfcf9370797</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFBifdcOYjY0DJo_aTkw-U8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 02:00:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/797e56eb5f694a0787cbebfcf9370797" target="_blank"&gt;Florida starts painstaking hand recount in US Senate race&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Volunteers gathered around folding tables Friday to begin a painstaking hand recount in Florida's acrimonious U.S. Senate contest, with a goal of determining the intent of about 93,000 voters whose ballots for Republican Gov. Rick Scott or Democratic Sen. Bill Nelson could not be counted by machine. The hand recount is required by state law whenever candidates are separated by 0.25 percentage points or less. Unofficial results showed Scott ahead of Nelson by 0.15 percentage points, or fewer than 13,000 votes out of more than 8 million cast. In Broward County, of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>This Is How You Fight Betsy DeVos - Jezebel</title><link>https://theslot.jezebel.com/this-is-how-you-fight-betsy-devos-1830463538</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJrP1Nc9XU5zkkLpAvAzpK8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowlYECMLFMMOX4ngY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 17:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://theslot.jezebel.com/this-is-how-you-fight-betsy-devos-1830463538" target="_blank"&gt;This Is How You Fight Betsy DeVos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Jezebel&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image: Associated Press Like so many other educators, 31-year-old speech therapist Kathy Hoffman watched the confirmation hearing of Betsy DeVos with horror. Then, Hoffman decided to do something about it: she ran for office and, against the odds, won. Hoffman will become Arizona’s next superintendent for public instruction, narrowly beating former state Senate minority leader David Schapira in the primaries, and then Republican Frank Riggs, a former California congressman and a major proponent of charter schools, in the general election. “It was very clear from many of her statements she h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://theslot.jezebel.com">Jezebel</source></item><item><title>The Judge at the Center of the Florida Recount Battle - The Wall Street Journal</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-judge-at-the-center-of-the-florida-recount-battle-1542304166?mod=hp_major_pos9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA9yEig8THjEcx-BYtNPdHAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1tzJATDnyxUw6qS5Aw</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 21:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-judge-at-the-center-of-the-florida-recount-battle-1542304166?mod=hp_major_pos9" target="_blank"&gt;The Judge at the Center of the Florida Recount Battle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Wall Street Journal&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The federal judge who made key rulings on Thursday in the Florida recount battle has previously overseen a number of voting-rights cases and ruled against Gov. Rick Scott and his administration in some of them—at times with blistering language. U.S. District Judge Mark Walker, who was nominated in 2012 by President Obama and confirmed in the Senate on a 94-0 vote, became chief judge of the U.S. District Court for the Northern District of Florida in Tallahassee this year. He is known for making jocular comments from the bench and sometimes writing biting opinions. In February, Judge Walker f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.wsj.com">The Wall Street Journal</source></item><item><title>Judge Gives Florida Voters Time to Fix Signature Issues - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/florida-judge-voters-fix-signature-problems-1217237</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECZp43SymqXbBDjUkdFuKFMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMNiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:31:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/florida-judge-voters-fix-signature-problems-1217237" target="_blank"&gt;Judge Gives Florida Voters Time to Fix Signature Issues&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A federal judge Thursday morning ordered that 4,000 Florida voters with rejected ballots from signature discrepancies on mail-in and provisional ballots be granted two days to fix the problem, giving voters until Saturday at 5 p.m. to prove their identity. The ruling came just hours before the 3 p.m. deadline for the statewide recount to be finished, making it unclear exactly how the judge’s ruling will impact the recount process. Florida Governor Rick Scott, the Republican who’s declared victory over incumbent Democratic Senator Bill Nelson and taken to Capitol Hill—even though the electio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>No decision yet in key Florida recount lawsuit over mismatched ballot signatures - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/politics/florida-recount-lawsuit-signature-match-judge-court/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK3uojgNEghFKFsxmIeCgjcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 11:12:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/politics/florida-recount-lawsuit-signature-match-judge-court/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;No decision yet in key Florida recount lawsuit over mismatched ballot signatures&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The federal court hearing in Florida on whether to count thousands of rejected mail-in and provisional ballots concluded on Wednesday after more than five hours without a decision from Judge Mark Walker. Florida law requires signatures on vote-by-mail and provisional ballots match the signatures on file for each voter. Attorneys for Democratic Sen. Bill Nelson's re-election campaign argued that Florida's signature-match rules violate the US Constitution and called for the judge to invalidate the law. Lawyers representing the state of Florida and the National Republican Senatorial Committee,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Florida judge gives more time for voters to fix rejected ballots - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/florida-judge-time-voters-fix-rejected-ballots-181115150951933.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHtKoYNWk7OsQK_fviXRGicqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 17:16:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/florida-judge-time-voters-fix-rejected-ballots-181115150951933.html" target="_blank"&gt;Florida judge gives more time for voters to fix rejected ballots&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A federal judge is giving thousands of Florida voters until the end of Saturday to fix their ballots if they haven't been counted due to mismatched signatures. US District Judge Mark Walker ruled early Thursday that current Florida law on mail-in ballots places a substantial burden on voters. The ruling comes as Florida wraps a recount in three statewide races. Walker did not go along with a request from Democrats to count all ballots with mismatched signatures. Instead he ordered that local election officials give voters until 5pm local time on Saturday to correct the problem so that their...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Bitter battle for Florida Senate seat goes to hand recount - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/058c5f727bab45be9372110fbba9c07a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEtznLWLf7qycd_9zxpWvGEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 00:27:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/058c5f727bab45be9372110fbba9c07a" target="_blank"&gt;Bitter battle for Florida Senate seat goes to hand recount&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida's acrimonious battle for the U.S. Senate headed Thursday to a legally required hand recount after an initial review by ballot-counting machines showed Republican Gov. Rick Scott and Democratic Sen. Bill Nelson separated by less than 13,000 votes. But the highly watched contest for governor between Republican Ron DeSantis and Democrat Andrew Gillum appeared to be over, with a machine recount showing DeSantis with a large enough advantage over Gillum to avoid a hand recount in that race. Gillum, who conceded the contest on Election Night only to retract his co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Bill Nelson suffers court setbacks as hand recount continues in Florida - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/politics/bill-nelson-rick-scott-florida-recount/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEN2hNny-PF6HFS0I-zI6ugqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 23:57:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/politics/bill-nelson-rick-scott-florida-recount/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bill Nelson suffers court setbacks as hand recount continues in Florida&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Bill Nelson's already improbable path towards victory in a recount has gotten narrower, with the Democrat suffering a series of setbacks in court and in county election offices across the state. The drumbeat of relatively bad news for Democrats in Florida has left any chance Nelson had of overtaking Republican Gov. Rick Scott's 12,603 vote lead in a recount as a longshot, at best, with the three-term senator needing to win an overwhelming number of votes in the ongoing manual recount or scoring a series of clear wins in court. Nelson was handed a consequential loss early on Friday morn...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Latest: At least 55,000 ballots in Senate hand recount - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/39153d5dc9ca42bfadf2867c476ec17c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLJDGVY07TJ_0Bui_AWwm0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 05:10:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/39153d5dc9ca42bfadf2867c476ec17c" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: At least 55,000 ballots in Senate hand recount&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — The Latest on Florida's election recount (all times local): 7 p.m. Election offices across Florida will have to hand count at a bare minimum almost 54,000 ballots in the U.S. Senate race. A survey of 64 of Florida's 67 counties by The Associated Press put the number of overvotes and undervotes Thursday evening at 53,769 ballots in the U.S. Senate race between incumbent Democratic Sen. Bill Nelson and GOP Gov. Rick Scott. The only counties that hadn't reported those counts were three of the state's largest: Broward, Lee and Palm Beach counties. In an overvote, a vote...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Day 6 of Florida recount: What you need to know - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/15/politics/florida-recount-state-of-play/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPf4upEqCdNjtxBBlblVWG4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 19:51:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/15/politics/florida-recount-state-of-play/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Day 6 of Florida recount: What you need to know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was already shaping up to be an important day in the recount saga for Florida's US Senate, governor and agriculture commissioner races, and now a federal judge has extended a deadline to allow voters whose mail-in and provisional ballots had signature issues more time to correct them. Here's a look at where we begin the sixth day of the recount. Deadline day Florida's 67 counties must officially submit their numbers from the automatic machine recount by 3 p.m. ET. Those numbers will then be certified by the secretary of state. We expect that 66 out of 67 counties will get there with time...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>How Trump’s favored midterm candidates performed - Vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/11/7/18066194/midterm-results-trump-candidates</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELnJD58add4hYol4KWJmOGAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowlOzSATCaiDUwo9dy</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 22:30:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/11/7/18066194/midterm-results-trump-candidates" target="_blank"&gt;How Trump’s favored midterm candidates performed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christina Animashaun/Vox Trump bragged that the candidates he backed won. The reality is more complicated. Does President Donald Trump have electoral coattails? And will independent voters who chose Trump in 2016 vote for Republicans not named Donald Trump in 2018? On Tuesday, Republicans in states like Minnesota, Nevada, and West Virginia found out the answer: sort of. Beginning on March 10, Donald Trump participated in 42 rallies to support Republican candidates running for House and Senate positions and in gubernatorial contests. He visited several states that went for him in 2016 multip...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.vox.com">Vox.com</source></item></channel></rss>