<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Liberal Party of Canada - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREV6Tm10eUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-CA&amp;gl=CA&amp;ceid=CA:en</link><language>en-CA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:37:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Raj Grewal no longer a member of Liberal caucus: chief whip Mark Holland - Global News</title><link>https://globalnews.ca/news/4718874/raj-grewal-out-of-liberal-caucus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSm_2zYYugAOQmx6i_OIOcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqeP_CjDdg_oCMMTh6QU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 16:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://globalnews.ca/news/4718874/raj-grewal-out-of-liberal-caucus/" target="_blank"&gt;Raj Grewal no longer a member of Liberal caucus: chief whip Mark Holland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Global News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following Liberal MP Raj Grewal reversing his pledge to resign, MP Mark Holland from the Ajax-Durham region tweeted that Grewal is no longer a member of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://globalnews.ca">Global News</source></item><item><title>'With a heavy heart,' Brian Gallant says he'll resign as Liberal leader - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/new-brunswick/liberal-leader-brian-gallant-new-brunswick-election-1.4906417</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENNPkZpY5C2vm8BsaeY5_TgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 07:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/new-brunswick/liberal-leader-brian-gallant-new-brunswick-election-1.4906417" target="_blank"&gt;'With a heavy heart,' Brian Gallant says he'll resign as Liberal leader&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brian Gallant has announced his intention to resign as leader of the New Brunswick Liberal Party as soon as a new leader can be chosen.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Striking Canada Post employees rally outside federal Liberal convention in Kelowna - Global News</title><link>https://globalnews.ca/news/4674097/striking-canada-post-employees-liberal-mps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYWOdSbvADhGd1heGpwdG4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqeP_CjDdg_oCMMTh6QU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 07:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://globalnews.ca/news/4674097/striking-canada-post-employees-liberal-mps/" target="_blank"&gt;Striking Canada Post employees rally outside federal Liberal convention in Kelowna&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Global News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dozens of Canada Post workers gathered outside the federal Liberal party's B.C. convention in Kelowna on Saturday. They were hoping for a word with party ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://globalnews.ca">Global News</source></item><item><title>Gallant will enjoy financial perks of decision to stay Liberal leader until successor found - CBC.ca</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/new-brunswick/gallant-liberal-leader-resignation-financial-benefits-pension-1.4908238</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMidGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNiYy5jYS9uZXdzL2NhbmFkYS9uZXctYnJ1bnN3aWNrL2dhbGxhbnQtbGliZXJhbC1sZWFkZXItcmVzaWduYXRpb24tZmluYW5jaWFsLWJlbmVmaXRzLXBlbnNpb24tMS40OTA4MjM40gFjaHR0cHM6Ly93d3ctY2JjLWNhLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3Mvd3d3LmNiYy5jYS9hbXAvMS40OTA4MjM4P2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 07:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/new-brunswick/gallant-liberal-leader-resignation-financial-benefits-pension-1.4908238" target="_blank"&gt;Gallant will enjoy financial perks of decision to stay Liberal leader until successor found&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC.ca&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former premier Brian Gallant's decision to remain as party leader while Liberals choose a replacement departs from the normal practice of provincial leaders ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC.ca</source></item><item><title>Federal Liberal Party convention wraps up in Kelowna - Global News</title><link>https://globalnews.ca/news/4675822/federal-liberal-party-convention-kelowna/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPtt39B8asiM-IruX3vEWgUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqeP_CjDdg_oCMMTh6QU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 07:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://globalnews.ca/news/4675822/federal-liberal-party-convention-kelowna/" target="_blank"&gt;Federal Liberal Party convention wraps up in Kelowna&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Global News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The convention offers an opportunity for the party to start crafting its election platform for 2019 and a chance for B.C. residents to speak up.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://globalnews.ca">Global News</source></item><item><title>Brian Gallant plans to resign as Liberal leader - CBC.ca</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/new-brunswick/brian-gallant-plans-resignation-1.4906015</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiVmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNiYy5jYS9uZXdzL2NhbmFkYS9uZXctYnJ1bnN3aWNrL2JyaWFuLWdhbGxhbnQtcGxhbnMtcmVzaWduYXRpb24tMS40OTA2MDE10gFjaHR0cHM6Ly93d3ctY2JjLWNhLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3Mvd3d3LmNiYy5jYS9hbXAvMS40OTA2MDE1P2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 07:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/new-brunswick/brian-gallant-plans-resignation-1.4906015" target="_blank"&gt;Brian Gallant plans to resign as Liberal leader&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC.ca&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former New Brunswick premier Brian Gallant plans to resign as Liberal leader on Thursday, almost two weeks after his government lost a confidence vote in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC.ca</source></item><item><title>Liberal Party to nominate Don Rusnak as candidate for 2019 federal election - CBC.ca</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/thunder-bay/rusnak-nomination-liberal-candidate-1.4906735</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiWGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNiYy5jYS9uZXdzL2NhbmFkYS90aHVuZGVyLWJheS9ydXNuYWstbm9taW5hdGlvbi1saWJlcmFsLWNhbmRpZGF0ZS0xLjQ5MDY3MzXSAWNodHRwczovL3d3dy1jYmMtY2EuY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy93d3cuY2JjLmNhL2FtcC8xLjQ5MDY3MzU_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 07:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/thunder-bay/rusnak-nomination-liberal-candidate-1.4906735" target="_blank"&gt;Liberal Party to nominate Don Rusnak as candidate for 2019 federal election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC.ca&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After serving nearly three years as the Member of Parliament for the Thunder Bay — Rainy River district, Don Rusnak will be nominated as the Liberal candidate ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC.ca</source></item><item><title>François Legault wrangles concessions on asylum seekers, dairy farmers - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/montreal/first-ministers-meeting-asylum-seekers-1.4936439</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOe41vbMeRTDeXSeE1CCZ4gqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/montreal/first-ministers-meeting-asylum-seekers-1.4936439" target="_blank"&gt;François Legault wrangles concessions on asylum seekers, dairy farmers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The federal government will consider increasing the compensation Quebec receives for providing care for asylum seekers, Premier Francois Legault said Friday after a meeting of Canada's first ministers. Quebec wants $295 million for its efforts. Ottawa initially indicated it was only willing to pay half that amount — enough to reimburse housing costs. But Legault said Prime Minister Justin Trudeau displayed more openness in Friday's meeting. "This afternoon he went a bit further to say he was ready to look at other sorts of expenses than housing," Legault told reporters in Montreal. "The min...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Alberta's oil price gap 'directly related to Justin Trudeau's policies,' says Scheer - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/tasker-scheer-justin-trudeau-policies-alberta-1.4930286</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK1K7ikHJBz34v6Vr-PR6oMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:02:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/tasker-scheer-justin-trudeau-policies-alberta-1.4930286" target="_blank"&gt;Alberta's oil price gap 'directly related to Justin Trudeau's policies,' says Scheer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conservative Leader Andrew Scheer said Monday that Prime Minister Justin Trudeau is "directly" responsible for cratering oil prices in Western Canada — pointing the finger at federal energy policies he blames for leaving pipeline capacities constrained and Alberta producers scrambling to sell their product for pennies on the dollar. With the Trans Mountain expansion and Keystone XL stalled and the Northern Gateway project shelved, Alberta's producers have been forced to accept prices far below world levels for their oil. TransCanada also pulled the plug on Energy East amid shifting demands ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Ethics Watchdog Mario Dion Concerned About 'Advice' Andrew Scheer's Office Gave MP Stephanie Kusie - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/05/ethics-watchdog-mario-dion-concerned-about-advice-andrew-scheers-office-gave-mp-stephanie-kusie_a_23609457/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHOp9eOnutUbC4eljWIbQ6EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w18vGBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/05/ethics-watchdog-mario-dion-concerned-about-advice-andrew-scheers-office-gave-mp-stephanie-kusie_a_23609457/" target="_blank"&gt;Ethics Watchdog Mario Dion Concerned About 'Advice' Andrew Scheer's Office Gave MP Stephanie Kusie&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — The federal ethics watchdog says he's concerned that Conservative Leader Andrew Scheer's office encouraged a Tory MP to violate the conflict-of-interest code for members of the House of Commons. In a written ruling Tuesday, Mario Dion says Calgary Conservative MP Stephanie Kusie contravened the code last March 29 when she posted on social media a letter she'd sent the ethics commissioner that day asking him to investigate Raj Grewal, who was a Liberal MP at the time. Kusie was one of two MPs to ask Dion to investigate whether Grewal was in a conflict of interest when he invited a c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Federal Government Drops Controversial Wording From Summer Jobs Program - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/06/summer-jobs-program-attestation_a_23610627/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB9MbGiY7pyQpuQ6UKg4hpUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/06/summer-jobs-program-attestation_a_23610627/" target="_blank"&gt;Federal Government Drops Controversial Wording From Summer Jobs Program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — Contentious wording in Ottawa's summer jobs program that tied pro-abortion beliefs to funding eligibility is being dropped after a backlash to what was styled last year as a values test. Instead, the federal Liberals have re-tooled the 2019 version of the Canada Summer Jobs program to require applicants to declare they don't work to infringe on any Canadian's legal rights. Wording on the application for the 2018 version of the program required groups to say neither their core mandate nor the jobs being funded actively worked to undermine constitutional, human and reproductive right...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Opposition parties demand Trudeau explain his plan to end U.S. tariffs - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/conservative-ndp-tariff-trade-1.4931774</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE13uQ1HaCUPFVSmBkXMg4oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:37:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/conservative-ndp-tariff-trade-1.4931774" target="_blank"&gt;Opposition parties demand Trudeau explain his plan to end U.S. tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's a political long-shot, but opposition parties are teaming up to find out more about what Ottawa is doing to get the Trump administration to lift its tariffs on Canadian steel and aluminum. Conservative and New Democrat MPs today requested an emergency meeting of the Standing Committee on International Trade to consider a motion that would demand the prime minister appear before the committee to answer questions about Canada's tariff strategy. The meeting has been scheduled for Thursday. In a letter to the committee's clerk, Christine Lefrance, opposition members say they want Justin Tr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Tories win federal byelection in eastern Ontario - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/liberals-conservatives-byelection-results-1.4931088</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGWIaWf_atwVyB8YA0fMSy8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 12:44:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/liberals-conservatives-byelection-results-1.4931088" target="_blank"&gt;Tories win federal byelection in eastern Ontario&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Conservatives held on to the eastern Ontario riding of Leeds-Grenville-Thousand Islands and Rideau Lakes in Monday night's federal byelection. With all 238 polls reporting and more than 29,000 votes counted, Conservative candidate Michael Barrett was ahead with 57.8 per cent of the vote by the night's end, according to Elections Canada's preliminary results. The Liberals were looking for signs of growth in tonight's federal byelection as they attempted to reclaim a seat that has not been held by a Liberal since before the 2004 federal elections. There were five candidates vying for offi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Scheer Booed By Chiefs For Failing To Differentiate Himself From Harper - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/06/andrew-scheer-boo-first-nations-chiefs-afn_a_23610886/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEq4HaLE9Hkuf3vb4oSaPc8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w18vGBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/06/andrew-scheer-boo-first-nations-chiefs-afn_a_23610886/" target="_blank"&gt;Scheer Booed By Chiefs For Failing To Differentiate Himself From Harper&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TORONTO — Conservative Leader Andrew Scheer was booed at the Assembly of First Nations Special Chiefs Assembly Thursday after he was unable to explain how he's different from Stephen Harper. Scheer had just finished a speech at Ottawa's Westin hotel, pledging his commitment to reconciliation when the floor was opened to questions. Former prime minister Harper "lost the trust from First Nations," a speaker said before asking Scheer to name one policy change that differs him from his predecessor. The opposition leader did not answer the question. "I'm going to have to ask you to have a little...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Ottawa earmarks $20M to rejoin NATO airborne surveillance program - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/awac-nato-surveillance-ukraine-1.4931098</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHIjbFE9Lo25ELdtwBQbIaIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:30:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/awac-nato-surveillance-ukraine-1.4931098" target="_blank"&gt;Ottawa earmarks $20M to rejoin NATO airborne surveillance program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Liberal government has budgeted up to $20 million in this fiscal year to rejoin NATO's Airborne Early Warning and Control System (AWACS) program, reversing a Conservative-era budget cut in the name of alliance utility and solidarity. Defence Minister Harjit Sajjan and other senior officials recently appeared before a House of Commons committee to talk about the country's return to the long-standing alliance programme, which sees more than a dozen nations cost-share the operation of E3-A surveillance planes. New documents, released to CBC News under access to information law, show Canada...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Ex-Harper immigration minister calls out Scheer over 'factually incorrect' statements on UN migration pact - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/alexander-scheer-trudeau-un-compact-1.4932698</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOJKj4TvjP4CVyUbz_9cJ6YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 02:03:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/alexander-scheer-trudeau-un-compact-1.4932698" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-Harper immigration minister calls out Scheer over 'factually incorrect' statements on UN migration pact&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conservative Leader Andrew Scheer is being called out by a former immigration minister in Stephen Harper's government for factual inaccuracies in a public statement Scheer made Tuesday in which he called on the Liberals to reject a UN agreement on migration. Speaking in the foyer of the House of Commons Tuesday afternoon, Scheer said his party strongly opposes Prime Minister Justin Trudeau's "plan to sign Canada on to the UN Global Compact on Migration." Scheer said that by signing the compact, Canada would open the door to foreign bureaucrats directing its immigration policy. "It gives inf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Justin Trudeau Accuses Andrew Scheer Of Using ‘Rebel Media Talking Points’ On UN Migration Agreement - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/04/justin-trudeau-accuses-andrew-scheer-of-using-rebel-media-talking-points-on-un-migration-agreement_a_23608648/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDSZf73M1yUt-HWrkrS24e0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/04/justin-trudeau-accuses-andrew-scheer-of-using-rebel-media-talking-points-on-un-migration-agreement_a_23608648/" target="_blank"&gt;Justin Trudeau Accuses Andrew Scheer Of Using ‘Rebel Media Talking Points’ On UN Migration Agreement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — As Canada prepares to sign on to a United Nations agreement on migration, Conservative politicians are pushing back, saying signing it would be tantamount to erasing Canada's borders. But the Liberals say Conservatives are simply trying to court voters being fed conspiracy theories about the UN agreement fuelled by the online news outlet Rebel Media. The Global Compact on Migration is set to become the first, inter-governmentally negotiated agreement under the UN to cover all dimensions of international migration; it is aimed at improving co-operation between countries and will be ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Tories Easily Win Federal Byelection In Leeds-Grenville-Thousand Islands and Rideau Lakes - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/03/tories-poised-to-win-federal-byelection-in-leeds-grenville-thousand-islands-and-rideau-lakes_a_23607687/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENht1ZTyLVZK9VWq803Yb0UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 03:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/03/tories-poised-to-win-federal-byelection-in-leeds-grenville-thousand-islands-and-rideau-lakes_a_23607687/" target="_blank"&gt;Tories Easily Win Federal Byelection In Leeds-Grenville-Thousand Islands and Rideau Lakes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — The Conservatives easily hung onto a long-time Tory fiefdom Monday, scoring a convincing victory in a federal byelection held in eastern Ontario. With all polls reporting in Leeds-Grenville-Thousand Islands and Rideau Lakes, Conservative candidate Michael Barrett, a municipal councillor, had racked up 57.8 per cent of the vote. Liberal contender Mary Jean McFall was second with 35.8 per cent, while the NDP trailed with three per cent — just 24 votes ahead of the Greens. The riding became vacant when Conservative MP Gord Brown died in May. He had been the MP since 2004. Some 35 per ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Ottawa to overhaul how it deals with First Nations historical claims - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/indigenous/carolyn-bennett-specific-claims-overhaul-1.4930894</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrEUx7br1ZELOSNnl7xfkYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/indigenous/carolyn-bennett-specific-claims-overhaul-1.4930894" target="_blank"&gt;Ottawa to overhaul how it deals with First Nations historical claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The federal government is poised to overhaul the way it settles historical claims from First Nations over issues like loss of reserve lands and mishandled funds, according to Carolyn Bennett, the minister of Crown-Indigenous relations. In an interview with CBC News, Bennett said her government would soon announce a replacement to the current drawn-out model where federal officials have three years to decide on whether to accept or reject what's known as a specific claim. That deadline is often missed. "The new system is going to make a huge difference," she said on Monday. "People aren't go...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Ontario Auditor General's Report Says Social Assistance Costs Soared Under Former Liberal Government - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/05/ontario-auditor-general-report_a_23609552/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO0jqdSmsTIAz9jf5LNOO9oqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w18vGBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/05/ontario-auditor-general-report_a_23609552/" target="_blank"&gt;Ontario Auditor General's Report Says Social Assistance Costs Soared Under Former Liberal Government&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TORONTO — Ontario's social assistance costs ballooned under the previous Liberal government but the system failed to help recipients become self-reliant, the province's auditor general said Wednesday. In her annual report, Bonnie Lysyk said the number of Ontario Works cases has increased by almost 25 per cent since 2009, hiking costs up more than 55 per cent to nearly $3 billion. At the same time, the program only helped 10 to 13 per cent of recipients find work in the last five years, Lysyk said. "A central finding in almost all of the audits this year was that spending of public monies di...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>P.E.I. Could Make History With Canada's 1st Green Party Government - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/03/pei-green-party_a_23607272/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI8omOW9AAyQbC0ZM-uE0PoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 17:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/03/pei-green-party_a_23607272/" target="_blank"&gt;P.E.I. Could Make History With Canada's 1st Green Party Government&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiny Prince Edward Island has long embraced the politically unusual: it had the first premier of non-European heritage, the first elected woman premier and the first openly gay male premier. Now, polls are suggesting Island voters could soon elect Canada's first Green government. "It's real," says pollster Don Mills, CEO of Halifax-based Corporate Research Associates (CRA). "We've been tracking their upward momentum for well over a year." Slight edge on the Liberals With a provincial election less than a year away, the Greens are on a tear. A CRA poll of 300 Islanders in August suggested th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Ottawa warns that a crackdown on impaired drivers is fast approaching - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/impaired-driving-c46-legislation-blair-justice-1.4931910</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECo8bWYdCEEkIe-Y5RPVMRUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:52:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/impaired-driving-c46-legislation-blair-justice-1.4931910" target="_blank"&gt;Ottawa warns that a crackdown on impaired drivers is fast approaching&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liberal ministers are warning that the risk of being nabbed for impaired driving will increase "exponentially" this holiday season — even as they concede their new impaired driving law is likely to face a court challenge. Justice Minister Jody Wilson-Raybould and Border Security and Organized Crime Reduction Minister Bill Blair held a news conference Tuesday to remind Canadians that in two weeks, they will be subject to mandatory alcohol screening if they're stopped by police. "That, frankly, is a game-changer," Blair said. "And what we want all Canadian drivers to understand is that ... sh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>'Grossly unfair': Judges push back on Liberal plan to make their expenses public - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/judges-liberal-legislation-c58-1.4925791</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAvOoz35p5N5Tm64L88BAF4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/judges-liberal-legislation-c58-1.4925791" target="_blank"&gt;'Grossly unfair': Judges push back on Liberal plan to make their expenses public&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal judges are fighting a proposed law that would force them to make their travel and other expenses public, calling it "unacceptable." The Liberal government is pushing proactive disclosure rules as part of sweeping reforms to improve transparency and accountability. But legal representatives warn the new rules could undermine judicial independence, erode public confidence in the justice system and put the personal safety of judges in jeopardy. At issue is Bill C-58, a bill to reform the Access to Information and Privacy Act that has cleared the House of Commons and is now being review...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>MP Raj Grewal remaining MP for now, addresses allegations of ethical breaches - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/raj-grewal-mp-liberal-gambling-allegation-video-von-scheel-1.4928872</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBCG7GzW2i8vb-54aQn9yqgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 18:01:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/raj-grewal-mp-liberal-gambling-allegation-video-von-scheel-1.4928872" target="_blank"&gt;MP Raj Grewal remaining MP for now, addresses allegations of ethical breaches&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liberal MP Raj Grewal has announced his intention to leave the party caucus, but will stay on as an MP for the time being amid questions surrounding his conduct and gambling addiction. In an 11-minute video posted to Facebook late Friday night, Grewal addressed multiple allegations against him raised in the House of Commons and in legions of media reports. "I know my silence this past week has raised questions and speculation – and for that, I truly apologize," he begins. Grewal then launches into an exhaustive, detailed account of his version of the events since he was elected to his Bramp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Raj Grewal's Gambling Debts Surfaced In Broader Money Laundering Probe: Source - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/29/raj-grewals-gambling-debts-surfaced-in-broader-money-laundering-probe-source_a_23604493/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELx96xTktVkvtmOH8IgYnREqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/29/raj-grewals-gambling-debts-surfaced-in-broader-money-laundering-probe-source_a_23604493/" target="_blank"&gt;Raj Grewal's Gambling Debts Surfaced In Broader Money Laundering Probe: Source&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — Word of Liberal MP Raj Grewal's gambling debts surfaced on police wiretaps in a much broader probe into other people suspected of money laundering and terrorist financing, says a source with knowledge of the events. Grewal's sudden decision to step down as the member for the southern Ontario riding of Brampton East was prompted by a gambling problem that led him to incur significant personal debts, the Prime Minister's Office said last week. "They have people talking about his gambling debts on the wire."Canadian Press source The source, who requested anonymity due to the sensitivi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Bill C-76 Opens 'Opportunity' For Foreign Governments To Influence Canadian Elections, Senators Told - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/29/bill-c-76-opens-opportunity-for-foreign-governments-to-influence-canadian-elections-senators-told_a_23604822/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGWV8HKPoBPeRdZQamDy0W4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 22:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/29/bill-c-76-opens-opportunity-for-foreign-governments-to-influence-canadian-elections-senators-told_a_23604822/" target="_blank"&gt;Bill C-76 Opens 'Opportunity' For Foreign Governments To Influence Canadian Elections, Senators Told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — More Canadians living abroad should not be allowed to vote, a Senate committee heard Thursday, because hostile foreign governments might use their mail-in ballots to fraudulently influence federal elections. Speaking to the upper chamber's legal and constitutional affairs committee, expat journalist David Frum told his sister, Conservative Sen. Linda Frum, and her colleagues that while he doesn't fear extending the vote to Canadians such as him, who live in the United States, he believes that thousands of Canadians "who live in non-democratic societies could be used as pawns by the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Reaction to closure of Canadian GM plant: Flurry of words and one radical suggestion - rabble.ca</title><link>http://rabble.ca/news/2018/11/reaction-closure-canadian-gm-plant-flurry-words-and-one-radical-suggestion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEkWblHrO32EcKxC1TN1Ic4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowrb6YATCRgwMwu78B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://rabble.ca/news/2018/11/reaction-closure-canadian-gm-plant-flurry-words-and-one-radical-suggestion" target="_blank"&gt;Reaction to closure of Canadian GM plant: Flurry of words and one radical suggestion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;rabble.ca&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost as soon as General Motors announced earlier this week it would be closing its Oshawa plant, political leaders in Ottawa and Toronto took to the microphones and social media. And a Toronto-based journalist proposed a radical idea. From Ontario Premier Doug Ford to members of the Trudeau government in Ottawa, the messages were similar: There is not much they can do to keep the GM Oshawa jobs. That ship has left the dock, in Ford’s words. But both levels of government did promise to do what they could to help the displaced workers, through enhanced employment insurance and job re-traini...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://rabble.ca">rabble.ca</source></item><item><title>Minister who claims to be a friend of labour prepares to force postal workers back to work - rabble.ca</title><link>http://rabble.ca/news/2018/11/minister-who-claims-be-friend-labour-prepares-force-postal-workers-back-work</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMjDMiLe_f7qUdy8Ek6ag-wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowrb6YATCRgwMwu78B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://rabble.ca/news/2018/11/minister-who-claims-be-friend-labour-prepares-force-postal-workers-back-work" target="_blank"&gt;Minister who claims to be a friend of labour prepares to force postal workers back to work&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;rabble.ca&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Thursday November 22, federal Labour Minister Patty Hadju introduced a procedural motion in the House of Commons to fast track not-yet-introduced legislation that would force more than 50,000 striking postal workers back to work. Speaking to reporters, Hadju said that, for now, the Liberal government is “in a place where we still are encouraging the parties to get that negotiated agreement together.” The government has not shown its hand yet on the back-to-work bill. And postal strikes are, of course, rotating. The mail, including the hundreds of thousands of parcels Canadians order onli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://rabble.ca">rabble.ca</source></item><item><title>Raj Grewal May Not Be Resigning As Brampton East MP After All - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/01/raj-grewal-may-not-be-resigning-brampton-east-mp_a_23605812/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOm0uLXtIID2ezkCYzfvo04qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 07:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/12/01/raj-grewal-may-not-be-resigning-brampton-east-mp_a_23605812/" target="_blank"&gt;Raj Grewal May Not Be Resigning As Brampton East MP After All&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ontario MP Raj Grewal says he's changed his mind about definitively resigning his Brampton East seat, after more than a week of controversy arising from his professed gambling addiction. In a lengthy post on Facebook late Friday, as well as a video statement, Grewal laid out some of his personal finances and addressed some of the "half-truths" that he said have emerged in the past several days. "My sins are not ones based in corruption and dishonesty; they are born out of human frailty," said Grewal, 33. On Nov. 22, Grewal abruptly announced he was stepping down as the southern Ontario ridi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>A Tax Credit Can Help Save Canadian Journalism, But Never Buy It - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/jerry-dias/journalism-tax-credits_a_23604591/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3tuESbml2lrN68Lx3JSGEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8wibdI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 19:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/jerry-dias/journalism-tax-credits_a_23604591/" target="_blank"&gt;A Tax Credit Can Help Save Canadian Journalism, But Never Buy It&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the media in Canada and around the world, the internet and social media have changed everything. The way the news is presented has changed. The way it is consumed has changed. The way it is paid for has changed, too often to the detriment of traditional media. What has not changed is the central role media plays in our society as a vital part of our democratic system — and that's why media companies and workers, Unifor included, have for years pushed the federal government to find a way to support local news. The recent federal financial update from the federal government contained some...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Grewal still in Liberal caucus a week after saying he'd resign over gambling addiction - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/grewal-gambling-addiction-caucus-house-1.4926254</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRNUEdUBAezKNTd4PR4mkUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:25:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/grewal-gambling-addiction-caucus-house-1.4926254" target="_blank"&gt;Grewal still in Liberal caucus a week after saying he'd resign over gambling addiction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite informing the Prime Minister's Office last week that he was resigning as an MP to deal with a gambling addiction, MP Raj Grewal remains a member of both the Liberal caucus and the House of Commons. The news comes despite opposition demands for clarification on when the PMO was informed Grewal had come to the attention of the RCMP and the OPP. "When we met he said he was resigning as a Member of Parliament. It was my understanding that that was going to be imminent and I suspect that that is something that he will be doing in the very short term," said Mark Holland, the chief governm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>RCMP knew Atwal was joining PM's trip — but did not tell Trudeau's security detail: report - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/atwal-trudeau-report-rcmp-1.4930636</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMd0n88G8-FezkE1_WgrPtMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 22:55:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/atwal-trudeau-report-rcmp-1.4930636" target="_blank"&gt;RCMP knew Atwal was joining PM's trip — but did not tell Trudeau's security detail: report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RCMP admitted that they made a mistake when they failed to inform Prime Minister Justin Trudeau's protective detail that would-be political assassin Jaspal Atwal was planning to join the PM during his official visit to India earlier this year, according to a new report by a joint committee of MPs and senators. The report by the National Security and Intelligence Committee of Parliamentarians, released today, details how the RCMP "had information that suggested that Mr. Atwal was going with the Prime Minister on the official trip to India, but did not validate that information." "The RCM...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Doug Ford Says He Won't Point Fingers At Trudeau Government For Looming Closure Of Oshawa GM Plant - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/26/doug-ford-trudeau-gm-plant_a_23601395/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDSms8Q9BKRkgvyNbIF13fgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/26/doug-ford-trudeau-gm-plant_a_23601395/" target="_blank"&gt;Doug Ford Says He Won't Point Fingers At Trudeau Government For Looming Closure Of Oshawa GM Plant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ontario Premier Doug Ford says he will not be casting blame on the federal Liberal government over the decision by General Motors to close an assembly plant in Oshawa and lay off nearly 3,000 workers. Speaking to reporters in Toronto Monday, Ford said he discussed the "devastating" news with Prime Minister Justin Trudeau and has urged the federal government to extend employment insurance eligibility for those affected by five weeks to a maximum of 50 weeks. More from HuffPost Canada: - General Motors' Oshawa Plant One Of Many To Be Shut Down As Automaker Restructures - PMO 'Very Disappointe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Jagmeet Singh's Remarks On Bill C-89 Have A 'Lot Of Baloney' - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/29/jagmeet-singhs-remarks-on-bill-c-89-have-a-lot-of-baloney_a_23604816/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_wuSknXogQ_gNxqxxbx0QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w18vGBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/29/jagmeet-singhs-remarks-on-bill-c-89-have-a-lot-of-baloney_a_23604816/" target="_blank"&gt;Jagmeet Singh's Remarks On Bill C-89 Have A 'Lot Of Baloney'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — "What we would expect is the prime minister to do everything in his power to ensure that there's a free and fair negotiation. But instead what he's doing is bringing in the worst, most draconian legislation today, completely undemocratic, and what he's doing is trampling on the rights of working people." NDP Leader Jagmeet Singh. Nov. 23, 2018. —— After five weeks of rotating strikes and a growing backlog of undelivered mail, Justin Trudeau's Liberal government last week introduced back-to-work legislation for the Canadian Union of Postal Workers. Bill C-89 was rushed through the H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Why Ottawa Seems To Be Backing Away From Right-To-Housing Pledge - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/27/feds-right-to-housing_a_23602578/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK7RfVuwwtsS6O98XfhqZuUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8wibdI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 18:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/27/feds-right-to-housing_a_23602578/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Ottawa Seems To Be Backing Away From Right-To-Housing Pledge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — Worried that they'd create too much new bureaucracy by hiring a new watchdog and setting up an adjudication system to enforce a right to housing they've promised, the federal Liberals appear ready to back off both. The Liberals' decade-long housing strategy, released a year ago, promised to recognize a right for every Canadian to have adequate housing and to remove government roadblocks to getting it, alongside aggressive spending to build and repair affordable housing units. Under the $40-billion plan, that right was to be boosted by a federal housing advocate who would give peopl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Conservative senators blame independents for delaying back-to-work bill - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/conservative-senators-back-to-work-canada-post-1.4920086</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGKtZVqPLWlFJDzuwnlwWXQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:32:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/conservative-senators-back-to-work-canada-post-1.4920086" target="_blank"&gt;Conservative senators blame independents for delaying back-to-work bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conservative senators say they wanted to push Canada Post back-to-work legislation through on Sunday but are pointing the finger at independent senators for delaying the third and final reading until Monday. The House of Commons introduced the bill earlier this week and pushed it through in quick fashion, then asked the Senate to do the same. Conservative Senator Leo Housakos said his caucus had signalled to the Independent Senators Group (ISG) they were willing to sit on Sunday to pass Bill C-89 as soon as possible. "We offered our full cooperation to get it read, tabled and passed by [Sun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Notley says Alberta will buy rail cars to move oil, wants Ottawa to chip in - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/notley-alberta-rail-cars-move-oil-trudeau-1.4923976</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAfa6hjZIng6oDX2qBf-xxEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 21:34:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/notley-alberta-rail-cars-move-oil-trudeau-1.4923976" target="_blank"&gt;Notley says Alberta will buy rail cars to move oil, wants Ottawa to chip in&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberta Premier Rachel Notley said today her government is only weeks away from finalizing a purchase of rail cars to move oil and help close massive price gaps that have short-changed government coffers and Canadian oil producers. She also said she wants the federal Liberal government to contribute financially to the plan. "We're not wasting any time," Notley told a Canadian Club luncheon in Ottawa Wednesday, formally announcing the rail car purchase. "Alberta's oil is going to flow one way or another — if not by pipelines, then by rail or by truck. "Don't mistake me — this is not the long...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Liberal MP Raj Grewal quitting politics, citing 'personal and medical reasons' - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/raj-grewal-to-step-down-1.4916960</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN5Zr0E2koq3HK19eYD3g_YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:46:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/raj-grewal-to-step-down-1.4916960" target="_blank"&gt;Liberal MP Raj Grewal quitting politics, citing 'personal and medical reasons'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liberal MP Raj Grewal is citing "personal and medical reasons" for his decision to quit federal politics, according to a post on his Facebook page. "Yesterday, I informed the chief government whip that I will be resigning my seat as member of Parliament for Brampton East due to personal and medical reasons," he said in the post. "To the people of Brampton East, serving as your MP has been the greatest privilege of my life. This has been a decision I've struggled with for some time now and one I made with great difficulty and real sadness. But I feel I need this time to focus on my health an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Liberals Will Run Against Jagmeet Singh In Burnaby South Byelection, Bucking ‘Leader’s Courtesy’ - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/22/liberals-jagmeet-singh-burnaby-south_a_23597149/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBHiBbwOwY2_XAmjfmojvO4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w18vGBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 17:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/22/liberals-jagmeet-singh-burnaby-south_a_23597149/" target="_blank"&gt;Liberals Will Run Against Jagmeet Singh In Burnaby South Byelection, Bucking ‘Leader’s Courtesy’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal Liberals will not be extending a so-called "leader's courtesy" to give the NDP's Jagmeet Singh an easier path to the House of Commons A senior Liberal source unauthorized to speak on the matter has confirmed to HuffPost Canada that Liberals will run a candidate against Singh in an upcoming byelection in the British Columbia riding of Burnaby South. The source confirmed earlier reports from both The Hill Times and CBC News. The byelection is expected to be called early in the new year and take place in February. The government will also call votes to fill vacancies in two other ridin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>'It's not good': Security report on Trudeau's problem-plagued India trip set to drop Monday - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/trudeau-india-atwal-1.4926456</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZmG6NITRkBk_oohR7MJFgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:33:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/trudeau-india-atwal-1.4926456" target="_blank"&gt;'It's not good': Security report on Trudeau's problem-plagued India trip set to drop Monday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings of a special security review into Prime Minister Justin Trudeau's much-maligned trip to India early this year will be released Monday. Copies of the classified report are in the hands of the Prime Minister's Office and Public Safety Minister Ralph Goodale. While a source told CBC News the PMO doesn't see the report as a major concern, another person with knowledge of the report's findings acknowledged that "it's not good." The sources spoke to CBC News on the condition of anonymity because they were not authorized to speak about it. The report — the first ever conducted by the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Doug Ford Blames Justin Trudeau's Incoming Carbon Tax For General Motors Plant Closure - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/28/doug-ford-gm-closure-oshawa-justin-trudeau_a_23603876/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEkqkNUBrP3PwDuMmJ78BPIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8wibdI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 01:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/28/doug-ford-gm-closure-oshawa-justin-trudeau_a_23603876/" target="_blank"&gt;Doug Ford Blames Justin Trudeau's Incoming Carbon Tax For General Motors Plant Closure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ontario Premier Doug Ford says years of Liberal policies are to blame for General Motors' decision to close its plant in Oshawa, Ont. "GM didn't make this decision overnight," Ford told reporters at Queen's Park on Wednesday. "They didn't make it six months ago. It is the result of years of governments that just don't care about job creators, or how hard it is to run a business or create a job." The premier singled out Prime Minister Justin Trudeau — just two days after saying he wouldn't point the finger at the federal government. "You can't campaign for a job-killing carbon tax on Monday,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Auditor general trashes Liberal plan to keep CF-18s flying until 2032 - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/ag-cf-18s-1.4912813</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJpv1OrSPk5tDlBoan2A_3QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 03:17:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/ag-cf-18s-1.4912813" target="_blank"&gt;Auditor general trashes Liberal plan to keep CF-18s flying until 2032&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canada's auditor general has shot down the Liberal government's handling of the air force's aging CF-18s in a blistering report that raises questions about national security, and even long-term safety, regarding the viability of the country's frontline fighter jets. Auditor General Michael Ferguson's fall report, tabled Tuesday, methodically picks apart the recent policy change at the Department of National Defence, which requires the military to have enough warplanes to meet Canada's commitments to both NORAD and NATO at the same time. Watch Power &amp; Politics take a look at the ups and down...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>'We're outraged': Union rips Liberal back-to-work bill for Canada Post carriers - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/canada-post-back-to-work-legislation-1.4915974</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEID7JoZE98lt2qSU5gFHApcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDBjx0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 20:35:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/canada-post-back-to-work-legislation-1.4915974" target="_blank"&gt;'We're outraged': Union rips Liberal back-to-work bill for Canada Post carriers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The union representing Canada Post carriers is accusing the federal government of violating its members' constitutional rights by pushing emergency legislation to force them back to work. Labour Minister Patty Hajdu tabled the bill in the House of Commons Thursday morning, triggering a swift rebuke from the Canadian Union of Postal Workers (CUPW). Canada Post is in its fifth week of rotating strikes by thousands of unionized workers, with no sign yet of a breakthrough in contract negotiations. Hajdu said the Liberal government is a strong supporter of organized labour and workers' rights an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Doug Ford Says Ontario Budget Won't Be Balanced By 'Slashing And Burning' - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/18/doug-ford-says-ontario-budget-wont-be-balanced-by-slashing-and-burning_a_23592961/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBB57gPse5_aLG9NjkJ3t88qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/18/doug-ford-says-ontario-budget-wont-be-balanced-by-slashing-and-burning_a_23592961/" target="_blank"&gt;Doug Ford Says Ontario Budget Won't Be Balanced By 'Slashing And Burning'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TORONTO — Days after his government delivered its first major fiscal update, Premier Doug Ford said his government "may" balance the province's budget in the final year of its mandate. Ford made the comments during a "fireside chat" with Toronto Sun editor in chief Adrienne Batra at the Ontario Progressive Conservative policy convention in Toronto on Saturday. Asked how he would eliminate a deficit his government now says is $14.5 billion, Ford stressed it will take some time. "We're not going to go in there and start slashing and burning," he said. "We're going to do it responsibly. We wil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Andrew Scheer pushes lifetime firearms ban for criminals, calls Liberal policies 'lazy' - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/andrew-scheer-pushes-lifetime-firearms-ban-for-criminals-calls-liberal-policies-lazy-1.4913638</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMqWciL2A4MuQPzhNdX5peQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 20:12:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/andrew-scheer-pushes-lifetime-firearms-ban-for-criminals-calls-liberal-policies-lazy-1.4913638" target="_blank"&gt;Andrew Scheer pushes lifetime firearms ban for criminals, calls Liberal policies 'lazy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conservative Leader Andrew Scheer unveiled a series of firearms policies Tuesday meant to curb gun violence — and slammed the Liberal government's plan to study a national handgun ban as a "lazy" effort that could punish lawful gun owners. While the Conservative caucus has attacked the tighter firearms inventory controls in Bill C-71 — legislation introduced by Public Safety Minister Ralph Goodale — as a revival of the much-maligned long-gun registry, Scheer himself has now proposed a series of measures to restrict firearms ownership. Speaking to reporters in Vancouver, Scheer said a Conser...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Senate postpones Canada Post back-to-work legislation decision until Monday - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/senate-canada-post-legislation-strike-1.4919485</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHXYszuqwVoKO9lh3mnDmT8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 00:32:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/senate-canada-post-legislation-strike-1.4919485" target="_blank"&gt;Senate postpones Canada Post back-to-work legislation decision until Monday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Senate opted to push a final decision on the government's proposed Canada Post back-to-work legislation to Monday, after hours of debate and witness testimony. Senators were prepared to sit on Sunday, if necessary, but after nearly eight hours of witness testimony and debate, they decided to reschedule the third and final reading of Bill C-89 for Monday afternoon. That means back-to-work legislation could come into effect as early as Tuesday afternoon, if the legislation is passed on Monday. The rare weekend sitting saw intense discussions about the government's motivation for forcing w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Fall Economic Statement From Feds Lays Out Billions In Business Tax Breaks - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/21/fall-economic-statement-morneau_a_23596395/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELhZBGLzuFwYripDLco3QhIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8wibdI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 21:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/21/fall-economic-statement-morneau_a_23596395/" target="_blank"&gt;Fall Economic Statement From Feds Lays Out Billions In Business Tax Breaks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — The federal Liberals have come up with a $16-billion answer to Canada's competitiveness concerns. Ottawa's long-awaited plan to help Canada compete with the United States for investment dollars is the centrepiece of its latest fall economic statement, which forecasts slightly deeper annual deficits over the coming years. Finance Minister Bill Morneau had faced pressure to lower the corporate tax rate in response to major tax and regulatory reforms in the U.S. In Wednesday's economic update, Morneau chose a cheaper approach — but one that will still use billions worth of extra feder...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>What Is 'Back-To-Work' Legislation? And How Does It Work? - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/26/what-is-back-to-work-legislation-and-how-does-it-work_a_23601207/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED2f8s6TVU8JxHT1Iwixy-EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8wibdI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 22:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/26/what-is-back-to-work-legislation-and-how-does-it-work_a_23601207/" target="_blank"&gt;What Is 'Back-To-Work' Legislation? And How Does It Work?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Canada Post strike saga entered a dramatic new chapter last week when the federal government announced it was considering using a law to get postal workers back on the job. Last week, Labour Minister Patty Hajdu said the Liberal government did not want to resort to using back-to-work legislation, but noted there was "limited progress" in the talks between the Canadian Union of Postal Workers (CUPW) and Canada Post and that the feds had "exhausted" all options. Hajdu said the Liberals maintain that the best outcome is one that is reached by both parties at the negotiating table, but if t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Liberals deepen federal deficit in response to Trump tax cuts - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/bill-morneau-fall-economic-statement-fiscal-update-1.4913219</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEErmficVwV20HdOZDMn-IyAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDBjx0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 01:47:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/bill-morneau-fall-economic-statement-fiscal-update-1.4913219" target="_blank"&gt;Liberals deepen federal deficit in response to Trump tax cuts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Liberal government is spending billions to help corporate Canada compete with the U.S. and to prop up struggling news organizations — showing a willingness to go deeper into deficit with no timeline for returning to a balanced budget. In his fall fiscal update, delivered this afternoon, Finance Minister Bill Morneau touted Canada's strong economic performance but warned that global uncertainty, unpredictable oil prices, lingering trade disputes and deep tax cuts brought in by U.S. President Donald Trump are all posing serious challenges. The fall economic statement delivers $17.6 billio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Postal union launches protest campaign as employees halt rotating strikes - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/cupw-legislation-strike-action-response-1.4922372</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILKkTTxWu7Sj900qV4--y0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDBjx0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:25:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/cupw-legislation-strike-action-response-1.4922372" target="_blank"&gt;Postal union launches protest campaign as employees halt rotating strikes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal back-to-work legislation may have ended rotating strikes by postal workers — but their union now says it's switching to a campaign of "non-violent civil disobedience" to press its contract claims. In a statement issued Tuesday, Canadian Union of Postal Workers Union (CUPW) National President Mike Palecek said that while legal strike action is ending, the pressure campaign is just beginning. "You cannot legislate labour peace. We are now moving to a different phase of the struggle," he said. Union members were instructed to return to regularly scheduled shifts as of noon ET today, an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Auditor General Fall Report 2018: Canada Lacks Pilots To Fly Old Jets We're Buying From Australia - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/20/auditor-general-fall-report-fighter-jets_a_23594820/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDmJyyj3vrux3Pe-q0iWnTwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/20/auditor-general-fall-report-fighter-jets_a_23594820/" target="_blank"&gt;Auditor General Fall Report 2018: Canada Lacks Pilots To Fly Old Jets We're Buying From Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — The Trudeau government pressed ahead with its plan to buy second-hand fighter jets from Australia on Tuesday despite withering fire from the federal auditor general, who warned that the military might not have anybody to fly them. Six years after blowing up the Harper government's plan to buy new F-35s without a competition, auditor general Michael Ferguson targeted the Liberals' own attempts to buy jets. He first picked apart the government's aborted plan to purchase "interim" Super Hornets to bolster Canada's aging CF-18 fleet, and then its current plan to buy used Australian fig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Trudeau to meet federal party leaders to talk support for French Canadians in wake of Ford cuts - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/trudeau-scheer-singh-may-meeting-1.4923288</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChm-t6vVY68ga5BUAmppQUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDO3RQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 20:01:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/trudeau-scheer-singh-may-meeting-1.4923288" target="_blank"&gt;Trudeau to meet federal party leaders to talk support for French Canadians in wake of Ford cuts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prime Minister Justin Trudeau will meet with the leaders of the four other main federal political parties Wednesday to discuss what can be done to support French Canadians in the wake of Ontario Premier Doug Ford's recent cuts. The session was mentioned in Trudeau's daily itinerary report, which said only that the prime minister was meeting to discuss "issues facing the Canadian Francophonie" with the NDP's Jagmeet Singh, the Green Party's Elizabeth May, the Conservatives' Andrew Scheer and the interim leader of the Bloc Québécois, Mario Beaulieu. A senior government official speaking on ba...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Jagmeet Singh says he will continue to run in Burnaby South - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/jagmeet-singh-says-he-will-continue-to-run-in-burnaby-south-1.4917867</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBl3pyAALCWj9ABoXabYwpwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 18:27:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/jagmeet-singh-says-he-will-continue-to-run-in-burnaby-south-1.4917867" target="_blank"&gt;Jagmeet Singh says he will continue to run in Burnaby South&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal NDP Leader Jagmeet Singh says he will continue to stand as his party's candidate in the B.C. riding of Burnaby South, despite news this week that the Liberal MP in his home riding of Brampton is leaving politics. "I made it clear my decision to run in Burnaby South and I continue to remain clear on that decision," he told reporters on Friday. Singh's statement comes hours after Brampton East Liberal MP Raj Grewal announced his decision to quit federal politics, citing "personal and medical reasons." Singh, who held the Brampton riding at the provincial level until late 2017, had pre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>RCMP's disciplinary review body struggling with a 'significant backlog of files' - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/rcmp-external-review-committee-1.4922450</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECyQsfadmzdL_3025eSlIscqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 10:33:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/rcmp-external-review-committee-1.4922450" target="_blank"&gt;RCMP's disciplinary review body struggling with a 'significant backlog of files'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RCMP's disciplinary review body — the independent committee that investigates things like harassment complaints and Mountie misconduct — says it's drowning in casework. The RCMP External Review Committee's warning came in its annual departmental plan, recently tabled in the House of Commons. "The ERC will face continued operational pressures in delivering its case reviews in 2018-19 due to the need to manage a significant backlog of files and increased workload projections," noted the report. It's not the first time the committee has warned the government about the backlog. It told Parl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>MPs vote to proceed with fast-tracking Canada Post back-to-work legislation through Commons - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/canada-post-union-legislation-1.4917647</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ8hukxtBLdIQzEwZmFAcV4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 02:09:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/canada-post-union-legislation-1.4917647" target="_blank"&gt;MPs vote to proceed with fast-tracking Canada Post back-to-work legislation through Commons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A majority of MPs in the House of Commons have voted in favour of the Liberal government's motion to fast-track legislation through Parliament that would force Canada Post employees back to work. Canada Post is in its fifth week of rotating strikes by thousands of unionized workers, with no sign yet of a breakthrough in contract negotiations. The Liberals won the vote 173 to 13 with the help of a handful of Conservative MPs who remained in Ottawa for the vote. A majority of NDP MPs stood and left the House in protest after their vote, rendering their votes invalid. Some NDP MPs raised a fis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>731,000 Canadians Borrow Money To Pay For Prescription Drugs: Study - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/20/debt-canada-pharmacare-study_a_23595253/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOc44NkeU62NwJdT6t0ac3AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 23:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/20/debt-canada-pharmacare-study_a_23595253/" target="_blank"&gt;731,000 Canadians Borrow Money To Pay For Prescription Drugs: Study&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — A gap in medication coverage forced an estimated 731,000 Canadians to borrow money to pay for out-of-pocket prescription drug costs last year, according to a new study published Tuesday. After surveying more than 28,000 people, researchers at the University of British Columbia found "potentially vulnerable" groups including children, seniors, and low-income earners to be disproportionately affected by high drug costs. "These new findings suggest that many people are going into debt to cover the costs of their prescription medications every year," said study author Ashra Kolhatkar i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Doug Ford Says He Doesn't Want To Be Prime Minister - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/20/doug-ford-says-he-doesnt-want-to-be-prime-minister_a_23595165/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP1qBKTc0lvpw2AWcNZ2DrgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w18vGBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/20/doug-ford-says-he-doesnt-want-to-be-prime-minister_a_23595165/" target="_blank"&gt;Doug Ford Says He Doesn't Want To Be Prime Minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TORONTO — Ontario Premier Doug Ford isn't mulling a run for the prime minister's office. The Progressive Conservative leader, who has launched repeated attacks on Justin Trudeau and his Liberal government, said Tuesday that he had no national political ambitions and is committed to leading the province. "I'm zoned in on this province, nothing else," the premier told reporters. "Not federally, nothing but fixing the financial mess that we inherited." Ford was asked about his political aspirations after he called on Trudeau, ahead of Wednesday's federal fall economic update, to stop a plan to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Liberals confirm they're running against Singh as byelections planned for February - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/byelections-jagmeet-singh-liberals-1.4915391</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGf_BBRixQGj0sx4Q4i44r8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 23:07:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/byelections-jagmeet-singh-liberals-1.4915391" target="_blank"&gt;Liberals confirm they're running against Singh as byelections planned for February&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NDP Leader Jagmeet Singh will get his chance to enter Parliament in February, when the Liberal government holds byelections to fill the three remaining vacancies in the House of Commons, CBC News has confirmed. The Liberals recently called a byelection in the Ontario riding of Leeds–Grenville–Thousand Islands and Rideau Lakes for Dec. 3, leaving vacancies in three other ridings unfilled. That move was met with a chorus of criticism from the Conservatives, New Democrats, Bloc Québécois and Greens, who demanded that votes also be called to fill the vacancies in the ridings of Outremont, York–...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Fall Economic Statement Unveils 3 New Tax Credits To Save Canadian Journalism Industry - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/21/fall-economic-statement-journalism_a_23596418/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKz-m5UxibunWv-cYO3tLXAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 21:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/21/fall-economic-statement-journalism_a_23596418/" target="_blank"&gt;Fall Economic Statement Unveils 3 New Tax Credits To Save Canadian Journalism Industry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — The Liberal government has unveiled its arms-length attempt to save the country's struggling news industry by introducing three new tax measures to incentivize Canadians to pay for journalism. The measures, included in the fall economic statement Wednesday and estimated to cost $595 million over the next five years, are intended to open new avenues of financial support for domestic news organizations that produce "a wide variety" of original content. The changes come on the heels of promises in last spring's budget to allocate $50 million over five years to support local journalism...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Tories Suggest Liberals Want To ‘Buy’ The Media Before 2019 Election - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/20/tories-liberals-media-bailout_a_23595207/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECTYjyhp0fvZacNvBWgnYvcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/20/tories-liberals-media-bailout_a_23595207/" target="_blank"&gt;Tories Suggest Liberals Want To ‘Buy’ The Media Before 2019 Election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canada's heritage minister says Conservatives are trafficking in conspiracy theories by hinting the federal government wants to "buy" the struggling news industry to curry favourable coverage in the next election. Pablo Rodriguez rose in question period Tuesday to field questions ahead of this week's fall economic statement. His colleague, Finance Minister Bill Morneau, is expected to unveil measures Wednesday that could include help for journalists who are seeing job cutsand newsrooms closed due to declining advertising revenues. Quebec MP Steven Blaney rose in the House of Commons to note...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Tories accuse Trudeau of bribing media with tax breaks - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/tories-accuse-libs-bribing-press-1.4917411</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMMfxT1HZVzuygqLDXv3lxYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 16:31:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/tories-accuse-libs-bribing-press-1.4917411" target="_blank"&gt;Tories accuse Trudeau of bribing media with tax breaks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Conservative Opposition is accusing Prime Minister Justin Trudeau of trying to bribe Canadian media to secure favourable media coverage in the run-up to next year's federal election. The accusations came a day after Finance Minister Bill Morneau announced in the fall economic update that the government was introducing $600 million in tax credits and incentives to help the media industry over the next five years. "Justin Trudeau thinks it is the job of the media to shower him with praise and coincidentally, in an election year, he's forcing Canadian taxpayers to dole out $600 million in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Jagmeet Singh Says Plan To Raise Low Poll Numbers Is To 'Keep On Talking' - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/19/jagmeet-singh-polls_a_23594137/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3SeaRCUNMakanLFVlyTnMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8NBI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/19/jagmeet-singh-polls_a_23594137/" target="_blank"&gt;Jagmeet Singh Says Plan To Raise Low Poll Numbers Is To 'Keep On Talking'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OTTAWA — Federal NDP Leader Jagmeet Singh says his plan is to "keep on talking" to buck a trend in recent opinion polls that suggest support for his party is now closer to the Greens than it is with the Liberals and Conservatives. More cross-country tours, Singh told reporters Monday, will be key to lift the party's profile and appeal in the year before the next election. He pledged to "keep on raising" concerns about housing, climate change, and to "talk to Canadians across the country." _Watch: Jagmeet Singh says NDP is 'trending up' one year into leadership _ Evading questions about his ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item></channel></rss>