<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Double jeopardy - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNREkyY1hRU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-CA&amp;gl=CA&amp;ceid=CA:en</link><language>en-CA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:06:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>The Latest: Justices unlikely to upset double jeopardy rule - National Post</title><link>https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/the-latest-justices-unlikely-to-upset-double-jeopardy-rule</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780128591120</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/the-latest-justices-unlikely-to-upset-double-jeopardy-rule" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Justices unlikely to upset double jeopardy rule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;National Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/us/politics/supreme-court-double-jeopardy.html" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court’s Double Jeopardy Case May Have Implications for Trump Associates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/potential-blow-manafort-supreme-court-unlikely-change-double-jeopardy-rule-n944891" target="_blank"&gt;In potential blow to Manafort, Supreme Court unlikely to change double jeopardy rule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;NBCNews.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/courts_law/supreme-court-seems-reluctant-to-prohibit-state-and-federal-prosecutions-of-same-crime/2018/12/06/78f0d820-f982-11e8-863c-9e2f864d47e7_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court seems reluctant to prohibit state and federal prosecutions of same crime&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/supreme-courts-double-jeopardy-case-holds-mueller-probe-implications-kavanaugh-vote-key" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court’s double-jeopardy case holds Mueller probe implications; Kavanaugh vote key&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fox News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWlRdXNPbWpZQU1FYW42bExUNkpld2dLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://nationalpost.com">National Post</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court double jeopardy case could impact presidential pardon power - CNN International</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/supreme-court-double-jeopardy-presidential-pardon-power/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiZGh0dHBzOi8vZWRpdGlvbi5jbm4uY29tLzIwMTgvMTIvMDYvcG9saXRpY3Mvc3VwcmVtZS1jb3VydC1kb3VibGUtamVvcGFyZHktcHJlc2lkZW50aWFsLXBhcmRvbi1wb3dlci_SAbIBaHR0cHM6Ly9hbXAtY25uLWNvbS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL2FtcC5jbm4uY29tL2Nubi8yMDE4LzEyLzA2L3BvbGl0aWNzL3N1cHJlbWUtY291cnQtZG91YmxlLWplb3BhcmR5LXByZXNpZGVudGlhbC1wYXJkb24tcG93ZXIvaW5kZXguaHRtbD9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:06:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/supreme-court-double-jeopardy-presidential-pardon-power/" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court double jeopardy case could impact presidential pardon power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN International&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court on Thursday will consider an exception to the Fifth Amendment's ban on prosecuting an individual twice for the same offense in a case that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN International</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court seems likely to keep double jeopardy exception - National Post</title><link>https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/supreme-court-takes-up-closely-watched-double-jeopardy-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vbmF0aW9uYWxwb3N0LmNvbS9wbW4vbmV3cy1wbW4vc3VwcmVtZS1jb3VydC10YWtlcy11cC1jbG9zZWx5LXdhdGNoZWQtZG91YmxlLWplb3BhcmR5LWNhc2XSAa4BaHR0cHM6Ly9uYXRpb25hbHBvc3QtY29tLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3MvbmF0aW9uYWxwb3N0LmNvbS9wbW4vbmV3cy1wbW4vc3VwcmVtZS1jb3VydC10YWtlcy11cC1jbG9zZWx5LXdhdGNoZWQtZG91YmxlLWplb3BhcmR5LWNhc2UvYW1wP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/supreme-court-takes-up-closely-watched-double-jeopardy-case" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court seems likely to keep double jeopardy exception&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;National Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON — The Supreme Court seemed likely Thursday to preserve a constitutional rule that allows state and federal governments to prosecute someone ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqdQgKIm9DQklTVFRvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NrQUtFUWpMdzhXbGpZQU1FU2NkamstTzdSMm1FaXRUZFhCeVpXMWxJRU52ZFhKMElIUmhhMlZ6SUhWd0lHUnZkV0pzWlNCcVpXOXdZWEprZVNCallYTmxLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://nationalpost.com">National Post</source></item><item><title>SCOTUS case could impact presidential pardons - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/06/supreme-court-double-jeopardy-mueller-flynn-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG3mz2VpsYvC4DCWPxNO8PsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:34:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/06/supreme-court-double-jeopardy-mueller-flynn-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;SCOTUS case could impact presidential pardons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN's Ariane de Vogue explains the connection between a Supreme Court case related to the Fifth Amendment's double jeopardy clause and the Mueller investigation. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US Supreme Court Appears Wary of Expanding 'Double Jeopardy' - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-supreme-court-appears-wary-of-expanding-double-jeopardy-/4689956.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIIhrkoh1r40xGo6Eza7x0MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:30:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-supreme-court-appears-wary-of-expanding-double-jeopardy-/4689956.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Supreme Court Appears Wary of Expanding 'Double Jeopardy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. Supreme Court justices on Thursday expressed skepticism about putting limits on criminal charges being brought against people for the same offenses by both federal and state prosecutors in a case involving an Alabama man charged with illegally possessing a gun. Depending on how the court rules, the case could have implications for Special Counsel Robert Mueller's investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 U.S. election and any coordination between Moscow and Republican Donald Trump's campaign. A ruling against the government could limit the ability of states to bring charges a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court double jeopardy case could impact presidential pardon power - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/supreme-court-double-jeopardy-presidential-pardon-power/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELEF_bt-GEh3oQJylyRWsgsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:35:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/supreme-court-double-jeopardy-presidential-pardon-power/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court double jeopardy case could impact presidential pardon power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court grappled on Thursday with a case concerning an exception to the Fifth Amendment's ban on prosecuting an individual twice for the same offense in a case that could also possibly impact President Donald Trump's pardon power as it applied to the Robert Mueller probe. Decades ago, the Supreme Court developed an exception to the Fifth Amendment's double jeopardy clause and it is now being asked to rethink precedent. The so-called "separate sovereigns exception" provides that a person can be tried twice for the same offense if the prosecutions occur in state and federal courts. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>There’s an Exception to the Double-Jeopardy Rule - The Atlantic</title><link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2018/12/gamble-v-united-states-case-double-jeopardy/577342/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBPAf36JDkAiKiQ8fx4y-GUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowm_EEMKAiMJXamQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2018/12/gamble-v-united-states-case-double-jeopardy/577342/" target="_blank"&gt;There’s an Exception to the Double-Jeopardy Rule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Atlantic&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ask a lawyer to explain “sovereignty” and you’ll hear an elevated discussion of Enlightenment political thought, along with some name-dropping—Hobbes, Montesquieu, Madison. Ask Terance Gamble, and he will have a more concrete answer: 34 months of his life. On Thursday, the Supreme Court will hear Gamble’s complaint in Gamble v. United States: If the Constitution protects against “double jeopardy,” what allows both the state of Alabama and the U.S. government to convict and imprison him for the very same crime? In 2008, Gamble was convicted in Alabama state court of second-degree robbery, a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theatlantic.com">The Atlantic</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court takes up closely watched double jeopardy case - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/c9c65cff3e4f4420aa4fe86d7554ea6d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM5czPAV7gdaWcAaHwztCnkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:21:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/c9c65cff3e4f4420aa4fe86d7554ea6d" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court takes up closely watched double jeopardy case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Constitution says you can't be tried twice for the same offense. And yet Terance Gamble is sitting in prison today because he was prosecuted separately by Alabama and the federal government for having a gun after an earlier robbery conviction. The Supreme Court is considering Gamble's case on Thursday, and the outcome could have a spillover effect on the investigation into Russian meddling in the 2016 election. At issue is whether to overturn a court-created exception to the Constitution's double-jeopardy bar that allows state and federal prosecutions for the same crim...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court postpones arguments for Bush national day of mourning - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/politics/supreme-court-postponement-bush-day-of-mourning/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEiugXyb5U4xm3my9jnP6D0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:37:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/politics/supreme-court-postponement-bush-day-of-mourning/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court postpones arguments for Bush national day of mourning&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court will delay arguments in a case involving an exception to the Constitution's double jeopardy clause for one day to mark the national day of mourning Wednesday honoring former President George H.W. Bush. The oral arguments in Gamble v. United States will instead be held Thursday, according to a Sunday news release from the court's public information officer. The case involves an exception to the double jeopardy clause of the Fifth Amendment, which allows individuals to be charged for the same offense in both state and federal court. The case could have an impact on President...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Surjit Singh Chhokar murder: Ronnie Coulter jailed for life after retrial under double jeopardy law - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/surjit-singh-chhokar-murder-scottish-waiter-double-jeopardy-ronnie-coulter-jailed-for-life-retrial-a7389386.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF7WnozLw1PmGjjFWRL_ciUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/surjit-singh-chhokar-murder-scottish-waiter-double-jeopardy-ronnie-coulter-jailed-for-life-retrial-a7389386.html" target="_blank"&gt;Surjit Singh Chhokar murder: Ronnie Coulter jailed for life after retrial under double jeopardy law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man has been jailed for life for the “despicable and cowardly” murder of waiter Surjit Singh Chhokar in a retrial under double jeopardy laws. Ronnie Coulter was found guilty at the High Court in Glasgow earlier this month of stabbing the 32-year-old almost 18 years ago. The attack happened as Mr Chhokar returned from his work at an Indian restaurant in Wishaw, North Lanarkshire, on 4 November 1998. Coulter, 48, was previously acquitted when he stood trial in 1999 for the murder but was convicted by a majority when the case became only the second to return to court since Scotland's centuri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Double jeopardy won't protect Michael Slager - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2016/12/06/opinions/double-jeopardy-south-carolina-trial-cevallos/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPFvJgo7RGk5QVgyMFZd15gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 01:48:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2016/12/06/opinions/double-jeopardy-south-carolina-trial-cevallos/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Double jeopardy won't protect Michael Slager&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Danny Cevallos (@CevallosLaw) is a CNN Legal Analyst and a personal injury and criminal defense attorney practicing in Pennsylvania and the US Virgin Islands. The opinions expressed in this commentary are his. Before Michael Slager, the former North Charleston police officer, went on trial for murder in the death of Walter Scott, his lawyers argued their client was the target of "double-teaming" by the state of South Carolina and the federal government. They called the joint investigations -- and the plan for each jurisdiction to pursue charges against Slager -- "chilling" and "unconscionab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Man jailed for life for murder of waiter Surjit Singh Chhokar after 'double jeopardy' conviction - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/31/man-jailed-for-life-for-murder-of-waiter-surjit-singh-chhokar-af/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPAgbjQldtCOaMt5K01xIMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 12:54:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/31/man-jailed-for-life-for-murder-of-waiter-surjit-singh-chhokar-af/" target="_blank"&gt;Man jailed for life for murder of waiter Surjit Singh Chhokar after 'double jeopardy' conviction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man has been jailed for life for the "despicable and cowardly" murder of waiter Surjit Singh Chhokar in a retrial under double jeopardy laws. Ronnie Coulter was found guilty at the High Court in Glasgow earlier this month of stabbing the 32-year-old almost 18 years ago. The attack happened as Mr Chhokar returned from his work at an Indian restaurant in Wishaw, North Lanarkshire, on November 4, 1998. Coulter, 48, was previously acquitted when he stood trial in 1999 for the murder but was convicted by a majority when the case became only the second to return to court since Scotland's centur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Michael Slager's Lawyers Ask For Federal Civil Rights Charges To Be Dropped - International Business Times</title><link>http://www.ibtimes.com/walter-scott-trial-update-michael-slagers-lawyers-ask-federal-civil-rights-charges-be-2492612</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAf8B_czqC9dIVtdgEpOlf4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDDIhrIF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 19:03:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ibtimes.com/walter-scott-trial-update-michael-slagers-lawyers-ask-federal-civil-rights-charges-be-2492612" target="_blank"&gt;Michael Slager's Lawyers Ask For Federal Civil Rights Charges To Be Dropped&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lawyers representing former Charleston South Carolina police officer Michael Slager, whose trial in state court over killing an unarmed black motorist in 2015 ended in a hung jury in December, requested Monday for the dismissal of federal charges against their client. Slager’s lawyers filed a request in federal court saying that it was “crushing” and “unfair” for the former officer to defend himself over shooting and killing Walter Scott against state and federal charges simultaneously, the New York Daily News reported Tuesday. It has been reported that President Donald Trump’s administra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>Russia Meeting Puts President's Son in Legal Jeopardy - Newsweek</title><link>http://www.newsweek.com/trump-jr-legal-jeopardy-635182</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECGZ1w8JyZbQws078K_-Fu8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMNiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 20:56:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.newsweek.com/trump-jr-legal-jeopardy-635182" target="_blank"&gt;Russia Meeting Puts President's Son in Legal Jeopardy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could Donald Trump Jr. go to jail? The question seems less far-fetched than it might have 24 hours ago, now that we’ve seen the emails in which he eagerly expresses interest in meeting with a Russian national purportedly offering damaging information about Democrat Hillary Clinton provided by the Russian government. Legal scholars and law enforcement officials are debating how much legal jeopardy the president’s oldest son finds himself in as a result of his 2016 meeting with a Russian lawyer at Trump Tower in New York City. The encounter, which took place just days after the elder Trump ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>5 Interesting Supreme Court Cases Kavanaugh Could Decide This Term - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/supreme-court-cases-decisions-brett-kavanaugh_us_5bbba129e4b028e1fe402b92</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDyajmG49w83VAXBjIva6JEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 19:47:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/supreme-court-cases-decisions-brett-kavanaugh_us_5bbba129e4b028e1fe402b92" target="_blank"&gt;5 Interesting Supreme Court Cases Kavanaugh Could Decide This Term&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a whirlwind of testimonies, investigations and protests leading up to Justice Brett Kavanaugh’s confirmation to the Supreme Court on Saturday, the embattled justice now begins his lifetime position ruling on the country’s most contentious cases. While President Donald Trump’s pick for the highest court in the land has been scrutinized over how he’ll vote on issues relating to reproductive rights, climate change and other hot-button issues, the cases Kavanaugh is scheduled or likely to hear this term will give Americans their first insight into how far he’ll swing the court to the righ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>A new Supreme Court case aims to close the huge loophole in US “double jeopardy” law - Quartz</title><link>https://qz.com/1409615/scotus-case-gamble-vs-us-challenges-the-state-sovereign-exception-to-double-jeopardy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP94x0TB8MdAWdjs-PVhJvEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowi4-MATDXsRUwhP2ZAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 14:23:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://qz.com/1409615/scotus-case-gamble-vs-us-challenges-the-state-sovereign-exception-to-double-jeopardy/" target="_blank"&gt;A new Supreme Court case aims to close the huge loophole in US “double jeopardy” law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Quartz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Supreme Court is back in session after its summer recess. On the docket this term is Gamble v. US, a case that challenges the “separate sovereign” exception to the Fifth Amendment’s double jeopardy clause, an exception which allows multiple prosecutions stemming from a single offense. The matter may have important ramifications for criminal defendants, including Donald Trump’s former campaign chairman Paul Manafort, who is being investigated by federal special prosecutor Robert Mueller and New York authorities (pdf). The Fifth Amendment to the US Constitution prohibits double jeopard...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://qz.com">Quartz</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court begins new term in shadow of Kavanaugh fight - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/01/politics/supreme-court-term-first-day-kavanaugh/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJlnvHfCfYf0Y48g3Jbn_vkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 11:10:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/01/politics/supreme-court-term-first-day-kavanaugh/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court begins new term in shadow of Kavanaugh fight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A short-handed Supreme Court will take the bench again on Monday to gavel in a term that has been totally eclipsed by the raging battle over the confirmation of Brett Kavanaugh. Back in July when President Donald Trump announced that he would nominate Kavanaugh to take the seat of retiring Justice Anthony Kennedy, a move that would cement a conservative majority for decades to come, Republicans hoped that Kavanaugh would be seated for the start of the new term. That all changed when Christine Blasey Ford came forward with allegations of sexual assault, which Kavanaugh vehemently denies. Now...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Lawyers try one more spin of the bottle for justice over Bowraville murders - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/24/lawyers-try-one-more-spin-of-the-bottle-for-justice-over-bowraville-murders</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPj7UPZwtitn_YABK4szNewqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 03:43:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/24/lawyers-try-one-more-spin-of-the-bottle-for-justice-over-bowraville-murders" target="_blank"&gt;Lawyers try one more spin of the bottle for justice over Bowraville murders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The harrowing journey for the Bowraville multiple murder case is not over yet. Following his unsuccessful trip to the New South Wales court of criminal appeal, the NSW attorney general Mark Speakman has flagged an intention to take his application for a retrial to the high court. Good for him. The court of criminal appeal delivered an unhappy judgment earlier this month. The application to retry a suspect, given the identity of “XX”, was rejected by a well-credentialed court, which indulged in a tight statutory construction to arrive at the answer, NO RETRIAL. By now Indigenous Australians ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>A Supreme Court Case Could Liberate Trump to Pardon His Associates - The Atlantic</title><link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/09/trump-pardon-orrin-hatch-supreme-court/571285/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2FA8_4Dsifizg6HB5HunkqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowm_EEMKAiMPtZ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 18:08:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/09/trump-pardon-orrin-hatch-supreme-court/571285/" target="_blank"&gt;A Supreme Court Case Could Liberate Trump to Pardon His Associates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Atlantic&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key Republican senator has quietly weighed in on an upcoming Supreme Court case that could have important consequences for Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s Russia investigation. The Utah lawmaker Orrin Hatch, who sits on the Senate Judiciary Committee, filed a 44-page amicus brief earlier this month in Gamble v. United States, a case that will consider whether the dual-sovereignty doctrine should be put to rest. The 150-year-old exception to the Fifth Amendment’s double-jeopardy clause allows state and federal courts to prosecute the same person for the same criminal offense. According to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theatlantic.com">The Atlantic</source></item><item><title>Analysis: Double jeopardy and the Bowraville decision: Where to now? - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-14/bowraville-double-jeopardy-colleen-walker-clinton-speedy-duroux/10243750</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPsfKxKCPwm8RtAm3IdndWgqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 19:18:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-14/bowraville-double-jeopardy-colleen-walker-clinton-speedy-duroux/10243750" target="_blank"&gt;Analysis: Double jeopardy and the Bowraville decision: Where to now?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NSW Court of Criminal Appeal has refused an application by the NSW Attorney-General to retry the person police suspect of killing three Aboriginal children in Bowraville between 1990 and 1991. The first of the children, Colleen Walker, disappeared 28 years ago this week. A month later, in October 1990, 4-year-old Evelyn Greenup disappeared following a house party. The following January, 16-year-old Clinton Speedy-Duroux went missing. Initially, police treated the children's disappearances as missing persons cases. In January 1991, Clinton's body was found. Much has been written in recen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Ruling against Bowraville retrial sparks protest from 'heartbroken' families - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-13/bowraville-murders-retrial-ruled-out-by-nsw-court/10240954</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIzRexTTDyy4lUi2CEDwNT0qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 23:44:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-13/bowraville-murders-retrial-ruled-out-by-nsw-court/10240954" target="_blank"&gt;Ruling against Bowraville retrial sparks protest from 'heartbroken' families&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Riley Stuart and Mazoe Ford Relatives have broken down outside court in an emotional protest after it was ruled a man should not be retried for the murders of two children in Bowraville in the early 1990s, or tried over the murder of a third. Today's decision is a landmark development in one of Australia's most confusing and long-running legal sagas, which has loomed large over the outback town for 30 years. The bodies of Evelyn Greenup, four, and Clinton Speedy-Deroux, 16, were found in bushland near Bowraville — on the NSW mid-north coast — in the early 1990s. The man, who cannot be na...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Judge rules against 3rd trial for US agent in fatal shooting - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/466cac6bd2444b9ca2c214e45a8b9cf0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIa3tl2NRdHlvWcyrUoMm6EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 02:44:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/466cac6bd2444b9ca2c214e45a8b9cf0" target="_blank"&gt;Judge rules against 3rd trial for US agent in fatal shooting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — A U.S. State Department agent who shot and killed a man in a Hawaii fast-food restaurant cannot be tried a third time, a U.S. judge ruled Friday. Hawaii prosecutors may not proceed with a retrial against Special Agent Christopher Deedy, U.S. District Judge Derrick Watson in Honolulu ruled. Prosecutors vowed to appeal. Deedy was in Honolulu providing security for the 2011 Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation summit. After bar-hopping with friends on his first night in Waikiki, Deedy fatally shot Kollin Elderts during an altercation in a McDonald's. A 2013 murder trial ended in a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Death sentence appeal rejected in triple murder case - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/7eec3004bdf94374a6547ae126896e20</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELyfhBgvR-yn-akDrWnHAhUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 18:20:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/7eec3004bdf94374a6547ae126896e20" target="_blank"&gt;Death sentence appeal rejected in triple murder case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HARTFORD, Conn. (AP) — A Connecticut man who gunned down two adults and a 9-year-old girl on a city street has lost his attempt to have his former death sentence erased from the record in an effort to improve his life in prison. The state Supreme Court on Monday rejected an appeal by Richard Roszkowski, who did not challenge the validity of his murder convictions but wanted the death sentence he received in 2014 declared null and void. Some issues in the appeal were moot because the same court declared capital punishment in the state unconstitutional in 2015. Nearly all the state's 11 forme...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court agrees to hear 'double jeopardy' case in the fall - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/28/politics/supreme-court-double-jeopardy-clause/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKVryQ7TwfgvBiN7yMT1cjYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 15:15:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/28/politics/supreme-court-double-jeopardy-clause/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court agrees to hear 'double jeopardy' case in the fall&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court on Thursday agreed to hear a case to consider whether the double jeopardy clause of the Fifth Amendment bars states and the federal government from separately trying the same person for the same criminal offense. The double jeopardy case stems from the prosecution of Terance Martez Gamble, who was pulled over by police in 2015 for a broken tail light. Marijuana paraphernalia and a firearm were found in the car during the stop. "Current precedent allows such prosecutions by 'separate sovereigns.' If the court overrules its prior precedent, it could make it more difficult fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ex-Goldman Sachs programer seeks to overturn code theft conviction - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-goldman-sachs-theft-programmer/ex-goldman-sachs-programer-seeks-to-overturn-code-theft-conviction-idUSKCN1J02YW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC9w1jLE9fTMS6J0Nfn7DfYqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 22:11:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-goldman-sachs-theft-programmer/ex-goldman-sachs-programer-seeks-to-overturn-code-theft-conviction-idUSKCN1J02YW" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-Goldman Sachs programer seeks to overturn code theft conviction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Brendan Pierson NEW YORK (Reuters) - Former Goldman Sachs Group Inc programer Sergey Aleynikov on Monday filed a new challenge to his criminal conviction of stealing computer code from the investment bank when he left for another job. Aleynikov, whose case partly inspired Michael Lewis' bestselling book "Flash Boys" on high-frequency trading in the U.S. equity market, previously got his conviction overturned by the judge who oversaw his 2015 trial in Manhattan Supreme Court. A New York appeals court reinstated the conviction, and the New York Court of Appeals, the state's highest court, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Judge denies Manafort motion to throw out charges of lying - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/d6b50bf5b6ff4527949e3971f4b870d5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEM6yDfX4CwFBohMffcSFJAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 21:45:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/d6b50bf5b6ff4527949e3971f4b870d5" target="_blank"&gt;Judge denies Manafort motion to throw out charges of lying&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal judge on Friday rejected former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort's attempt to have some of the criminal charges against him thrown out. It was the latest setback for Manafort, who has seen U.S. District Judge Amy Berman Jackson toss out his civil suit challenging the authority of special counsel Robert Mueller and dismiss a similar move in his criminal case. He faces charges of acting as an unregistered foreign agent and money-laundering conspiracy and also two false-statement charges related to information he shared with the Justice Department about his Ukr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Don’t Let Trump Off the Hook, New York - The New York Times</title><link>http://archive.li/64Upl</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDexoE-oKmaMY5XO0jCXEugqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 18:30:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://archive.li/64Upl" target="_blank"&gt;Don’t Let Trump Off the Hook, New York&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Legislature needs to approve a proposal to limit enhanced double jeopardy protections, so those pardoned by the president can face state changes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://archive.li">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>New York’s Double-Jeopardy Loophole - The Atlantic</title><link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/04/schneiderman-double-jeopardy/558389/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEObNJ7O8kji9f2YoOWe8MOQqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowm_EEMKAiMPtZ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/04/schneiderman-double-jeopardy/558389/" target="_blank"&gt;New York’s Double-Jeopardy Loophole&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Atlantic&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York state has long functioned as the ace up the sleeve of President Trump’s critics. The reasoning goes like this: Trump could attempt to pardon people implicated in the Russia probe, whether Michael Cohen, Paul Manafort, or someone else, thus preventing a trial or perhaps insulating himself from legal ramifications. The vast discretion affording the chief executive in the pardon power would allow the president to short-circuit accountability. However, the pardon power only applies to federal laws, so another jurisdiction could haul figures like Cohen and Manafort, or even potentially ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theatlantic.com">The Atlantic</source></item><item><title>New York Attorney General Seeks Power to Bypass Presidential Pardons - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/18/nyregion/schneiderman-trump-mueller-pardons.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFoAlUNhe1oJK3D-NYErkIcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloIY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 19:19:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/18/nyregion/schneiderman-trump-mueller-pardons.html" target="_blank"&gt;New York Attorney General Seeks Power to Bypass Presidential Pardons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eric Schneiderman wants to change state law so that he could prosecute presidential aides if they are pardoned. They would lose their “double jeopardy” protection.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>New York Attorney General Pushes To Sidestep Any Trump Pardons - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-york-attorney-general-trump-pardons_us_5ad80c11e4b029ebe020e310</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVOhwMyFFNRA6gl6MuRh5kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 04:28:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-york-attorney-general-trump-pardons_us_5ad80c11e4b029ebe020e310" target="_blank"&gt;New York Attorney General Pushes To Sidestep Any Trump Pardons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York’s attorney general has asked officials to change state law so President Donald Trump’s aides can be tried for any criminal acts committed in the state, even if they have been given a presidential pardon. In a letter sent to New York’s top lawmakers, including Democratic Gov. Andrew Cuomo, Attorney General Eric Schneiderman (D) said that he was troubled by Trump’s frequent discussion of his ability to issue pardons and that he was worried those who had committed crimes in the state would escape prosecution. New York has a double jeopardy law that prevents individuals from being char...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>New York attorney general wants power to bypass Trump pardons - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-new-york-pardons/new-york-attorney-general-wants-power-to-bypass-trump-pardons-idUSKBN1HP31C</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECVWUwhhVcVTMt7g2LIzcjcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 01:52:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-new-york-pardons/new-york-attorney-general-wants-power-to-bypass-trump-pardons-idUSKBN1HP31C" target="_blank"&gt;New York attorney general wants power to bypass Trump pardons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jonathan Stempel NEW YORK (Reuters) - New York's attorney general on Wednesday asked Governor Andrew Cuomo and state legislators to give him and other local prosecutors power to bring criminal charges against people pardoned by U.S. President Donald Trump. In a letter, Attorney General Eric Schneiderman urged Cuomo and legislative leaders to close a loophole in New York's double jeopardy law shielding recipients of presidential pardons from state prosecution. A change could make it more difficult for Trump aides and others who might be pardoned to escape criminal prosecution, even if spe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Could New York state prosecutors bring charges against Cohen even if Trump pardons him? - Vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/2018/4/18/17252554/trump-cohen-new-york-state-laws</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL9IesVqDxbNvWugJRPNyK0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowlOzSATCaiDUwtaKsBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 21:31:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/2018/4/18/17252554/trump-cohen-new-york-state-laws" target="_blank"&gt;Could New York state prosecutors bring charges against Cohen even if Trump pardons him?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Cohen, President Donald Trump's personal attorney, takes a phone call on April 13, 2018. Yana Paskova/Getty Images Correction: A previous version of this article included incorrect information. It has been updated. Correction: A previous version of this article incorrectly stated that New York Attorney General Eric Schneiderman could indict Trump attorney Michael Cohen for breaking state laws regardless of whether Cohen was convicted of breaking federal versions of those same laws — and regardless of whether Trump pardoned him. The article has been updated with the correct informati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.vox.com">Vox.com</source></item><item><title>Stephen Lawrence: timeline of key events - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/apr/19/stephen-lawrence-timeline-of-key-events</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAL2Iz81PaRz2L8ewL0jX2MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 16:41:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/apr/19/stephen-lawrence-timeline-of-key-events" target="_blank"&gt;Stephen Lawrence: timeline of key events&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;22 April 1993 Stephen Lawrence is stabbed to death in an unprovoked racist attack by a gang of white youths as he waits at a bus stop in Eltham, south-east London, with his friend Duwayne Brooks. Over the days that follow, police receive several tipoffs. Between them, all sources point to the same suspects: brothers Neil and Jamie Acourt, Gary Dobson, and David Norris. 25-27 April 1993 Police take a statement from the alleged victim of another stabbing by the same suspects, and confirmation of the Acourts’ address from their mother. The other two suspects have been seen outside the same add...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>New York attorney general attempts to circumvent Trump pardon power - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/apr/19/new-york-state-law-trump-pardons-eric-schneiderman</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKV0HFD0EEb5axjnl9pHMpYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 13:10:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/apr/19/new-york-state-law-trump-pardons-eric-schneiderman" target="_blank"&gt;New York attorney general attempts to circumvent Trump pardon power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York state law must be clarified to ensure anyone pardoned by President Donald Trump may still be charged with violations of state law, the state attorney general, Eric Schneiderman, said on Wednesday. Schneiderman, a Democrat who has emerged as a key figure in investigations related to Trump and his administration, urged state lawmakers to quickly eliminate a loophole in current state statute that he said could be used to fight state charges by anyone who has received a federal pardon for similar federal charges. “Simply put, a defendant pardoned by the president for a serious federal ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Lawmakers propose giving top NY prosecutor power to bypass Trump pardons - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-new-york-pardons/lawmakers-propose-giving-top-ny-prosecutor-power-to-bypass-trump-pardons-idUSKBN1HR2SK</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF3qrfDHoKmY1QS9W8TXoJ0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 18:21:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-new-york-pardons/lawmakers-propose-giving-top-ny-prosecutor-power-to-bypass-trump-pardons-idUSKBN1HR2SK" target="_blank"&gt;Lawmakers propose giving top NY prosecutor power to bypass Trump pardons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jonathan Stempel NEW YORK (Reuters) - New York state lawmakers on Friday introduced legislation to give the state's attorney general and other local prosecutors the power to bring criminal charges against people pardoned by U.S. President Donald Trump. The bill is intended to close what New York Attorney General Eric Schneiderman called a loophole in state law that could permit Trump to pardon people for state crimes, which he has no authority to do, as well as federal crimes. Passage could make it harder for Trump aides who might be pardoned to escape prosecution, even if special counse...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>NCA considering new criminal inquiry into Stephen Lawrence case - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/apr/15/nca-considering-new-criminal-inquiry-into-stephen-lawrence-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOONvpldrcnDienvDYA4VPsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 16:22:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/apr/15/nca-considering-new-criminal-inquiry-into-stephen-lawrence-case" target="_blank"&gt;NCA considering new criminal inquiry into Stephen Lawrence case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Crime Agency is considering starting a new criminal inquiry into the Stephen Lawrence case, potentially placing four former detectives under criminal investigation for the offence of misconduct in public office. It is understood that the inquiry would focus on why officers in charge of the first Metropolitan police investigation into Lawrence’s murder 25 years ago did not make arrests for two weeks, despite police repeatedly being given the names of suspects. Lawrence, 18, was stabbed to death by a racist gang of at least five white youths on 22 April 1993. It took 19 years for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Stephen Lawrence murder: police say they have run out of leads - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/apr/11/stephen-lawrence-murder-police-say-they-have-run-out-of-leads</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM07Uq7Mgr1sqp8PezQJLmAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 15:15:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/apr/11/stephen-lawrence-murder-police-say-they-have-run-out-of-leads" target="_blank"&gt;Stephen Lawrence murder: police say they have run out of leads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scotland Yard has said it has run out of leads in the Stephen Lawrence murder investigation, ahead of the 25th anniversary of the racist killing. It will wait until a three-part BBC documentary about the case is broadcast next week to see if anyone new comes forward. The Met police said it was reviewing the case, which means it is considering closing it down. At least three of the gang who shouted abuse before the black teenager was stabbed at a south-east London bus stop in 1993 are still free. The force’s leadership believe they have exhausted all leads and avenues of inquiry in one of th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Death row inmate sues after 'botched' execution - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/03/07/health/alabama-execution-lawsuit/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENQQRmRj96IqsSMZUjM3wAkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 23:29:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/03/07/health/alabama-execution-lawsuit/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Death row inmate sues after 'botched' execution&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Alabama death row inmate whose execution went wrong is asking that his death sentence be vacated. The attempted execution was "botched and bloody," as the inmate's lawyer put it, and left the inmate under "physical and mental duress." Doyle Lee Hamm was convicted in 1987 of committing murder during a robbery and sentenced to death. On February 22, the 61-year-old was being prepped for intravenous lethal executionat the Holman Correctional Facility when staff and medical personnel tried and failed for 2½ hours to find veinsin his groin, feet and legs. A federal judge ordered a medical exa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Family of murdered Muslim teenager say they feel discriminated against by police after they fail to convict anyone for eight years - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/abdul-karim-boudiaf-murdered-muslim-teenager-family-discriminated-police-david-lammy-a8106241.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFZexEqBWATfzhOLd1z3si8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 23:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/abdul-karim-boudiaf-murdered-muslim-teenager-family-discriminated-police-david-lammy-a8106241.html" target="_blank"&gt;Family of murdered Muslim teenager say they feel discriminated against by police after they fail to convict anyone for eight years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The grieving family of a murdered Muslim teenager have said they feel let down by police and prosecutors due to the failure to secure a conviction eight years after they lost their son. AbdulKarim Boudiaf, an aspiring lawyer from Tottenham, was 18 when he was fatally shot in the neck while walking with friends outside a pub in north London in 2009. A man stood trial for his death, but no one has ever been convicted. The family, with the backing of their local MP David Lammy, are now calling on police to reactivate the investigation. Read more - Officer who detained Rashan Charles before his...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Bowraville murders' prime suspect propositioned 16yo girl, court told - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-29/bowraville-landmark-appeal-hearing-begins-in-nsw/9204668</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEE5Eu45ZxskAqb6S6eTxAYqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 22:56:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-29/bowraville-landmark-appeal-hearing-begins-in-nsw/9204668" target="_blank"&gt;Bowraville murders' prime suspect propositioned 16yo girl, court told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A hearing into whether a man should be retried for the murders of two Aboriginal children in the early 1990s has heard he tried to pressure another girl, who later disappeared, into having sex with him. The man, who cannot be named for legal reasons, has long been seen by police as the prime suspect in the deaths of four-year-old Evelyn Greenup, Clinton Speedy-Duroux, 16, and Colleen Walker, 16, over a five-month period in 1990 and 1991. He was acquitted of the murder of Clinton at a trial in 1994 and the murder of Evelyn at a separate trial in 2006. The families of the three children, who ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item></channel></rss>