<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>WWE - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNR2Q1TVY4U0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-CA&amp;gl=CA&amp;ceid=CA:en</link><language>en-CA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:37:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>WWE Rumors: Brock Lesnar Too Busy To Appear On UFC - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-brock-lesnar-too-busy-appear-ufc-boss-says-2740373</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0MfwzDGjXNAU1nAClGKHcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCP97EF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-brock-lesnar-too-busy-appear-ufc-boss-says-2740373" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Rumors: Brock Lesnar Too Busy To Appear On UFC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reigning WWE Universal Champion Brock Lesnar is waiting in the wings although some are speculating of seeing him make a surprise appearance at WWE TLC at the SAP Center in San Jose, California on Dec. 16. With time to spare, some are also entertaining the possibility of seeing him on the UFC although President Dana White doesn't see it happening. During a recent press conference, White was thrown a question on possibly bringing back Lesnar to the UFC. The 49-year-old UFC boss said that his focus is not on Brock and that the 41-year-old is swamped with a bunch of WWE deals, Ringside News fir...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>WWE Could Be Calling Up Several NXT Stars, But That's Not Necessarily A Good Thing - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/07/wwe-could-be-calling-up-several-nxt-stars-but-thats-not-necessarily-a-good-thing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEjEqZf8Ft4znZ-QyktaL3IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/07/wwe-could-be-calling-up-several-nxt-stars-but-thats-not-necessarily-a-good-thing/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Could Be Calling Up Several NXT Stars, But That's Not Necessarily A Good Thing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE is on the verge of calling up multiple NXT superstars, but recent history should give the company pause about promoting its standout performers to the main roster. Credit: WWE.com Among the names who reportedly could be in line for a call-up to the main roster are EC3, Velveteen Dream and Aleister Black. According to Barnburner’s Joe Peisich (h/t Ringside News), EC3 could make his debut at the 2019 Royal Rumble while Velveteen Dream has long been rumored for a move to Raw or SmackDown. Likewise, Wrestling Observer Radio (h/t Cageside Seats) recently reported that “there has been a lot o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bray Wyatt May Appear At WWE TLC PPV - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-bray-wyatt-may-pinch-hit-injured-braun-strowman-2740157</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMQgpRY8tOPfnX4fHbYt_uEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCP97EF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:42:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-bray-wyatt-may-pinch-hit-injured-braun-strowman-2740157" target="_blank"&gt;Bray Wyatt May Appear At WWE TLC PPV&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE TLC is almost here, and one of the matches to look forward to is the battle of the behemoths involving Braun Strowman and Baron Corbin. There are big stakes on the line and possibly some twists happening along the way. According to CBS Sports, Strowman got the match he had wanted from Raw Commissioner Stephanie McMahon to face Corbin. There are two stipulations for the match, which will take place on Dec. 16 at the SAP Center in San Jose, California. If Strowman wins, he gets to face Brock Lesnar for the Universal title at the Royal Rumble, and Corbin will lose his powers as interim gen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>WWE Rumors: Becky Lynch Yet To Get Clearance, Strowman Doubtful For TLC - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-becky-lynch-injury-scare-braun-strowman-update-ahead-tlc-2740093</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMb002kMauKJnn4abkWh3iwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:30:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-becky-lynch-injury-scare-braun-strowman-update-ahead-tlc-2740093" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Rumors: Becky Lynch Yet To Get Clearance, Strowman Doubtful For TLC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE's final pay-per-view of 2018 – Tables, Ladders and Chairs (TLC) – is just around the corner and talks still continues to surround the availability of the company’s biggest stars of the moment – Becky Lynch and Braun Strowman. The Irish woman, who is the SmackDown women’s champion, was set to headline the previous pay-per-view Survivor Series, but a freak incident which saw her break her nose and suffer a concussion saw her skip the event with Charlotte Flair taking her place instead. Lynch is probably the most popular star in the sports entertainment franchise at the moment with the WWE...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>5 Major WWE Stars Who Badly Need To Switch Shows - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/06/5-major-wwe-stars-who-badly-need-to-switch-shows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGkrOcYZd-genbZZWeYK-zUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/06/5-major-wwe-stars-who-badly-need-to-switch-shows/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Major WWE Stars Who Badly Need To Switch Shows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE has recently made a number of significant roster moves, including babyface turns for Braun Strowman and Elias as well as moves to the dark side for Dean Ambrose and Daniel Bryan. Credit: WWE.com At least partly due to the unfortunate departure of Roman Reigns, WWE was forced to make those adjustments to its Raw roster, but even before that, numerous changes were made at the top of the card. While names like Bobby Lashley and the Bella Twins have also turned heel over the last couple of months, there is still a sense among fans that Raw’s recent historically low viewership (and the fact ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Tom Billington, former Stampede Wrestling superstar, dies - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-stampede-wrestling-dynamite-kid-death-1.4933561</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFxm6Kj36EqMj-7hHhv8FuwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 04:42:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-stampede-wrestling-dynamite-kid-death-1.4933561" target="_blank"&gt;Tom Billington, former Stampede Wrestling superstar, dies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former pro wrestler Tom Billington — known to fans as the Dynamite Kid, and a fixture of Canada's Stampede Wrestling — died Wednesday in England, on his 60th birthday. He was best known as one-half of the British Bullldogs tag team, along with his real-life cousin Davey Boy Smith, and their mascot, a bulldog named Matilda. Smith's son Harry, who now wrestles under the name Davey Boy Smith Jr., called Billington an inspiration. "I was really happy and glad I got to see Dynamite one last time last June in the U.K.," he tweeted. "Dynamite was certainly an inspiration to myself and many others....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>WWE's Vince McMahon, Commissioner Oliver Luck Officially Announce 8 XFL Cities - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/12/05/wwes-vince-mcmahon-commissioner-oliver-luck-officially-announce-8-xfl-cities/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEr_vpHmOoL_pbf4obzM9NIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/12/05/wwes-vince-mcmahon-commissioner-oliver-luck-officially-announce-8-xfl-cities/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE's Vince McMahon, Commissioner Oliver Luck Officially Announce 8 XFL Cities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The XFL has officially announced the eight cities that will host teams for its inaugural season/reboot in 2020. Dallas, St. Louis, Houston, Los Angeles, New York, Seattle, Tampa Bay and Washington D.C. will all become XFL cities for the $100 million league financed by Vince McMahon’s Alpha Entertainment, LLC. The XFL has announced the eight cities for its relaunch in 2020. During a press conference at MetLife Stadium that touched upon the league’s emphasis on technology and innovation, brevity, fan engagement and player safety, XFL Commissioner Oliver Luck—introduced by WWE Chairman Vince M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The XFL Goes PG - The Wall Street Journal</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-xfl-goes-pg-1544110503</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECcRpOvDrZRB8LgWFwu20RgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1tzJATDnyxUw54IY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-xfl-goes-pg-1544110503" target="_blank"&gt;The XFL Goes PG&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Wall Street Journal&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;East Rutherford, N.J. There he was, Vince McMahon, talking once more about big plans for Vince McMahon football. At least he said he was Vince McMahon. I am still not 100% convinced. He was no more than 30 feet away from me, in a cozy club area of MetLife Stadium in New Jersey, and he sure looked like Vince McMahon—barrel chest; slicked-back hair, now with a distinguished stripe of gray; the type of suntan it can take a St. Barts winter to achieve. Yes: he still looked like he could flip me over a top rope if he wanted to. He looked like he could flip pretty much anyone over a top rope if h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.wsj.com">The Wall Street Journal</source></item><item><title>Former WWE star Cody Rhodes full of praise for the rise of British wrestling - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/general/wwe-mma-wrestling/cody-rhodes-wwe-interview-british-fight-forever-wrestling-events-a8668301.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF_oF4T9BLeuRQPz0Zj09NoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/general/wwe-mma-wrestling/cody-rhodes-wwe-interview-british-fight-forever-wrestling-events-a8668301.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former WWE star Cody Rhodes full of praise for the rise of British wrestling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of American wrestling’s biggest names believes that the UK scene is giving the United States a run for its money. Cody Rhodes is a former WWE Intercontinental champion and now one of the industry’s brightest independent stars. He’s now in the UK and is ready to be part of a string of events under the banner of an all-new British wrestling promotion, Fight Forever. While the 33-year-old is one of the headline names on the card alone, much of the focus will be on UK stars including Flip Gordon, Jimmy Havoc and Viper to name just a few. WWE Survivor Series in pictures - 25 show all WWE Sur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>WWE Star Dynamite Kid Dies On 60th Birthday - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/dynamite-kid-cause-death-what-happened-1245216</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXeZTS7AUmWr29DDe_53roqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:08:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/dynamite-kid-cause-death-what-happened-1245216" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Star Dynamite Kid Dies On 60th Birthday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dynamite Kid, a legendary name in the WWE franchise, died Wednesday, which was his 60th birthday WWE confirmed. The wrestler, whose real name was Tommy Billington, had been suffering complications from wrestling since 1986. The exact cause of his death is unknown. The initial announcement of Billington’s death came from his nephew, Davey Boy Smith Jr. on Twitter. “It deeply saddens me to announce the passing of Tom Billington the 'Dynamite Kid.' I was really happy and glad I got to see Dynamite one last time last June in the UK,” he wrote. “Dynamite was certainly an inspiration to myself an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>WWE SmackDown Has A New Top Heel In Daniel Bryan, So It's Time For The Miz To Turn Babyface - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/05/wwe-smackdown-has-a-new-top-heel-in-daniel-bryan-so-its-time-for-the-miz-to-turn-babyface/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPHOHlreCL-HPB-zmF2YqPMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/05/wwe-smackdown-has-a-new-top-heel-in-daniel-bryan-so-its-time-for-the-miz-to-turn-babyface/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE SmackDown Has A New Top Heel In Daniel Bryan, So It's Time For The Miz To Turn Babyface&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once loaded with a star-studded slate of babyfaces, WWE SmackDown now finds itself in need of another fan favorite. Credit: WWE.com Daniel Bryan just turned heel and has completely shed himself of anything that resembles the lovable underdog he once was. Even though WWE has done a poor job with its follow-up to Shane McMahon’s surprising win at Crown Jewel and to Raw’s clean sweep of SmackDown at Survivor Series, McMahon is also apparently in the early stages of a heel turn that will be part of a long-term angle in route to WrestleMania 35. Meanwhile, the face of the brand AJ Styles is repo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Xavier Woods Career Remains In Full Throttle - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-xavier-woods-reveals-future-plans-upupdowndown-game-studio-more-2739434</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFP5qcNQ8rwqXmgnCvBT7Y0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCP97EF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 04:35:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-xavier-woods-reveals-future-plans-upupdowndown-game-studio-more-2739434" target="_blank"&gt;Xavier Woods Career Remains In Full Throttle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xavier Woods, also known in real life as Austin Creed, is no stranger to the WWE fame, although he has expanded his success online. The 32-year-old added another feather to his cap last April when his YouTube channel, UpUpDownDown, was awarded the Guinness World Record for the “Most Subscribed To Celebrity Video Game Channel.” With so much going for him, the WWE star admitted that he still has more planned ahead. In an exclusive interview with Manila Bulletin Sports Online, Woods wants a lot of things, goals of which he hopes to accomplish in time. “Oh, I want lots of things! I want everyth...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>MTV and Ice Cube are bringing back ‘Celebrity Deathmatch’ - NME Live</title><link>https://www.nme.com/news/tv/celebrity-deathmatch-returning-mtv-ice-cube-2417275</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGFScFD9WrbkDnsQQMUyM00qFggEKg4IACoGCAow_598MLC1CTChqAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:39:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nme.com/news/tv/celebrity-deathmatch-returning-mtv-ice-cube-2417275" target="_blank"&gt;MTV and Ice Cube are bringing back ‘Celebrity Deathmatch’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;NME Live&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The surreal stop-motion show originally ran from 1998-2002, before a short revival in 2006-07 'Celebrity Deathmatch' Celebrity Deathmatch is being rebooted by MTV and Ice Cube. The stop-motion series – which sent up numerous celebrities by depicting them as ultra-violent wrestlers – originally ran from 1998 to 2002 for 75 episodes (excluding the two pilots). A brief revival of the show began in 2006, but it came to an end less than a year later after just 16 episodes. MTV Studios are now reviving Celebrity Deathmatch, with Ice Cube set to star in and executively produce this latest version ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nme.com">NME Live</source></item><item><title>WWE Monday Night Raw: 5 People Who Could Save The Show From Its Current Tailspin - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/12/04/wwe-monday-night-raw-5-people-who-could-save-the-show-from-its-current-tailspin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELoRh5Hs5u0zISsj03zR4HIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/12/04/wwe-monday-night-raw-5-people-who-could-save-the-show-from-its-current-tailspin/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Monday Night Raw: 5 People Who Could Save The Show From Its Current Tailspin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After dreadful TV ratings from the November 27 show, and a less than critically acclaimed followup on December 3, Monday Night Raw is in a downward spiral. (Photo by JP Yim/Getty Images) Amidst a variety of injuries, the show desperately needs a fresh new face or a repackaged old one to revive its audience, and to put it plainly, to make the program more entertaining. Drew McIntyre has the goods, but it’s hard to saddle one person with the responsibility of saving a three-hour program. McIntyre and other top stars like Seth Rollins need worthy opponents and allies. The following stars might...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>British Wrestling Legend 'Dynamite Kid', Dies Aged 60 - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/dynamite-kid-british-wrestling-legend-dies-aged-60-tributes-pour-2739189</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELuonPQmr6tAs6SYsSYH10wqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCP97EF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:27:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/dynamite-kid-british-wrestling-legend-dies-aged-60-tributes-pour-2739189" target="_blank"&gt;British Wrestling Legend 'Dynamite Kid', Dies Aged 60&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wrestling legend Thomas Billington popularly known as the ‘Dynamite Kid’ died at the age of 60 Wednesday. Coincidentally, the former World Wrestling Federation (WWF), now known as the World Wrestling Entertainment (WWE), star’s death occurred on the same day he was celebrating his 60th birthday. The cause of death remained unclear at this moment but the Dynamite Kid had been battling a number of health issues in recent years and had been wheelchair-bound since the end of his career. The Lancashire-born wrestler started his career in the United Kingdonm before moving to Japan and then to the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>XFL Teams and Venues Announced - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/what-xfl-teams-tickets-venues-season-1245824</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDS7lwplcJhKKLPiBnfMSwYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMIiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:20:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/what-xfl-teams-tickets-venues-season-1245824" target="_blank"&gt;XFL Teams and Venues Announced&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next step in the re-formation of the XFL is complete as the eight teams that will make up the rebooted new football league, and their home cities and venues, were announced today. While the new XFL won’t launch its inaugural season until February 2020, founder Vince McMahon along with Commissioner and CEO Oliver Luck - and representatives of the eight host cities - presented the plans to fans. “After months of research and consideration, we’re thrilled to announce the cities and venues of the XFL’s eight inaugural teams,” Luck said in a press release. “We are committed to being ingraine...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>Monday Night RAW (12/3) Results - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/wwe-monday-night-raw-live-results-december-3-2018-1241744</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOtPCtob5k5tb0ZejR4l7ycqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:10:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/wwe-monday-night-raw-live-results-december-3-2018-1241744" target="_blank"&gt;Monday Night RAW (12/3) Results&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nov. 26 episode of WWE’s Monday Night RAW was one of the worst this year, but the company continues to build stories heading into its Tables, Ladders and Chair pay-per-view on Dec. 16. Baron Corbin is running Monday Night RAW with an iron fist, and he’s drawn a line in the sand. If you’re not going to back him as the General Manager of RAW, then you’re against him. And that means you’ll have to deal with him, Bobby Lashley and Drew McIntyre. With Braun Strowman on the shelf after elbow surgery, is there anyone on the RAW roster who can stop him? The feud between Dean Ambrose and Interco...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>WWE Raw Fans Are Calling The Show 'The Worst Ever' And Are Tuning Out In Droves - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/04/wwe-raw-fans-are-calling-the-show-the-worst-ever-and-are-tuning-out-in-droves/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHbMeY_Ef9l4DFFVl0mcN0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 12:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/04/wwe-raw-fans-are-calling-the-show-the-worst-ever-and-are-tuning-out-in-droves/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Raw Fans Are Calling The Show 'The Worst Ever' And Are Tuning Out In Droves&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE has arguably the best roster in company history. Too bad the same can’t be said about the product of its flagship show, Monday Night Raw. Credit: WWE.com The red brand is one week removed from an episode that has been universally panned by critics. In a poll conducted by NoDQ.com, just 5% of respondents said they enjoyed last week’s episode, and if we’re being honest with ourselves here, that number is surprisingly high. The site compiled a plethora of tweets demonstrating fan displeasure with what has been labeled as an all-time awful episode, which is really saying something given how...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Rumors: TLC Triple-Threat Surprise Planned - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-tlc-triple-threat-surprise-planned-aj-styles-contract-update-2738676</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEApbEVnm4FUoEcA1njoPfZgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:38:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-tlc-triple-threat-surprise-planned-aj-styles-contract-update-2738676" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Rumors: TLC Triple-Threat Surprise Planned&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Becky Lynch aka "The Man" is arguably one of the biggest draws in the World Wrestling Entertainment (WWE) at the moment and rumors are rife that the company has big plans for the Irish woman in the coming months. Lynch is currently the reigning SmackDown women’s champion and will be defending her title against Charlotte Flair and Asuka in the upcoming Tables Ladders and Chairs (TLC) pay-per-view, WWE’s final showpiece event of 2018. The Irish woman, who has welcomed the comparison to compatriot and Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC) star Conor McGregor, was scheduled to face former UFC wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>How to Watch XFL Team Reveal Livestream - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/xfl-teams-cities-livestream-press-conference-1244302</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBbyXYZV1z2nbg-0GC0eym8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:00:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/xfl-teams-cities-livestream-press-conference-1244302" target="_blank"&gt;How to Watch XFL Team Reveal Livestream&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t heard, the XFL is making a comeback. WWE’s Vince McMahon, who is also the league’s founder and chairman, will announce in a live press event the cities and venues that will represent the football league’s first season. Eight cities and venues will be revealed as the XFL prepares for the 2020 season. The press conference also promises to have more details on the state of the league. So who will the eight cities joining the XFL be? It seems that the official XFL website prematurely posted a listing of cities - which has since been deleted - that will join the league. Those citi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>WWE Raw Results: News And Notes After Drew McIntyre Suffers First Singles Loss To Dolph Ziggler - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/12/03/wwe-raw-results-news-and-notes-after-drew-mcintyre-suffers-first-singles-loss-to-dolph-ziggler/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOPq1sLRik_OasJY0ELakBAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 04:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/12/03/wwe-raw-results-news-and-notes-after-drew-mcintyre-suffers-first-singles-loss-to-dolph-ziggler/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Raw Results: News And Notes After Drew McIntyre Suffers First Singles Loss To Dolph Ziggler&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Raw was an improvement upon last week’s largely miserable broadcast as Dolph Ziggler turned babyface, splitting from Drew McIntyre, before going on to shockingly defeat the Scottish Psychopath with help from Finn Balor. Drew McIntyre suffered his first singles loss since returning to WWE at the hands of Dolph Ziggler. Ronda Rousey’s planned tag team match alongside Natalya was changed after the two were attacked by the Riott Squad in the opening segment, leading to Rousey and Ember Moon prevailing over Nia Jax and Tamina. WWE Raw saw a 5% dip last week as competition from the NFL and fa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Add Natalya To The Growing List Of Possible Heel Turns In WWE - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/12/03/add-natalya-to-the-growing-list-of-possible-heel-turns-in-wwe/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVMoHvuwCnegmDmzBA81WkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/12/03/add-natalya-to-the-growing-list-of-possible-heel-turns-in-wwe/" target="_blank"&gt;Add Natalya To The Growing List Of Possible Heel Turns In WWE&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Natalya has been advertised to tag with Ronda Rousey on Raw, thereby setting off panic alarms within WWE’s fanbase that yet another heel turn could be on the horizon. Ronda Rousey and Natalya will team up Monday on Raw. WWE has fallen in love with the heel turn in 2018, as a product dominated by heels has suffered both creatively and in terms of viewership. Becky Lynch, Daniel Bryan, Charlotte (I think) and Dean Ambrose are just a few names who recently turned heel to widely varying results, and despite having a palpable void at babyface—with Roman Reigns currently out of action and Braun S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Austin's Surprise Prediction About WWE Star Becoming 'Top Guy' - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/stone-cold-makes-surprise-prediction-about-wwe-star-becoming-top-guy-2738197</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELQz4LGIyvCtF1Q4oCYTn-4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 11:50:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/stone-cold-makes-surprise-prediction-about-wwe-star-becoming-top-guy-2738197" target="_blank"&gt;Austin's Surprise Prediction About WWE Star Becoming 'Top Guy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;World Wrestling Entertainment (WWE) Hall of Famer Stone Cold Steve Austin has named two wrestling stars he would love to work with if he ever returned to WWE, which is very unlikely to happen in the near future. Austin, who was popularly known as the ‘Rattle Snake’ during his days as a professional wrestler, last appeared in the ring at WrestleMania 19 – WWE’s flagship pay-per-view event. He is unlikely to come out of retirement after having been forced to quit due to multiple knee injuries and a severe neck injury. The 53-year-old is currently on a Legends contract with the WWE and is one ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>WWE, Becky Lynch And The End Of The Traditional Pro Wrestling Babyface - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/03/wwe-becky-lynch-and-the-end-of-the-traditional-pro-wrestling-babyface/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELmhr-bxnlzqnGH3KJUIZ-UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/03/wwe-becky-lynch-and-the-end-of-the-traditional-pro-wrestling-babyface/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE, Becky Lynch And The End Of The Traditional Pro Wrestling Babyface&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traditional babyfaces are becoming extinct in WWE. Credit: WWE.com One could argue that it started around 2006, when John Cena became WWE’s biggest draw since the Attitude Era and its unquestioned merchandise king, despite obvious resistance to “The Champ” from many of the company’s most passionate supporters. Over the last decade-plus, other stars have followed similar career paths as faux babyfaces who are pushed like the heroes of an epic novel but despised like the loathed villain of an action flick, a reality that has most notably affected the career trajectory of WWE’s new top merchan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Former WWE Champion Making MMA Debut In January - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/former-wwe-champion-jack-swagger-set-debut-bellator-214-2738562</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2rwxWMJ-gRD6eGvyimuO0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCP97EF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:56:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/former-wwe-champion-jack-swagger-set-debut-bellator-214-2738562" target="_blank"&gt;Former WWE Champion Making MMA Debut In January&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jack Swagger, whose real name is Jake Hager, finally has a date for his much-awaited debut in mixed martial arts. The former WWE champion signed with Bellator MMA last year and was expected to compete in the heavyweight division. But having been over a year since the announcement in November, there was no real news on when Swagger would compete with his debut later being pushed back. That was until Monday when Swagger confirmed on "Ariel Helwani's MMA Show" that he would compete on the undercard of Bellator 214 which takes place Jan. 26 in Inglewood, California. His opponent will be J.W. Ki...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>5 Huge Heel Turns WWE Must Pull Off ASAP - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/02/5-huge-heel-turns-wwe-must-pull-off-asap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAUSscZDRIqY68MiQ-iLDd8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 18:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/02/5-huge-heel-turns-wwe-must-pull-off-asap/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Huge Heel Turns WWE Must Pull Off ASAP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE has flipped its roster upside down and inside out over the past few months. Credit: WWE.com Due at least in part to the ongoing absence of Roman Reigns, WWE’s creative team has enacted a series of major babyface and heel turns to reshape its roster as Reigns battles leukemia. Notable heel turns include ones for Bobby Lashley, Daniel Bryan, the Bella Twins and Dean Ambrose, while top stars like Elias and Braun Strowman have done the opposite and solidified themselves as full-fledged fan favorites. The series of changes to WWE’s heel/babyface alignment was a necessary move both to reset t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Superstar Nia Jax Gets Real About Body Positivity In Wrestling - Refinery29</title><link>https://www.refinery29.com/en-us/wwe-nia-jax-wrestler-evolution-body-self-love-interview-video</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDJafj3MDsD4j1Jz35iMScqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqOXeCjDQ5dYBML3V0QM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.refinery29.com/en-us/wwe-nia-jax-wrestler-evolution-body-self-love-interview-video" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Superstar Nia Jax Gets Real About Body Positivity In Wrestling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Refinery29&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some, body positivity may not typically start with a body slam. But for WWE Superstar Nia Jax, born Savelina Fanene, loving herself began with the wrestling. Coming from a long line of Samoan wrestlers, including her cousin Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson, Jax grew up watching a much different world of wrestling on television. "I noticed they were always beautiful women but skinnier and smaller than me," Jax said. "I just never really saw somebody like me in the business, and I didn't think that somebody like me would fit in to that business." Jax's aunt ultimately encouraged her by telling h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.refinery29.com">Refinery29</source></item><item><title>John Cena to receive SI's Muhammad Ali Legacy Award - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/36b63610972f475db66957dca8db0fa4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKjbHN9XrdasWxLhyyGwbFAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwnZidAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:00:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/36b63610972f475db66957dca8db0fa4" target="_blank"&gt;John Cena to receive SI's Muhammad Ali Legacy Award&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE superstar John Cena is the recipient of this year's Sports Illustrated Muhammad Ali Legacy Award. The award, which was announced Thursday, is given each year to an athlete or sports figure who embodies the ideals of sportsmanship, leadership and philanthropy while using sports as a platform. Cena will receive the award at the Sportsperson of the Year Awards show on Dec. 11 in Los Angeles. "To have a legacy award of any kind bestowed upon you is tremendous," Cena said during an interview with The Associated Press. "To be in the company of people who have received this and to receive an h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>This Week In WWE Biz: John Cena Plans, Ronda Rousey To SmackDown?, CM Punk Return, More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/01/this-week-in-wwe-biz-john-cena-plans-ronda-rousey-to-smackdown-cm-punk-return-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA5P3bCOUcy6Z-0-Ul54USwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/12/01/this-week-in-wwe-biz-john-cena-plans-ronda-rousey-to-smackdown-cm-punk-return-more/" target="_blank"&gt;This Week In WWE Biz: John Cena Plans, Ronda Rousey To SmackDown?, CM Punk Return, More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Star John Cena Likely To Be On Raw For WrestleMania Season “The Champ” is headed to the red brand. According to Wrestling Inc, John Cena will exclusively be working Raw events beginning next year: John Cena will return to action at RAW and SmackDown live events starting on December 26th. It appears as if Cena will be working for the RAW brand heading into WrestleMania, as he is only booked for RAW live events and Monday Night RAW television tapings starting in January. Cageside Seats adds that Cena is ”expected back for the run up to Royal Rumble.” WHAT’S IT MEAN FOR WWE? After recently...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>European Star WALTER Signs with WWE: Report - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/european-star-walter-signs-wwe-report-1232316</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM8TY9gW4wGLQgpy7yD8v3YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:56:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/european-star-walter-signs-wwe-report-1232316" target="_blank"&gt;European Star WALTER Signs with WWE: Report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE has reportedly signed one of the top independent professional wrestlers in Europe after months of rumored interest. Walter Hahn, better known by his ring name "WALTER," has reportedly signed with the company, sources told PWInsider.com on Monday. WWE reportedly had interest in signing the Austrian wrestler several months ago, as originally reported by Dave Meltzer of the Wrestling Observer Newsletter. Hahn denied the reports at the time, but reportedly began negotations with the company at a later date, according to PWInsider. "Nobody overred anything, not true!" he tweeted in response ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>5 Huge Babyface Turns WWE Could Soon Pull Off - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/30/5-huge-babyface-turns-wwe-could-soon-pull-off/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA1TKViVkIjmzSR0MQeZBvcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/30/5-huge-babyface-turns-wwe-could-soon-pull-off/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Huge Babyface Turns WWE Could Soon Pull Off&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE has no issues pulling off a memorable heel turn here and there, but doing the same with babyfaces is a little trickier. Credit: WWE.com The company inadvertently hit the jackpot when it tried wholeheartedly to push Becky Lynch as a heel only for her to become arguably its most popular star, and it once again made the right call when both Braun Strowman and Elias were solidified as babyfaces just a couple of months ago. Throughout history, these organic and successful face turns have proven to be the exception rather than the rule, however, and it hasn’t always been that easy for a once ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fox Want Ronda Rousey On SmackDown - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-ronda-rousey-leave-raw-fox-want-rowdy-smackdown-2737113</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAd6bjv3hPD3PLskk_kHGBwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:30:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-ronda-rousey-leave-raw-fox-want-rowdy-smackdown-2737113" target="_blank"&gt;Fox Want Ronda Rousey On SmackDown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOX Sports is already gearing up for SmackDown Live next year as they reportedly want Ronda Rousey to switch WWE brands. Rousey is the current Raw women's champion and has quickly become one of the brand's leading stars ever since making her WWE debut earlier this year. And according to Justin LaBar of Wrestling Inc, FOX wants her to be a part of the SmackDown roster when they take over broadcast rights for the show from the USA Network in October next year. It was previously reported that FOX network officials wanted the SmackDown product to have less comedy and take more of a sports direc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>John Cena Wins Muhammad Ali Legacy Award - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/john-cena-joins-colin-kaepernick-recipient-muhammad-ali-legacy-award-2737541</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHALN7FivufdOdOmcWMJRcAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCP97EF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 05:03:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/john-cena-joins-colin-kaepernick-recipient-muhammad-ali-legacy-award-2737541" target="_blank"&gt;John Cena Wins Muhammad Ali Legacy Award&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sports Illustrated announced Thursday that World Wrestling Entertainment (WWE) superstar John Cena will receive the prestigious Muhammad Ali Legacy Award to be presented at the Sports Illustrated Sportsperson of the Year show on Dec. 11 at the Beverley Hills Hilton in Los Angeles. The 16-time WWE champion is receiving the award for his philanthropy work outside the ring. He has made the Make-A-Wish Foundation the center of his charity work and has granted over 600 wishes to terminally ill children – more than any other person connected with the foundation. He is also a major advocate for br...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>FOX Wants Ronda Rousey On WWE SmackDown, Which Complicates An Already Muddled Women's Division - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/29/fox-wants-ronda-rousey-on-wwe-smackdown-which-complicates-an-already-muddled-womens-division/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKpHGXJqRieAq-eRToBNNzsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/29/fox-wants-ronda-rousey-on-wwe-smackdown-which-complicates-an-already-muddled-womens-division/" target="_blank"&gt;FOX Wants Ronda Rousey On WWE SmackDown, Which Complicates An Already Muddled Women's Division&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ronda Rousey could be moving to WWE SmackDown. Well, at least if FOX gets its wish. Credit: WWE.com According to a report from Wrestling Inc, FOX officials want the former UFC star on the blue brand when the show heads to its new home in October 2019: Wrestling Inc. has learned that FOX wants to have Ronda Rousey on the SmackDown roster when SmackDown Live! moves to the network. FOX feels that Rousey’s MMA background, popularity and credibility as an athlete will be a major selling point to promote the show. As part of a pair of blockbuster TV deals that could earn WWE more than $540 millio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Smackdown Vs Raw: Which Show Needs Lars Sullivan More? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/28/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-which-show-needs-lars-sullivan-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJT1J0VZhKel7K3bIe1sM5YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/28/wwe-smackdown-vs-raw-which-show-needs-lars-sullivan-more/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Smackdown Vs Raw: Which Show Needs Lars Sullivan More?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lars Sullivan is getting “the next big thing” treatment on WWE programming the past two weeks. Lars Sullivan The NXT standout is a physical specimen who could generate some attention with the big shows if his arrival is handled correctly. Clearly, that’s a big if. As of now, the WWE is teasing Lars’ show affiliation with a variety of promos asking “where will Lars Sullivan land?” There is a case to be made for him going to Smackdown and Raw, but when you look at both rosters, it appears the blue brand is a better landing spot for him. Raw’s roster has been ravaged by injury to Braun Strowma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Real Reason Styles Was Removed From Mixed-Match Challenge - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/real-reason-aj-styles-removed-mixed-match-challenge-spoilers-tlc-report-2736627</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOWyaS3QnRe6irRVoxjj-IwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 12:00:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/real-reason-aj-styles-removed-mixed-match-challenge-spoilers-tlc-report-2736627" target="_blank"&gt;Real Reason Styles Was Removed From Mixed-Match Challenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;World Wrestling Entertainment (WWE) star AJ Styles has been a bit-part player since he surrendered his WWE title to Daniel Bryan in the SmackDown episode prior to Survivor Series earlier this month. Styles was hit a with a low blow by Bryan away from the referee’s view which brought the former’s 371 days as the champion to an end. He was then not seen during the Survivor Series pay-per-view event and during the following SmackDown Live airing at the Staples Center. It was being suggested that Styles’ presence in the upcoming shows will be limited as he is yet to agree on a new deal with his...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>WWE Raw Viewership Data Suggests Baron Corbin Has 'Go-Away' Heat - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/29/wwe-raw-viewership-data-suggests-baron-corbin-has-go-away-heat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEEQqFvtScHd7IPIaedzgb8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/29/wwe-raw-viewership-data-suggests-baron-corbin-has-go-away-heat/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Raw Viewership Data Suggests Baron Corbin Has 'Go-Away' Heat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Raw saw its audience drop on a show dominated by Baron Corbin, which has become something of a trend since the former Money in the Bank winner became a Constable-turned-General-Manager-Elect on the red brand. Baron Corbin defeated Finn Balor in a 2-on-1 main event match. Monday’s Raw averaged 2.369 million viewers, a 5% drop from the previous week. More specifically, the WWE flagship saw a whopping 19.2% drop from first to third-hour viewership. The average viewership of 2.111 million viewers marked the second-lowest third-hour figure in Raw history. It’s not entirely fair to blame Raw’...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Monday Night RAW Results (11/26) - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/wwe-monday-night-raw-live-results-november-26-1231919</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFJHx5MxXixShXgIx0L2aXkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 01:17:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/wwe-monday-night-raw-live-results-november-26-1231919" target="_blank"&gt;Monday Night RAW Results (11/26)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title defenses are expected to go down on the latest episode of WWE’s Monday Night RAW. According to WWE.com, Intercontinental Champion Seth Rollins is set to issue an open challenge for his title tonight. With multiple Superstars staking claim to answering that challenge on social media, who will step up to take on The Architect? The other title defense comes in the RAW Tag Team division as the champs, Authors of Pain, take on Bobby Roode and Chad Gable. Roode and Gable got the best of AOP last week, but can they capture the Tag Titles or will the champs snuff them out? On the non-title fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>WWE SmackDown Is Using Becky Lynch To Make Charlotte Flair More Popular, And It Will Backfire - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/28/wwe-smackdown-is-using-becky-lynch-to-make-charlotte-flair-more-popular-and-it-will-backfire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN81XxdW6U-YZCSQV2mFOskqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 12:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/28/wwe-smackdown-is-using-becky-lynch-to-make-charlotte-flair-more-popular-and-it-will-backfire/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE SmackDown Is Using Becky Lynch To Make Charlotte Flair More Popular, And It Will Backfire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE inadvertently struck gold when Becky Lynch, through her own doing, became the most popular superstar in the entire company. Credit: WWE.com The SmackDown Women’s Champion, as she herself will tell you, wasn’t the handpicked golden girl of the women’s division, and it’s highly doubtful that WWE’s higher-ups could have ever envisioned that she would revolutionize women’s wrestling the way she seems to do so on a daily basis. But Lynch’s unparalleled charisma, her strong Twitter game and her unforgettable takeover of Raw a few weeks ago has transformed “The Irish Lass Kicker” from a cult f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Rumored All Elite Wrestling Promotion Linked To Billionaire Khan Has Uphill Battle As WWE Competitor - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/26/rumored-all-elite-wrestling-promotion-linked-to-billionaire-khan-has-uphill-battle-as-wwe-competitor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI-gEQg73QHyEvfKUxl7jMcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/26/rumored-all-elite-wrestling-promotion-linked-to-billionaire-khan-has-uphill-battle-as-wwe-competitor/" target="_blank"&gt;Rumored All Elite Wrestling Promotion Linked To Billionaire Khan Has Uphill Battle As WWE Competitor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A non-WWE news story garnered all the attention this Thanksgiving-day weekend after trademarks were filed for a rumored pro wrestling vehicle dubbed All Elite Wrestling. The Elite could be launching a wrestling promotion. The rumored promotion has been linked to popular independent wrestlers Cody Rhodes, Kenny Omega, the Young Bucks (known collectively as The Elite) and Tony Khan—longtime wrestling fan, member of the billionaire Khan family and co-owner of the Jacksonville Jaguars. Trademarks filed include All Elite Wrestling, AEW, AEW Double or Nothing, Double or Nothing, AEW All Out, All ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE 'Character Change' Expected In 2019 - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-shane-mcmahon-undergo-character-change-2019-2735633</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDRUEi2BwvUE2-75CPSOT0IqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 11:30:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-shane-mcmahon-undergo-character-change-2019-2735633" target="_blank"&gt;WWE 'Character Change' Expected In 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Smackdown Live commissioner Shane McMahon could be undergoing a "character change" next year. According to Dave Meltzer of the Wrestling Observer Newsletter, as per Wrestling Inc, it will take place in the first quarter of 2019, meaning it would likely occur heading into Wrestlemania season. "There's no word yet on exactly what they have planned but this will tie in with Shane's World Cup tournament win at Crown Jewel and Team SmackDown losing all of their matches on the main card of the Survivor Series pay-per-view," Wrestling Inc wrote. "Shane's character change will likely be a set-u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>Seth Rollins' Aimless Feud With Dean Ambrose Will Hurt Him As A Possible Challenger For Brock Lesnar - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/28/seth-rollins-aimless-feud-with-dean-ambrose-will-hurt-him-as-a-possible-challenger-for-brock-lesnar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELgNlXxP2lv6bFAwSorwYKwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/28/seth-rollins-aimless-feud-with-dean-ambrose-will-hurt-him-as-a-possible-challenger-for-brock-lesnar/" target="_blank"&gt;Seth Rollins' Aimless Feud With Dean Ambrose Will Hurt Him As A Possible Challenger For Brock Lesnar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Roman Reigns and Braun Strowman currently sidelined due to illness and injury, respectively, Seth Rollins has emerged as a possible candidate to challenge Brock Lesnar for the WWE Universal Championship come WrestleMania 35. Seth Rollins is the de facto favorite to challenge Brock Lesnar for the WWE Universal Championship. Tickets for WrestleMania 35 in MetLife Stadium have been moving quickly as WWE looks to best its $12.3 million live gate from WrestleMania 29 in that same building, which marked WWE’s highest-grossing event in history at the time. And while it’s mostly speculation su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Raw Suddenly Has A Massive Shortage Of Top Babyfaces - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/27/wwe-raw-suddenly-has-a-massive-shortage-of-top-babyfaces/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP5XNZ4-7IjvS0wkzHHJuOYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 12:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/27/wwe-raw-suddenly-has-a-massive-shortage-of-top-babyfaces/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Raw Suddenly Has A Massive Shortage Of Top Babyfaces&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t look now, but WWE suddenly finds itself with a shortage of top babyfaces on its flagship show, Monday Night Raw. Credit: WWE.com In 2018, WWE has primarily pushed three stars as the biggest fan favorites on the red brand: Roman Reigns, Braun Strowman and Ronda Rousey. For a wide variety of reasons, however, that suddenly isn’t possible. Reigns is sidelined indefinitely as he battles leukemia. Strowman is reportedly working with a pair of “blown out” knees, just underwent surgery to have bone spurs removed from his elbow and may miss next month’s pay-per-view TLC, where he’s scheduled ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>2 WWE Main Roster Stars Accept Deals To Join New Promotion - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/2-wwe-main-roster-superstars-moving-new-promotion-report-says-2735237</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzIi2Dx73yCUvSSz-MV-o4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:20:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/2-wwe-main-roster-superstars-moving-new-promotion-report-says-2735237" target="_blank"&gt;2 WWE Main Roster Stars Accept Deals To Join New Promotion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two WWE main roster superstars have reportedly agreed to join a new wrestling promotion when their contracts expire. Earlier this month, it was revealed All Elite Wrestling, LLC had filed trademarks for a new wrestling promotion headed by Tony Khan, co-owner of the Jacksonville Jaguars. "According to the trademark filings, All Elite Wrestling, LLC is based out of Jacksonville, FL," the report read. "That would also align with the rumors about the Khan family being involved. ... All Elite Wrestling, LLC is registered to an address at 1 TIAA Bank Field Drive in Jacksonville. That address just...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>WWE Raw Results: News And Notes After General Manager-Elect Baron Corbin Defeats Finn Balor - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/26/wwe-raw-results-news-and-notes-after-general-manager-elect-baron-corbin-defeats-finn-balor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHyvATLnTkd1E2aWua4kbvMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 04:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/26/wwe-raw-results-news-and-notes-after-general-manager-elect-baron-corbin-defeats-finn-balor/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Raw Results: News And Notes After General Manager-Elect Baron Corbin Defeats Finn Balor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Raw was dominated by Baron Corbin as the heel acting General Manager dubbed himself General Manager-elect. Book-ending the show, WWE made the risky choice of promoting a Raw featuring a Baron Corbin main event. Baron Corbin dubbed himself the General Manager Elect on Raw. Corbin appeared in the main event against Roman Reigns for the WWE Universal Championship on the September 17 broadcast of Raw, but the show still saw a 14.3% drop from the first to the third hour, although it did face competition from the NFL and the Emmys. Though Raw faced stiff competition from last week’s historic ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>John Cena Is Finally Returning To WWE, But His Long-Term Future Remains Uncertain - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/26/john-cena-is-finally-returning-to-wwe-but-his-long-term-future-remains-uncertain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEi-dYLVXm63_pKp8PCJ80AqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/26/john-cena-is-finally-returning-to-wwe-but-his-long-term-future-remains-uncertain/" target="_blank"&gt;John Cena Is Finally Returning To WWE, But His Long-Term Future Remains Uncertain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE has, for more than a decade, relied on John Cena as the face of the company, but his time as Vince McMahon’s No. 1 star appears to be nearing its end. Credit: WWE.com WWE.com confirmed this week that Cena will be returning to the company for a slew of live event appearances beginning next month, including his TV return to the Raw brand on Jan. 7: - Madison Square Garden, New York – Dec. 26 - Nassau Coliseum, New York – Dec. 27 - Royals Farms Arena, Baltimore — Dec. 28 - PPG Paints Arena, Pittsburgh – Dec. 29 - Amalie Arena, Tampa, Fla. – Dec. 30 - Columbus Civic Center, Columbus, Ga. – ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WATCH: Reigns Makes Public Appearance Since Leukemia - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/watch-roman-reigns-makes-first-appearance-leukemia-announcement-returns-1229849</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL6Q_uaoje_n-KPoKW0nIbsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 23:00:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/watch-roman-reigns-makes-first-appearance-leukemia-announcement-returns-1229849" target="_blank"&gt;WATCH: Reigns Makes Public Appearance Since Leukemia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE superstar and former Georgia Tech football player Roman Reigns made his first public appearance since announcing his leukemia diagnosis during the Yellow Jackets’ game against Georgia. "I'm the real Big Dog here, to hell with Georgia baby," Reigns said prior to the game's kickoff, referring to his WWE character's "Big Dog" nickname. Reigns, whose real name is Joe Anoa'i, played defensive tackle for the Yellow Jackets from 2003-06 and was a first-team All-ACC selection as a senior, recording nine tackles for loss and 4.5 sacks, before playing in the CFL and eventually embarking on a care...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>Ronda Rousey Vs. Becky Lynch And The 5 Best Options To Main Event WWE WrestleMania 35 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/25/ronda-rousey-vs-becky-lynch-and-the-5-best-options-to-main-event-wwe-wrestlemania-35/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDUeRzC7a0ItRg3LnTT5c08qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 17:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/25/ronda-rousey-vs-becky-lynch-and-the-5-best-options-to-main-event-wwe-wrestlemania-35/" target="_blank"&gt;Ronda Rousey Vs. Becky Lynch And The 5 Best Options To Main Event WWE WrestleMania 35&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE fans can usually see the WrestleMania main event coming from a mile away, but this year has been the exception to that rule. Credit: WWE/YouTube Roman Reigns’ shocking leukemia announcement reportedly threw all initial WrestleMania 35 plans “out the window,” including a potential blockbuster match between Reigns and The Rock, while a slew of other circumstances also forced WWE to make even more significant changes to the rumored card for its biggest pay-per-view of 2019. Becky Lynch’s untimely injury in route to Survivor Series made WWE revert to Plan B, a dream match between Ronda Rous...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WATCH: Enzo Amore Ejected From Survivor Series - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/watch-enzo-amore-ejected-survivor-series-staples-center-1221309</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBTnsrCzGFSrfRdQdyOZYV4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 04:46:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/watch-enzo-amore-ejected-survivor-series-staples-center-1221309" target="_blank"&gt;WATCH: Enzo Amore Ejected From Survivor Series&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former WWE superstar Enzo Amore used to proudly boast that "you can't teach that" after listing several attributes during his ring entrance. However, there's likely one lesson that learned on Sunday: don't attempt to hijack your former employer's pay-per-view event. Amore, whose real name is Eric Arndt, was escored out of Staples Center after attempting to hijack the crowd at WWE's Survivor Series event. The 29-year-old reportedly entered the arena in a disguise before revealing himself to the fans in attendance. Amore reportedly attempted to diver attention from the show by cutting a promo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>John Cena And Nikki Bella Are Not Back Together - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/john-cena-tweets-about-negativity-after-nikki-bella-shares-old-instagram-photo-2736180</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPtA6GEUQUuYaFhmI89p7sMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:32:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/john-cena-tweets-about-negativity-after-nikki-bella-shares-old-instagram-photo-2736180" target="_blank"&gt;John Cena And Nikki Bella Are Not Back Together&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nikki Bella caused fans to fly into a frenzy when she shared a photo of herself and ex-fiancé John Cena on Thanksgiving, fueling rumors the couple could be getting back together. Days after the sentimental photo was posted, the 41-year-old took to Twitter to share a cryptic message about negativity. Bella and Cena first announced their break up in April, weeks ahead of their spring wedding date. Although they briefly reconciled and moved forward with their wedding plans, they split for good over the summer. However, fans begin to believe the exes were reconciling when Bella posted a picture...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>WWE RAW Live Results (11/19) - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/wwe-monday-night-raw-live-results-1222680</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIm2K8DmjBLzYZqTDqKyNFIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 01:59:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/wwe-monday-night-raw-live-results-1222680" target="_blank"&gt;WWE RAW Live Results (11/19)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Survivor Series was a one-sided affair, as Monday Night RAW dominated SmackDown Live, taking six of the seven brand vs brand matches on Sunday. Now that the RAW roster and acting general manager Baron Corbin came out on top, how will the Red Brand move forward towards the Tables, Ladders and Chairs pay-per-view and Royal Rumble? According to WWE.com, Braun Strowman—who eliminated four of the five SmackDown competitors in the Survivor Series match—will get his wishes from RAW commissioner Stephanie McMahon. First, he’ll get his match against Corbin, who cost him the Universal Championship at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>WWE Survivor Series 2018 Review: Raw Obliterated SmackDown Live 6-0, But So What, This PPV Was Great - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/19/wwe-survivor-series-2018-review-raw-obliterated-smackdown-live-6-0-but-so-what-this-ppv-was-great/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPu1ySZH278bUvgtoim8DJwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/19/wwe-survivor-series-2018-review-raw-obliterated-smackdown-live-6-0-but-so-what-this-ppv-was-great/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 Review: Raw Obliterated SmackDown Live 6-0, But So What, This PPV Was Great&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the men’s Team Raw vs. Team SmackDown Survivor Series elimination match, Raw’s Drew McIntyre blasted SmackDown’s Samoa Joe with a Claymore Kick seconds into the match to score a decisive pinfall and an early elimination. Charlotte Flair turned heel in entertaining fashion during WWE Survivor Series 2018. Fans in the Los Angeles Staples Center reacted in-kind with chants of “bull—t!” It was a microcosm of the major talking point, and ensuing outrage, coming out of Survivor Series as the established Raw flagship utterly dominated the more hipster-friendly and wrestling-centric SmackDow...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Survivor Series 2018: Charlotte Flair Upsetting Ronda Rousey And 5 Potentially Huge Surprises - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-charlotte-flair-upsetting-ronda-rousey-and-5-potentially-huge-surprises/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOA1MfP6FElt6LxHWAc3oSUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-charlotte-flair-upsetting-ronda-rousey-and-5-potentially-huge-surprises/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018: Charlotte Flair Upsetting Ronda Rousey And 5 Potentially Huge Surprises&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 underwent a slew of creative changes this week and will now be headlined by Ronda Rousey vs. Charlotte Flair, Brock Lesnar vs. a now-heel WWE Champion Daniel Bryan, Shinsuke Nakamura vs. Seth Rollins and a trio of traditional 5-on-5 elimination matches. Credit: WWE.com The event will be WWE’s third in as many weeks, which has resulted in a jam-packed slate of programming for Raw and SmackDown that has left both shows in a state of flux recently, especially after Bryan’s shocking heel turn and Becky Lynch’s injury that forced WWE to scrap her dream match with Rousey....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE's Excess Of Heel Turns In 2018 Reduce The Promotion To A One-Trick Pony - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/21/wwes-excess-of-heel-turns-in-2018-reduce-the-promotion-to-a-one-trick-pony/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJO3-GW7_FROTmQ9RxC4U34qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 13:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/21/wwes-excess-of-heel-turns-in-2018-reduce-the-promotion-to-a-one-trick-pony/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE's Excess Of Heel Turns In 2018 Reduce The Promotion To A One-Trick Pony&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tuesday night’s SmackDown Live kicked off with Charlotte explaining her actions from Survivor Series on Sunday, after she turned heel in the climactic moments of a great match against Ronda Rousey. Explanation or not, Charlotte was cheered, just as Becky Lynch was during her explanation for turning heel on Charlotte at SummerSlam. Charlotte turned heel Sunday night at Survivor Series but was given a hero’s welcome Tuesday night on SmackDown Live. Later on in the night, it was Daniel Bryan’s turn to answer for his heel actions, as he gave an excellent monologue that served as a darker, more ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: Brock Lesnar Beating Daniel Bryan Proves WWE Ignores Its Audience - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-brock-lesnar-beating-daniel-bryan-proves-wwe-ignores-its-audience/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPKvZz9aW4iEWe-WM7JWLx4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 03:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-brock-lesnar-beating-daniel-bryan-proves-wwe-ignores-its-audience/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: Brock Lesnar Beating Daniel Bryan Proves WWE Ignores Its Audience&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 featured the exact same outcome as last year’s Universal Champion vs. WWE Champion match: Raw’s Brock Lesnar defeating SmackDown’s WWE Champion, this time Daniel Bryan. Credit: WWE/Twitter For some reason or another, Vince McMahon apparently didn’t want to do a match pitting AJ Styles against Roman Reigns at Survivor Series, but with Reigns’ unfortunate leukemia diagnosis throwing a major wrench into WWE’s creative plans, he still chose to do a champion vs. champion match that had fans worried about the bout’s outcome as soon as it was announced. Originally, it look...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: Nia Jax Gets Booed Out Of Los Angeles, Becomes Sole Survivor - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-nia-jax-gets-booed-out-of-los-angeles-becomes-sole-survivor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP4RUlF53M5veK2DR9r2N7oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-nia-jax-gets-booed-out-of-los-angeles-becomes-sole-survivor/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: Nia Jax Gets Booed Out Of Los Angeles, Becomes Sole Survivor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Becky Lynch is the biggest babyface in WWE, then Nia Jax has become the biggest heel in the company by proxy after her well-publicized errant punch on Lynch which forced her to pull out of Survivor Series. Nia Jax became the sole survivor at WWE Survivor Series 2018. Just as Lynch’s rise came as a result of real-life sympathy from WWE’s fanbase despite the company doing everything it can to promote her as a heel, resentment toward Nia Jax has exploded as a result of a real-life injury to a fan favorite as Jax’s track record in the category of in-ring safety continues to be marred by acci...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>John Cena Return Dates Revealed - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-john-cena-return-dates-revealed-2734499</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIOF-aPbJe-kKyeCGswS8koqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 11:30:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-john-cena-return-dates-revealed-2734499" target="_blank"&gt;John Cena Return Dates Revealed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sixteen-time WWE champion John Cena is set to return to the company next month during the festive period. Cena hasn't wrestled since he teamed up with Bobby Lashley to defeat Elias and Kevin Owens at last month's WWE Super Show-Down event in Melbourne, Australia. However, PWInsider has confirmed he will appear in the following events in December: - Raw live event on Dec. 26 in Madison Square Garden, New York. - Smackdown live event on Dec. 27 at Nassau Coliseum in Long Island, New York. - Smackdown live event on Dec. 28 in Baltimore, Maryland. - Smackdown live event on Dec. 29 in Tampa, Flo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: 5 Reasons Sunday's PPV Was The Best Of The Year - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/19/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-5-reasons-sundays-ppv-was-the-best-of-the-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJsA5TRmmM1jLqAVBksvoC0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 05:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/19/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-5-reasons-sundays-ppv-was-the-best-of-the-year/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: 5 Reasons Sunday's PPV Was The Best Of The Year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Putting together a professional wrestling pay-per-view is an art. There are a ton of moving parts and if I’m being completely honest, promotions miss more than they hit in this area. On Sunday night, the WWE hit the bullseye with Survivor Series. Bryan-Lesnar The final of the promotion’s Big 4 pay-per-view shows had a number of positive elements, the following five are the reason it was the WWE’s best pay-per-view of the year. First, take a look at all of the results from the Staples Center in Los Angeles. - Universal Champion Brock Lesnar def. WWE Champion Daniel Bryan - Raw Women’s Champi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Survivor Series results: Ronda Rousey attacked by Charlotte Flair as Brock Lesnar beats Daniel Bryan - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/general/wwe-mma-wrestling/wwe-survivor-series-results-ronda-rousey-charlotte-flair-attack-brock-lesnar-daniel-bryan-who-won-a8640496.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPjjVkVf4aS4__IFgOdMswsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/general/wwe-mma-wrestling/wwe-survivor-series-results-ronda-rousey-charlotte-flair-attack-brock-lesnar-daniel-bryan-who-won-a8640496.html" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Survivor Series results: Ronda Rousey attacked by Charlotte Flair as Brock Lesnar beats Daniel Bryan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monday Night Raw proved dominant over Smackdown Live at WWE Survivor Series, but Ronda Rousey’s brutal attack at the hands of Charlotte Flair proved to be the biggest talking point from a frantic night in Los Angeles. WWE’s red brand won all the key clashes on the night that saw stars from the company’s two flagship shows go head to head, most notably Universal Champion Brock Lesnar’s incredible win over WWE Champion Daniel Bryan. But Charlotte’s decision to sacrifice her chances of victory in order to attack the former UFC champion with anything she could get her hands on – having only ent...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Real Reason Why AJ Styles Lost To Daniel Bryan - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-real-reason-why-aj-styles-lost-daniel-bryan-2734175</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHZxUFha96I555Ri2IM-G2QqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 11:00:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-rumors-real-reason-why-aj-styles-lost-daniel-bryan-2734175" target="_blank"&gt;Real Reason Why AJ Styles Lost To Daniel Bryan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many were surprised when AJ Styles lost his WWE championship to Daniel Bryan last week on Smackdown, ending a 371-day reign in the process. Bryan turned heel for the first time since 2012 as he struck Styles with a low blow before performing his running knee finisher to become a four-time WWE champion. As a result, Styles would also miss out on a rematch with Brock Lesnar at Sunday's Survivor Series event with Bryan instead taking his place, and many believe the injury to Smackdown women's champion Becky Lynch was a major factor behind the change of plans, as her brand supremacy match with ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>Survivor Series 2018 Card - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/wwe-survivor-series-2018-card-matches-1218165</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELhoqMLSA_xFnHnDzppCtAQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 20:47:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/wwe-survivor-series-2018-card-matches-1218165" target="_blank"&gt;Survivor Series 2018 Card&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final “Big 4” pay-per-view of the WWE’s year is upon us as Survivor Series descends on Los Angeles for a night of brand vs brand action. Survivor Series 2018, like last year, will pit RAW and SmackDown against each other as both brands’ superstars fight for supremacy. Champions will take on champions, and by the end of the night one brand will come out on top.There’s also a title match in the Cruiserweight division, so there are stakes outside of the whole brand supremacy concept. Considering the week WWE had with Becky Lynch’s injury and Daniel Bryan’s heel turn, this Sunday’s event is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>AJ Styles And 5 Snubbed Superstars At WWE Survivor Series 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/18/aj-styles-and-5-snubbed-superstars-at-wwe-survivor-series-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECA0CGXlIsvJYlmwdLlgWToqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/18/aj-styles-and-5-snubbed-superstars-at-wwe-survivor-series-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;AJ Styles And 5 Snubbed Superstars At WWE Survivor Series 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Survivor Series boasts an uncharacteristically svelt lineup of eight matchups, all of which will pit the Raw brand against SmackDown Live. Despite the extended length of pay-per-views in this climate, several high-profile WWE Superstars will find themselves without a dance partner at one of WWE’s biggest pay-per-views of the year. AJ Styles is not advertised to compete at WWE Survivor Series 2018. This year’s list of WWE Superstars not currently advertised to compete in the November classic include rising stars, former world champions, future hall of famers and, in some cases, possibly ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: Braun Strowman Is Sole Survivor Amidst Reports Of Backstage Heat - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-braun-strowman-is-sole-survivor-amidst-reports-of-backstage-heat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENAmSJp4hIG5NES91eS1a2oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 02:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-braun-strowman-is-sole-survivor-amidst-reports-of-backstage-heat/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: Braun Strowman Is Sole Survivor Amidst Reports Of Backstage Heat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 certainly seemed to put the kibosh on reports that Braun Strowman could have some good old fashioned backstage heat. Credit: WWE/Twitter Strowman was one of three sole survivors and had a whopping four eliminations for Team Raw in the traditional 5-on-5 Survivor Series elimination match, marking the latest in a series of bizarre booking decisions for one of WWE’s biggest stars. After Strowman’s short-lived and ultimately pointless heel run that lasted less than three months, combined with his failure to successfully cash in his Money in the Bank briefcase, Strowman ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Becky Lynch Welcomes Conor McGregor Comparison - International Business Times</title><link>https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-survivor-series-becky-lynch-welcomes-conor-mcgregor-comparison-after-rousey-spat-2733359</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB2GuHrFrJDtNsAOJQS4PicqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow9891MIGZDDCJgrIF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 12:50:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/wwe-survivor-series-becky-lynch-welcomes-conor-mcgregor-comparison-after-rousey-spat-2733359" target="_blank"&gt;Becky Lynch Welcomes Conor McGregor Comparison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Business Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE SmackDown women’s champion Becky Lynch has no problem being compared to Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC) bad boy Conor McGregor. The professional wrestler feels it is because they are both the faces of their respective franchises and that they hail from Ireland. Lynch, who refers to herself as “The Man,” after beating Charlotte Flair to the women’s title in September is probably the most spoken about WWE star at the moment. The Irish professional wrestler has displayed a new level of aggression inside and outside the ring in recent months — and she took it to a new level on Monday w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ibtimes.com">International Business Times</source></item><item><title>LOOK: Enzo Amore Photo at Security Doors for RAW - Newsweek</title><link>https://www.newsweek.com/look-enzo-amores-photo-staples-center-security-doors-prohibit-wwe-raw-1223145</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA9bP4K1e-HUV6T0tMhtAxIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMJiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 03:52:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/look-enzo-amores-photo-staples-center-security-doors-prohibit-wwe-raw-1223145" target="_blank"&gt;LOOK: Enzo Amore Photo at Security Doors for RAW&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE made sure former wrestler Enzo Amore didn't attempt to hijack another one of its live events for the second consecutive night. Amore, whose real name is Eric Arndt, had his photo posted at security doors to prohibit his entrance to Monday Night RAW at the Staples Center. On Sunday, the former Cruiserweight champion was escored out of the same arena after attempting to hijack the crowd at WWE's Survivor Series event. The 29-year-old reportedly entered the arena in a disguise before revealing himself to the fans in attendance. Amore reportedly attempted to diver attention from the show by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: Drew McIntyre Emerging As Sole Survivor Will Ignite Huge Push - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-drew-mcintyre-emerging-as-sole-survivor-will-ignite-huge-push/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMmxvtz9gLPkhtZ9BzTwe1gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 02:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-drew-mcintyre-emerging-as-sole-survivor-will-ignite-huge-push/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: Drew McIntyre Emerging As Sole Survivor Will Ignite Huge Push&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 made it perfectly clear that the push is on for Drew McIntyre. Credit: WWE.com McIntyre emerged from the traditional 5-on-5 Survivor Series elimination match as the sole survivor for Team Raw alongside Bobby Lashley and Braun Strowman, the latest piece of evidence that WWE is going all in on “The Scottish Terminator,” who quickly eliminated Samoa Joe from the match on Sunday Less than two weeks ago on Raw, McIntyre picked up perhaps the biggest main roster win of his career when he defeated Kurt Angle in lopsided fashion in a bout that surprisingly portrayed Angle a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: Shane McMahon's Memorable Performance Highlights Huge Issue - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-shane-mcmahons-memorable-performance-highlights-huge-issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN5u5Y3s9FVO5EDc-LkZawcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 02:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/18/wwe-survivor-series-2018-results-shane-mcmahons-memorable-performance-highlights-huge-issue/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 Results: Shane McMahon's Memorable Performance Highlights Huge Issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018 turned out to be, much like Crown Jewel, the Shane McMahon show as the SmackDown Commissioner was the last man standing for Team SmackDown, which lost to Team Raw in the men’s elimination match. Credit: WWE/Twitter Already a controversial event, Crown Jewel stirred up even more trouble when Shane-O-Mac, who wasn’t even an official entrant in the first-ever World Cup, somehow managed to win the eight-man tournament anyway. The move was widely criticized because it shortchanged The Miz out of a potential career-defining victory, because it made a 48-year-old non-wrest...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>This Week In WWE Biz: Ronda Rousey Plans, The Rock Vs. Brock Lesnar?, Daniel Bryan Heel Turn, More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/17/this-week-in-wwe-biz-ronda-rousey-plans-the-rock-vs-brock-lesnar-daniel-bryan-heel-turn-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP4EVdvinDdmgLhH4-n3CJ0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/blakeoestriecher/2018/11/17/this-week-in-wwe-biz-ronda-rousey-plans-the-rock-vs-brock-lesnar-daniel-bryan-heel-turn-more/" target="_blank"&gt;This Week In WWE Biz: Ronda Rousey Plans, The Rock Vs. Brock Lesnar?, Daniel Bryan Heel Turn, More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WWE Reportedly Not Doing Brock Lesnar Vs. Braun Strowman At WrestleMania 35, Update On Plans For Strowman On this week’s Raw, Stephanie McMahon struck a deal with Braun Strowman to give him another crack at Brock Lesnar and the Universal Championship, but that bout likely won’t take place at WrestleMania 35. According to Dave Meltzer Wrestling Observer Radio (h/t WrestlingNews.co), “The Monster Among Men” vs. “The Beast” is not slated to take place at WWE’s flagship pay-per-view: This is subject to change but I was told directly that Braun Strowman and Brock Lesnar is not gonna happen at Wr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ronda Rousey Is Facing Her First Real Challenge In The WWE, Rejection - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/23/ronda-rousey-is-facing-her-first-real-challenge-in-the-wwe-rejection/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFHjWCVkrtlq6eBw7xNQP94qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/23/ronda-rousey-is-facing-her-first-real-challenge-in-the-wwe-rejection/" target="_blank"&gt;Ronda Rousey Is Facing Her First Real Challenge In The WWE, Rejection&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Ronda Rousey was still new, she saw the best side of the WWE Universe. Now she’s finding out what life is like on the other side. Ronda Rousey Rousey deserves credit for taking on the WWE challenge as a full-time performer. She probably could have arranged some sort of part-time deal that positioned her to be the female Brock Lesnar. However, she didn’t want that kind of role. That initially worked for her and it only augmented her appeal as a former UFC champion. Rousey’s athleticism and rapid growth as an in-ring performer helped to put her over even more. The pop she’d get in arenas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WWE Survivor Series 2018: Daniel Bryan's Heel Turn Comes With Good And Bad News - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/16/wwe-survivor-series-2018-daniel-bryans-heel-turn-comes-with-good-and-bad-news/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAKANmN86NQZlC6mN9sIclQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alfredkonuwa/2018/11/16/wwe-survivor-series-2018-daniel-bryans-heel-turn-comes-with-good-and-bad-news/" target="_blank"&gt;WWE Survivor Series 2018: Daniel Bryan's Heel Turn Comes With Good And Bad News&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is Daniel Bryan won the WWE Championship. The bad news is he turned heel, and figures to take a hit in merchandise sales while losing his uniquely genuine connection with the WWE Universe. Daniel Bryan turned heel Tuesday night on SmackDown Live. The good news is Bryan is a veteran of this craft and his newly minted heel turn should lead to creative windfall for his character. Natural baby aces like Sami Zayn and Becky Lynch have thrived in this exact same position. Even more good news, due to WWE’s ineptitude in booking babyfaces, heels in WWE these days are far more popular ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>