<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Death of Sammy Yatim - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNSGRyWDNoZlpCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-CA&amp;gl=CA&amp;ceid=CA:en</link><language>en-CA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:26:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>MANDEL: Justice at last for Sammy Yatim - Toronto Sun</title><link>https://torontosun.com/news/local-news/mandel-justice-at-last-for-sammy-yatim</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFeM7vOHDKMMU_8d4UbqPy4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowlYn0CjCyjLwCMNDxzAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://torontosun.com/news/local-news/mandel-justice-at-last-for-sammy-yatim" target="_blank"&gt;MANDEL: Justice at last for Sammy Yatim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Toronto Sun&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At long last, Sammy Yatim can rest in peace.With the Supreme Court's refusal to hear an appeal of his conviction and sentence, James Forcillo is out of options.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://torontosun.com">Toronto Sun</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court will not hear appeal of Toronto cop who shot teen on streetcar - Global News</title><link>https://globalnews.ca/news/4734738/supreme-court-james-forcillo-appeal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780128211642</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://globalnews.ca/news/4734738/supreme-court-james-forcillo-appeal/" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court will not hear appeal of Toronto cop who shot teen on streetcar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Global News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/supreme-court-won-t-hear-james-forcillo-s-appeal-in-sammy-yatim-shooting-1.4934600" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court won't hear James Forcillo's appeal in Sammy Yatim shooting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://ca.news.yahoo.com/supreme-court-denies-leave-appeal-150722629.html" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court denies leave to appeal for cop who shot teen on streetcar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Yahoo News Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theglobeandmail.com/canada/article-supreme-court-denies-toronto-cop-james-forcillos-appeal/" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court denies leave to appeal for Toronto police officer James Forcillo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Globe and Mail&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/supreme-court-to-say-if-it-will-hear-case-of-toronto-cop-who-shot-teen-on-streetcar-1.4206944" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court denies leave to appeal for Toronto cop who shot teen on streetcar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CTV News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWk2cGF5bWpZQU1FWHRrQXM5ZmZIMGdLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://globalnews.ca">Global News</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court dismisses former cop James Forcillo’s appeal in shooting of Sammy Yatim - Toronto Star</title><link>https://www.thestar.com/news/gta/2018/12/06/supreme-court-to-decide-today-on-whether-to-hear-james-forcillos-appeal.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG-NtK4QclQHnrFfuyPDbPIqFggEKg4IACoGCAow6bV4MPfJDDCRiUc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:11:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com/news/gta/2018/12/06/supreme-court-to-decide-today-on-whether-to-hear-james-forcillos-appeal.html" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court dismisses former cop James Forcillo’s appeal in shooting of Sammy Yatim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Toronto Star&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forcillo was convicted of attempted murder in Yatim's 2013 shooting death. He had applied to have his case heard at Canada's highest court after the Ontario ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com">Toronto Star</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court to deliver ruling on leave to appeal for Toronto cop convicted in death of Sammy Yatim - Global News</title><link>https://globalnews.ca/news/4726565/supreme-court-appeal-james-forcillo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPIylBfq3Y5F3wg2Z40Rd6AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqeP_CjDdg_oCMMTh6QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://globalnews.ca/news/4726565/supreme-court-appeal-james-forcillo/" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court to deliver ruling on leave to appeal for Toronto cop convicted in death of Sammy Yatim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Global News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;April 30, 2018: Ontario's highest court has rejected the appeal of James Forcillo, the Toronto police officer convicted in the 2013 shooting death of Sammy Yatim, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://globalnews.ca">Global News</source></item><item><title>Lawyer blasts delays in case of officer accused of excessive force for Tasering Sammy Yatim - Toronto Star</title><link>https://www.thestar.com/news/gta/2018/11/13/lawyer-blasts-delays-in-case-of-officer-accused-of-excessive-force-for-tasering-sammy-yatim.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGbyzJG4c5gFF4AXdaquSwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow6bV4MPfJDDCtvTk</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com/news/gta/2018/11/13/lawyer-blasts-delays-in-case-of-officer-accused-of-excessive-force-for-tasering-sammy-yatim.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lawyer blasts delays in case of officer accused of excessive force for Tasering Sammy Yatim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Toronto Star&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lawyer representing Sammy Yatim's father in a Toronto police disciplinary hearing is raising concerns about delays in the case of the officer who Tasered ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com">Toronto Star</source></item><item><title>Ontario Police Watchdog Charges Waterloo Officer With Attempted Murder - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/29/siu-attempted-murder-charge_a_23604819/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMs-sMoGBHNhEE5e5b7EJJwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w18vGBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 21:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/11/29/siu-attempted-murder-charge_a_23604819/" target="_blank"&gt;Ontario Police Watchdog Charges Waterloo Officer With Attempted Murder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first time in its 28-year history, Ontario's police watchdog has charged an officer with attempted murder. Veteran Waterloo Region Sgt. Richard Dorling faces this and three other criminal charges related to the shooting of a 30-year-old Hamilton man on an afternoon in March in Cambridge, Ont., the Special Investigations Unit (SIU) announced Wednesday. "This is the first case in which the SIU laid an attempt murder charge," confirmed SIU spokesperson Monica Hudon. Hamilton Police had been investigating a break and enter when they tracked a stolen vehicle to an industrial area of Camb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Police sergeant who Tasered Sammy Yatim faces misconduct charge - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/police-sergeant-who-tasered-sammy-yatim-faces-misconduct-charge-1.4051591</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGGWqjEsMPzeQSkfo7YMg4oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 23:48:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/police-sergeant-who-tasered-sammy-yatim-faces-misconduct-charge-1.4051591" target="_blank"&gt;Police sergeant who Tasered Sammy Yatim faces misconduct charge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The police sergeant who Tasered 18-year-old Sammy Yatim as he lay dying of gunshot wounds on the floor of a Toronto streetcar is facing a police misconduct charge, nearly four years after the teen's death. The Office of the Independent Police Review Director (OIPRD) recommended the charge against Sgt. Dusan Dan Pravica in connection with the incident on July 27, 2013. Pravica had entered the streetcar telling Yatim — who had already been shot nine times by fellow officer Const. James Forcillo — to "drop the knife." Pravica wrote in his police notes from that night that Yatim tried to stand ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Toronto police Const. James Forcillo's appeal set to begin, new evidence may be coming - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/forcillo-appeal-evidence-stress-toronto-police-yatim-1.4315751</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJlvSyt5b8EHc1WbqFxzt8MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/forcillo-appeal-evidence-stress-toronto-police-yatim-1.4315751" target="_blank"&gt;Toronto police Const. James Forcillo's appeal set to begin, new evidence may be coming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toronto police Const. James Forcillo's appeal begins Monday, a process that will include a hearing to discuss new evidence that Forcillo's lawyers argue could undermine testimony from his trial. Forcillo, convicted of attempted murder for the 2013 shooting of 18-year-old Sammy Yatim on a Toronto streetcar, had his bail extended last week just days before he was set to turn himself in. He will remain out of prison, with strict conditions, until April 2018 or until his lawyers present the new evidence. That could come early next year, as the appeal is broken into two stages. According to docu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>'She gonna get shot,' bystander says, but then watches police wait for woman in crisis to climb off cruiser - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/mental-health-crisis-tps-police-finch-islington-1.3919510</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIYuqaQUmvvsTpWTRT-9Q1EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 01:57:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/mental-health-crisis-tps-police-finch-islington-1.3919510" target="_blank"&gt;'She gonna get shot,' bystander says, but then watches police wait for woman in crisis to climb off cruiser&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video opens to show a woman clearly in distress, weaving in the middle of a crowded Toronto street and yelling as she pulls herself up on the hood of a police cruiser and starts kicking at its windshield. Another cruiser pulls up to the intersection at Finch Avenue West at Milady Road with its lights flashing and the woman moves on to start beating at the new car with her feet. "She gonna get shot," said the person taking the video on Sunday from an upper-storey window. But that's not what happens. Unlike the videos of police interactions that typically make the news, no one in this wil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Use of force 'appears to be justified' in video of police shooting, former SIU director says - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/police-shooting-video-1.4301658</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO0GAWkMDCsUlMytYROYAUkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 01:05:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/police-shooting-video-1.4301658" target="_blank"&gt;Use of force 'appears to be justified' in video of police shooting, former SIU director says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A shooting by a Toronto police officer to stop a brutal and prolonged stabbing attack last week appears to be justified, says a former director of Ontario's police watchdog, based on his viewing of video of the incident that is making the rounds on social media. The video was taken on the morning of Sept. 14 after police were called to Driftwood Avenue and Cobbler Crescent, north of Jane and Finch, around 9:15 a.m. for reports of an assault. The two officers found one man stabbing another on the sidewalk, according to a news release from the Special Investigations Unit. One officer fired hi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>James Forcillo appeal challenges crucial interpretation of Sammy Yatim streetcar killing - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/forcillo-appeal-yatim-1.4317368</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC8dN3Js5Pwh2w-GYHcW1cYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 21:26:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/forcillo-appeal-yatim-1.4317368" target="_blank"&gt;James Forcillo appeal challenges crucial interpretation of Sammy Yatim streetcar killing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lawyers for Toronto Police Const. James Forcillo began their bid to overturn his conviction on Monday by asking the Ontario Court of Appeal to reconsider a crucial interpretation of the way the fatal shooting of 18 year-old Sammy Yatim unfolded on a Toronto streetcar in 2013. Last year, a jury acquitted Forcillo of second-degree murder but convicted him of attempted murder. He was sentenced to six years in prison but remains free on bail pending the outcome of his appeal. Yatim's mother, Sahar Bahadi, attended the proceeding on Monday, telling reporters she believes the court will uphold Fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Officer convicted of shooting Sammy Yatim wants Supreme Court to hear his case - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/officer-convicted-of-shooting-sammy-yatim-wants-supreme-court-to-hear-his-case-1.4740470</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFkUBhebPFgEAP1bedxvce4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 14:35:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/officer-convicted-of-shooting-sammy-yatim-wants-supreme-court-to-hear-his-case-1.4740470" target="_blank"&gt;Officer convicted of shooting Sammy Yatim wants Supreme Court to hear his case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Const. James Forcillo is asking the Supreme Court of Canada to allow him to appeal his attempted murder conviction in the shooting death of Sammy Yatim five years ago. Forcillo's lawyers, Michael Lacy, Joseph Wilkinson and Bryan Badali, filed the application seeking an appeal on June 26. In an unusual verdict, a jury acquitted Forcillo of second-degree murder but convicted him of attempted murder in connection with Yatim's death aboard a Dundas streetcar on the night of July 27, 2013. Forcillo was sentenced to six years in jail — one year above the mandatory minimum for attempted murder. Fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Const. James Forcillo, Toronto Cop Convicted In Streetcar Shooting, Seeks Supreme Court Appeal - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/07/10/james-forcillo-supreme-court-appeal_a_23478815/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJC5Jp5o7q3ePu1jwvhg_0oqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w18vGBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 16:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/07/10/james-forcillo-supreme-court-appeal_a_23478815/" target="_blank"&gt;Const. James Forcillo, Toronto Cop Convicted In Streetcar Shooting, Seeks Supreme Court Appeal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Toronto police officer convicted of attempted murder in the shooting death of a troubled teen on an empty streetcar is seeking leave to bring his case before Canada's top court. Const. James Forcillo fired two separate volleys at 18-year-old Sammy Yatim, who was standing alone and holding a small knife. In 2016, a jury acquitted Forcillo of the more serious charge of second-degree murder related to the first volley of shots — which killed the teen — but found him guilty of attempted murder related to the second round, fired seconds later while Yatim was lying on his back. Lawyers for Forc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Officer who shot Sammy Yatim pleads guilty to perjury, gets 6 months added to sentence - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/yatim-forcillo-sentence-1.4686639</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMoonDf9nq2Kgiog9_PvUOUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 22:37:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/yatim-forcillo-sentence-1.4686639" target="_blank"&gt;Officer who shot Sammy Yatim pleads guilty to perjury, gets 6 months added to sentence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Const. James Forcillo had fired two separate volleys at Sammy Yatim as the 18-year-old was standing alone holding a small knife on a streetcar in 2013. A jury convicted Forcillo of attempted murder in 2016 and he was sentenced to six years in prison. His lawyers say he pleaded guilty perjury in a Toronto court on Thursday, and the other new charges were dropped.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>A Brutal Attack in Toronto Is Met With Restraint - The New Yorker</title><link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/a-brutal-attack-in-toronto-is-met-with-restraint</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHilgU7RJN6nFOSSZgacAOkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowjMqjCjCJhZwBMNWYrQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:53:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/a-brutal-attack-in-toronto-is-met-with-restraint" target="_blank"&gt;A Brutal Attack in Toronto Is Met With Restraint&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New Yorker&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Monday, a man drove a rented van onto a sidewalk in Toronto, killing ten pedestrians and injuring fourteen others. Unlike in similar vehicle attacks—in iconic locations in Berlin, Nice, London, and New York—which have been inspired by the Islamic State, the attacker apparently identified with the so-called incel movement: the “involuntarily celibate” men who profess violent hatred toward the women who have ignored or spurned them. His choice of location was also anomalous. The mile-long stretch where the attack took place is on Toronto’s periphery, at the end of a subway line. Twenty yea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newyorker.com">The New Yorker</source></item><item><title>‘Get Down or You’ll Be Shot!’: Videos of Van Driver’s Arrest Captivate Social Media - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/23/world/americas/canada-toronto-van-pedestrians.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ5ZqfytKD9BHI6Lfv8xlNIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 23:36:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/23/world/americas/canada-toronto-van-pedestrians.html" target="_blank"&gt;‘Get Down or You’ll Be Shot!’: Videos of Van Driver’s Arrest Captivate Social Media&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amateurs with smartphones recorded the episode on a Toronto street, and the videos quickly begin trending on Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Officer praised after taking down Toronto van attack suspect without gunfire - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/officer-praised-taking-van-attack-suspect-custody-peaceful-1.4632661</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHbX1VHtzu4qq-gTbRZ5YuUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 15:51:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/officer-praised-taking-van-attack-suspect-custody-peaceful-1.4632661" target="_blank"&gt;Officer praised after taking down Toronto van attack suspect without gunfire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Toronto police officer who apprehended the suspect in Monday's van attack in a busy area north of downtown has been identified as Const. Ken Lam, and experts are praising him for his handling of the arrest. "Hats off, kudos to the officer. He clearly received very good training," said Phil Gurski, a former CSIS analyst and president and CEO of Borealis Threat and Risk Consulting. "He followed that training to the nth degree. And he was able to neutralize a guy who had just carried out a heinous attack. "Now the guy is alive, he's not dead, which means you can question him and you can ho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Toronto Van Attack: Officer Praised Over Response - Newsweek</title><link>http://www.newsweek.com/toronto-van-attack-officer-hailed-hero-refusing-shoot-suspect-898361</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECcUfEJ9ijSCnWLjGspksC4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow77zbCjDiq8wBMMiCsgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 09:19:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.newsweek.com/toronto-van-attack-officer-hailed-hero-refusing-shoot-suspect-898361" target="_blank"&gt;Toronto Van Attack: Officer Praised Over Response&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were it not for one Toronto police officer, the final moments of the Monday van attack that has sent shockwaves across Canada and around the world might have played out very differently. While that officer has yet to be named, he is already being hailed as a hero for refusing to fire his weapon at the man suspected of killing ten people and leaving 15 others seriously injured after plowing a van into a crowd of pedestrians at a busy intersection. Dramatic video of a standoff between the officer and the suspect, who police have identified as 25-year-old Alek Minassian, shows the man, clad in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.newsweek.com">Newsweek</source></item><item><title>Criminal consequences for police officers are rare when a civilian dies - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/manitoba/deadly-force-police-criminal-charges-1.4607134</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPNLVyyfWX8v5U0TCEjltMkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/manitoba/deadly-force-police-criminal-charges-1.4607134" target="_blank"&gt;Criminal consequences for police officers are rare when a civilian dies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story is part of Deadly Force, a CBC News investigation into police-involved fatalities in Canada. Critics say changes are needed to a system that sees hundreds of people die following fatal police encounters, and virtually no criminal consequences for officers. The comments come in reaction to a CBC News investigation that found criminal charges were laid against 18 police officers involved in fatal encounters since 2000, with only two ending in convictions. The research shows 461 people have died in encounters with police over 18 years. Police representatives say with the amount of s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Toronto Const. James Forcillo charged with perjury, attempting to obstruct justice - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/james-forcillo-charged-1.4461116</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPzZNDtvssVZSgvWwTLLZfEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 21:01:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/james-forcillo-charged-1.4461116" target="_blank"&gt;Toronto Const. James Forcillo charged with perjury, attempting to obstruct justice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toronto police Const. James Forcillo, who was convicted of attempted murder in the 2013 shooting death of Sammy Yatim, has been charged with perjury and attempting to obstruct justice. The charges come as a result of breach of bail allegations by the province's Special Investigations Unit, which sparked a separate investigation by the Toronto Police Service's professional standards unit, according to a news release from the police force. Last year, the 34-year-old Forcillo was sentenced to six years in prison for shooting 18-year-old Yatim on a streetcar. Forcillo was arrested in mid-Novemb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>James Forcillo's bail revoked after alleged house arrest violation - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/forcillo-bail-revoked-1.4426219</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHfOQT9nH19bDy-ELvKCwlgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 15:36:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/forcillo-bail-revoked-1.4426219" target="_blank"&gt;James Forcillo's bail revoked after alleged house arrest violation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bail has been revoked for Const. James Forcillo, the suspended Toronto police officer convicted in the 2013 shooting death of Sammy Yatim. Forcillo was arrested in mid-November by Toronto police for allegedly breaching the bail conditions related to his house arrest. On Thursday, a judge ruled his bail would be revoked. Forcillo's lawyer said after his court appearance that part of the reason Forcillo agreed to have his bail revoked was that his sureties — one of them being his ex-wife — were no longer willing to act in that capacity. Last year, Forcillo was sentenced to six years in prison...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item></channel></rss>