<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Calgary International Airport - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZ4ZVdwb0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-CA&amp;gl=CA&amp;ceid=CA:en</link><language>en-CA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:48:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Suspected heroin smuggler swallowed pellets before arrest at Calgary airport, police say - CBC.ca</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/heroin-smuggling-arrested-airport-calgary-pellets-swallowed-cbsa-1.4933375</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780127235788</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/heroin-smuggling-arrested-airport-calgary-pellets-swallowed-cbsa-1.4933375" target="_blank"&gt;Suspected heroin smuggler swallowed pellets before arrest at Calgary airport, police say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC.ca&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://calgaryherald.com/news/crime/border-agents-make-large-heroin-bust-at-calgary-international-airport/wcm/4ba08a8a-7724-484d-8fee-38d2c3be50ca" target="_blank"&gt;Woman arrested at airport after ingesting 'dozens' of compressed heroin pellets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Calgary Herald&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://calgary.ctvnews.ca/cbsa-officers-seize-heroin-from-suitcase-at-calgary-international-airport-1.4205485" target="_blank"&gt;CBSA officers seize heroin from suitcase at Calgary International Airport&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CTV News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://calgarysun.com/news/crime/border-agents-make-large-heroin-bust-at-calgary-international-airport" target="_blank"&gt;Border agents make large heroin bust at Calgary International Airport&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Calgary Sun&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://globalnews.ca/news/4731795/heroin-bust-calgary-airport-rcmp-cbsa/" target="_blank"&gt;Charges laid against woman after heroin bust at Calgary Airport; suspect swallowed pellets to avoid detection: police&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Global News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpNM2ZDbGpZQU1FZVZBdGZ5VmI3czVLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC.ca</source></item><item><title>Calgary city councillors look to increase density under flight path - Global News</title><link>https://globalnews.ca/news/4725887/calgary-city-council-density-development-airport/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENjUOzgKkWpyn1SVCtgJM7MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqeP_CjDdg_oCMMTh6QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 03:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://globalnews.ca/news/4725887/calgary-city-council-density-development-airport/" target="_blank"&gt;Calgary city councillors look to increase density under flight path&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Global News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems a compromise worked out by city administration and the Calgary Airport Authority doesn't go far enough for some councillors when it comes to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://globalnews.ca">Global News</source></item><item><title>Nav Canada implements new ICAO separation standard at YYC - Skies Magazine</title><link>https://www.skiesmag.com/press-releases/nav-canada-implements-new-icao-separation-standard-at-yyc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNraWVzbWFnLmNvbS9wcmVzcy1yZWxlYXNlcy9uYXYtY2FuYWRhLWltcGxlbWVudHMtbmV3LWljYW8tc2VwYXJhdGlvbi1zdGFuZGFyZC1hdC15eWMv0gEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.skiesmag.com/press-releases/nav-canada-implements-new-icao-separation-standard-at-yyc/" target="_blank"&gt;Nav Canada implements new ICAO separation standard at YYC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Skies Magazine&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a world first, the new Established on RNP-AR (EoR) separation standard, implemented at Calgary International Airport (YYC), safely enables simultaneous ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.skiesmag.com">Skies Magazine</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/4zNjXuKv4nUcCFsccdaKSWEl5ltoFYAa1K9T-gQCWLLn2y7Nr0WsfPl33rWod3AgrW9RSnLheR6pmfQ4Hd7iMcevpUQJhqajlheIw4VIeev6LuleY5mSmg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>90-year-old in wheelchair forgotten by airlines at Calgary airport - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/british-columbia/senior-calgary-airport-1.4159892</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMm22L-2uragqL2NhfGI-SAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 15:00:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/british-columbia/senior-calgary-airport-1.4159892" target="_blank"&gt;90-year-old in wheelchair forgotten by airlines at Calgary airport&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 90-year-old airline passenger in a wheelchair says she was twice forgotten by airline staff during a stopover at Calgary International Airport. Mary Ellen Fallis was heading back to Texas Saturday after visiting her grandson and his family in Kelowna, B.C. She arrived at Calgary International Airport on an Air Canada flight to transfer to a United Airlines flight home. An Air Canada employee took her in a wheelchair to a transfer point between airlines, and Fallis said she was told to wait there for someone from United Airlines to take her to her next flight. "There was no indication that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Canadas Rockies Summer 2017 - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/tours/partners/trafalgar/canadas-rockies-summer-2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECbVkpT-dt413S0SaJ4GSkEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 11:33:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/tours/partners/trafalgar/canadas-rockies-summer-2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Canadas Rockies Summer 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview Grizzly bears, spectacular rock formations, thunderous waterfalls and the tranquil emerald waters of glacial lakes - take in the best of the Rocky Mountains on this in-depth exploration.You'll enjoy Insider moments like… getting escorted on horseback into the ranch of the Guinn family for a private BBQ. After a mouthwatering meal of Alberta beef and the trimmings, join the family for a line-dancing lesson. Price includes - 6 full breakfasts. - 3 dinners (including Be My Guest). - Audio Headsets for flexible sightseeing - Daily breakfast and an average of 50% of evening meals - Lu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Errant parachutist snarls flights to and from Calgary - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/parachute-calgary-airport-rcmp-1.4075841</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECdg3ChUksWtWt_b9zEQMO0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 17:22:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/parachute-calgary-airport-rcmp-1.4075841" target="_blank"&gt;Errant parachutist snarls flights to and from Calgary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A parachutist caused major problems at the Calgary International Airport early Monday evening, flying a powered parachute in the path of planes. RCMP say the parachute was spotted flying over the areas of south Airdrie and Balzac, resulting in flights being diverted from landing in Calgary. The control tower at the airport called the RCMP. "Calgary Police were also alerted. The HAWCS helicopter was in the air and upon the operator seeing the helicopter he was able to land quite promptly," said Const. Dan Martin with Airdrie RCMP. RCMP wouldn't say what the man was doing. The incident is sti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Hoax call at Calgary airport leads to temporary evacuation - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-airport-hoax-1.4165531</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBH2yqw0eLl9kpSpEB26Mc0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 23:50:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-airport-hoax-1.4165531" target="_blank"&gt;Hoax call at Calgary airport leads to temporary evacuation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things are returning to normal after a "hoax" call of an active shooter at the Calgary Airport caused confusion and an evacuation Friday evening, police confirm to CBC News. Travellers were allowed to return inside the building minutes after airport officials made an announcement over the public intercom system. A traveller on her way to Regina says it was a scary situation. "I sat down in my seat and a few minutes later the flight's captain comes on the intercom to inform us there were reports of an active shooter," Taylor Pledger told CBC News. "They locked the doors and shut down the air...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Calgary airport criticized after converting 5 disabled stalls to Lexus-only parking - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/airport-parking-lexus-mosley-calgary-reserved-disabled-1.4255651</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcx6obvm1zaHptXgPSqAF0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 17:13:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/airport-parking-lexus-mosley-calgary-reserved-disabled-1.4255651" target="_blank"&gt;Calgary airport criticized after converting 5 disabled stalls to Lexus-only parking&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Calgary Airport Authority has been criticized after it relocated some disabled parking bays that were converted to more lucrative "Lexus-only" spaces. It received a complaint after a family with access needs pulled into the short-term section of the parkade to find five accessible parking spaces they usually use were gone. The airport sold the space to Lexus so it could paint its logo on the floor and allow its customers to enjoy the prime location exclusively. Calgary Airport Authority spokesperson Jody Moseley says selling the bays as advertising space to the luxury car brand will mak...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Calgary Closes Park After Metal Slides Prove Too Hot For Tiny Tushes - Huffpost Canada</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2017/05/25/calgary-hot-metal-slides_n_16809860.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhPW1TxdJImRsGIf4yuVGoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8wg9qsAw</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:39:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2017/05/25/calgary-hot-metal-slides_n_16809860.html" target="_blank"&gt;Calgary Closes Park After Metal Slides Prove Too Hot For Tiny Tushes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Huffpost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALGARY — A popular Calgary playground has been forced to close for improvements because the sun is making metal slides too hot for kids to handle. Slides on the south-facing side of the playground are getting so heated that they reportedly singed a child. The play structure was opened just two years ago on St. Patrick's Island, but now it's closed for the $100,000 renovation. Shades had been installed to keep the metal cool, but they ended up being used as hammocks. Popular Calgary playground closed to fix a major flaw https://t.co/ssajHKixMe @CTVBradMacLeod #yyc pic.twitter.com/NNUcxh5eXz...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.ca">Huffpost Canada</source></item><item><title>Sunwing defends 6-hour break between flights for pilot who returned to duty drunk - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/miroslav-gronych-sunwing-double-flight-shift-1.4036936</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHthmiI-_6F_j5kyRrfDks8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/miroslav-gronych-sunwing-double-flight-shift-1.4036936" target="_blank"&gt;Sunwing defends 6-hour break between flights for pilot who returned to duty drunk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunwing Airlines is defending its scheduling in a case where a pilot showed up for the second flight of his 11-hour shift so drunk that he appeared to fall asleep in the captain's chair. But a pilots' group says the scheduling practice raises concerns. Miroslav Gronych pleaded guilty this week to having care and control of an aircraft with a blood alcohol level over .08 after being arrested at the Calgary airport on Dec. 31, 2016. According to an agreed statement of facts presented in court, Gronych flew into the Calgary airport at 12:48 a.m and was supposed to report back at 6 a.m. for a 7...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>'Balloonatic' who flew over Calgary in lawn chair gets more time to pay fine - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-daniel-boria-balloon-man-plea-1.3976933</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENSIbzYhQwOFr6Pv5F7N4EcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 20:53:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-daniel-boria-balloon-man-plea-1.3976933" target="_blank"&gt;'Balloonatic' who flew over Calgary in lawn chair gets more time to pay fine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Calgary man who strapped 120 helium balloons to a lawn chair and soared high into the air above the Stampede grounds in 2015 has been given another month to raise money for a required donation prior to his sentencing. Daniel Boria pleaded guilty in December 2016 on a charge of dangerous operation of an aircraft, saying it was part of a publicity stunt for his cleaning company. Provincial court Judge Bruce Fraser accepted a joint recommendation for a sentence of a $5,000 fine and also accepted a recommendation Boria make a $20,000 donation to a charity of his choice. On Friday, his lawyer,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Spectacular Canadian Rockies Summer 2018 - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/tours/partners/trafalgar/spectacular-canadian-rockies-summer-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJR3zTrJyTPmJ3C6gD1nYOQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 08:13:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/tours/partners/trafalgar/spectacular-canadian-rockies-summer-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Spectacular Canadian Rockies Summer 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview Experience the breathtaking Canadian Rockies on this memorable nine-day adventure filled with natural beauty and cosmopolitan cities. In the heart of the Rocky Mountains, enjoy journeys through the jagged snow-capped mountains, including its highest, Mount Robson, with slender fir trees and crystal-clear lakes. At Jasper National Park, you can start the day with a walk to the limestone Maligne Canyon, with interpretive signs to describe its unique geology. You can also join a rafting trip, taking you down the scenic Athabasca River, where a National Park guide describes how fir tra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Wallop Of October Snow Hits Calgary - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/10/02/october-snow-calgary_a_23548486/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFhLffM2H2EO0Mzqz_G9XugqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w8cpI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 17:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/10/02/october-snow-calgary_a_23548486/" target="_blank"&gt;Wallop Of October Snow Hits Calgary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHAT. THE. HECK?!? Calgarians were heaving a collective sigh Tuesday morning after waking up to a heavy winter blanket of snow. Across the city could be heard cries of "too soon!" Environment Canada updated its snowfall warning Tuesday morning, forecasting anywhere from 10 to 25 centimetres for some parts of Central and Southern Alberta, and as much as 45 centimetres for the mountains west of Calgary. Calgary #StayHomeYYC#YYC#YYCSNOWpic.twitter.com/9kAtiAA0sL — Neil Zeller (@Neil_Zee) October 2, 2018 Many drivers faced hours-long commutes to work Tuesday morning, as cars slipped, skidded, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>Feds announce $50M toward Airport Trail expansion project in Calgary - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-airport-trail-infrastructure-trudeau-1.4737534</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKb8lv_iFq0N7XZlTPJ_LXgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 23:08:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-airport-trail-infrastructure-trudeau-1.4737534" target="_blank"&gt;Feds announce $50M toward Airport Trail expansion project in Calgary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The federal government will contribute $50 million toward the expansion of Airport Trail, Prime Minister Justin Trudeau announced Friday in Calgary. The project will see a new segment of road built between 36th Street and 60th Street N.E., with an intersection at Metis Trail. It will also include the first stage of an interchange at 19th Street and Airport Trail, along with a new, southbound-to-westbound ramp at Stoney Trail and Airport Trail. It's the second phase of the Airport Trail expansion project, following the opening of the 620-metre, six-lane Airport Trail tunnel in 2014. - Calgar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>WestJet Flight Returns To Calgary After Fire Breaks Out In Cargo Hold - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/06/14/westjet-flight-fire-calgary_a_23459504/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECVhMAC6BqP6jjJFQ-4eULIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8w18vGBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 01:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/06/14/westjet-flight-fire-calgary_a_23459504/" target="_blank"&gt;WestJet Flight Returns To Calgary After Fire Breaks Out In Cargo Hold&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALGARY — The Transportation Safety Board sent investigators to Calgary International Airport on Thursday after a WestJet passenger plane was forced to return after taking off. The board said there was a fire in the cargo compartment of the Boeing 737. WestJet said in a statement that shortly after takeoff the crew on Flight 113 from Calgary to Vancouver was alerted by a fire indication light. The statement said all passengers and crew were safe and were unloaded after landing. WestJet apologized for the delay and inconvenience, but said safety is its first priority. The plane has been remo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>WestJet agrees to settlement process with pilots union - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/westjet-pilots-union-settlement-process-1.4679054</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENcZpKAwD2skJOUhcxSDB8AqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 02:39:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/westjet-pilots-union-settlement-process-1.4679054" target="_blank"&gt;WestJet agrees to settlement process with pilots union&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anxious air travellers can now rest easy with the threat of a WestJet strike seemingly at an end. The Calgary-based airline and the Air Line Pilots Association have agreed to a settlement process through the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service. Both sides have agreed to mediation — and if required, final and binding arbitration. "I think the most important news tonight is that the threat of strike action has been removed for WestJet guests. WestJet guests can now continue to book and travel in absolute confidence around their trip," said WestJet CEO Ed Sims from Calgary International...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Strike Threat Fades As WestJet, Air Line Pilots Association Agree To Mediation - HuffPost Canada</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/05/25/strike-westjet-air-line-pilots-association-union-mediation_a_23443936/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIviGu9dtGN60lZsazvmqYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1qfAAjCkrz8wibdI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 01:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2018/05/25/strike-westjet-air-line-pilots-association-union-mediation_a_23443936/" target="_blank"&gt;Strike Threat Fades As WestJet, Air Line Pilots Association Agree To Mediation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost Canada&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Calgary-based airline and the union that represents the pilots said Friday they have agreed to a settlement process that will involve a federal mediator. WestJet and the Air Line Pilots Association (ALPA) say if necessary they have agreed to use final and binding arbitration. In a joint release the airline and union said "WestJet guests can now book and travel with confidence." THE CANADIAN PRESS WestJet planes are seen at the Calgary Airport in Calgary on May 10, 2018. The two sides had resumed contract talks on Tuesday. The pilots were legally able to launch a strike last Saturday, bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.ca">HuffPost Canada</source></item><item><title>WestJet flight attendants claim they're paid less than minimum wage - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/business/westjet-minimum-wage-cupe-cfau-1.4575681</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENbVOK0np1X60yRoXNRNLz4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/business/westjet-minimum-wage-cupe-cfau-1.4575681" target="_blank"&gt;WestJet flight attendants claim they're paid less than minimum wage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some WestJet flight attendants are claiming the airline routinely pays its cabin crew less than minimum wage, since they are only paid for the amount of time they spend in the air, not their time at work. It's industry standard for flight attendants' pay to be based on the time from wheels up to wheels down, although most airlines also provide some compensation for the time flight attendants spend at airports before and after flights. WestJet does not, and it's become a sticking point with flight attendants as minimum wages rise across the country. The airline's compensation for flight atte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>Snow route parking ban issued for 2nd time this week after winter storm clobbers Calgary - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-winter-storm-snow-roads-slippery-1.4525960</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI6nGlolZzeyxyiB3aBSkJsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 23:46:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-winter-storm-snow-roads-slippery-1.4525960" target="_blank"&gt;Snow route parking ban issued for 2nd time this week after winter storm clobbers Calgary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A slow but unrelenting winter storm that has blanketed an already snowy Calgary made for a slippery morning commute Thursday and has triggered the second snow route parking ban this week. City officials say vehicles must be removed from designated snow routes by 10 a.m. Saturday to allow crews to clear those roads after as much as 20 centimetres came down since late Wednesday. The treacherous driving conditions had police suggesting Calgarians stay home if possible. But, no such luck for most Calgary students — neither major school board called a snow day. An Environment Canada winter storm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>What to Expect in 2018 - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/01/08/travel/what-to-expect-in-2018.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHP_pQOGm7qJi6B-695rYcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 10:00:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/01/08/travel/what-to-expect-in-2018.html" target="_blank"&gt;What to Expect in 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A look at what’s ahead, from new airport security procedures to new airline routes and rules for those so-called smart bags.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Good morning, Calgary! It's -8 C or +8 C, depending on which part of the city you're in - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-morning-weather-nov-22-2017-temperature-swings-1.4413832</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGcKLakfvoIPJ6Ds1NPa37wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCe5BQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 15:40:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/calgary-morning-weather-nov-22-2017-temperature-swings-1.4413832" target="_blank"&gt;Good morning, Calgary! It's -8 C or +8 C, depending on which part of the city you're in&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's a warm, windy morning in Calgary. It's also a calm, cold morning in Calgary. Temperatures varied by more than 16 C at different points across the city Wednesday morning as a chinook rolled in from the west. At 7 a.m., Environment Canada's weather station at the Calgary International Airport recorded the temperature at -8.1 C. At the same time, the station at Springbank Airport — just 25 kilometres to the west — was reading 8.4 degrees above zero. Environment Canada is forecasting a high of 11 C for Calgary on Wednesday and a relatively mild low of 6 C, as the warm wind blankets the cit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>How Bridges Evolved Into Signifiers of Urban Identity - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/882096/how-bridges-evolved-into-signifiers-of-urban-identity</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBx4_PSdKpu6xwhsfcGZ0-gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/882096/how-bridges-evolved-into-signifiers-of-urban-identity" target="_blank"&gt;How Bridges Evolved Into Signifiers of Urban Identity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Margaret Hunt Hill Bridge, Dallas, Texas. Image © Greig Cranna Increasingly close collaboration between architects and engineers has caused an explosion in bridge design over the last few decades, resulting in structures that are both bold yet rational. As a result, cities have exploited bridges as great monuments of design, to foster pride in the residents and promote themselves as a destination for tourists. These ideas have inspired photographer Greig Cranna as he travels the world, capturing the elegance of today's bridge infrastructure. Cranna has been documenting some of his stunning ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item></channel></rss>