<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Ontario Highway 407 - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZ5YlRBekVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-CA&amp;gl=CA&amp;ceid=CA:en</link><language>en-CA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:27:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Highway 407 bill tipped off Ontario woman about Range Rover she says she never bought - CBC News</title><link>http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/teacher-identity-theft-1.4109687</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDuSeqNZklK7dRCeglVcVnkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjDGlx0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 11:00:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/teacher-identity-theft-1.4109687" target="_blank"&gt;Highway 407 bill tipped off Ontario woman about Range Rover she says she never bought&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Ontario teacher is working to clear her name, and her credit score, after someone appears to have used her identity to open credit cards, take out a loan and purchase a luxury SUV. Tara Douglas arrived home from her teaching job in Bradford on April 28 to find a bill waiting for her for the Highway 407 toll expressway. The bill, however, was for trips she never took in a car she never bought. "I saw the licence plate did not belong to me and the trips that were on this 407 bill I had never taken," Douglas told CBC Radio's Metro Morning this week. She called the number on the bill and was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item><item><title>2 dead in tanker crash, fire on Toronto-area highway, officials say - CBC News</title><link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/tanker-fire-407-1.4886645</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK_D9kI1vKxPffQzeCfUj7QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowqKNmMKjdCjCT1B0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 03:26:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/tanker-fire-407-1.4886645" target="_blank"&gt;2 dead in tanker crash, fire on Toronto-area highway, officials say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two people are dead after a multi-vehicle collision involving a tanker truck on a major toll highway north of Toronto, officials say. The fuel tanker burst into flames on Highway 407, in Vaughan, Ont., just before 5 p.m. ET, according to the Ontario Provincial Police. OPP Sgt. Kerry Schmidt told CBC Toronto the tanker apparently crossed from the westbound lanes onto the eastbound side of the highway, and was involved in a collision with a passenger vehicle. Both vehicles burst into flames and were still smouldering hours later. Officials say two people have died after a tanker truck was cau...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cbc.ca">CBC News</source></item></channel></rss>