<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>John Magufuli - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNSEkwZUhsMGVCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:44:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Tanzania suffers peril of populism | News | Africa - Mail and Guardian</title><link>https://mg.co.za/article/2018-12-07-00-tanzania-suffers-peril-of-populism</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiSWh0dHBzOi8vbWcuY28uemEvYXJ0aWNsZS8yMDE4LTEyLTA3LTAwLXRhbnphbmlhLXN1ZmZlcnMtcGVyaWwtb2YtcG9wdWxpc23SAQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:00:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mg.co.za/article/2018-12-07-00-tanzania-suffers-peril-of-populism" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania suffers peril of populism | News | Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Mail and Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Repressive: John Magufuli ran for the presidency in 2015. He has swept out corrupt officials, but without following due process, and has aggressively sought ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mg.co.za">Mail and Guardian</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/3PFcNGYcr8geUkqOAxhzXc4bIO88pPCbp_pRisx1MdmYXxQ7O6h1q96BLiWfNeVJMkgaK2EDavJaUgXCHpi67K6GsYUAbg53uCXJxmyeo_um2jGFxs2LA1yPZVawBrKy7gez7pJQuXj-LxBUgSDQu2A19U4Z3TZf6-x21dLyIn41L5s=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>From #WhatwouldMagufuliDo to #Magufoolishness: What wil... - Daily Maverick</title><link>https://www.dailymaverick.co.za/article/2018-11-08-from-whatwouldmagufulido-to-magufoolishness-what-will-john-magufuli-do-next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMif2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5bWF2ZXJpY2suY28uemEvYXJ0aWNsZS8yMDE4LTExLTA4LWZyb20td2hhdHdvdWxkbWFndWZ1bGlkby10by1tYWd1Zm9vbGlzaG5lc3Mtd2hhdC13aWxsLWpvaG4tbWFndWZ1bGktZG8tbmV4dC_SAQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.dailymaverick.co.za/article/2018-11-08-from-whatwouldmagufulido-to-magufoolishness-what-will-john-magufuli-do-next/" target="_blank"&gt;From #WhatwouldMagufuliDo to #Magufoolishness: What wil...&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Daily Maverick&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania's John Magufuli has gone the way of other 'new' African presidents who once raised great hope, like Uganda's Yoweri Museveni or Rwanda's Paul ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.dailymaverick.co.za">Daily Maverick</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/1MhuBfCQZuxJJapyEXJq0Wm89CoiNaw5_fGXKwGlEmgFq7uHBh80L3ArVuGAydMOP3sKLG06AW5IIPhvRgK1OyqxxYLfZ53UX8OtvdtrB7J4NRFwc6u1no0weyh11vqARhMtduGK0d9XvY7PpgcAN-EohqCq=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>EU to review its financial support for Tanzania over human rights concerns - Mail and Guardian</title><link>https://mg.co.za/article/2018-11-18-eu-to-review-its-financial-support-for-tanzania-over-human-rights-concerns</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vbWcuY28uemEvYXJ0aWNsZS8yMDE4LTExLTE4LWV1LXRvLXJldmlldy1pdHMtZmluYW5jaWFsLXN1cHBvcnQtZm9yLXRhbnphbmlhLW92ZXItaHVtYW4tcmlnaHRzLWNvbmNlcm5z0gEA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mg.co.za/article/2018-11-18-eu-to-review-its-financial-support-for-tanzania-over-human-rights-concerns" target="_blank"&gt;EU to review its financial support for Tanzania over human rights concerns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Mail and Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EU to review its financial support for Tanzania over human rights concerns.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mg.co.za">Mail and Guardian</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/T0pub5ASQEODK73y-Fi6aI-_4TDUm9_pYq2TMt7LMyeuQ6KLHdhmK7h2zhStkt6BZaOiDp_RtMM7tRWp_fyGolmYLeylusnSoK6geHeDu2mrwO2pYw43YDmsCxpyC4krm0h8rq7v3yCjfJWXBDJrlwMaN3V2Nvdx=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Tanzanian president orders army to buy entire cashew harvest and eat it - TimesLIVE</title><link>https://www.timeslive.co.za/news/africa/2018-11-13-tanzanian-president-orders-army-to-buy-entire-cashew-harvest-and-eat-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMie2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRpbWVzbGl2ZS5jby56YS9uZXdzL2FmcmljYS8yMDE4LTExLTEzLXRhbnphbmlhbi1wcmVzaWRlbnQtb3JkZXJzLWFybXktdG8tYnV5LWVudGlyZS1jYXNoZXctaGFydmVzdC1hbmQtZWF0LWl0L9IBywFodHRwczovL3d3dy10aW1lc2xpdmUtY28temEuY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy93d3cudGltZXNsaXZlLmNvLnphL2FtcC9uZXdzL2FmcmljYS8yMDE4LTExLTEzLXRhbnphbmlhbi1wcmVzaWRlbnQtb3JkZXJzLWFybXktdG8tYnV5LWVudGlyZS1jYXNoZXctaGFydmVzdC1hbmQtZWF0LWl0Lz9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.timeslive.co.za/news/africa/2018-11-13-tanzanian-president-orders-army-to-buy-entire-cashew-harvest-and-eat-it/" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzanian president orders army to buy entire cashew harvest and eat it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TimesLIVE&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzanian president John Magufuli has ordered the army to buy up the entire country's crop of cashew nuts after private companies refused to pay the price ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.timeslive.co.za">TimesLIVE</source></item><item><title>Tanzanian president fires two ministers over cashew nut prices - TimesLIVE</title><link>https://www.timeslive.co.za/news/africa/2018-11-11-tanzanian-president-fires-two-ministers-over-cashew-nut-prices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMicmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRpbWVzbGl2ZS5jby56YS9uZXdzL2FmcmljYS8yMDE4LTExLTExLXRhbnphbmlhbi1wcmVzaWRlbnQtZmlyZXMtdHdvLW1pbmlzdGVycy1vdmVyLWNhc2hldy1udXQtcHJpY2VzL9IBwgFodHRwczovL3d3dy10aW1lc2xpdmUtY28temEuY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy93d3cudGltZXNsaXZlLmNvLnphL2FtcC9uZXdzL2FmcmljYS8yMDE4LTExLTExLXRhbnphbmlhbi1wcmVzaWRlbnQtZmlyZXMtdHdvLW1pbmlzdGVycy1vdmVyLWNhc2hldy1udXQtcHJpY2VzLz9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.timeslive.co.za/news/africa/2018-11-11-tanzanian-president-fires-two-ministers-over-cashew-nut-prices/" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzanian president fires two ministers over cashew nut prices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TimesLIVE&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzanian president John Magufuli said the government could buy up the country's cashew nut stock after he fired two ministers and dissolved the industry ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.timeslive.co.za">TimesLIVE</source></item><item><title>Africa exports its wealth for our enjoyment - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b8c20e7e-f270-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMa1BZlcc1X6H0Y3LjJCFmEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:15:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b8c20e7e-f270-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Africa exports its wealth for our enjoyment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This month, Tanzania’s government sent in the army. The deployment was not to repel an invading force or to crush a terrorist threat. The army’s instructions were clear: buy cashew nuts. The intervention, which sent global cashew prices higher, was intended to resolve a dispute between buyers of the unprocessed nut and farmers. John Magafuli, Tanzania’s president and an African Hugo Chávez in the making, was reacting to a fall in prices. Because of a bumper west African harvest, raw cashew prices had fallen across the world. Tanzania, the seventh-largest producer, is a swing supplier of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Under pressure from Western donors, Tanzanian leader prefers Chinese aid - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-china-aid/under-pressure-from-western-donors-tanzanian-leader-prefers-chinese-aid-idUSKCN1NW1SB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKjWOyJHdqUVTgyhx8XIhK4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 17:37:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-china-aid/under-pressure-from-western-donors-tanzanian-leader-prefers-chinese-aid-idUSKCN1NW1SB" target="_blank"&gt;Under pressure from Western donors, Tanzanian leader prefers Chinese aid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzanian President John Magufuli, who has faced threats in recent weeks from Western donors to cut off aid in response to human rights concerns, said on Tuesday he prefers assistance from China, as Beijing imposes fewer conditions. "The thing that makes you happy about their aid is that it is not tied to any conditions. When they decide to give you (assistance), they just give you," Magufuli said, according to a statement posted on State House's website. He delivered the comments at the launch of a new library at the University of Dar es Salaam built at a cost of 93.6 billion Tanzanian shi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>In Tanzania, a bulldozer president tests donors - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-politics/in-tanzania-a-bulldozer-president-tests-donors-idUSKCN1NS08R</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ-m6s_wYHBCfjXTVKrLOSMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 04:37:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-politics/in-tanzania-a-bulldozer-president-tests-donors-idUSKCN1NS08R" target="_blank"&gt;In Tanzania, a bulldozer president tests donors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The soldiers started fanning out in the cashew nut growing regions of southern Tanzania - a jolting sight for traders and, campaigners say, a watershed moment for a country once held up as a darling of development groups. The government said the troops were there last week to make sure growers and markets were obeying new orders by President John Magufuli, known to his supporters as "the bulldozer". His forceful interventions on everything from commerce to sexual morality have placed him on a collision course with donors. On Monday, soldiers were out again further north in the tourist hub o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Cashew traders scramble after Tanzanian government intervention - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a9981660-e9b4-11e8-a34c-663b3f553b35</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOJEjpXZ2sF4_t-ZgvYxyi4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 04:00:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a9981660-e9b4-11e8-a34c-663b3f553b35" target="_blank"&gt;Cashew traders scramble after Tanzanian government intervention&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cashew prices have jumped after John Magufuli, Tanzania’s president, ordered the army to buy the country’s entire 2018 cashew nut harvest. The African nation is the seventh-largest producer of the nut, but a stand-off between farmers and buyers has prompted the president to act. His intervention has come at a critical time. Tanzania is one of the few growers that harvests the crop between October and January — the fallow months before the leading growers of Vietnam, India and Nigeri start exporting in February and March. Prices for processed kernels have jumped 10 per cent to $3.8 per pound...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tanzania's Magufuli orders seizure of expatriate construction workers' passports - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-politics-idUSKBN16A1OL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGUUdQLMV0wU5upcjJ6KcXMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:49:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-politics-idUSKBN16A1OL" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania's Magufuli orders seizure of expatriate construction workers' passports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Fumbuka Ng'wanakilala DAR ES SALAAM (Reuters) - Tanzanian President John Magufuli ordered the confiscation on Friday of passports belonging to foreign employees of an Indian infrastructure company managing a water project that is running late. Magufuli, nicknamed "the Bulldozer" for pushing through his policies, has been praised by Western donors for an anti-corruption drive and cutting wasteful government spending since he came to power in November 2015. Opponents, however, accuse him of becoming increasingly authoritarian, undermining democracy by curbing political activity and crackin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>School bus crash kills 36 in Tanzania - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/05/06/africa/tanzania-school-bus-crash/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEALHMhUpGzj2sOVXjgqjqNgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 02:24:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/05/06/africa/tanzania-school-bus-crash/" target="_blank"&gt;School bus crash kills 36 in Tanzania&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A school bus full of students swerved off a steep road in Tanzania on Saturday morning and fell into a ravine, killing 36 people -- 33 of them children, authorities said. The fatal crash happened in city of Arusha in Tanzania's northern Karatu District, on the edge of the Ngorongoro Conservation Area. "The place where it happened is a hill, with a steep slope, and it was raining when the accident happened," Aruba Police Commander Charles Mkumbo said. Mkumbo added investigators were still trying to determine exactly what caused the bus to leave the road. "We don't know if the driver was new ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>More than 30 children die as bus plunges into ravine in Tanzania - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/05/06/30-children-die-bus-plunges-ravine-tanzania/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAOuv8Yaxx2DY8KhfXPEFRMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 18:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/05/06/30-children-die-bus-plunges-ravine-tanzania/" target="_blank"&gt;More than 30 children die as bus plunges into ravine in Tanzania&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thirty-two schoolchildren, two teachers and a minibus driver where killed in Tanzania when their vehicle plunged into a roadside ravine in the northern tourist region of Arusha on Saturday, a senior police official said. "The accident happened when the bus was descending on a steep hill in rainy conditions," Arusha regional police commander Charles Mkumbo told Reuters by telephone. "We are still investigating the incident to determine if it was caused by a mechanical defect or human error on the part of the driver." Scene of the crashCredit: Reuters The students killed in the accident, whic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Acacia bows to new Tanzania rules; shares slip - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/3cb6426b-c32e-34ac-a85d-21e2aa58b5e5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDAKkoL0t5-plyHDsPRUKM0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 09:03:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3cb6426b-c32e-34ac-a85d-21e2aa58b5e5" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia bows to new Tanzania rules; shares slip&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Acacia were lower on Friday morning after the FTSE 250 gold company said it would comply with new legislation in Tanzania, home to its three operating mines. Acacia said it would comply with the new rules that will see royalty payments increase to 6 per cent from 4 per cent and the implantation of a 1 per cent clearing fee on exports. Acacia, which is majority owned by Barrick Gold, has been embroiled in a bitter dispute with Tanzania’s president John ‘the bulldozer’ Magufuli that some analysts say could threaten the company’s future. He’s has accused the company of operating ille...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Police officers die in ambush near Dar es Salaam - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/police-officers-die-ambush-dar-es-salaam-170414111327625.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE2c8PqDT84YDIno0CVS7kwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:57:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/police-officers-die-ambush-dar-es-salaam-170414111327625.html" target="_blank"&gt;Police officers die in ambush near Dar es Salaam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials say eight Tanzanian police officers have been ambushed and killed while returning from patrol outside the commercial hub of Dar es Salaam. The attack happened on Thursday night in an area called Jaribu. Ernest Mangu, police chief, said on Friday that the identities of the assailants are unknown. The assailants first fired at the driver of the patrol vehicle before killing seven other officers and seizing their weapons. An investigation has been launched into the killings, he said, adding that the motive was not immediately apparent. President John Magufuli said in a message to the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Acacia serves notice of arbitration on Tanzania mines - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a129cec7-de8a-35b7-8a75-4f8bf64b902f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK27UPIThypaeTkGbewtSvsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 14:15:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a129cec7-de8a-35b7-8a75-4f8bf64b902f" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia serves notice of arbitration on Tanzania mines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acacia Mining said it had served notice of arbitration in London against the government of Tanzania over its two mines in the country, which have been unable to export following a ban by President John Magufuli. The London-listed gold miner said it had served notice at the international arbitration court to protect the company but “remains of the view that a negotiated resolution is preferable to the current disputes and the company will continue to work to achieve this.” Two government commissions appointed by Tanzania’s president have accused Acacia of understating the mineral levels in i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Acacia Mining: deconstructive policy - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/67fd42b8-414d-11e7-82b6-896b95f30f58</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAzD8mJy7KrnK2ikhMAwQb8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 16:00:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/67fd42b8-414d-11e7-82b6-896b95f30f58" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia Mining: deconstructive policy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heavy machinery to extract gold usually stays in the mine. Not in Tanzania. There, the “bulldozer” is President John Magufuli, who gets what he wants. But Mr Magufuli’s stance is pummelling shares in Acacia Mining. London-listed Acacia, formerly known as African Barrick, mines gold ore in Tanzania. It then exports the powdered concentrate to facilities elsewhere for processing. Since March, Tanzania has blocked shipments of the intermediate product. This week, government officials accused Acacia of under-reporting gold exported. Mr Magufuli is not just displeased with Acacia. He has fired h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Acacia Mining shares plunge as Tanzania keeps ban on gold exports - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2c913ce0-4092-11e7-9d56-25f963e998b2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHovbkvwX1WWixWqw54v59sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 17:30:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2c913ce0-4092-11e7-9d56-25f963e998b2" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia Mining shares plunge as Tanzania keeps ban on gold exports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Tanzania-focused gold miner Acacia Mining fell 30 per cent on Wednesday after the country accused it of under-reporting the amount of metal in its shipments and kept a ban on exports. Acacia said an investigation by Tanzania’s presidential committee had found the value of minerals within concentrates in containers at the port city of Dar es Salaam was more than 10 times the declared amount. The probe determined Acacia had “not fully declared all of the minerals contained in the concentrate and the directive halting the export of metallic mineral concentrates remains in place”, the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Acacia shares rise on hopes of resolving Tanzania export ban - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e7a5dac0-479c-11e7-8d27-59b4dd6296b8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-X5PmsO_3GcErw7Vzi-UAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 16:58:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e7a5dac0-479c-11e7-8d27-59b4dd6296b8" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia shares rise on hopes of resolving Tanzania export ban&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Acacia Mining rose on Friday after the gold miner said it was hopeful for a resolution with the Tanzanian government over a ban on exports from the east African country. Brad Gordon, chief executive, said he expected talks with senior levels of government to start after the publication of a second presidential investigation into mining that is due “within the next one to two weeks”. “We remain hopeful we’ll be able to agree a resolution to the current export ban with the government but we continue to consider all of our options,” Mr Gordon said. Shares in Acacia fell 30 per cent l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Rights Groups: Freedom of the Press Under Fire in Tanzania - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/freedom-of-the-press-tanzania/4046528.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK32Cbpo_pqnPxIU2u_TAd4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 16:41:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/freedom-of-the-press-tanzania/4046528.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rights Groups: Freedom of the Press Under Fire in Tanzania&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human rights organizations accuse Tanzania's government of using repressive legislation to muzzle the media, civil society and opposition politicians critical of the institution. The critics say cyber crime laws, which took effect two years ago, have been used against nine media organizations, with the Mwanahalisi newspaper the latest to be banned. Rights groups are calling on the government to align its laws with the practices and standards of the international community. Mwanahalisi is the second newspaper to be banned in Tanzania in one year. The government said the paper had violated pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Acacia shares rise after Tanzania agrees to dispute talks - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/79e8e4c3-049d-33f6-99d3-828c8bca1746</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEmG133a-fBml4K7vkoqvDQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 12:26:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/79e8e4c3-049d-33f6-99d3-828c8bca1746" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia shares rise after Tanzania agrees to dispute talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania and Acacia Mining have agreed to hold talks to resolve an escalating dispute over the London-listed company’s operations in the country that is threatening the miner’s future. Acacia will pay all outstanding money it owes the government and cooperate to build a smelter, the Tanzanian government said in a statement after President Magufuli met John Thornton, the executive chairman of Barrick Gold, which owns 63.9 per cent of Acacia. A panel of experts will be established to determine how much Acacia owes Tanzania, the statement added. Shares rose as much as 7.5 per cent on the news ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Opposition Lawmaker Shot, Wounded in Tanzania's Capital - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/oppositon-lawmakers-shot-wounded-in-tanzania-capital/4018960.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHu8Vutom93RLQlN7xWFQwMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 13:56:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/oppositon-lawmakers-shot-wounded-in-tanzania-capital/4018960.html" target="_blank"&gt;Opposition Lawmaker Shot, Wounded in Tanzania's Capital&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gunmen shot and badly wounded Tanzania's most outspoken opposition figure Thursday near his home in the capital, the government said, in an attack that shocked the East African nation known for its relative peace and stability. Lawmaker Tundu Lissu of the Chadema party, who recently faced criminal charges after he called President John Magufuli a dictator, was wounded by an unknown assailant in Dodoma, said Home Affairs Minister Mwigulu Nchemba. Lissu was shot in the stomach, leg and arm, said Dr. Charles James, a regional medical officer. A statement from the opposition party said the lawm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Acacia shares tumble after Tanzania keeps export ban - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ac90a954-25a0-351a-b581-8243cce7b544</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFTLbWAyuLj963AvtINMh9MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 10:56:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ac90a954-25a0-351a-b581-8243cce7b544" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia shares tumble after Tanzania keeps export ban&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Tanzania-focused gold miner Acacia Mining fell as much as 12 per cent on Wednesday morning after the Tanzanian government accused it of under-reporting the mineral content of its exports and said it would maintain its ban on exports of unprocessed gold and copper. The London-listed company said an investigation by Tanzania’s Presidential Committee said Acacia had “not fully declared all of the minerals contained in the concentrate and the directive halting the export of metallic mineral concentrates remains in place.” The investigation follows Tanzania’s decision in March to ban e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tanzania's President Signs New Mining Bills into Law - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-president-signs-new-mining-bill-into-law-/3936493.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOTlo5WA6yFc6SVbwhy92HcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 22:15:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-president-signs-new-mining-bill-into-law-/3936493.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania's President Signs New Mining Bills into Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzanian President John Magufuli said on Monday he has signed into law new mining bills which require the government to own at least a 16 percent stake in mining projects. The laws, which also increase royalties tax on gold and other minerals, were passed by parliament last week despite opposition from the mining industry body. Magufuli reiterated on Monday that no new mining licenses would be issued until Tanzania "puts things in order" and that the government would review all existing mining licenses with foreign investors. "We must benefit from our God-given minerals and that is why we ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Acacia buys $3m in put options to hedge against gold price falls - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/07be6c56-7807-37c0-8243-95d9f33fe01b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8c_OZRA3vohQZRe74tgiIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 07:46:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/07be6c56-7807-37c0-8243-95d9f33fe01b" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia buys $3m in put options to hedge against gold price falls&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acacia Mining, which is locked in a dispute with the Tanzanian government following a ban on its exports, said it had bought $3.2m of put options on gold to help shore up its balance sheet. The company, one of the largest producers of gold in Africa, said it bought put options, which give it the right to sell gold at a set price, on 210,000 ounces of gold at a strike price of $1,300 an ounce. The options expire in equal installments of 35,000 ounces per month over the next six months. The purchases are part of measures to “mitigate cash flows” after Acacia announced this week it would cease...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tanzania forced to deploy military to purchase cashew nuts from farmers amid price row - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/tanzania-deploy-military-cashew-nuts-farmers-price-row-john-magufuli-a8633311.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEWWPqcgCgHnIOnV2resW68qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/tanzania-deploy-military-cashew-nuts-farmers-price-row-john-magufuli-a8633311.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania forced to deploy military to purchase cashew nuts from farmers amid price row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania has been forced to deploy the military to purchase cashew nuts from farmers in a bid to resolve the current row over prices. President John Magufuli ordered an increase in cashew nut prices, the country’s most valuable export crop, in an attempt to safeguard farmers from unsustainably low prices. Farmers had halted sales after saying the amount the crop could command was too low for them to continue to operate. After fixing prices of the commodity, Mr Magufuli rejected offers of $1.3 (£1) per kilogram from the private sector. Instead he ordered the military to buy the produce for $...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Acacia Mining accused of operating illegally in Tanzania - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/7f53064e-4f7d-11e7-bfb8-997009366969</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMY5V750th7NjI9YBHrvj1EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 17:21:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/7f53064e-4f7d-11e7-bfb8-997009366969" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia Mining accused of operating illegally in Tanzania&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Acacia Mining fell sharply on Monday after Tanzania accused the London-listed company of operating illegally in the east African country and indicated it wanted to take part ownership of the miner. A committee appointed by John Magufuli, Tanzania’s president, also accused Acacia of underpaying the government tens of billions of dollars over the 20 years it has been operating in the country. The findings come less than a month after a separate committee alleged that Acacia had under-reported the gold and copper levels in its concentrate exports by more than 10 times. The government...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tanzania and Acacia Mining to seek peace deal in exports row - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b63eb0a6-5110-11e7-bfb8-997009366969</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTcXPBQ516Vnu6DtW2f04IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 16:57:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b63eb0a6-5110-11e7-bfb8-997009366969" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania and Acacia Mining to seek peace deal in exports row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania and Acacia Mining have agreed to negotiate a resolution to an escalating dispute over the London-listed company’s operations in the country that threatens the miner’s future. The breakthrough came after John Thornton, executive chairman of Canada’s Barrick Gold, which owns 63.9 per cent of Acacia, flew to Tanzania to meet President John Magufuli. The east African country has accused Acacia of operating illegally and cheating the country of tens of billions of dollars by understating by more than 10 times the gold and copper concentrate levels in its mineral exports. Mr Thornton sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tanzanian President Tells Security Forces to Target Drug Traffickers - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-president-tells-security-forces-target-drug-traffickers/3708358.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGgmwzgFCBfIYkm3F6CvVNYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 19:47:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-president-tells-security-forces-target-drug-traffickers/3708358.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzanian President Tells Security Forces to Target Drug Traffickers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President John Magufuli told Tanzania's security forces on Monday to crack down on the drug trade and said no one should be spared, even if they are top politicians or their relatives. Magufuli, nicknamed "The Bulldozer" for the way he pushes through projects, has launched a drive against corruption, tax evasion and poaching since taking office in November 2015. His new drive against drugs reflects growing international concerns that East Africa is being used by traffickers. While most Europe-bound Afghan heroin still goes through Iran and the Balkans, a spate of record-size hauls near Keny...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Denmark cuts millions in aid to Tanzania after homophobic comments - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-16/denmark-withdraws-tanzania-aid-homophobic-comments-paul-makonda/10503740</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED5RhvD9D2dZEgZtYWMq_V0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 01:46:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-16/denmark-withdraws-tanzania-aid-homophobic-comments-paul-makonda/10503740" target="_blank"&gt;Denmark cuts millions in aid to Tanzania after homophobic comments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A homophobic call to action from a senior Tanzanian politician has ended up costing the country $13.7 million, after Denmark said it would cut aid funding over the comments. Key points: - Denmark gave Tanzania $52 million in aid funding last year - Tanzania's Government distanced itself from the comments, but there are fears of an anti-gay crackdown - Denmark's move came as the World Bank scrapped a plan to loan Tanzania $412 million Tanzania's second-biggest donor made the move after the administrative chief of capital city Dodoma, Paul Makonda, urged citizens to "report" suspected gay peo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Gold mining firm slapped with tax bill 190 times its annual revenue - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2017/07/25/investing/acacia-tanzania-gold-mine-tax-bill/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGSj_3FaufavX8ZAIgjmfQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 15:59:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2017/07/25/investing/acacia-tanzania-gold-mine-tax-bill/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gold mining firm slapped with tax bill 190 times its annual revenue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania has presented the country's biggest gold producer with a tax bill that's four times the size of its economy. London-listed mining firm Acacia said Monday it had received a $190 billion tax bill from the Tanzanian government that covers the past 17 years. The demand is for $40 billion in back taxes and around $150 billion in penalties and interest. Acacia rejected the findings, saying that its taxes have been paid in full. The size of the bill is staggering: The total amount is roughly 190 times Acacia's revenue in 2016, and four times the size of Tanzania's $47 billion annual GDP. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Tanzania Buying New Planes for Troubled National Airline to Boost Tourism - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-buying-new-planes-to-boost-tourism/3624655.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFWzZb6PiptByDapAmbADZsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 04:00:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-buying-new-planes-to-boost-tourism/3624655.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania Buying New Planes for Troubled National Airline to Boost Tourism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania plans to revamp its cash-strapped national carrier by buying new planes as part of plans to boost tourism and transport sectors, Tanzanian President John Magufuli said on Monday. Home to the famous Serengeti National Park and Africa's highest mountain Kilimanjaro, Tanzania relies heavily on revenues from tourism - its biggest foreign exchange earner, bringing in around $2 billion a year. Magufuli said his government wants to increase direct flights between Tanzania and Asian and European markets in a bid to boost annual foreign visitor arrivals beyond current levels of around 1 mil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>School bus crashes in Tanzania killing dozens - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/may/06/tanzania-school-minibus-crash-arusha</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG-38ALvrekEZgDv6bvCSHwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 17:24:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/may/06/tanzania-school-minibus-crash-arusha" target="_blank"&gt;School bus crashes in Tanzania killing dozens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A school bus has crashed in Tanzania killing 32 schoolchildren, two teachers and the driver after it plunged into a roadside ravine in the northern tourist region of Arusha, a senior police official has said. “The accident happened when the bus was descending on a steep hill in rainy conditions,” regional commander Charles Mkumbo said. “We are still investigating the incident to determine if it was caused by a mechanical defect or human error on the part of the driver.” The pupils killed in the accident, which occurred at about 9.30am in Karatu district, were aged 12 to 13, and from the Luc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Tanzania's Tundu Lissu recovering after gun attack - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/tanzania-tundu-lissu-recovering-gun-attack-170908185550801.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOwCwnGgYc1GPLm8ZvV9H0cqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 20:58:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/tanzania-tundu-lissu-recovering-gun-attack-170908185550801.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania's Tundu Lissu recovering after gun attack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzanian opposition legislator Tundu Lissu is recovering in a Kenyan hospital after being wounded in a gun attack at his residence in Tanzania's administrative capital, Dodoma, according to his party. Abdallah Safari, the vice president of main opposition party CHADEMA, said at a news conference on Friday that Lissu was taken to the Aga Khan hospital in neighbouring Kenya's capital, Nairobi, "after a decision by his family and his party". "His health is improving," he said. Vincent Mashinji, CHADEMA secretary-general, said: "Those who wanted to kill him have failed." The motive for the sho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Tanzania: Investors' Optimism Wanes As President Magufuli Proves Unpredictable - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/riskmap/2017/07/11/tanzania-investors-optimism-wanes-as-president-magufuli-proves-unpredictable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6AAF5YaJhRrtqvzN3k4QoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 16:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/riskmap/2017/07/11/tanzania-investors-optimism-wanes-as-president-magufuli-proves-unpredictable/" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania: Investors' Optimism Wanes As President Magufuli Proves Unpredictable&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Tanzanian woman walks past a campaign billboard for John Magufuli in October 2015. (AP Photo/Khalfan Said) By Patricia Rodrigues Tanzanian President John Magufuli made international headlines in October 2015 when he was elected amid a wave of optimism stemming from his tough stance against corruption. Magufuli quickly embarked on a campaign to tackle public sector graft and to dismantle corruption networks in his first year in office. Investors and international media were impressed: it seemed that an African leader was matching election rhetoric with action, and that a promise to tackle ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Tanzania Threatens Crackdown on LGBT Advocates - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-threatens-crackdown-on-lgbt-advocates-/3917207.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDvWCnZdDqg2dTmij5VBcYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 23:15:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-threatens-crackdown-on-lgbt-advocates-/3917207.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania Threatens Crackdown on LGBT Advocates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania has threatened to arrest and expel activists, as well as de-register all non-governmental organizations that campaign for gay rights. Homosexuality is a criminal offense in the East African nation, where the law states that suspects convicted of having "carnal knowledge of any person against the order of nature" could face up to 30 years in jail. At a rally late on Sunday, Tanzania's Home Affairs Minister Mwigulu Nchemba said both domestic and foreign campaigners for gay rights would now face punitive measures in the country. "Those who want to campaign for gay rights should find a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Tanzania Dam Project Said to Affect World Heritage Site - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-dam-project-said-to-affect-world-heritage-site/3927621.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOg0RJZ7qenhi1CC6O6QXYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 14:03:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-dam-project-said-to-affect-world-heritage-site/3927621.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania Dam Project Said to Affect World Heritage Site&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations has called it one of Africa's biggest remaining wilderness areas. Now a dispute over a planned hydropower dam in Tanzania's Selous wildlife reserve pits the country's president against conservationists who say the project could cause irreparable damage to the UNESCO World Heritage site. On Tuesday, a few days after President John Magufuli said the Stiegler's Gorge dam will be built "come rain, come sun," the WWF conservation group said in a report that the project threatens an important wetland as well as the livelihoods of more than 200,000 people in impoverished areas, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Petra Diamonds market value falls after Tanzania seizes $15m shipment - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2017/sep/11/petra-diamonds-market-value-falls-tanzania-seizes-shipment</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIOBPYOoXOipDmxOWBq4GbgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 10:14:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2017/sep/11/petra-diamonds-market-value-falls-tanzania-seizes-shipment" target="_blank"&gt;Petra Diamonds market value falls after Tanzania seizes $15m shipment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Petra Diamonds’ stock market value fell after the Tanzanian government seized a parcel of gems valued at nearly $15m (£11.4m) as part of a parliamentary investigation into alleged wrongdoing in the diamond sector. The London-listed company also had to shut down its Williamson mine, the source of the stones, as “certain key personnel” were questioned by the Tanzanian authorities looking into how diamonds are being valued. Shares in the company, which said it had not been made “formally aware” of the reason for the investigation, fell nearly 25% when the market opened, before recovering to se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Tanzania's Magufuli Threatens to Shut Mines If Firms Delay Tax Talks - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzanias-magufuli-threatens-shut-mines-firms-delay-tax-talks/3953644.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDBWC1CXxzNo1ymU7RuhCzEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 14:35:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzanias-magufuli-threatens-shut-mines-firms-delay-tax-talks/3953644.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania's Magufuli Threatens to Shut Mines If Firms Delay Tax Talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania's President John Magufuli has threatened to close down all gold mines in the country if mining companies delay talks with his government aimed at resolving allegations of tax evasion. The announcement by Magufuli, nicknamed "the Bulldozer" for his forceful leadership style, marks a further escalation of a dispute with foreign companies like Acacia Mining over export revenues. "We have asked them to come for talks ... they have agreed to come. But if they delay those talks, I will close down all the mines," Magufuli told a cheering crowd at a public rally in the northwestern town of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenya, Tanzania Aim to Reset Economic Partnership - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-tanzania-aim-to-reset-economic-partnership/3573132.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMv2KjFr1NoHntyJYI5WHaQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 17:15:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-tanzania-aim-to-reset-economic-partnership/3573132.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya, Tanzania Aim to Reset Economic Partnership&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania’s president is making his first state visit to Kenya since taking office last October, in a bid to improve relations strained by economic competition. Kenya is "quite important to Tanzania," President John Magufuli told reporters upon arriving Monday in the northern neighbor’s capital city, Nairobi, for a two-day visit. Magufuli cited data from the Tanzania Investment Center, which reports that 529 Kenyan companies have invested roughly $1.7 billion in Tanzania, creating employment for about 56,000 Tanzanians. Tanzania is the fastest-growing economy in East Africa, according to the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>35 killed in school minibus crash in Tanzania - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-accident-idUSKBN1820GE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGTBC5hPupYMbD0UBvW1ucIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 17:48:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-accident-idUSKBN1820GE" target="_blank"&gt;35 killed in school minibus crash in Tanzania&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Fumbuka Ng'wanakilala DAR ES SALAAM (Reuters) - Thirty-two schoolchildren, two teachers and a minibus driver where killed in Tanzania when their vehicle plunged into a roadside ravine in the northern tourist region of Arusha on Saturday, a senior police official said. "The accident happened when the bus was descending on a steep hill in rainy conditions," Arusha regional police commander Charles Mkumbo told Reuters by telephone. "We are still investigating the incident to determine if it was caused by a mechanical defect or human error on the part of the driver." The students killed in t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tanzania orders arrest of opposition MP for insulting president - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-politics-idUSKBN19P1JJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECOqpkANXT0JN_ejlTYrUscqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 12:38:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-politics-idUSKBN19P1JJ" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania orders arrest of opposition MP for insulting president&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Fumbuka Ngwanakilala DAR ES SALAAM (Reuters) - Tanzanian authorities ordered the detention of an opposition lawmaker on Tuesday for insulting President John Magufuli, days after the president ordered officials to take action against 'incitement'. The opposition has accused Magufuli, nicknamed "the Bulldozer" for his blunt leadership style, of presiding over an increasingly authoritarian government. Kinondoni District Commissioner Ali Hapi ordered police to detain Halima Mdee, a lawmaker from the main opposition CHADEMA party, in the commercial capital Dar es Salaam and keep her for 48 ho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tanzania's president warns newspapers over dissent - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-media-idUSKBN14X1OM</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOMfY4htFey5kmcXZEnP-6UqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:22:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-media-idUSKBN14X1OM" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania's president warns newspapers over dissent&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAR ES SALAAM (Reuters) - Tanzanian President John Magufuli said on Friday the "days were numbered" for newspapers deemed to incite dissent, comments that will add to opposition concern that his government is further narrowing the space for public criticism. Magufuli, nicknamed "the bulldozer" for pushing through his policies, has won some praise from Western donors for an anti-corruption drive and cutting wasteful public spending, but opponents accuse him of increasingly undermining democracy by curbing dissent and stifling free speech. The government declared opposition protest illegal la...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Mr. President, Cows Are Not Homophobic: Inside Tanzania’s LGBT Crackdown - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/mr-president-cows-are-not-homophobic-inside-tanzanias-lgbt-crackdown</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPqQbHi7p25zzae39iUyWC0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 03:20:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/mr-president-cows-are-not-homophobic-inside-tanzanias-lgbt-crackdown" target="_blank"&gt;Mr. President, Cows Are Not Homophobic: Inside Tanzania’s LGBT Crackdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cows “disapprove” of gay sex, insisted the Tanzanian President John Magufuli in a speech criticizing those who campaign for LGBT equality. “Those who teach such things do not like us, brothers. They brought us drugs and homosexual practices that even cows disapprove of,” AFP reported Magufuli as saying last Thursday. The American Veterinary Medical Association disagrees. “Cows are not homophobic. Cows don’t know if you’re gay and they don’t care,” an AVMA spokesman told The Daily Beast. (We are awaiting comment from the American Association of Bovine Practitioners.) Days after Magufuli’s sp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Acacia falls 17% as Tanzanian government demands $190bn in tax dispute - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/eb9266b8-697b-3c21-98ad-74e1dd1c88aa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBbr-fcEwq5rNq5eqdEf0nkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 07:47:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/eb9266b8-697b-3c21-98ad-74e1dd1c88aa" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia falls 17% as Tanzanian government demands $190bn in tax dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Acacia Mining touched a more than three-year low on Tuesday morning after its battle with Tanzanian authorities escalated as the government demanded Acacia pay almost $200bn worth of unpaid taxes and fines. Acacia has been locked in a dispute with Tanzania’s president John Magufuli since March, when he banned the export of unprocessed ores in an effort to boost the country’s domestic smelting industry. The government has since accused Acacia, one of Africa’s largest gold producers and one of Tanzania’s largest private employers, of illegally under-reporting the amount of metal in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tanzania Demands More from Mining Companies - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-demands-more-mining-companies/4027473.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGnuxEdxbKpnCMqf44FYIlUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-demands-more-mining-companies/4027473.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania Demands More from Mining Companies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania's government has been cracking down on irregularities in the mining sector, most recently confiscating diamonds worth $15 million from British company Petra Diamonds, accusing it of devaluing exports. And in July, the government demanded gold miner Acacia pay $190 billion in what it asserted were unpaid taxes, saying the company had underreported its exports. "They are stealing from us. It's strange, and some who were involved are our people," said Tanzanian President John Magufuli. Chatham House Africa program research assistant Rebekka Rumpel says that Tanzania's government previ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Acacia Mining ‘strongly’ rejects accusations of Tanzanian government - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ae2503f0-274d-38f8-8aef-d44263c6a015</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFYKWbjy1JLb2HQCxrj2g1gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 13:12:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ae2503f0-274d-38f8-8aef-d44263c6a015" target="_blank"&gt;Acacia Mining ‘strongly’ rejects accusations of Tanzanian government&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acacia Mining has “strongly” rejected accusations by the Tanzanian government that the London-listed company has under-declared its revenues and tax payments in the east African nation over a “number of years by tens of billions of dollars”. The company was responding to the publication of a second report into Acacia’s Tanzania operations by a presidential-appointed committee. The report has yet to be made public but Acacia said the committee has recommended “the payment of outstanding taxes and royalties, re-negotiation of large-scale mineral development agreements, government ownership in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tanzania spat hits cash balances at Acacia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/02742db9-197a-37e3-a8d7-80ab2a165110</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKlzihN5idpM9tQU4PiMN0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 06:46:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/02742db9-197a-37e3-a8d7-80ab2a165110" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania spat hits cash balances at Acacia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold miner Acacia reported a “significant” deterioration in cash position following a clash with the government of Tanzania, which has banned exports of unprocessed ore. Acacia said its cash balance had fallen to $176m from $318 million in the six months to June, as a result of being unable to realise $175m of revenue because of the ban and $51m tax bill. The president of Tanzania, John Magufuli, is trying to shake up the country’s mining industry and promote more domestic processing of raw materials. To the end he has banned exports of unprocessed ore and approved laws that enable the gove...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Petra Diamonds warns on Tanzania-induced hit to banking facilities - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/faa48413-10ba-323c-b3f1-bd02b557f76a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENFxl0LF6l8t-JSmwEiEXR8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 06:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/faa48413-10ba-323c-b3f1-bd02b557f76a" target="_blank"&gt;Petra Diamonds warns on Tanzania-induced hit to banking facilities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Petra Diamonds said restrictions on exports from Tanzania following the seizure of over $14m worth of diamonds in the East African country could hit its lending facilities. If it is unable to resume sales from its Williamson mine in Tanzania before the end of the year, the company may breach covenants on its loans, Petra said. “Petra will monitor the situation very closely and take decisive action if required to preserve shareholder value,” Petra said. Earlier this month the Tanzanian government seized a consignment of diamonds due for export and held a number of staff for questioning, as p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tanzania’s bulldozer president takes on London miner - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/28923506-5c29-11e7-9bc8-8055f264aa8b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFKvSB0GQg1XQiGG9EOdhS0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 14:19:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/28923506-5c29-11e7-9bc8-8055f264aa8b" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania’s bulldozer president takes on London miner&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzanian president John Magufuli was quick to live up to his nickname as “the bulldozer” after he won an election on promises of purging corruption and inefficiency. He fired thousands of officials deemed corrupt or underperforming. Salaries that had been paid to 13,369 ghost workers were halted and those involved punished. Contracts the president felt had been awarded improperly were cancelled. But Mr Magufuli, whom critics accuse of becoming increasingly authoritarian, is now facing an even sterner test: a multibillion-dollar tax dispute with the country’s largest foreign investor, Londo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tanzanian president discloses salary, one of lowest among African leaders - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-president/tanzanian-president-discloses-salary-one-of-lowest-among-african-leaders-idUSKCN1C91FU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOx7ghP3mr5-reG9ueHcT-MqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 11:13:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-president/tanzanian-president-discloses-salary-one-of-lowest-among-african-leaders-idUSKCN1C91FU" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzanian president discloses salary, one of lowest among African leaders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Fumbuka Ng'wanakilala DAR ES SALAAM (Reuters) - Tanzanian President John Magufuli has revealed he earns a salary of 9 million Tanzanian shillings ($4,000) per month, making him one of the lowest paid African leaders as he pursues a much-criticized policy of deep public spending cuts. In a speech to local officials in the capital on Tuesday he also said his government had slashed salaries of executives at state-owned companies at 15 million Tanzanian shillings ($6,700) a month -- more than his own. "They can leave if they don't want it," he said. He said abuse of public funds was "rampant...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Burundian President Tells Refugees to Come Home - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/burundian-president-tells-refugees-to-come-home/3954138.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPjklShOqc4fzavJ_SMmrA4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 19:50:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/burundian-president-tells-refugees-to-come-home/3954138.html" target="_blank"&gt;Burundian President Tells Refugees to Come Home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burundi's President Pierre Nkurunziza has invited people who fled the country during violent political unrest two years ago to return home. Nkurunziza extended the invitation Thursday during a visit to Tanzania, his first trip outside Burundi since a coup attempt on May 13, 2015. The U.N. refugee agency says Tanzania currently hosts more than 240,000 Burundians, most of them living in camps near the two countries' shared border. Nkurunziza met with Tanzanian President John Magufuli in the Ngara district. The two men addressed a large crowd, in which Nkurunziza, speaking Kiswahili, delivered...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Denmark, citing human rights, withholds some aid to Tanzania - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/7635d615d73346e3ad37e5c0608bb086</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELDxKRXThGBbdD9zgbhXRBsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 16:00:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/7635d615d73346e3ad37e5c0608bb086" target="_blank"&gt;Denmark, citing human rights, withholds some aid to Tanzania&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KAMPALA, Uganda (AP) — Denmark is cutting about $10 million in aid to the government of Tanzania over what it called "negative developments" in human rights in the East African country. Ulla Tornaes, Denmark's minister for development cooperation, said on Twitter she is "deeply concerned" by developments such as a Tanzanian official's "completely unacceptable homophobic statements." Tanzania is increasingly under the spotlight over its human rights record. Denmark is one of the largest donors to Tanzania, whose government depends substantially on foreign benefactors to run many of its progr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Tanzania loses Denmark aid over rights concerns after World Bank scraps loan - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-denmark-aid-idUSKCN1NK0PF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPAoxWDhdKVPr29Wyv2-SFQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 15:19:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-denmark-aid-idUSKCN1NK0PF" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania loses Denmark aid over rights concerns after World Bank scraps loan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denmark, Tanzania's second-biggest donor, said it would withhold $10 million worth of aid money due to concerns over human rights abuses and what it called unacceptable homophobic comments made by a government official. The decision came on the same day that the World Bank said it had scrapped a plan to loan Tanzania $300 million after the country reaffirmed its policy of banning pregnant girls from school and made it a crime to question official statistics. In the last few weeks, President John Magufuli's government has been criticized by rights groups and foreign governments for what they...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tanzania loses $300 million World Bank loan amid crackdown concerns - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/13/africa/tanzania-world-bank-loan-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJK95FjzT72vcnGQq03cSDEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 17:19:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/13/africa/tanzania-world-bank-loan-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania loses $300 million World Bank loan amid crackdown concerns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Bank has pulled a planned $300 million educational loan to Tanzania amid concerns about the country's policy of banning pregnant girls from going to school. The $300 million program was meant to help Tanzania's Ministry of Education improve access to quality secondary education. It was scheduled to be approved by the bank's management late last month, but a source within the bank told CNN the program was instead withdrawn and will not be going forward. Tanzania's policy of expelling pregnant girls from schools was one of the reasons for the loan to be withdrawn, the source said. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US Concerned by Rising Attacks on Human Rights in Tanzania - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-concerned-by-rising-attacks-on-human-rights-in-tanzania/4653684.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwKtqzMLOrSbeYBjEGEkmAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 14:54:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-concerned-by-rising-attacks-on-human-rights-in-tanzania/4653684.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Concerned by Rising Attacks on Human Rights in Tanzania&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States has spoken out against Tanzanian moves to cut back human rights and civil liberties, including arrests and harassment of "marginalized" people such as homosexuals. President John Magufuli's government has been criticized by opposition politicians and international rights groups for what they say is growing authoritarianism and intolerance of dissent. The government rejects the criticism. "We are troubled by the continued arrests and harassment of marginalized persons, including lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender people and others who seek to exercise their rights to fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Are anti-gay witch hunts really protecting 'African values'? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/anti-gay-witch-hunts-protecting-african-values-181106105153386.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKkHWF0NBRqrWLSIQWe0HF0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 10:10:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/anti-gay-witch-hunts-protecting-african-values-181106105153386.html" target="_blank"&gt;Are anti-gay witch hunts really protecting 'African values'?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On October 29, governor of Tanzania's largest city Dar-es-Salaam, Paul Makonda, announced that he formed an anti-gay unit to hunt down "suspected" homosexuals. Makonda is an ardent Christian and close ally of Tanzanian President John Magufuli, a traditionalist who believes "even cows disapprove of" homosexuality. The Tanzanian government distanced itself from Makonda's latest anti-gay witch-hunt a full five days after it made headlines in local media, by stating that his planned crackdown "is not part of official policy". However, the government's belated attempt to denounce Makonda's actio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Tanzania disowns gay witch-hunt plan by city administrator - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/63764b9c-e1cc-11e8-a6e5-792428919cee</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDp_zGb7OP6DUOKeVBU4ER0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 15:52:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/63764b9c-e1cc-11e8-a6e5-792428919cee" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania disowns gay witch-hunt plan by city administrator&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Campaigners have given a cautious welcome to comments from Tanzania’s government that disown a plan by the administrator of the country’s biggest city to hunt down and punish members of the gay community. The regional commissioner for Dar es Salaam, Paul Makonda, last week called on Tanzanians to report gay people living in the city, saying that a specially convened team would start rounding up gays and lesbians from Monday. A few days later — following an international outcry — the foreign affairs ministry issued a statement “to inform the public that those sentiments are individual and do...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tanzania frees two members of CPJ journalists' advocacy group - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-rights/tanzania-frees-two-members-of-cpj-journalists-advocacy-group-idUSKCN1ND1FF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPTve95fD2RDnXax00tWJYsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 14:57:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tanzania-rights/tanzania-frees-two-members-of-cpj-journalists-advocacy-group-idUSKCN1ND1FF" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania frees two members of CPJ journalists' advocacy group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzania released two staff members of the New York-based Committee to Protect Journalists (CPJ) on Thursday, a day after they were detained and their passports seized, the South African Foreign Ministry said. Tanzanian Immigration Department spokesman Ali Mtanda said Angela Quintal and Muthoki Mumo were arrested for violating the terms of their visas by holding meetings with local journalists. "They were supposed to get a separate permit for that," he said. CPJ accused the authorities of sending a false tweet from Quintal's personal account saying that they had been released, and making se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tanzania Frees Detained CPJ Journalists - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-frees-detained-cpj-journalists-brdg/4650025.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDgGR1HqisGdOIUM--pKluwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 15:35:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/tanzania-frees-detained-cpj-journalists-brdg/4650025.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania Frees Detained CPJ Journalists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two staff members of the New York-based Committee to Protect Journalists were freed Thursday, a day after Tanzanian immigration authorities took the women from their Dar es Salaam hotel and held them at an unknown location. CPJ, in a statement on its website, welcomed the release of colleagues Angela Quintal and Muthoki Mumo, Africa program coordinator and representative, respectively. The organization said the women had safely left the country, and it urged Tanzanian authorities “to halt their ongoing crackdown against a free press.” On Twitter, CPJ had expressed fears for the safety of th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>EU recalls ambassador in protest at Tanzania's threat to 'hunt down homosexuals' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/eu-recalls-ambassador-protest-tanzanias-threat-hunt-homosexuals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM4_W5jzlv_q45ObFIjligoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 17:05:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/eu-recalls-ambassador-protest-tanzanias-threat-hunt-homosexuals/" target="_blank"&gt;EU recalls ambassador in protest at Tanzania's threat to 'hunt down homosexuals'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Union recalled its ambassador to Tanzania on Monday as police plans to hunt down and jail homosexuals in the country’s largest city prompted international outrage. A 17-member committee charged with identifying and locating gay men in Dar es Salaam is due to begin work this week after it began collecting names of possible homosexuals submitted by members of the general public. The city’s regional commissioner, Paul Makonda, said he had identified more than 200 suspects after encouraging residents to inform on their neighbours and trawl through their friends’ social media accoun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>A tainted imperial legacy that fuels the oppression of gay people in Africa - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/04/tainted-imperial-legacy-that-fuels-oppression-of-gay-people-in-africa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELFwdNEqDIGPjFAa7315-wgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 06:29:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/04/tainted-imperial-legacy-that-fuels-oppression-of-gay-people-in-africa" target="_blank"&gt;A tainted imperial legacy that fuels the oppression of gay people in Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Tanzania, teenage girls who become pregnant are not allowed back in school; female MPs are forbidden from wearing fake eyelashes and nails; now, a senior government official has called on the public to report gay people so that they can be punished. This infantilisation of women and homophobia is all part of President John Magufuli’s “morality crusade”. When he was elected in 2015, he was seen as a decisive figure determined to run a frugal government, stamp out corruption and deliver better services in the east African country. However, in a flash, he turned from cracking down on corrup...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Queer Tanzanians Remain Fearful Despite Government Denouncing LGBTQ Crackdown - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/lgbtq-tanzania-crackdown_us_5be1f569e4b0769d24c601cc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBbdnGGlGu2COgPABi2HusqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 20:18:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/lgbtq-tanzania-crackdown_us_5be1f569e4b0769d24c601cc" target="_blank"&gt;Queer Tanzanians Remain Fearful Despite Government Denouncing LGBTQ Crackdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI, Nov 5 (Thomson Reuters Foundation) - LGBT+ people in Tanzania on Monday welcomed a move by the government distancing itself from a planned crackdown on sexual minorities in the city of Dar es Salaam, but said it did not go far enough - with many still fearful of attack or arrest. Tanzania’s foreign ministry said on Sunday a plan by the city’s administrative chief Paul Makonda to set up a committee to identify and arrest homosexual people did not represent the national government’s position. But LGBT+ people in the port city told the Thomson Reuters Foundation the government was lat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Tanzania's LGBT community 'fearing for their lives' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/05/africa/tanzania-crackdown-on-gays-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP4OUrP3S1F9qSUc76S8wF0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 16:11:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/05/africa/tanzania-crackdown-on-gays-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania's LGBT community 'fearing for their lives'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Members of Tanzania's LGBT community are fearing for their lives, hiding in their homes and even fleeing the country after threats from a powerful politician to round up gay Tanzanians, activists said. The announcement from the regional governor of Tanzania's largest city, Dar es Salaam, has also led to a new travel warning by the US State Department warning US citizens to remove any material on social media that could "run afoul" of Tanzania's anti-homosexuality laws. "I have closed my office today and we will not be operating for a while," said James Wandera Ouma, one of the few activists...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Hundreds in hiding as Tanzania launches anti-gay crackdown - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/05/tanzania-gay-people-in-hiding-lgbt-activists-crackdown</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJajRID1hEzP8b-vFS7_-WkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 17:55:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/05/tanzania-gay-people-in-hiding-lgbt-activists-crackdown" target="_blank"&gt;Hundreds in hiding as Tanzania launches anti-gay crackdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of LGBT activists in Tanzania have gone into hiding after a senior official announced a taskforce aiming to identify and punish gay people in Dar es Salaam. Paul Makonda, the city’s administrative head, said he had put together a team of officials and police that would target gay people, who could face lengthy prison sentences, in an intensification of anti-LGBT discrimination. In an interview posted on YouTube, Makonda called for Tanzanians to report gay people and told a news conference he had already received more than 5,700 messages from the public, including more than 100 name...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Give me their names': Tanzanian governor launches anti-gay squad - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-01/tanzanian-governor-launches-anti-gay-squad/10454722</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKwMmi1UjqOIuWAL0vXPrMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 02:24:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-01/tanzanian-governor-launches-anti-gay-squad/10454722" target="_blank"&gt;'Give me their names': Tanzanian governor launches anti-gay squad&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tanzanian authorities are set to track down and arrest gay people — who face at least 30 years in prison — after the announcement of an anti-gay surveillance squad. Key points - Tanzanian law prohibits sex between men, with minimum 30-year jail penalty (no mention of women) - 17-person squad to scour social media for information on same-sex couples - Forced anal examinations still practised Paul Makonda, governor of the country's largest city Dar es Salaam, issued the directive in a news conference delivered on Monday. The 17-member squad will seek out same-sex couples through social media,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Tanzania announces 'surveillance squad' to hunt down homosexuals - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/01/tanzania-announces-surveillance-squad-hunt-homosexuals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP9TJ0EwkXf_NaIQwGNJFLsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 16:11:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/01/tanzania-announces-surveillance-squad-hunt-homosexuals/" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania announces 'surveillance squad' to hunt down homosexuals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Residents in Tanzania’s biggest city have been urged to inform on their gay neighbours and friends ahead of a police operation to hunt down and jail homosexuals. A 17-member committee appointed by Paul Makonda, Dar es Salaam’s powerful regional commissioner, will attempt to identify all gay men living in the coastal city after it first convenes next Monday. Mr Makonda, a close ally of Tanzania’s president, John Magufuli, said that a list of 200 suspects had already been drawn up thanks to public tip offs and a trawl through Tanzanians’ social media accounts. “I have information about the pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>US warns its citizens in Tanzania over anti-gay crackdown - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/04/us-warns-citizens-tanzania-anti-gay-crackdown</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPlPFQmXpnIATWS-kPv-F6UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 17:36:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/04/us-warns-citizens-tanzania-anti-gay-crackdown" target="_blank"&gt;US warns its citizens in Tanzania over anti-gay crackdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US has warned its citizens in Tanzania to be cautious after the commercial capital Dar es Salaam announced a crackdown on homosexuality, a criminal offence in the country. Related: Thousands ‘living in fear’ after Tanzania calls on public to report gay people In an alert on its website late on Saturday, the US embassy in Tanzania advised Americans to review their social media profiles and internet footprints. “Remove or protect images and language that may run afoul of Tanzanian laws regarding homosexual practices and explicit sexual activity,” it said. The alert said any US citizen who...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Gay Witch-Hunt Sparks Fear, Panic in Tanzania's LGBT+ Community - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/gay-witch-hunt-sparks-fear-panic-in-tanzania-lgbt/4639992.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1wVFbjAzKrOo0L0ZCLnDQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 14:27:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/gay-witch-hunt-sparks-fear-panic-in-tanzania-lgbt/4639992.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gay Witch-Hunt Sparks Fear, Panic in Tanzania's LGBT+ Community&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gay and transgender people in Tanzania have gone into hiding fearing for their lives after a senior government official called on the public to report suspected homosexuals so that they could be arrested beginning Monday. Paul Makonda, regional commissioner for Tanzania's main city of Dar es Salaam, announced the crackdown Monday. He said a team would be set up to identify and arrest the "many homosexuals," who could face up to 30 years in jail. Makonda's announcement has sparked panic and fear among thousands of LGBT+ people in the east African nation. Some said they were too scared to go ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>