<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Minister of Police - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV3Wm1Kck9XNFNBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:04:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Police Minister reveals plans for Anti-Gang Unit in EC - EWN</title><link>https://ewn.co.za/2018/12/04/bheki-cele-reveals-plans-for-anti-gang-unit-in-ec</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVAhqIQskvDm7odQ72L6oMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowgdKhCTCd8pYCMPbf2QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 08:03:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://ewn.co.za/2018/12/04/bheki-cele-reveals-plans-for-anti-gang-unit-in-ec" target="_blank"&gt;Police Minister reveals plans for Anti-Gang Unit in EC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;EWN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Police Minister and National Police Commissioner Khehla Sitole visited the northern areas of Port Elizabeth on Monday to engage with community policing ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://ewn.co.za">EWN</source></item><item><title>Anti-gang unit off to a flying start, says delighted Cele - TimesLIVE</title><link>https://www.timeslive.co.za/news/south-africa/2018-11-29-anti-gang-unit--off-to-a-flying-start-says-delighted-cele/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMic2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRpbWVzbGl2ZS5jby56YS9uZXdzL3NvdXRoLWFmcmljYS8yMDE4LTExLTI5LWFudGktZ2FuZy11bml0LS1vZmYtdG8tYS1mbHlpbmctc3RhcnQtc2F5cy1kZWxpZ2h0ZWQtY2VsZS_SAcMBaHR0cHM6Ly93d3ctdGltZXNsaXZlLWNvLXphLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3Mvd3d3LnRpbWVzbGl2ZS5jby56YS9hbXAvbmV3cy9zb3V0aC1hZnJpY2EvMjAxOC0xMS0yOS1hbnRpLWdhbmctdW5pdC0tb2ZmLXRvLWEtZmx5aW5nLXN0YXJ0LXNheXMtZGVsaWdodGVkLWNlbGUvP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.timeslive.co.za/news/south-africa/2018-11-29-anti-gang-unit--off-to-a-flying-start-says-delighted-cele/" target="_blank"&gt;Anti-gang unit off to a flying start, says delighted Cele&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TimesLIVE&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police Minister Bheki Cele is ecstatic over the “successes” of the newly launched anti-gang unit.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.timeslive.co.za">TimesLIVE</source></item><item><title>Police Minister Cele vows to reduce gang-related murders in WC - EWN</title><link>https://ewn.co.za/2018/11/30/operation-thunder-cracks-down-on-crime-in-the-cape</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOWkgC_p6CVTRuwvj5FJHlAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowgdKhCTCd8pYCMO3KkQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 06:15:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://ewn.co.za/2018/11/30/operation-thunder-cracks-down-on-crime-in-the-cape" target="_blank"&gt;Police Minister Cele vows to reduce gang-related murders in WC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;EWN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over 800 gang-related murders occurred in the Western Cape in the past year.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://ewn.co.za">EWN</source></item><item><title>'We should have responded better': Bheki Cele on Global concert fiasco - DispatchLIVE</title><link>https://www.dispatchlive.co.za/news/2018-12-05-we-should-have-responded-better-bheki-cele-on-global-concert-fiasco/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMic2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRpc3BhdGNobGl2ZS5jby56YS9uZXdzLzIwMTgtMTItMDUtd2Utc2hvdWxkLWhhdmUtcmVzcG9uZGVkLWJldHRlci1iaGVraS1jZWxlLW9uLWdsb2JhbC1jb25jZXJ0LWZpYXNjby_SAcYBaHR0cHM6Ly93d3ctZGlzcGF0Y2hsaXZlLWNvLXphLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3Mvd3d3LmRpc3BhdGNobGl2ZS5jby56YS9hbXAvbmV3cy8yMDE4LTEyLTA1LXdlLXNob3VsZC1oYXZlLXJlc3BvbmRlZC1iZXR0ZXItYmhla2ktY2VsZS1vbi1nbG9iYWwtY29uY2VydC1maWFzY28vP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:41:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.dispatchlive.co.za/news/2018-12-05-we-should-have-responded-better-bheki-cele-on-global-concert-fiasco/" target="_blank"&gt;'We should have responded better': Bheki Cele on Global concert fiasco&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;DispatchLIVE&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police minister Bheki Cele has admitted that the South African Police *Service* (SAPS) should have responded "better" to assist Global Citizen concert-goers ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.dispatchlive.co.za">DispatchLIVE</source></item><item><title>South Africa minister to appeal court order against head of elite police unit: report - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-police-idUSKBN16R0CW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBi6zGjK5VZCP5WXne5yWi8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 06:26:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-police-idUSKBN16R0CW" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa minister to appeal court order against head of elite police unit: report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (Reuters) - South Africa's police minister will fight a court order to remove the head of an elite police investigation unit, popularly known as the Hawks, after the court ruled his appointment unlawful, media said on Monday. Berning Ntlemeza was appointed in 2015 to lead the powerful Directorate of Priority Crime Investigation, but two domestic non-government bodies, Freedom Under Law and the Helen Suzman Foundation, applied to the High Court to have Ntlemeza removed on the grounds that he was unfit for the office. Sandile Ngidi, a spokesman for Police Minister Nathi Nhleko, s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Dutch tourist group cuts South Africa visit short after armed bus robbery - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-netherlands-crime/dutch-tourist-group-cuts-south-africa-visit-short-after-armed-bus-robbery-idUSKCN1C128O</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM4Cz5DNkYQoKR_Ghh8WG2EqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 16:03:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-netherlands-crime/dutch-tourist-group-cuts-south-africa-visit-short-after-armed-bus-robbery-idUSKCN1C128O" target="_blank"&gt;Dutch tourist group cuts South Africa visit short after armed bus robbery&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Ed Stoddard JOHANNESBURG (Reuters) - A group of 36 Dutch tourists were flying out of South Africa on Tuesday after they were robbed at gunpoint on Sunday in a brazen heist while traveling from Johannesburg's main international airport to their hotel, officials said. The incident is an embarrassment for South Africa, a country keen to promote itself as a tourist destination but scarred by violent crime. Tourism accounts for 3 percent of GDP and is seen as a bright spot in an otherwise moribund economy. Journalists saw the group pull out of the hotel in a bus under police escort after they...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>South African minister resigns amid assault probe - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-violence-idUSKCN1AZ0B1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN7SyZh11l6YC37kVif0bxIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 09:36:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-violence-idUSKCN1AZ0B1" target="_blank"&gt;South African minister resigns amid assault probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (Reuters) - A South African deputy minister who is being investigated by police for allegedly assaulting a woman in a nightclub has resigned, the president's office said on Saturday. Footage apparently showing deputy higher education minister Mduduzi Manana assaulting a woman earlier this month sparked outrage from civil society and opposition parties and prompted Manana to offer a public apology. "President Jacob Zuma has received and accepted the resignation of the Deputy Minister of Higher Education and Training, Mr Mduduzi Manana," the presidency said in a statement. The po...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>South Africa: murders surge by more than 7% in a year - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/11/south-africa-murders-surge-by-more-than-7-percent-in-a-year</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECRdZHbwuq7dmyWDdf2k0w8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:55:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/11/south-africa-murders-surge-by-more-than-7-percent-in-a-year" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa: murders surge by more than 7% in a year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Murders in South Africa have surged by more than 7% in the last year, with more than 20,000 people killed in 12 months, new official statistics have shown. The country has long struggled to with violent crime. The new figures, released on Tuesday, showed that 57 people were murdered daily over a 12-month period between April 2017 and March 2018. “It borders close to [a] war zone while there is a peace,” said Bheki Cele, the police minister. Related: Murders of farmers in South Africa at 20-year low, research shows He added: “We haven’t reached a state of lawlessness in South Africa and we w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Six People Killed in Overnight Attack on South African Police Station - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-police-attack/4263708.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMyBDL1hoMuoxKUk2rOBfqkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 10:21:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-police-attack/4263708.html" target="_blank"&gt;Six People Killed in Overnight Attack on South African Police Station&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five South African police officers and an off-duty soldier were killed Wednesday during an attack on a rural police station. A police spokesman says an armed gang stormed the outpost in the southern village of Engcobo shortly after midnight local time and killed three of the officers. They stole a cache of weapons and abducted two other police officers as they escaped in a police van. The soldier was shot and killed as the gang fled. The bodies of the two abducted officers were later discovered dumped on the side of a road. Police Minister Fikile Mbalula called the attack "a national traged...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>