<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Manis - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNR1JvTldvU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:53:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Malaysia torches 2.8 tonnes of African pangolin scales - News24</title><link>https://www.news24.com/Green/News/malaysia-torches-28-tonnes-of-african-pangolin-scales-20181206</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5ld3MyNC5jb20vR3JlZW4vTmV3cy9tYWxheXNpYS10b3JjaGVzLTI4LXRvbm5lcy1vZi1hZnJpY2FuLXBhbmdvbGluLXNjYWxlcy0yMDE4MTIwNtIBAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:51:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.news24.com/Green/News/malaysia-torches-28-tonnes-of-african-pangolin-scales-20181206" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia torches 2.8 tonnes of African pangolin scales&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;News24&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia torched nearly three tonnes of seized scales of endangered pangolins worth $9m in a bid to deter illegal wildlife trafficking from Africa.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.news24.com">News24</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/ADSSNgbRq5XnFQ_dI3djH8clSLmAs1ciG-eTYlmO86I02sD0_pvVZKnJRUFyhBmY2lGxtxmgLvXXC_ogEQ8enjfBUIiMPC7FoRAp81dikd2AUIiC5-e3JepZz0xADBQq2bCK4hQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Malaysia torches African pangolin scales worth $9m - EWN</title><link>https://ewn.co.za/2018/12/06/malaysia-torches-african-pangolin-scales-worth-usd9m</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIvwMjOGjmwzg0fTqcbOmjYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowgdKhCTCd8pYCMO3KkQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:21:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://ewn.co.za/2018/12/06/malaysia-torches-african-pangolin-scales-worth-usd9m" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia torches African pangolin scales worth $9m&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;EWN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;They're trying to stop trafficking in the species whose scales are highly prized in Chinese medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpFbWFhbWpZQU1FU043N0NUc0RBb1BLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://ewn.co.za">EWN</source></item><item><title>Hunters bludgeon endangered pangolin to death for Asian medicine, undercover footage reveals - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/pangolin-endangered-killed-hunted-video-asian-china-medicine-assam-india-a8663901.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGzfX2QO4X1MHoRDLNzhERsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 18:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/pangolin-endangered-killed-hunted-video-asian-china-medicine-assam-india-a8663901.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hunters bludgeon endangered pangolin to death for Asian medicine, undercover footage reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Undercover footage has revealed hunters tracking down a terrified pangolin and bludgeoning it to death to be sold for superstitious Asian “medicine” practices. Wildlife crime investigators filmed the video to expose how the world’s most-trafficked mammal is being driven to extinction by ruthless black-market operators who exploit both local communities and beliefs in fake medical treatments. Secretly captured by an undercover researcher on their mobile phone in India, the clip shows the pangolin clinging for life in a hollowed-out tree as its tail is tugged. The hunters use axes to cut the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>For some Indian farmers, pangolin poaching is too lucrative to resist - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/asia/india-pangolin-hunters-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAOXg5sGzjsfH9YvrYlA2SkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:26:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/asia/india-pangolin-hunters-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;For some Indian farmers, pangolin poaching is too lucrative to resist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An increasing demand for the scales and meat of the endangered pangolin in China and Vietnam is pushing impoverished farmers in India's north-east into the illegal trade, a new report has found. Pangolins are often recognized as the world's most highly-trafficked mammal and their body parts can fetch large sums of money -- the poorest hunters in India's Assam state can earn a full year's salary for a single pangolin, researchers from World Animal Protection (WAP) and the University of Oxford said Monday, following a two-year investigation. Of 141 people interviewed in 31 villages over a per...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Literal Tons Of The World's Most Trafficked Mammal Seized In China - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pangolin-scales-china_us_5863fb79e4b0de3a08f6d4b4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECf0d9RLK9sLCEo_7teSsOEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 22:30:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pangolin-scales-china_us_5863fb79e4b0de3a08f6d4b4" target="_blank"&gt;Literal Tons Of The World's Most Trafficked Mammal Seized In China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese authorities seized more than 3 tons of animal parts taken from the bodies of dead pangolins earlier this month in one of the country’s largest smuggling busts involving the world’s most trafficked mammal. Customs officials found 101 bags of pangolin scales hidden in a shipment of timber during a routine inspection in Shanghai, according to reports from local media. Estimates say the scales came from 5,000 to 7,500 different animals and could have had a street value of more than $2 million. Pangolins have quickly become a striking face in the fight against wildlife crime, with almost...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>10 amazing creatures hiding in Brunei's rainforest - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2016/08/23/travel/gallery/brunei-amazing-wildlife/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFpxdw-rH1tPeO8FlStbZaQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 23:08:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2016/08/23/travel/gallery/brunei-amazing-wildlife/" target="_blank"&gt;10 amazing creatures hiding in Brunei's rainforest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the northeast corner of Borneo, an island off the southeast coast of Asia, lies the tiny kingdom of Brunei. It may be a small country, with a population of just over 400,000, but there's an excellent reason for travelers to make a stop there: its rainforests are home to some of the animal kingdom's rarest creatures, many of which can only be found in the region. A wonder to behold, their scarcity also means they're not always easy to find. Some of Brunei's wildlife is so precious that conservationists take care not to share detailed locations of animal sightings or typical habitats such ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Chinese customs officials seize 3 tonnes of endangered pangolin scales in 'biggest ever' bust - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/china-pangolin-scales-smuggling-biggest-bust-endangered-species-chinese-medicine-africa-customs-a7501681.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH5THzi-Y155fkHCI6H7Z2EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 10:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/china-pangolin-scales-smuggling-biggest-bust-endangered-species-chinese-medicine-africa-customs-a7501681.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese customs officials seize 3 tonnes of endangered pangolin scales in 'biggest ever' bust&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese customs officials have seized almost three tonnes of pangolin scales being smuggled through Shanghai. Three people were arrested after the huge 2.9-tonne shipment, said to be the largest quantity ever impounded, was uncovered in a container that was supposed to be carrying timber from Africa. Xinhua news agency reported that such a quantity of scales meant that between 5,000 and 7,500 of the critically endangered animals had been killed by traffickers. The 10 winners of Wildlife Photographer of the Year 2016 - 10 show all The 10 winners of Wildlife Photographer of the Year 2016 - 1/...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Scale of pangolin slaughter revealed – millions hunted in central Africa alone - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/jul/20/scale-of-pangolin-slaughter-revealed-millions-hunted-in-central-africa-alone</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF1lPah4TRts_88soktbT38qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 11:00:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/jul/20/scale-of-pangolin-slaughter-revealed-millions-hunted-in-central-africa-alone" target="_blank"&gt;Scale of pangolin slaughter revealed – millions hunted in central Africa alone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The true scale of the slaughter of pangolins in Africa has been revealed by new research showing that millions of the scaly mammals are being hunted and killed. Pangolins were already known to be the world’s most trafficked wild mammal, with at least a million being traded in the last decade to supply the demand for its meat and scales in Asian markets. Populations of Asian pangolins have been decimated, leaving the creatures highly endangered and sharply shifting the focus of exploitation to Africa’s four species. Pangolins are secretive, nocturnal and some species live in trees, making th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How much do you know about pangolins, the world's most trafficked mammal? - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/11/much-do-know-pangolins-worlds-trafficked-animal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMp_o4yOOsASgR3LFwCZgggqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 10:01:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/11/much-do-know-pangolins-worlds-trafficked-animal/" target="_blank"&gt;How much do you know about pangolins, the world's most trafficked mammal?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pangolins are unique and beautiful; unusually, they're covered head to tail in dragon-like scales. They are featured in the Google Doodle, as the tech giant has joined up with WWF to raise awareness about these endangered creatures. They are threatened by illegal poaching, and according to the conservation charity, over a million pangolins have been taken from the wild in the the past decade to feed demand in China and Vietnam. How much do you know about them? Test your knowledge in our quiz below.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Three tonnes of pangolin scales seized at Thai airport - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/02/three-tonnes-pangolin-scales-seized-thai-airport/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPkEjF4c9_wN3O5L3P1bTvkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 20:17:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/02/three-tonnes-pangolin-scales-seized-thai-airport/" target="_blank"&gt;Three tonnes of pangolin scales seized at Thai airport&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thai authorities on Thursday displayed to journalists nearly 3 tonnes of scales from pangolins, the world's most poached animal, seized in anti-smuggling operations since December. The scales, worth more than $800,000, were shipped from Africa and confiscated by police, customs and wildlife officials at Bangkok's Suvarnabhumi Airport. Thai customs chief Kulit Sombatsiri told reporters that an estimated 6,000 pangolins were killed to produce almost 3 tonnes of scales, which are used in traditional medicines in Asia. The pangolin is the world's most poached animal A ban on global trade of pan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>This Is How A Species Goes Extinct - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pangolins-extinction_us_5812e332e4b064e1b4b190bd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXq-LSejqaFLQClye4_2O0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 08:05:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pangolins-extinction_us_5812e332e4b064e1b4b190bd" target="_blank"&gt;This Is How A Species Goes Extinct&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Editor’s note: The images below may be upsetting to some readers. When photographer Paul Hilton arrived at a clearing in Sumatra, Indonesia, last year, there was just a backhoe, a couple of law enforcement officials and an open pit about to be set on fire ― the final act of a major wildlife crime bust. The day before, Hilton had been in a warehouse in the city of Medan when police raided the building on a tip that a seafood trading company was trafficking in smuggled creatures hunted for their valuable body parts. He photographed the raid and the lucky critters that made it out alive. Thoug...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Chinese Officials Investigated For Allegedly Serving Endangered Pangolin At Banquet - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pangolin-banquet-china-investigation_us_589d517be4b03df370d5035c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA86qGkTSK90DORjyZrRY9sqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:04:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pangolin-banquet-china-investigation_us_589d517be4b03df370d5035c" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese Officials Investigated For Allegedly Serving Endangered Pangolin At Banquet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese authorities have launched an investigation into whether government officials dined on pangolin, the world’s most trafficked mammal, at a banquet in Guangxi province in 2015. The investigation was prompted by a resurgence of social media interest in a series of photographs of the meal, first published in 2015. The photos were posted by Weibo user Ah_cal, who claimed the banquet had been hosted by Chinese government officials. One of the dishes shown was a pot of meat, which Ah_cal described as “cooked pangolin.” The pangolin meat was “delicious,” the Weibo user wrote in a caption, no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Malaysian authorities seize 700kg of pangolin scales smuggled from Africa - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/05/08/malaysian-authorities-seize-700kg-pangolin-scales-smuggled-africa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKxjLXCjpL7VT6GZXeKH_gIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 11:04:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/05/08/malaysian-authorities-seize-700kg-pangolin-scales-smuggled-africa/" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysian authorities seize 700kg of pangolin scales smuggled from Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian authorities said Monday they have seized pangolin scales worth 9.2 million ringgit (£1.6 million) and believed to have been smuggled from Africa. Deputy customs director Paddy Abdul Halim says officers made two seizures last week at the Kuala Lumpur airport cargo warehouse based on a tip. On May 2, officers seized eight bags of pangolin scales weighing 408 kilograms that were flown from Ghana and transited in Dubai before arriving at the Kuala Lumpur airport on May 1. A pangolin is seen out of its cage after being confiscated by the Department of Wildlife and Natural Parks in Kual...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Chinese officials seize record number of pangolin scales - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2016/12/29/asia/pangolin-seizure/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJlhwbFbfdBFN8cO4W6a7hoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 10:25:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2016/12/29/asia/pangolin-seizure/" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese officials seize record number of pangolin scales&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pangolin, a scaly anteater who sleeps by day and eats insects by night, is more popular than ever in China. But that very demand -- often wanted for illegal reasons, like the purchase of its meat or scales -- has driven the mammal toward extinction. The illegal trade of pangolins hit a new milestone this month when Shanghai customs officials seized more than 3 tons of pangolin scales --the largest pangolin seizure in China's history, officials said. Three suspects were captured. On December 10, Shanghai customs officials inspected a container that arrived from Africa filled with large l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Gentle, Adorable Pangolins Are Critically Endangered By Misguided Medical Beliefs - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/stevensalzberg/2017/02/13/gentle-adorable-pangolins-are-critically-endangered-by-misguided-medical-beliefs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFx70RDhZTsm5JATP-lkXWMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/stevensalzberg/2017/02/13/gentle-adorable-pangolins-are-critically-endangered-by-misguided-medical-beliefs/" target="_blank"&gt;Gentle, Adorable Pangolins Are Critically Endangered By Misguided Medical Beliefs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This picture taken on October 22, 2016 shows Lam Kim Hai, 24, a vet of Save Vietnam Wildlife (SVW), holding an injured pangolin in Cuc Phuong National Park.The reclusive pangolin has become the most trafficked mammal on earth due to soaring demand in Asia for their scales for traditional medicine and their flesh, considered a delicacy. (Photo credit: HOANG DINH NAM/AFP/Getty Images) Pangolins, timid little anteaters that are covered with scales, are being hunted to extinction. Why? Because some humans think their scales can be used as medicine. Pangolin scales are made of keratin, the same ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Cameroon Seizes 670 kg of Pangolin Bound for Malaysia - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/cameroon-seizes-670kg-of-pangolin-bound-for-malaysia/3645268.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM3Q7RrQbdfuQk88M1cfEyEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 16:37:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/cameroon-seizes-670kg-of-pangolin-bound-for-malaysia/3645268.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cameroon Seizes 670 kg of Pangolin Bound for Malaysia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cameroon says it has intercepted more than 670 kilograms of African pangolin that authorities say were being smuggled from the Central African country to Malaysia. The pangolin is the world’s most trafficked mammal, and conservationist groups are calling for severe sanctions on the three traffickers who have been arrested. Cameroon customs lieutenant, Wara Wara Francois Noel, of the Yaounde-Nsimalen international airport told VOA the recovered pangolin scales were found in several meat packets. He said the three smugglers had bribed their way into the airport, but authorities were mobiliz...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Malaysia Seizes 330 Exotic Tortoises From Madagascar - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3851421.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGPaBgypM5zu18ZGuBK7dbsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 06:26:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3851421.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia Seizes 330 Exotic Tortoises From Madagascar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian authorities said Monday that they have seized 330 exotic tortoises from Madagascar worth 1.2 million ringgit ($276,721), in the latest heist of illegal wildlife and animal parts being smuggled into the country. Deputy customs director Abdull Wahid Sulong said that 325 Indian Star tortoises and five Ploughshare tortoises were packed into five boxes and labeled as stones. He said the live tortoises, usually kept as pets, arrived via Etihad Airways from Antanaviro Airport in Madagascar on Sunday. Customs officials found the boxes at the Kuala Lumpur airport cargo warehouse on the sam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>More than 100 endangered live pangolins seized in Thailand - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/08/31/100-endangered-live-pangolins-seized-thailand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEXse_MRGx9JifIwE_eHlPwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 19:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/08/31/100-endangered-live-pangolins-seized-thailand/" target="_blank"&gt;More than 100 endangered live pangolins seized in Thailand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thai customs have confiscated 136 live pangolins, the world's most poached animal, and 450 kg of pangolin scales worth £58,000. The animals and animal parts were found in two pickup trucks after authorities received a tip that they had been smuggled from Malaysia. Video block text&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Cameroon Burns 3 Tons of Pangolins Seized From Smugglers - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/cameroon-burns-three-tons-of-pangolins-seized-from-smugglers/3731950.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIiTCUv0SfxyDbwB1qWcqckqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 15:27:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/cameroon-burns-three-tons-of-pangolins-seized-from-smugglers/3731950.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cameroon Burns 3 Tons of Pangolins Seized From Smugglers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cameroon has burned more than three tons of pangolin skins and scales seized from smugglers and destined for Asian countries. The central African state says by burning the skins of the world's most trafficked mammal and arresting smugglers, it is sending strong signals that Cameroon will no longer be a country where poaching and smuggling run rampant. Philip Ngole Ngwese, Cameroon's Minister of Forestry and Wildlife says the pangolin skins and scales were seized on three occasions at the Douala and Yaounde international airports. He says seven suspects are answering charges in Cameroon law ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>'Pangolin Princess' detained in China after posting images online of cooked wildlife - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/14/pangolin-princess-detained-china-posting-images-online-cooked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHK0NHBVvpdM3LiHIjYzdMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 14:00:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/14/pangolin-princess-detained-china-posting-images-online-cooked/" target="_blank"&gt;'Pangolin Princess' detained in China after posting images online of cooked wildlife&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman who was nicknamed “Pangolin Princess” in China after she posted online images of various cooked wildlife that she had eaten has been held by police, authorities said on Tuesday. Among the dishes posted by the woman, who was named Ms Lin by authorities, was a soup made up of meat from eight different animals, including “pangolin, snake and swan”. Another photo showed a dish which was described by Ms Lin – who could face ten years in prison under Chinese law - as “pangolin-blood fried rice”, along with images of live caged owls and pangolin. 'Pangolin Princess' Ms LinCredit: Southern ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Malaysia seizes nearly $1 million in trafficked wildlife at airport - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-trafficking-wildlife-idUSKBN1AI0DU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILd0clbf5h0jfvOjZ5oVBUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 05:28:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-trafficking-wildlife-idUSKBN1AI0DU" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia seizes nearly $1 million in trafficked wildlife at airport&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR (Reuters) - Malaysian authorities seized trafficked ivory tusks and pangolin scales worth nearly $1 million over the weekend, airport customs officials said on Wednesday, the latest in a series of seizures in Asia of products made from endangered animals. Malaysia has been singled out by conservationists as a major transit point for the illegal trafficking of endangered species, as well as products made from them. Last month, Hong Kong seized more than 7,200 kilograms (kg) of ivory tusks shipped from Malaysia, the largest single seizure in 30 years. Officials on Sunday afternoo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Malaysian authorities seize massive haul of illegally trafficked wildlife - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/08/02/malaysian-authorities-seize-massive-haul-illegally-trafficked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIcyKYkSkk07ZqgBtiV0q4EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 07:28:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/08/02/malaysian-authorities-seize-massive-haul-illegally-trafficked/" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysian authorities seize massive haul of illegally trafficked wildlife&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian authorities say they've seized 23 pieces of elephant tusks and 301 kilograms of pangolin scales believed to have been smuggled from Africa in a haul worth over £700,000. Customs senior official Mohamad Pudzi Man said officials raided the Kuala Lumpur airport cargo warehouse and found the ivory in two boxes marked as "food stuff." The ivory, worth almost £50,000, was flown in on an Etihad Airways flight from Lagos and transited in Abu Dhabi before arriving in Kuala Lumpur. Later, officials confiscated six sacks of pangolin scales worth over $650,000 shortly after it arrived on an E...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Army, royalty and presidents intensify the war on poachers at illegal wildlife trade summit - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/illegal-wildlife-trade-conference-london-2018-duke-cambridge-william-africa-elephants-pangolins-a8580821.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK72DOfcxBaWvC2ZahpZ3ZEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/illegal-wildlife-trade-conference-london-2018-duke-cambridge-william-africa-elephants-pangolins-a8580821.html" target="_blank"&gt;Army, royalty and presidents intensify the war on poachers at illegal wildlife trade summit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;James Cowen joined the Army intent on fighting the bad guys killing people in war zones. If anyone had told him a posting to Africa would transform him into a passionate wildlife advocate, he probably would have thought they were under the influence of black magic. “I saw an elephant or family of them every day for four months, and every single time it took my breath away. And that’s what we’re fighting for – for experience to endure, that we wouldn’t be the last people to catch our breath when we see an elephant in real life,” Major Cowen says. The fight he refers to is just as real as one...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Vietnam seizes eight tonnes of ivory, pangolin scales - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-vietnam-wildlife-trafficking/vietnam-seizes-eight-tonnes-of-ivory-pangolin-scales-idUSKCN1MF0GT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHGXWD_-HSuQjPumu2BsDmAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 05:54:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-vietnam-wildlife-trafficking/vietnam-seizes-eight-tonnes-of-ivory-pangolin-scales-idUSKCN1MF0GT" target="_blank"&gt;Vietnam seizes eight tonnes of ivory, pangolin scales&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vietnamese authorities have seized more than eight metric tonnes of pangolin scales and ivory in one of the Southeast Asian country's largest wildlife trafficking cases for years, the government said on Friday. Trade in ivory and pangolin is illegal in Vietnam, but wildlife trafficking remains widespread. Police found more than two tonnes of ivory and six tonnes of pangolin scales hidden in a plastic waste container at Tien Sa port in the central Vietnamese city of Danang on Thursday, the government said in a statement. The container, owned by Vietnam's Thien Truong Su Co., originated from ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Cameroon Busts Pangolin Trafficking to Vietnam - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/cameroon-busts-pangolin-trafficking-to-vietnam/4539278.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB1A9j7-ydMrSPXu116yojsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 15:05:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/cameroon-busts-pangolin-trafficking-to-vietnam/4539278.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cameroon Busts Pangolin Trafficking to Vietnam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a major wildlife trafficking bust, Cameroon authorities have arrested six men for smuggling more than 700 kilograms of endangered pangolins and pangolin scales from the Central African Republic to Vietnam. Central Africa is a hotspot for illegally sourcing the scaly anteater for Asia, where its meat and scales fetch up to $1,000 per kilo. Cameroon’s wildlife protection service said its officers and police caught six traffickers as they were attempting last week to smuggle pangolins and their scales through the Douala International Airport. They arrested five people from Cameroon and one ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Live animals, meat, ivory, wood seized in trafficking stings - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/abb53f5d1921485dae23dde73d40950d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDnCHdo7rGpwRkh1gWnWPa0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgw3utQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 01:57:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/abb53f5d1921485dae23dde73d40950d" target="_blank"&gt;Live animals, meat, ivory, wood seized in trafficking stings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARIS (AP) — Thousands of live animals along with tons of meat, ivory, pangolin scales and timber were seized in a monthlong global crackdown on the illegal wildlife trade that Interpol said exposed the international reach of traffickers. The live animals recovered in the stings included turtles in Malaysia and parrots in Mexico. Canada intercepted 18 tons of eel meat arriving from Asia. Those arrested included two flight attendants in Los Angeles and a man in Israel whose house was raided after he posted a hunting photograph on social media. Operation Thunderstorm, involving 92 countries, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Cameroon Investigates Illegal Ivory, Pangolin Scales Bound for China - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/cameroon-illegal-ivory-pangolin-scales-china/4346731.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGCs1p95NtxZuW-HusDnruoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 16:38:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/cameroon-illegal-ivory-pangolin-scales-china/4346731.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cameroon Investigates Illegal Ivory, Pangolin Scales Bound for China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Law enforcement officials in Cameroon say investigations continue following a large discovery of illegal wildlife products hidden in shipping containers bound for China. At least 1,000 kilograms of pangolin scales and several hundred elephant tusks were found April 6, in containers of cocoa that were to be transported to China from the Douala international airport. Officials have not yet determined the country of origin for the contraband. Poaching of elephants and pangolins remains a problem in Cameroon; however, the country has also served as a regional hub for smugglers. Didier Ngono, an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Freedom to roam – rewilding South Africa's Tswalu Kalahari Reserve - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/africa/south-africa/articles/rewilding-in-south-africa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECvnB2DXTiZAbFuhnPEc-MoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/africa/south-africa/articles/rewilding-in-south-africa/" target="_blank"&gt;Freedom to roam – rewilding South Africa's Tswalu Kalahari Reserve&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was an old lion past his prime with a dove-grey coat and a broken canine tooth, but he was still an impressive beast, his grizzled features framed by a lustrous black mane that fell like a rug around his shoulders. All day we had followed the tracks he and his brother had left in the red sands of South Africa’s Tswalu Kalahari Reserve, each four-toed pad as wide as my outstretched hand. Now he lay in all his majesty, just a few yards in front of us, staring into the thorny thickets where his brother had just departed after an extraordinary demonstration of mutual grooming and affectionat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Echidnas help in fight against international wildlife traffickers - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-02-19/echidnas-deployed-to-sniff-out-endangered-wildlife-trafficking/9461610</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENcZB5ButQKR5SR03nCTYKYqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 09:00:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-02-19/echidnas-deployed-to-sniff-out-endangered-wildlife-trafficking/9461610" target="_blank"&gt;Echidnas help in fight against international wildlife traffickers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia's echidnas are helping to pin-point the trail of international criminal groups engaged in the illegal trafficking of endangered wildlife. Ecologists in Sydney hope the monotreme could hold the key to cracking who is behind the illegal trade in the critically endangered pangolin. Native to Africa and Asia, the pangolin — also known as a scaly anteater — is the world's most trafficked mammal, with estimates more than 1 million have been taken from the wild in the past decade. The echidnas at Sydney's Taronga Zoo are being used to help develop a scientific method to identify where tr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Prince William warns that there are too many people in the world - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/11/02/prince-william-warns-many-people-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECthqdJHDiDhDiFpk8u-G2oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 22:33:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/11/02/prince-william-warns-many-people-world/" target="_blank"&gt;Prince William warns that there are too many people in the world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapidly growing human populations risk having a "terrible impact" on the world, the Duke of Cambridge has warned. The Duke said that as a result, wildlife was being put under "enormous pressure" and called for the issue to be addressed with renewed vigour. His concerns echo those of his grandfather, the Duke of Edinburgh, who in 2011 advocated “voluntary family limitation" as a means of solving overpopulation, which he described as the biggest challenge in conservation. His grandson, royal patron of the Tusk Trust, told the charity’s gala dinner in London that measures needed to be taken to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item></channel></rss>