<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Philomena Mbete Mwilu - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZuWW14a2VuaDJhQklDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:04:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Kenya Deputy Chief Justice arrested over alleged corruption - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/9b04310e5f8846dead94a6e684061813</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFreViRGHGnppLEdLgc0R6AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 16:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/9b04310e5f8846dead94a6e684061813" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Deputy Chief Justice arrested over alleged corruption&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya (AP) — Kenya's deputy chief justice, the country's second highest ranking judicial officer, was arrested Tuesday for alleged abuse of office, tax evasion and taking of bribes. Philomena Mwilu was released on $50,000 bail until Wednesday when she will be asked to answer to the charges. Kenya's director of prosecutions Noordin Haji said he ordered Mwilu's arrest and that the decision was made "independently" but many Kenyans remember that President Uhuru Kenyatta had warned of unspecified action against the judiciary when the Supreme Court nullified his election victory last ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Kenyan court temporarily halts criminal action against deputy chief justice - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-corruption/kenyan-court-halts-criminal-action-against-deputy-chief-justice-idUSKCN1LE149</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDoWShVCIF-_GxpUO9ss3R8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 13:58:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-corruption/kenyan-court-halts-criminal-action-against-deputy-chief-justice-idUSKCN1LE149" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan court temporarily halts criminal action against deputy chief justice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya's high court on Wednesday temporarily halted criminal proceedings against the deputy chief justice who had been arrested a day earlier and charged on suspicion of corruption, failure to pay taxes and improper dealings with a local bank. Chief magistrate Lawrence Mugambi was presiding over the plea hearing of the deputy chief justice Philomena Mwilu on Wednesday when the ruling came down from the high court, and he adjourned the case until Friday, when he will give further directions on its order. High court Judge Chacha Mwita, allowing an application filed by Mwilu seeking to stop the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Kenya’s deputy chief justice arrested for suspected corruption: police, prosecutor - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-corruption/kenyas-deputy-chief-justice-arrested-for-suspected-corruption-police-prosecutor-idUSKCN1LD1FC</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbZbNwyI9PjWSz_MCVG5_wqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 16:03:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-corruption/kenyas-deputy-chief-justice-arrested-for-suspected-corruption-police-prosecutor-idUSKCN1LD1FC" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya’s deputy chief justice arrested for suspected corruption: police, prosecutor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya’s deputy chief justice Philomena Mwilu was arrested on Tuesday on suspicion of corruption, failure to pay tax, and improper dealings with a local bank now in receivership, the police and the country's top prosecutor said. Chief Public Prosecutor Noordin Mohamed Haji told a news conference that Mwilu had abused her office for personal gain, undermining public integrity in the judiciary. The director of criminal investigations, George Kinoti, told Reuters in a text message: "I can confirm the arrest of the deputy chief justice." Reuters was unable to immediately contact representatives ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Unprecedented Election Season Defines 2017 for Kenya - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/unprecedented-election-season-kenya/4180672.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELCxZiAJoeWdu6Rx_dU1vdgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 14:00:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/unprecedented-election-season-kenya/4180672.html" target="_blank"&gt;Unprecedented Election Season Defines 2017 for Kenya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya's months-long political roller coaster finally came to an end in November, when President Uhuru Kenyatta was sworn in for his second term. After the country's August polls, in which Kenyatta was declared the winner over Raila Odinga, the Supreme Court annulled the presidential election, citing irregularities in the transmission of election results. In its ruling, the Supreme Court highlighted the electoral commission, or IEBC's, refusal of a court order to open its computer servers. "[That] leaves us with no option but to accept the petitioners claims that the IEBC's IT system was inf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenya chief justice says police 'enhanced' security after shooting - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-election-judges/kenya-chief-justice-says-police-enhanced-security-after-shooting-idUSKBN1D21AI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPPG2T5CGvCzhnnqK4bAMHsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 11:01:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-election-judges/kenya-chief-justice-says-police-enhanced-security-after-shooting-idUSKBN1D21AI" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya chief justice says police 'enhanced' security after shooting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI (Reuters) - Kenya's chief justice said the national police chief had "enhanced" the security of Supreme Court judges after one of their bodyguards was shot, denying a Reuters report that a request for extra security had been turned down. The judges' safety was thrust into focus last week after the shooting, which occurred on Tuesday evening. The next day, five out of seven judges failed to come to court to issue a judgment on an election petition seeking to delay the next day's presidential poll, sparking widespread speculation of intimidation. A senior judicial source told Reuters ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Kenya Deputy Chief Justice's Driver Shot, Injured - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-election-violence/4084386.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAwB-exKb3k-3o_SYHUcnGEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 18:54:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-election-violence/4084386.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Deputy Chief Justice's Driver Shot, Injured&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The driver of Kenya's Deputy Chief Justice Philomena Mwilu was shot and wounded Tuesday, two days ahead of the country's re-run of presidential elections, according to Nairobi police. Mwilu's driver, identified by local media as Police Constable Titus Musyoka and in some reports described as a bodyguard was shot in the shoulder. Police said it was not yet clear whether the Mwilu was in the car at the time. Thursday's vote is Kenya's second try this year to elect as president. The Supreme Court threw out the results of the August 8 election because of what it called "irregularities and illeg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>No election in Kenya is better than a flawed election - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cd2aab18-b9a6-11e7-8c12-5661783e5589</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBOTa79LoOQaE9V6SH17W8sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 04:02:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cd2aab18-b9a6-11e7-8c12-5661783e5589" target="_blank"&gt;No election in Kenya is better than a flawed election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democracy in Kenya has taken a decidedly odd twist. This month in London, supporters of Raila Odinga, the forever nearly-man of Kenyan politics, were holding up placards marked “No Election” — surely one of the stranger pro-democracy rallying cries. Mr Odinga’s supporters do not want Thursday’s presidential re-run to go ahead. They argue that a fair election is impossible, given the make-up of the country’s electoral commission and the circumstances under which it is operating. Yet it will go ahead anyway. The last straw came on Wednesday when the supreme court failed to convene a quorum to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>