<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Western Sahara - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRGd5Y1dzU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:30:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Morocco-Polisario Western Sahara talks an 'ice-breaker' - News24</title><link>https://www.news24.com/Africa/News/morocco-polisario-western-sahara-talks-an-ice-breaker-20181203</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5ld3MyNC5jb20vQWZyaWNhL05ld3MvbW9yb2Njby1wb2xpc2FyaW8td2VzdGVybi1zYWhhcmEtdGFsa3MtYW4taWNlLWJyZWFrZXItMjAxODEyMDPSAQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 18:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.news24.com/Africa/News/morocco-polisario-western-sahara-talks-an-ice-breaker-20181203" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco-Polisario Western Sahara talks an 'ice-breaker'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;News24&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A UN envoy is set to host an "initial round-table" in Geneva this week between Morocco and the Polisario Front in a bid to kick-start dialogue on the disputed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.news24.com">News24</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/HpMp3rpQyPpHdvJQbNh9cRVLrxFjVdRLeMhBYezhgdujU5ACG8FhaiHmXBJVaMckPZ9HD6Rt-uaDPbfO3eFEMepIHleb-i7vZqIr1VQzkV4eVKSEGMhbAnWu5A_rndozz1ZgpQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>UN envoy: 'Peaceful solution' to Western Sahara conflict possible - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/envoy-peaceful-solution-western-sahara-conflict-181206164240438.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELBDX-h0cpwGxAwrpJnIhpEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:11:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/envoy-peaceful-solution-western-sahara-conflict-181206164240438.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN envoy: 'Peaceful solution' to Western Sahara conflict possible&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UN envoy for Western Sahara said he believes a peaceful solution to the decades-long conflict between Morocco and the Polisario Front is possible. Horst Koehler, a former German president, told reporters in Geneva on Thursday that he was "very pleased to announce the delegations committed to engaging further," adding all sides promised to meet again for a similar "roundtable" in the first quarter of 2019. The talks, which were attended by the foreign ministers of Morocco, Algeria, Mauritania, and representatives from the Western Saharan Polisario secessionist movement, are the first to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>No breakthrough at rare U.N. Western Sahara talks - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-westernsahara-talks/no-breakthrough-at-rare-un-western-sahara-talks-idUSKBN1O51PV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6D-zAI2mlS2Yf6CKqwxmsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:27:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-westernsahara-talks/no-breakthrough-at-rare-un-western-sahara-talks-idUSKBN1O51PV" target="_blank"&gt;No breakthrough at rare U.N. Western Sahara talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.N. talks on disputed Western Sahara ended on Thursday without a breakthrough, but all sides agreed to meet again in early 2019, U.N. envoy Horst Koehler said. U.N. efforts have repeatedly failed to broker a settlement over the desert territory, contested between Morocco and the Algerian-backed Polisario since Spain left in 1974. This week's dialogue in Geneva between the foreign ministers of Algeria, Morocco, Mauritania and the Polisario Front independence movement was the first in six years. The parties had "engaged openly and in a spirit of mutual respect", Koehler said, in what were th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>UN Hosts Meeting of Regional Envoys Over Western Sahara - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-hosts-meeting-of-regional-envoys-over-western-sahara/4687979.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEErgmybHV4dEBAq1xsntIxQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:32:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-hosts-meeting-of-regional-envoys-over-western-sahara/4687979.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Hosts Meeting of Regional Envoys Over Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N. secretary-general's envoy for Western Sahara is meeting with foreign ministers from Algeria, Morocco and Mauritania plus leaders of the Polisario Front over the future of the Morocco-annexed territory. U.N. envoy Horst Koehler, a former German president, hosted a "round-table" discussion among the attendees at the first U.N.-hosted talks on the territory in six years, after meeting with them bilaterally earlier Wednesday. The U.N. says the two-day meeting is a first step toward a renewed negotiations process aiming to "provide for the self-determination of the people of Western Sah...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Norway oil fund ends investment ban on Cairn and Kosmos - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/6b148556-f240-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPyizquH8X3vw7slV_aQ-6wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 12:35:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6b148556-f240-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Norway oil fund ends investment ban on Cairn and Kosmos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world’s largest sovereign wealth fund has reversed a decision to exclude oil and gas producers Cairn Energy and Kosmos Energy from its portfolio after they ended controversial exploration operations off the coast of Western Sahara. Norway’s oil fund in 2016 banned the two companies from its investment portfolio over what it described as “serious violations of fundamental ethical norms” because of their oil and gas exploration off the disputed territory of Western Sahara on behalf of Moroccan authorities. But on Tuesday Norges Bank said it would revoke the exclusions on the recommendatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>The house that Tateh built ... out of sand-filled plastic bottles - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/jun/30/house-tateh-built-sand-filled-recycled-waste-plastic-bottles-western-sahara-</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBorC-6p1hG-03ijgmFINC4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 06:00:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/jun/30/house-tateh-built-sand-filled-recycled-waste-plastic-bottles-western-sahara-" target="_blank"&gt;The house that Tateh built ... out of sand-filled plastic bottles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of women drink tea under the shade of a tent and cast an eye over the construction of an odd, circular house. The half-built dwelling is the brainchild of Tateh Lehbib Braica, 27, an engineer who wanders among the workers. We need to talk about plastic bottles On the ground lie hundreds of sand-filled, 1.5 litre plastic bottles that serve as bricks. With them, Tateh has found a way to fight back against the harshness of the Algerian desert that is home to 90,000 long-term refugees from western Sahara. It’s not yet that hot, but in summer, when the temperature rises above 50C, it wil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UN seeks to broker new talks on Western Sahara - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/seeks-broker-talks-western-sahara-170411185406954.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjENaV6G51p2ecMRGVwAv8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 19:42:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/seeks-broker-talks-western-sahara-170411185406954.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN seeks to broker new talks on Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres has called for new talks on the decades-old Western Sahara conflict, saying negotiations should address proposals from both Morocco and separatist movement the Polisario Front. UN efforts have repeatedly failed to broker a settlement over the disputed territory, contested since 1975 when the colonial power Spain left, which Polisario says belongs to the Sahrawi people who fought a guerrilla war against Morocco until a 1991 UN-backed ceasefire. "I intend to propose that the negotiating process be relaunched with a new dynamic and a new spirit," Guterres ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>This Refugee Is Building Homes Out Of Plastic Bottles - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/tateh-lehbib-breica-refugee-plastic-bottles-houses-algeria_us_591c586ce4b0a7458fa49711</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBDHedhEc_aUCnfbw42GY00qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 09:00:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/tateh-lehbib-breica-refugee-plastic-bottles-houses-algeria_us_591c586ce4b0a7458fa49711" target="_blank"&gt;This Refugee Is Building Homes Out Of Plastic Bottles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story is part of a series on ocean plastics. In a refugee camp in the Sahara desert, one man is making homes more durable in the face of tough weather conditions ― and he’s using trash to do it. Tateh Lehbib Breica, a Sahrawi refugee living in a camp in Tindouf, Algeria, is building homes for other refugees out of plastic bottles filled with sand, according to the United Nations Refugee Agency (UNHCR) video above that was posted last week. Breica lives in Awserd refugee camp, one of five camps around Tindouf where Sahrawi refugees have lived for over 40 years, according to a January UN...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>UN Chief to Name ex-German President as Western Sahara Envoy - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-chief-to-name-ex-german-president-as-western-sahara-envoy-/3885272.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFQPQi2PS7z9b3g77SDr680qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 01:45:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-chief-to-name-ex-german-president-as-western-sahara-envoy-/3885272.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Chief to Name ex-German President as Western Sahara Envoy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The head of the United Nations will name former German president Horst Koehler as his new envoy for Western Sahara, in charge of restarting talks between Morocco and the Polisario independence movement over the disputed territory. The United Nations Security Council in April backed attempts to re-enter negotiations over Western Sahara, which has been contested since 1975 and where Morocco and Polisario fought a war until a 1991 ceasefire. "Following the usual consultations, I intend to appoint Horst Koehler of Germany as my personal envoy for Western Sahara," U.N. Secretary General Antonio ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Western Sahara standoff fuels tensions, diplomatic scramble - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-westernsahara-dispute-idUSKBN12Y0H6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECp24O-fKwhnOQYqZ51uYGYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 09:40:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-westernsahara-dispute-idUSKBN12Y0H6" target="_blank"&gt;Western Sahara standoff fuels tensions, diplomatic scramble&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Patrick Markey TIFARITI, Western Sahara (Reuters) - At a rocky outpost in Western Sahara, a new generation of soldiers who have never known war are mobilizing as tensions resurface in one of Africa's oldest disputes after a quarter century of uneasy peace. Young Sahrawi troops man new desert posts for the Polisario Front, which for more than 40 years has sought independence for the vast desert region - first in a guerrilla war against Morocco and then politically since a ceasefire deal in 1991. Now a standoff with Morocco, which controls the majority of Western Sahara, is renewing pressu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>African Leaders Preach Unity in Readmitting Morocco into AU - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/african-leaders-preach-unity-in-readmitting-morocco-into-au-/3700038.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAJA9kURLrTjyGSJrZ1VbcUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 15:23:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/african-leaders-preach-unity-in-readmitting-morocco-into-au-/3700038.html" target="_blank"&gt;African Leaders Preach Unity in Readmitting Morocco into AU&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The African Union has welcomed Morocco back into the continental body after more than three decades away. Even though the transition may not be smooth, African leaders say a united Africa is more important than ever in an increasingly complex and fast-changing world. That’s because the dispute that led Morocco to leave the AU decades ago has yet to be resolved. Morocco quit in 1984 because the AU recognized the independence of the disputed Western Sahara territory. Morocco continues to claim Western Sahara, and Western Sahara remains an AU member. Leaders brushed off concerns that this woul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>International Courts Order Pause In Disputed Exports Of Phosphates From Western Sahara - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2017/05/20/phosphates-exports-western-sahara/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQAh9Si9-HVJR3L_5fZrlwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 13:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2017/05/20/phosphates-exports-western-sahara/" target="_blank"&gt;International Courts Order Pause In Disputed Exports Of Phosphates From Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two cargo ships are currently being detailed in ports in Panama and South Africa under court orders, in the latest sign of difficulty for those involved in exports from Western Sahara, a territory in west Africa occupied by Morocco since 1975. The Ultra Innovation bulk carrier was detained under court order on May 17 while travelling through the Panama Canal. The vessel is carrying phosphate rock from Western Sahara. The cargo is due to be delivered to Canadian firm Agrium, which plans to use it to make fertilizer at its plant in Alberta, Canada. The Ultra Innovation, which is owned by Dani...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Activists Claims Victory As Morocco Pulls Out of Court Case Over Controversial Phosphate Exports - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2017/07/14/morocco-pulls-out-of-court-case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ2lhDMGrnWXgauTg9ZYzHMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 10:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2017/07/14/morocco-pulls-out-of-court-case/" target="_blank"&gt;Activists Claims Victory As Morocco Pulls Out of Court Case Over Controversial Phosphate Exports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opponents of phosphate exports from the disputed territory of Western Sahara have claimed victory, after Moroccan phosphate giant OCP announced on July 13 that it would not defend itself in a court case involving a cargo of minerals held up in South Africa. The NM Cherry Blossom has been detained in the port of Coega on the outskirts of Port Elizabeth, South Africa since 1 May, after the Polisario Front, the liberation movement for Western Sahara, launched a legal bid to stake its claim to the cargo. After an initial hearing on June 15, the court decided to send the case to trial. The cargo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>U.N. urges Algeria, Morocco to release trapped Syrian refugees - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-morocco-algeria-refugees-idUSKBN18Q1PI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMhBxVWcgBV1lFxJG0pferIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 14:41:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-morocco-algeria-refugees-idUSKBN18Q1PI" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. urges Algeria, Morocco to release trapped Syrian refugees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RABAT (Reuters) - Algeria and Morocco should to take action to assure safe passage to 41 Syrian refugees stranded along the border between both countries for weeks, the United Nations refugee agency (UNHCR)said on Tuesday. The Syrian refugees, including babies and a pregnant woman in need of medical care, have been stuck on the border since April 17, with Morocco and Algeria trading blame in what resulted in a diplomatic row last month. The North African neighbors often exchange diplomatic barbs over their 1,500-km (970-mile) land frontier from the Mediterranean Sea to the Sahara Desert. It...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Are Morocco and EU heading towards a political impasse? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/03/morocco-eu-heading-political-impasse-170301102342685.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECfLxjoLab0FUwYdrA1_PeIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 11:26:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/03/morocco-eu-heading-political-impasse-170301102342685.html" target="_blank"&gt;Are Morocco and EU heading towards a political impasse?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the early hours of February 20, around 600 sub-Saharan African migrants passed undetected to the Ceuta border fence. Attacking the six-metre fence at multiple points, 359 made it through the heavily fortified perimeter, leaving Morocco and arriving in the Spanish north African enclave of Ceuta. Three days earlier, almost 500 did the same - it the largest single penetration of the Ceuta border fence in a decade. News footage from the morning of February 20 shows hundreds of young men running through the city, and many later receiving treatment for injuries sustained from climbing the razo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>UN Urges Algeria, Morocco to Release Trapped Syrian Refugees - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3877580.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENI-p-9Bg70mUXVLbg2Z4q0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:43:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3877580.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Urges Algeria, Morocco to Release Trapped Syrian Refugees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Algeria and Morocco should to take action to assure safe passage to 41 Syrian refugees stranded along the border between both countries for weeks, the United Nations refugee agency (UNHCR)said on Tuesday. The Syrian refugees, including babies and a pregnant woman in need of medical care, have been stuck on the border since April 17, with Morocco and Algeria trading blame in what resulted in a diplomatic row last month. The North African neighbors often exchange diplomatic barbs over their 1,500-km (970-mile) land frontier from the Mediterranean Sea to the Sahara Desert. It has been shut sin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Moroccan pragmatism: A new chapter for Western Sahara - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/02/moroccan-pragmatism-chapter-western-sahara-170213074116469.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKpYnjdPxHxrq6KiODrUTK8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 11:34:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/02/moroccan-pragmatism-chapter-western-sahara-170213074116469.html" target="_blank"&gt;Moroccan pragmatism: A new chapter for Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;King Mohammed VI's new African policy reflects the Moroccan monarch's pragmatism and realism. While in the past, Morocco had adopted a disastrous "empty chair" policy, the new policy is proactive and positive for the outlook of Morocco's territorial integrity and the controversy it is facing over the Western Sahara. Owing to Morocco's absence from the African Union (AU) over the past 33 years, Morocco's rivals, mainly Algeria and South Africa, have been using the pan-African body to push their self-serving political and ideological agendas. The two countries have seemingly dominated the org...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Setback For Morocco, As Court Paves Way For Trial Over Disputed Western Sahara Phosphate Exports - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2017/06/15/south-africa-court-trial-western-sahara-phosphate-exports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELsyHoD7b0_GYDC0gX27Er4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2017/06/15/south-africa-court-trial-western-sahara-phosphate-exports/" target="_blank"&gt;Setback For Morocco, As Court Paves Way For Trial Over Disputed Western Sahara Phosphate Exports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fresh question mark has been placed over controversial phosphate exports from Western Sahara, after a South African court ruled on June 15 that a dispute over a cargo being held in Port Elizabeth should proceed to a full trial. The cargo in question is aboard the NM Cherry Blossom. On May 1 the ship entered the port of Coega on the outskirts of Port Elizabeth for refuelling. The phosphate it was carrying was en route to Tauranga in New Zealand, for delivery to Ballance Agri-Nutrients, a fertilizer company. The phosphate had been mined and sold by Moroccan phosphate giant OCP. Its wholly-o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Morocco will never recognise W Sahara: deputy FM - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/morocco-recognise-sahara-deputy-fm-170205181645379.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOyDLebX7L6dRBInXBu43lEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 19:22:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/morocco-recognise-sahara-deputy-fm-170205181645379.html" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco will never recognise W Sahara: deputy FM&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morocco will "never recognise" Western Sahara's independence despite rejoining the African Union after a decades-long dispute over the territory, Deputy Foreign Minister Nasser Bourita said. Last Monday, the AU approved Morocco's re-entry into the bloc which it quit in 1984 in protest at the admission of the Sahrawi Arab Democratic Republic (SADR) declared by the Polisario Front at the height of a war for the territory. "Not only does Morocco not recognise - and will never recognise - this so-called entity," Bourita told website Le Desk in an interview on Sunday. "It will (also) redouble it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>U.N. chief to name ex-German president as Western Sahara envoy - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-westernsahara-morocco-un-idUSKBN18T2JA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFfuS-U6Qribd2j0nwd9QxEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 17:10:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-westernsahara-morocco-un-idUSKBN18T2JA" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. chief to name ex-German president as Western Sahara envoy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (Reuters) - The United Nations chief will name former German president and one-time IMF director Horst Koehler, as his new envoy for Western Sahara, in charge of restarting talks between Morocco and Polisario independence movement over the disputed territory. The United Nations Security Council in April backed attempts to re-enter negotiations over Western Sahara, which has been contested since 1975 and where Morocco and Polisario fought a war until a 1991 ceasefire. "Following the usual consultations, I intend to appoint Horst Koehler of Germany as my personal envoy for Western Sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Agence d’Architecture A. Bechu &amp; Associés Wins Competition for New University Campus in Moroccan Oceanside Town - ArchDaily</title><link>http://www.archdaily.com/797643/agence-darchitecture-a-bechu-and-associes-wins-competition-for-new-university-campus-in-moroccan-oceanside-town</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED5Io_S1XDI6ZTQQ1XBzuzwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.archdaily.com/797643/agence-darchitecture-a-bechu-and-associes-wins-competition-for-new-university-campus-in-moroccan-oceanside-town" target="_blank"&gt;Agence d’Architecture A. Bechu &amp; Associés Wins Competition for New University Campus in Moroccan Oceanside Town&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of Agence d’Architecture A. Bechu &amp; Associés Agence d’Architecture A. Bechu &amp; Associés has won a competition to design a new campus for the University of Laâyoune to be located in the oceanside town of Foum el Oued, Morocco (Western Sahara). Launched by King Mohammed VI last February, the competition was named a national priority project supported by Office Chérifien des Phosphates (OCP), a Moroccan company and the world’s leading producer of phosphate. The project was aimed at contributing to the economic and social boom of the region by creating a new platform for innovation a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>UN Chief Wants New Talks in 40-year Western Sahara Impasse - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/united-nations-chief-new-talks-forty-year-western-sahara-impasse/3807700.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOTnB5RZCrSLvPxnRmEZRYEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 21:31:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/united-nations-chief-new-talks-forty-year-western-sahara-impasse/3807700.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Chief Wants New Talks in 40-year Western Sahara Impasse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.N. Secretary-General Antonio Guterres says he wants renewed negotiations to resolve the Western Sahara conflict, which has pitted Morocco against the Polisario Front independence movement for 40 years. In a report to the U.N. Security Council this week, Guterres proposed relaunching the negotiations "with a new dynamic and a new spirit." The goal, he said, should be reaching "a mutually acceptable political solution" that would include "an accord on the nature and form that the exercise of self-determination" would take for the disputed and mineral-rich Western Sahara area. Morocco annexe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Morocco summons Algeria envoy over Syrian refugees - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-morocco-algeria-idUSKBN17P06R</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKuPb5y4SvPdgVWSFQGihrUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 09:26:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-morocco-algeria-idUSKBN17P06R" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco summons Algeria envoy over Syrian refugees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RABAT (Reuters) - Morocco has summoned Algeria's ambassador to express concern after 54 Syrians attempted to "illegally enter" the country from Algeria, the ministry of foreign affairs said in a statement on Sunday. It said 54 Syrians attempted to enter Morocco through the border town of Figuig, an area surrounded by mountains, between April 17 and 19. It accused Algeria of forcing them to cross into Morocco. "Algeria must assume political responsibility and morality concerning this situation," the ministry statement on MAP state news agency said. "It is immoral and unethical to manipulate ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trouble in paradise: the Canary Island beach accused of illegally importing sand - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jul/28/trouble-in-paradise-the-canary-island-beach-accused-of-illegally-importing-sand</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGw_vqTcRzwhr1w0VR52_jEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:44:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jul/28/trouble-in-paradise-the-canary-island-beach-accused-of-illegally-importing-sand" target="_blank"&gt;Trouble in paradise: the Canary Island beach accused of illegally importing sand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When David Silva picked up a spade on a beach in the Canary Islands last summer and started shovelling sand from a wooden box, it seemed innocuous enough. The Manchester City and Spain football star is a local boy, and had given his valuable blessing to a beach project on Gran Canaria that promised to create new jobs with a tourism magnet complete with 500-berth marina and golf course. “The truth is that this is a fantastic development that people will relish returning to,” said Silva in his capacity as an “ambassador” for Anfi Group, the developer and tour operator that is marketing Tauro ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>U.N. Security Council backs new Western Sahara talks attempt - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-western-sahara-idUSKBN17V05C</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECapKK5CUc7goowzgN9_n8AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 06:19:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-western-sahara-idUSKBN17V05C" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. Security Council backs new Western Sahara talks attempt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ALGIERS (Reuters) - The United Nations Security Council has unanimously backed the U.N. chief's attempts to restart negotiations to end the Western Sahara conflict and extended its peacekeeping mission for another year. The resolution late on Friday came after the U.N. mission confirmed the Polisario Western Sahara independence movement had withdrawn its troops from the Guerguerat area in the disputed territory where they had faced off since last year with Moroccan forces. U.N. Secretary-General Antonio Guterres earlier this month called for Morocco and the Polisario Front, who fought a war...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Sahrawis sentenced to jail over Western Sahara killings - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/sahrawis-sentenced-jail-western-sahara-killings-170719152750978.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMi_r32PSKU4C7t8Zk3G7EMqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 21:37:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/sahrawis-sentenced-jail-western-sahara-killings-170719152750978.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sahrawis sentenced to jail over Western Sahara killings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Morocco court has sentenced 23 civilians to prison terms ranging from two years to life over the killing of 11 members of the Moroccan security forces in contested Western Sahara. A verdict was delivered at dawn on Wednesday by the Court of Appeals in Sale near Rabat, the official news agency MAP reported. The defendants and lawyers have boycotted court proceedings since May, announcing they would no longer attend what they said was a "mock trial". The killings took place in November 2010 as Moroccan forces moved to dismantle a camp in Gdim Izik camp where thousands of displaced Western S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>European Court Dismisses Morocco's Claim To Western Sahara, Throwing EU Trade Deal Into Doubt - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2016/12/21/european-court-dismisses-moroccos-claim-to-western-sahara-throwing-eu-trade-deal-into-doubt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEElHn9xMyVqZZF9H0OnFrvcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 16:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2016/12/21/european-court-dismisses-moroccos-claim-to-western-sahara-throwing-eu-trade-deal-into-doubt/" target="_blank"&gt;European Court Dismisses Morocco's Claim To Western Sahara, Throwing EU Trade Deal Into Doubt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morocco’s relations with the European Union (EU) have suffered a potentially significant setback, after the European Court of Justice (ECJ) ruled that Western Sahara cannot be treated as a part of Morocco, meaning that no EU-Morocco trade deals can apply to the territory. The December 21 court ruling was welcomed by Western Sahara’s liberation movement, the Polisario Front. Its representative to Europe, Mohamed Sidati, was in Luxembourg to receive the results of the ruling and said afterwards “The ruling confirms the long-established legal status of Western Sahara as a non-self-governing te...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Migrants allege sexual abuse and extortion at hands of EU-funded security forces in Morocco - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/migrants-allege-sexual-abuse-extortion-hands-eu-funded-security/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC75ppdqAUfE1GYkgWQluIgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 17:57:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/migrants-allege-sexual-abuse-extortion-hands-eu-funded-security/" target="_blank"&gt;Migrants allege sexual abuse and extortion at hands of EU-funded security forces in Morocco&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angel N'Zopkou, a softly-spoken 33-year-old hairdresser from Cameroon, knew the journey to join her husband in France would be long and arduous. But she had never imagined it would end being raped at knife-point by a Moroccan policeman whose salary and equipment is part funded by EU money. Mrs N'Zopkou had travelled nearly 4,000 miles from her home, crossing the Sahara via Nigeria, Niger and Algeria before arriving in Tangiers. The journey took over a month and cost €1,350, her life's savings. Waking up in one of the city-port’s many hostels she could see Spain, just 14km away across the St...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Morocco's king invites Algeria for 'frank, direct dialogue' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/morocco-king-invites-algeria-frank-direct-dialogue-181107080748154.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFA4AgavxgRac1OIgpx9O4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 12:17:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/morocco-king-invites-algeria-frank-direct-dialogue-181107080748154.html" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco's king invites Algeria for 'frank, direct dialogue'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;King Mohammed VI of Morocco has expressed his readiness to hold talks with neighbouring Algeria, a long-time regional rival. In a speech delivered on Tuesday, the king said dialogue was necessary to overcome the two countries' differences, as he proposed setting up a joint political consultation mechanism to resolve the ongoing dispute. "I should like to say today, in a very straightforward and responsible way that Morocco stands ready for a direct and frank dialogue with our sister nation, Algeria, in order to settle the transient and objective differences impeding the development of relat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>UN Welcomes Moves to Restart Negotiations on Western Sahara - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-welcomes-moves-to-restart-negotiations-on-western-sahara/4637416.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFnKQBLsG1hpwBz2djeHN7EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 21:06:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-welcomes-moves-to-restart-negotiations-on-western-sahara/4637416.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Welcomes Moves to Restart Negotiations on Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N. Security Council has approved a resolution welcoming stepped up efforts to try to restart negotiations to end the 42-year conflict over the mineral-rich Western Sahara between Morocco and the Polisario Front. Morocco annexed Western Sahara in 1975 and fought the Polisario Front until the U.N. brokered a cease-fire in 1991. A peacekeeping mission established to monitor it was also mandated to help prepare a referendum on the territory's future that has never taken place. Wednesday's vote on the U.S.-sponsored resolution extending the mission's mandate until April 30, 2019, was 12-0 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Irish Oil Exploration Firm Targeted In Complaint Over Western Sahara Drilling - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/10/24/irish-oil-exploration-firm-targeted-in-complaint-over-western-sahara-drilling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMae-3ZRnTB1OZcMuZp_GMQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/10/24/irish-oil-exploration-firm-targeted-in-complaint-over-western-sahara-drilling/" target="_blank"&gt;Irish Oil Exploration Firm Targeted In Complaint Over Western Sahara Drilling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Global Legal Action Network (GLAN), a Dublin-based pressure group, says it has made a formal complaint to the Irish government about oil exploration firm San Leon Energy and its activities in the disputed territory of Western Sahara. The complaint has been filed with the National Contact Point (NCP), a unit within the Department of Business, Enterprise and Innovation which oversees Irish companies’ compliance with corporate guidelines set by the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD). In its complaint, GLAN alleges that San Leon failed to secure the consent of the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>UN Invites Western Sahara Parties for New Talks in December - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-invites-western-sahara-parties-for-new-talks-in-december/4595100.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN2lGy18gbOxFyFvyITvtB8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 20:10:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-invites-western-sahara-parties-for-new-talks-in-december/4595100.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Invites Western Sahara Parties for New Talks in December&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations has invited Morocco, Algeria, Mauritania and the Polisario Front, a Western Sahara independence movement, for talks in Geneva on the conflict in the desert region next December, a U.N. spokeswoman said on Monday. U.N. efforts have repeatedly failed to broker a settlement over the territory, contested between Morocco and the Algerian-backed Polisario since Spanish colonial power left in 1974. U.N. Special Envoy for Western Sahara, Horst Kohler, has invited the foreign ministers of Morocco, Algeria and Mauritania as well as the secretary general of the Polisario Front for a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Build a wall across the Sahara? That's crazy – but someone still did it - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/22/western-sahara-wall-morocco-trump</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI29sZ-VWVbdurwz_qna9TsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 07:00:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/22/western-sahara-wall-morocco-trump" target="_blank"&gt;Build a wall across the Sahara? That's crazy – but someone still did it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump was widely ridiculed earlier this week for suggesting that Spain emulate his $25bn dream for the US-Mexico border and “build a wall” across the Sahara desert. Related: Donald Trump urged Spain to 'build the wall' – across the Sahara According to Spain’s foreign minister, Josep Borell, the US president told him: “The Sahara border can’t be bigger than our border with Mexico.” But Trump – and some of his critics – seems unaware that there is already a wall cordoning a corner of the Sahara: at 2,700km (1,700 miles) the Morocco Western Sahara wall, known as the Berm, is more than d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>U.S. Blockchain Firm Courts Controversy With Energy Project In Disputed Western Sahara - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/08/16/u-s-blockchain-firm-courts-controversy-with-energy-project-in-disputed-western-sahara/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDkD0y9z2KLC8qqjvDKpnUsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/08/16/u-s-blockchain-firm-courts-controversy-with-energy-project-in-disputed-western-sahara/" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. Blockchain Firm Courts Controversy With Energy Project In Disputed Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York-based Soluna Technologies has become embroiled in the political controversy over Western Sahara, after announcing plans for a project combining renewable energy and blockchain computing in the disputed territory. Soluna plans to develop a 900MW wind farm near the town of Dakhla which will power a blockchain computing facility. Blockchain is the foundation for energy-hungry processes such as mining for Bitcoin and other crypto-currencies. According to analysts Digiconomist, as of early August 2018 bitcoin mining used some 73 terawatt hours of energy a year – more than the total cons...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Trailblazing desert bitcoin project raises fresh questions over Morocco’s role in Western Sahara - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/bitcoin-morocco-western-sahara-mining-green-energy-dakhla-soluna-a8496601.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWHfW2fLf9_QyHAZcca1qkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 16:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/bitcoin-morocco-western-sahara-mining-green-energy-dakhla-soluna-a8496601.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trailblazing desert bitcoin project raises fresh questions over Morocco’s role in Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all the revolutionary potential of bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies, the digital inventions are extremely bad news for the environment. At the end of 2017, when bitcoin mania was at its peak, the surge in processing power needed by computers for mining and transactions upped its estimated annual energy consumption to a staggering 30 terawatt hours – roughly the same energy use as the entire country of Morocco. A new blockchain company, Soluna Technologies, is building a huge 900-megawatt wind farm in Dakhla in the Sahara to power its computing needs, touted as a potential model for po...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>EU Fisheries Deal With Morocco Sparks Criticism Over Inclusion Of Western Sahara Waters - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/07/24/eu-fisheries-morocco-western-sahara/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECexHeq8NyBOupNgl52s8zMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 13:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/07/24/eu-fisheries-morocco-western-sahara/" target="_blank"&gt;EU Fisheries Deal With Morocco Sparks Criticism Over Inclusion Of Western Sahara Waters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fresh legal row may be brewing over the EU’s trade links with Morocco, after the two sides finalised a controversial new fisheries agreement, following almost three months of negotiations. In a joint statement issued on July 20, the two sides said they had agreed on the content of a new sustainable fisheries agreement and that it would enter into force “as soon as possible”. The most contentious element of the agreement involves Western Sahara – the territory which has been occupied by Morocco since the mid-1970s. Morocco’s claim is not internationally recognized and the United Nations sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>ECJ ruling on western Sahara will affect far more than fishing - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/11154078-73b9-11e8-b6ad-3823e4384287</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELeBpH752veqCDgUt92RBJAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 03:00:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/11154078-73b9-11e8-b6ad-3823e4384287" target="_blank"&gt;ECJ ruling on western Sahara will affect far more than fishing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It must be a lot of fun to be a judge, though you have to assume a grave, un-fun, demeanour. You get to have opinions, picking out what supporting evidence you like and brushing aside what you do not like. It is not like being a sweaty, sleep-deprived scientist, subject to the whims of material reality. If you are a judge, material reality is subject to you. Consider the decision of the European Court of Justice on February 27, which ruled that a fisheries agreement between the EU and Morocco is “not applicable to western Sahara and to its adjacent waters”. Otherwise, the ECJ held, the deal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>The Not-So-Great Wall Of The Western Sahara - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/francistapon/2018/05/30/the-not-so-great-wall-of-the-western-sahara/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELYZahHPPJwjHwpoT_gZHRIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 09:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/francistapon/2018/05/30/the-not-so-great-wall-of-the-western-sahara/" target="_blank"&gt;The Not-So-Great Wall Of The Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Donald Trump thinks of long walls, he probably admires the Great Wall of China. He also ought to take a look at Morocco’s 2,700-kilometer wall. It is 13 percent of the length of the Great Wall of China. Morocco built it in the 1980s to draw a line in the sand between itself and the Polisario, a group of Sahrawi Republic independence fighters. The wall’s height varies, but it’s rarely higher than three meters. Since nobody was around when I got to a section of it, I climbed on top of it. It’s made out of sand and rock. It’s nothing like the solid construction of the Great Wall of China....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Morocco accuses Algeria of supporting Iran in Western Sahara feud - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/05/morocco-accuses-algeria-supporting-iran-western-sahara-feud-180513073052685.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP231Ado6E30ULh63C210LoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 09:25:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/05/morocco-accuses-algeria-supporting-iran-western-sahara-feud-180513073052685.html" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco accuses Algeria of supporting Iran in Western Sahara feud&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morocco's foreign minister has accused Algeria of being directly involved in Iran's support of the Polisario, a Western Sahara independence movement. Foreign Minister Nasser Bourita told French publication Jeune Afrique in an extensive interview that Algeria offered more than a meeting venue for members of the Polisario Front and Lebanese group Hezbollah, which Rabat accused Iran of using in its support of the independence movement. "Algeria has given more than its blessing. It has given an opening, backing and operational support," Bourita said. "In addition, some meetings between the Poli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Morocco cuts diplomatic ties with Iran over Western Sahara feud - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/05/morocco-cuts-diplomatic-ties-iran-western-sahara-feud-180501173229190.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGj1f15H52iPeHbJdiRgT48qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 19:11:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/05/morocco-cuts-diplomatic-ties-iran-western-sahara-feud-180501173229190.html" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco cuts diplomatic ties with Iran over Western Sahara feud&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morocco has announced it will cut diplomatic ties with Iran over Tehran's support for the Polisario Front, a Western Saharan independence movement. Morocco's foreign ministry said on Tuesday it will close its embassy in Tehran and expel the Iranian ambassador in Rabat over Iran's support for Polisario. Rabat accuses Tehran and Lebanese proxy Hezbollah of training and arming Polisario Front fighters. Morocco's foreign affairs minister, Nasser Bourita, told Al Jazeera that Rabat has evidence that incriminates the Iranian government, which assisted Hezbollah in providing financial as well as l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Iran denies Moroccan accusations of supporting Polisario Front - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/05/iran-denies-moroccan-accusations-supporting-polisario-front-180502150452407.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHVyIQUQVGPlVpTBcrDrhFcqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 17:39:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/05/iran-denies-moroccan-accusations-supporting-polisario-front-180502150452407.html" target="_blank"&gt;Iran denies Moroccan accusations of supporting Polisario Front&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran has denied Moroccan accusations of supporting the Polisario Front, a Western Sahara independence movement. An Iranian foreign ministry spokesman told local media on Wednesday the allegations were "completely baseless" and Iran respects the sovereignty of all countries. "One of the principles of Iranian foreign policy is recognising the sovereignty and territorial integrity of countries and not intervening in their internal affairs," spokesman Bahram Ghassemi said. Moroccan Foreign Minister Nasser Bourita said on Tuesday his country had evidence that Lebanese proxy Hezbollah was providi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Morocco Severs Ties with Iran, Accusing it of Backing Polisario Front - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/morocco-severs-ties-with-iran-accusing-it-of-backing-polisario-front/4372573.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENvNweLjC4fZmU4BBxAb5Q8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 17:10:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/morocco-severs-ties-with-iran-accusing-it-of-backing-polisario-front/4372573.html" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco Severs Ties with Iran, Accusing it of Backing Polisario Front&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morocco will sever diplomatic ties with Iran over Tehran's support for the Polisario Front, a Western Sahara independence movement, the Moroccan foreign minister said on Tuesday. Morocco claimed Western Sahara after colonial Spain left, but Polisario fought a guerrilla war for independence for the Sahrawi people until a U.N.-backed ceasefire. Morocco will close its embassy in Tehran and will expel the Iranian ambassador in Rabat, Foreign Minister Nasser Bourita told reporters. He said that Iran and its Lebanese Shi'ite ally, Hezbollah, were supporting Polisario by training and arming its fi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Morocco cuts ties with Iran over Sahara weapons dispute - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/3aebb7da756940c99434b420a45aa84b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGLW3PoZEiMfALyAATF8knoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 20:59:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/3aebb7da756940c99434b420a45aa84b" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco cuts ties with Iran over Sahara weapons dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RABAT, Morocco (AP) — Morocco severed relations with Iran Tuesday, accusing the Mideast country of providing funds, training and weapons to Polisario Front independence fighters in the disputed Western Sahara. Moroccan Foreign Minister Nasser Bourita said he spoke with his Iranian counterpart to officially end ties between the two countries. Morocco's ambassador already has departed Tehran, while the Iranian Embassy in Morocco will be closed "immediately," Bourita told reporters in Rabat. He said Morocco obtained and verified proof that Iran-backed Lebanese militant movement Hezbollah has p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Minister: Morocco Could Improve Human Rights in Western Sahara - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/morocco-could-improve-human-rights-in-western-sahara-rights-minister-says-/4341661.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMgBxOAgxFWHHa-DlK16_RgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:55:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/morocco-could-improve-human-rights-in-western-sahara-rights-minister-says-/4341661.html" target="_blank"&gt;Minister: Morocco Could Improve Human Rights in Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morocco's minister for human rights admitted his country could do better in the way it deals with civil rights in the disputed Western Sahara, as the North African kingdom warned it could act against the Polisario Front independence movement in the region. Mustapha Ramid told The Associated Press on Monday that Morocco is "working to enhance the institutional framing of human rights. Morocco is not hell for human rights, but it is not a heaven." Ramid spoke days after Morocco's foreign minister warned that all options, including military action, are on the table if the United Nations doesn'...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>More than 250 killed in Algerian military plane crash - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-algeria-plane/more-than-250-killed-in-algerian-military-plane-crash-idUSKBN1HI13L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDs8-egQootQCf4OvynVlP8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 16:51:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-algeria-plane/more-than-250-killed-in-algerian-military-plane-crash-idUSKBN1HI13L" target="_blank"&gt;More than 250 killed in Algerian military plane crash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Hamid Ould Ahmed ALGIERS (Reuters) - More than 250 people including Western Sahara refugees were killed when a military plane crashed near Algeria's capital on Wednesday, state media said, with witnesses saying they saw a wing catch fire shortly after the plane took off. Dozens of firefighters, rescue workers and military officials worked around the blackened fuselage of the aircraft, which had been ripped open near its wings. Bits of mangled and smouldering debris were scattered across the field near Boufarik airport southwest of Algiers where people were searching for bodies among the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Morocco Threatens UN Buffer Zones in Disputed Western Sahara - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/morocco-threatens-un-buffer-zones-in-disouted-western-sahara-/4329907.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO4RUWjdZy5qrEzjR5zAYtoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 03:55:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/morocco-threatens-un-buffer-zones-in-disouted-western-sahara-/4329907.html" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco Threatens UN Buffer Zones in Disputed Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morocco's government is threatening to take control of U.N.-monitored buffer zones in Western Sahara amid concerns that the mission is failing to keep out Polisario Front independence fighters. The warning Sunday came as U.N. Security Council members received Secretary-General Antonio Guterres' annual report on the situation in Western Sahara and the 27-year-old U.N. peacekeeping mission in the mineral-rich territory claimed by both Morocco and the Polisario. Moroccan Foreign Minister Nasser Bourita said Sunday that the Polisario recently moved members to the U.N.-controlled areas of Bir Le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Morocco warns against Polisario provocation in Western Sahara - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/04/morocco-warns-polisario-provocation-western-sahara-180402081056065.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE7WU5XMWlVJhZ_hIU-UrDcqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 10:37:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/04/morocco-warns-polisario-provocation-western-sahara-180402081056065.html" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco warns against Polisario provocation in Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morocco's ambassador to the UN has complained to the Security Council after the Polisario Front separatist movement sent some of its fighters to UN-monitored buffer zones in Morocco's contested Western Sahara region. Omar Hilale said on Sunday that the Algerian-backed Polisario Front, which fought a guerrilla war against Morocco until 1991, deployed some of its fighters to Western Sahara's Al Mahbes area where they "set up tents, dug a ditch and built constructions using sandbags". The ambassador said that the fighters left Algeria's Tindouf camps on "military vehicles", and warned that the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>European Court Rules Against Morocco Again, Barring Western Sahara's Waters From EU Fisheries Deal - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/02/27/ecj-morocco-western-sahara-fisheries/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHFvd7vIFgTIm-ryOSEyhiYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 10:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/02/27/ecj-morocco-western-sahara-fisheries/" target="_blank"&gt;European Court Rules Against Morocco Again, Barring Western Sahara's Waters From EU Fisheries Deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Union’s top court has ruled that a long-standing fisheries agreement between Morocco and the EU does not apply to the waters off the coast of Western Sahara. The ruling (pdf) issued by the European Court of Justice (ECJ) on February 27 is the second international court decision in less than a week to go against Morocco, following one by the South African High Court over a disputed cargo of Western Saharan phosphate. Morocco invaded Western Sahara in 1975 just as the former colonial power Spain pulled out. Ever since, it has tried to ensure its de facto control over the disputed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Africa Politics Creep Into French PM's Visit to Morocco - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/africa-creeps-french-pms-visit-morocco/4119152.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVhpAir0DpyLCGtbTTcZKwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 21:07:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/africa-creeps-french-pms-visit-morocco/4119152.html" target="_blank"&gt;Africa Politics Creep Into French PM's Visit to Morocco&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France's prime minister launched a mission Wednesday to reinvigorate trade and cooperation with Morocco, which has steadily positioned itself as a regional economic powerhouse focused on Africa instead of its former colonial ruler. French government ministers, state secretaries and a large group of business leaders accompanied Prime Minister Edouard Philippe to the Moroccan capital for a two-day visit. It was Philippe's first visit to the North African kingdom since his appointment in May. He chaired a Franco-Moroccan economic forum involving nearly 150 French and Moroccan companies. Howeve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>