<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Batsman - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREkyTUd3eEVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:53:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Virat Kohli booed as India build 166-run lead over Australia - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/dec/08/kohli-booed-as-india-build-166-run-lead</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWKqVFWtOanaIAXadGlKyUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 08:55:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/dec/08/kohli-booed-as-india-build-166-run-lead" target="_blank"&gt;Virat Kohli booed as India build 166-run lead over Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Booed to the crease by some Australian fans at Adelaide Oval, Indian captain Virat Kohli settled in style before falling to Nathan Lyon late on a rain-hit third day of the first Test. The tourists boasted a 166-run lead at stumps on Saturday, having reached 151-3 in their second innings. India’s hopes of setting a match-winning target took a hit when Kohli was caught at bat-pad, more than an hour after what had been the scheduled time for stumps, but first-innings centurion Cheteshwar Pujara remained unbeaten on 40. India will feel bullish as they hunt a 1-0 series lead and maiden Test seri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>India on top but spark of hope for Australia as Kohli falls late - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/india-in-box-seat-building-first-lead-after-day-three/10597492</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDuTERB5UX52x2JELWqzYFgqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 08:34:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/india-in-box-seat-building-first-lead-after-day-three/10597492" target="_blank"&gt;India on top but spark of hope for Australia as Kohli falls late&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia is 166 runs behind after a disappointing day three of the first Test against India in Adelaide, but the late wicket of dangerman Virat Kohli will offer some hope for the hosts. External Link: Match summary After a day of toil, Nathan Lyon took his first wicket of the innings when he snared the Indian captain for 34 with 15 minutes to go, thanks to a bat-pad catch by Aaron Finch. India's most in-form batsman Cheteshwar Pujara (40 not out) ended the day at the crease with Ajinkya Rahane (1 not out) as the tourists built on their 15-run advantage after Australia's first innings ended...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Cameron White, Scott Boland maintain Victoria's dominance - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/8043/report/1150123/victoria-vs-western-australia-16th-match-sheffield-shield-2018-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPA9hNvJn3BosFZ3rW2mqxcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:40:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/8043/report/1150123/victoria-vs-western-australia-16th-match-sheffield-shield-2018-19" target="_blank"&gt;Cameron White, Scott Boland maintain Victoria's dominance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cameron White's century and three wickets from Scott Boland put Victoria in charge of the Sheffield Shield clash with Western Australia at the MCG. White scored his 22nd first class century as Victoria piled up 9 for 424 before declaring early in the afternoon. White lost opener Nic Maddinson early in the day for a fabulous 162 but he got good support from wicketkeeper-batsman Sam Harper who made 39. White fell to a stunning catch from Hilton Cartwright peddling back from mid-on. David Moody picked up three of the last four wickets of the innings including White, Harper and James Pattinson....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Australia's timing off as India seizes control of Adelaide Test - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/australias-timing-off-as-india-seizes-control-of-adelaide-test/10597520</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBOqMOfXFpkViKIi3Q8APUqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:31:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/australias-timing-off-as-india-seizes-control-of-adelaide-test/10597520" target="_blank"&gt;Australia's timing off as India seizes control of Adelaide Test&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cricket, I'm sure you will have been told, is all about timing. It's timing that made the ball sound like a cannon coming off Virat Kohli's bat in that viral pre-match video, timing that meant Marcus Harris's Shield form gave selectors little choice but to name him in this Test squad, and timing that has helped India all but take Australia out of the first Test in Adelaide. External Link: Match summary It started from early in the day, when Australia still had designs on a first-innings lead and rain appeared its greatest obstacle to achieving it. The delays were frustrating, but the timing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Marsh the masochist has Australia needing to use its Head - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/marsh-the-masochist-has-australia-needing-to-use-its-head/10595550</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECZNOWdRm7xACfebXsHU31AqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:28:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/marsh-the-masochist-has-australia-needing-to-use-its-head/10595550" target="_blank"&gt;Marsh the masochist has Australia needing to use its Head&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At a certain point, you have to start wondering if he enjoys it. It's a difficult theory to entertain, but then again the mind of a masochist can be hard to understand for those who don't share their tendencies. Maybe, for some reason known only to himself, Shaun Marsh absolutely loves being abused by people on Twitter. External Link: Match summary Far-fetched as it may be, it nearly seems more logical than the alternative — that in the first over after lunch, with the score at 2-59, the most experienced batsman in this Australian team would play a slashing, cross-bat drive to a ball that d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Kane Williamson ton, Henry Nicholls 90* put New Zealand in control - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18879/report/1157383/new-zealand-vs-pakistan-3rd-test-nz-in-uae-2018-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDaKcPVZodyR2GitMCd4-LoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:51:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18879/report/1157383/new-zealand-vs-pakistan-3rd-test-nz-in-uae-2018-19" target="_blank"&gt;Kane Williamson ton, Henry Nicholls 90* put New Zealand in control&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where Kane Williamson began the morning simply trying to keep his side afloat, he will put his feet up this evening pondering the best way to press home an advantage that now decidedly belongs to his side in Abu Dhabi. A superlative second-innings century, his first in Asia in the second dig, took New Zealand within two runs of a 200-run lead. His partnership with Henry Nicholls, who looked unsettled in the morning, but is no longer jittery - had exceeded 200 by stumps as the visitors flipped over the advantage that had eluded them for the best part of three days. It took a Herculean partne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>KXIP rope in Ryan Harris and Craig McMillan as coaches - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/ci/content/story/1167990.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHILpsiCyzhCWRGhkCfH2hwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 20:57:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/ci/content/story/1167990.html" target="_blank"&gt;KXIP rope in Ryan Harris and Craig McMillan as coaches&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kings XI Punjab have appointed Ryan Harris, the former Australia quick, as the bowling coach for the 2019 IPL season. Harris replaces Venkatesh Prasad, who was in the position last year but resigned recently. Harris was the head coach of the Australia Under-19, who were runner-ups in the World Cup earlier this year. Kings XI, who finished seventh last season, also roped in former New Zealand batsman Craig McMillan as a fielding coach. McMillan, who is also the batting coach of New Zealand, is currently in the UAE for the ongoing Test series against Pakistan. "Having quality coaches like Har...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Cheteshwar Pujara rescues India with fighting century after Virat Kohli falls cheaply to fired-up Australia pacemen - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/12/06/cheteshwar-pujara-rescues-india-fighting-century-virat-kohli/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAtwr3XeCeDdxMpVcwZxJ0EqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCe8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:36:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/12/06/cheteshwar-pujara-rescues-india-fighting-century-virat-kohli/" target="_blank"&gt;Cheteshwar Pujara rescues India with fighting century after Virat Kohli falls cheaply to fired-up Australia pacemen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Australia vs India, first Test: live scoreboard Cheteshwar Pujara defied Australia's bowling attack and overcame stifling conditions at the Adelaide Oval with a century on the opening day of the first Test on Thursday. India were in danger of being bowled out cheaply after reckless batting in the opening two sessions, but Pujara scored 123 runs as India reached stumps on 250-9. The 30 year-old notched his 16th century and also passed 5,000 Test runs. Just before the close, Pujara was run out by a direct hit from Pat Cummins to end his 246-ball innings. Pujara played with the determination...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Australia v India, 1st Test Day 1 Match Day Stumps show - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dmN1Yq-hvfo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGZdtsC3BqHCQMx48XpT6fUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowwooT</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:48:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dmN1Yq-hvfo" target="_blank"&gt;Australia v India, 1st Test Day 1 Match Day Stumps show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VVS Laxman, Ajit Agarkar, Brad Hodge, and Raunak Kapoor discuss Cheteshwar Pujara's tremendous century and which Indian batsman played the worst shot. Subscribe to ESPNcricinfo: http://bit.ly/1jnGh6S Get our apps: Android: http://bit.ly/2vFVfzX iOS: http://apple.co/2vGj8rg Website: http://www.espncricinfo.com/ You can also find us at: https://www.facebook.com/Cricinfo https://twitter.com/ESPNcricinfo https://www.instagram.com/espncricinfo/&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>SA pick uncapped Zubayr Hamza for Pakistan Tests - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25467393/south-africa-pick-uncapped-zubayr-hamza-pakistan-tests</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGklnyzz0P77GpOVfAvwjIAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:36:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25467393/south-africa-pick-uncapped-zubayr-hamza-pakistan-tests" target="_blank"&gt;SA pick uncapped Zubayr Hamza for Pakistan Tests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zubayr Hamza, the 23-year-old Cape Cobras batsman, could make his Test debut against Pakistan on Boxing Day after being named in the 13-man South African squad for the upcoming three-match Test series. If he gains selection in the final XI he will become the 100th player to represent South Africa in Test cricket since readmission. "Zubayr has been one of the standout cricketers in domestic cricket over the past year and carried that form into the South Africa A tour to India where he averaged over 50 in the four-day series against tough opposition and under tough conditions," said CSA Natio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Day one of Aussie cricket's new regime leaves us hopeful for a bright summer - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-06/australia-india-day-one-leaves-us-hopeful-for-a-bright-summer/10591894</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXhQPkZ3W_3sDrhK0cGy3YqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:15:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-06/australia-india-day-one-leaves-us-hopeful-for-a-bright-summer/10591894" target="_blank"&gt;Day one of Aussie cricket's new regime leaves us hopeful for a bright summer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;About the only thing not asked of Virat Kohli before the first Test was whether he would twerk. Long, earnest essays were published on cricket sites about the potential vulnerabilities of Kohli's generally sumptuous play. Local tabloids resorted to the kind of childish taunts — "Scaredy Bats!" — they spit at the best and most threatening "foreigners". External Link: Richard Hinds tweet: Anyone else tired of the childish and predictable mocking of visiting teams by Australian media? It’s become a boorish tradition that reflects poorly on our country A viral video of Kohli belting the ball in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Harris confirmed for Test debut, Handscomb pips Mitch Marsh to last spot - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-05/marcus-harris-confirmed-for-test-debut-against-india/10584220</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOlNnmNjcLNYeotJhR4Ta10qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:17:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-05/marcus-harris-confirmed-for-test-debut-against-india/10584220" target="_blank"&gt;Harris confirmed for Test debut, Handscomb pips Mitch Marsh to last spot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peter Handscomb has been given the nod at Mitch Marsh's expense for the first Test between Australia and India in Adelaide, while opener Marcus Harris is a confirmed debutant. Key points: - Australia coach Justin Langer confirms Marcus Harris will open alongside Aaron Finch against India - Final spot in Test team granted to Peter Handscomb at expense of all-rounder Mitch Marsh - First Test of four against India begins on Thursday at the Adelaide Oval Test captain Tim Paine confirmed the younger Marsh brother had been axed for the first Test, with Handscomb to slot into the batting order tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Gautam Gambhir to retire from all cricket - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25450642/gautam-gambhir-retire-all-cricket</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENsqtbPZQ-jCFHMZX8qZuSQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25450642/gautam-gambhir-retire-all-cricket" target="_blank"&gt;Gautam Gambhir to retire from all cricket&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Indian opener Gautam Gambhir is set to retire from all cricket, calling time on a career that began in 1999-2000, and has lasted almost two decades. His last match will be Delhi's Ranji Trophy match against Andhra at his home ground, Feroz Shah Kotla, beginning on December 6. Gambhir announced his retirement through a video on social media. He admitted he had been "contemplating" and "dreading" quitting the game, but the "negative noises" were only increasing everyday, eventually forcing him to take the call. "It slapped me hard when I got those three ducks in a row in the 2014 IPL,"...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Rovman Powell to lead West Indies in ODIs in Bangladesh - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25451810/rovman-powell-lead-west-indies-odis-bangladesh</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELvu9auDQGKPa7QnoknTGV4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:58:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25451810/rovman-powell-lead-west-indies-odis-bangladesh" target="_blank"&gt;Rovman Powell to lead West Indies in ODIs in Bangladesh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In the absence of captain Jason Holder, the panel believes the team can still be competitive, especially with the return of Darren Bravo," Courtney Browne, the chairman of selectors, said. "Darren's experience will add value to the batting, which in turn will place selection pressure for spots in the squad." Evin Lewis, who had missed the limited-overs leg of the India tour citing personal reasons, will not be a part of the matches in Bangladesh as well, despite playing for Punjabi Legends in the T10 league last week. ESPNcricinfo understands Lewis turned down a West Indies central contrac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Mzansi purple patch no guarantee of World Cup selection - Hendricks - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25457834/mzansi-purple-patch-no-guarantee-world-cup-selection-hendricks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAkrfhkU1S2NKoQkIfmbKV0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:48:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25457834/mzansi-purple-patch-no-guarantee-world-cup-selection-hendricks" target="_blank"&gt;Mzansi purple patch no guarantee of World Cup selection - Hendricks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reeza Hendricks has strung together scores of 55, 104*, 108* and 79 in his last four innings, winning three Player-of-the-Match awards on the trot and helping Jozi Stars recover from a difficult start to rise to second on the points table. He has been the talisman that has turned Stars' Mzansi Super League campaign around, but he does not believe that T20 form will have a big impact on his chances of making South Africa's World Cup squad. "I don't think so, to be honest," Hendricks said when asked about turning T20 form into a ticket to England. "This is obviously a different format. I'd lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>England end-of-year awards: Sam Curran and Ben Foakes breathe new life as Moeen Ali hits back - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/12/03/england-end-of-year-awardssam-curran-andben-foakes-breathe-new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3CIBH5WBGAa36MQD5pdAsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/12/03/england-end-of-year-awardssam-curran-andben-foakes-breathe-new/" target="_blank"&gt;England end-of-year awards: Sam Curran and Ben Foakes breathe new life as Moeen Ali hits back&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Best match Fifth Test v India, the Oval In a year of thrilling Tests played by England’s bold young side, the summer’s finale had everything. Alastair Cook’s farewell century was a moment to stand the test of time. Cook had so many standing ovations, even he looked embarrassed by all the fuss. Joe Root made a hundred batting back at No 4, a moment of deeper significance for the team’s future, Cook added one final display of dogged stubbornness in scoring his 33rd Test century. India were set 464 to win, a world record, and at tea on the final day had a chance with 166 needed off 33 overs w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Why it is worth staying up through the night to watch the Australia v India Test series - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/12/05/australia-vs-india-worth-staying-night-watch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEdY-Bgg1dmlI_yo8LLRZ9IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:46:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/12/05/australia-vs-india-worth-staying-night-watch/" target="_blank"&gt;Why it is worth staying up through the night to watch the Australia v India Test series&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the marginally inconvenient time of midnight GMT on Thursday, the first match begins in what looks like a fascinating four-game Test series between Australia and India. On one side are the hosts: still struggling to resurrect themselves after a ball-tampering scandal that robbed them of their two best batsmen and most senior figures. On the other are the No 1-ranked team in world cricket, who have continually failed to prove themselves against the best nations away from home. Why should you be interested? Stop talking a big game and deliver For all that India are the team to beat in worl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Turn your speakers on: Kohli on fire in the Adelaide Oval nets - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-05/virat-kohli-looks-dangerous-after-incredible-nets-session/10583710</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAwjGTC_2Uoi0D513p_d8ScqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:29:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-05/virat-kohli-looks-dangerous-after-incredible-nets-session/10583710" target="_blank"&gt;Turn your speakers on: Kohli on fire in the Adelaide Oval nets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;That Virat Kohli is arguably the world's best batsman is no secret — his stats are formidable, and he certainly never goes hiding from a confrontation on the cricket field. Key points: - Kohli's eye looks in as he cracks bouncers and spinners in Adelaide nets - Kohli in supreme form last time India toured Australia, despite tourists' losing series - First of four Tests begins in Adelaide tomorrow But a video of the Indian captain practising in the batting nets ahead of the first Test against Australia at Adelaide Oval has given cricket fans a rare, keeper's-eye view of just how incredible a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Mitchell Marsh omission leaves Australia's quicks facing hefty workload - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25456253/mitchell-marsh-omission-leaves-australia-quicks-facing-hefty-workload</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEI-DyRBNx2-vK__5xE8ePoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:04:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25456253/mitchell-marsh-omission-leaves-australia-quicks-facing-hefty-workload" target="_blank"&gt;Mitchell Marsh omission leaves Australia's quicks facing hefty workload&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia's attempt to emulate their Ashes bowling formula from last summer, combined with question marks over a batting line-up shorn of Steven Smith and David Warner, has forced the omission of the vice-captain Mitchell Marsh from the team to face India in the first Test of the summer at a draining Adelaide Oval. Twelve months ago the selectors chose Mitchell Starc, Josh Hazlewood, Pat Cummins and Nathan Lyon as their sole four bowlers for the opening two Tests against England, before Marsh was called in as a reinforcement from the time of the third match onwards. The change in team balan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Australia drop Mitchell Marsh for first Test against India - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/dec/05/australia-drop-mitchell-marsh-for-first-test-against-india</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYx8K7twa1JsR1dn_taTHIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 03:04:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/dec/05/australia-drop-mitchell-marsh-for-first-test-against-india" target="_blank"&gt;Australia drop Mitchell Marsh for first Test against India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia have dropped vice-captain Mitch Marsh for the first Test against India in Adelaide, recalling Peter Handscomb in place of the oft-maligned allrounder. Marsh had been under serious pressure to retain his spot after lean tours of South Africa and the UAE and skipper Tim Paine has confirmed the West Australian’s omission in favour of in-form Victorian batsman Handscomb. Related: Nasty or nice Australia's chances against India aren't as bad as the seers say Opener Marcus Harris will make his debut in the series-opener starting at Adelaide Oval on Thursday, becoming Australia’s 456th m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Top-scoring in two World Cup finals stuff of dreams - Gambhir - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ffq4ePTECDU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECrgqCRNV5f92hQbOw2zOuAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowwooT</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:16:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ffq4ePTECDU" target="_blank"&gt;Top-scoring in two World Cup finals stuff of dreams - Gambhir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The former India batsman looks back at his career that has lasted nearly two decades. Subscribe to ESPNcricinfo: http://bit.ly/1jnGh6S Get our apps: Android: http://bit.ly/2vFVfzX iOS: http://apple.co/2vGj8rg Website: http://www.espncricinfo.com/ You can also find us at: https://www.facebook.com/Cricinfo https://twitter.com/ESPNcricinfo https://www.instagram.com/espncricinfo/&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Three seamers can make an impact, so India can play six batsmen - Zaheer - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oFNvTEjyciE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAGAHT8H4_vepSzH13AFPZkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowwooT</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:29:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oFNvTEjyciE" target="_blank"&gt;Three seamers can make an impact, so India can play six batsmen - Zaheer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former India seamer Zaheer Khan believes that India's wealth of bowling will allow for an extra batsman. Subscribe to ESPNcricinfo: http://bit.ly/1jnGh6S Get our apps: Android: http://bit.ly/2vFVfzX iOS: http://apple.co/2vGj8rg Website: http://www.espncricinfo.com/ You can also find us at: https://www.facebook.com/Cricinfo https://twitter.com/ESPNcricinfo https://www.instagram.com/espncricinfo/&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Smith memories stoke Mitchell Marsh's fire - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25447917/steven-smith-memories-stoke-mitchell-marsh-fire</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELrtnDfc78A9v9xTyIE_sUkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 12:56:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25447917/steven-smith-memories-stoke-mitchell-marsh-fire" target="_blank"&gt;Smith memories stoke Mitchell Marsh's fire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Memories of batting with the banned former captain Steven Smith during last summer's Ashes will be at the forefront of Mitchell Marsh's mind. This as he seeks to quieten a vociferous lobby of critics while making the No. 6 berth and the Australian vice-captaincy his own during the Test series against India. It's been a little less than a year since Marsh was recalled to the Australian Test side for the third Test of the home bout with England in Perth. He joined with Smith for a punishing stand worth 301 that not only delivered the allrounder his first Test hundred, but also effectively sea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Why The Indian Test Team Will Once Again Fall Short In Australia - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tristanlavalette/2018/12/03/why-the-indian-test-team-will-once-again-fall-short-in-australia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK6nU8JUgnwfRQv9NNpTqlwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 08:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tristanlavalette/2018/12/03/why-the-indian-test-team-will-once-again-fall-short-in-australia/" target="_blank"&gt;Why The Indian Test Team Will Once Again Fall Short In Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Virat Kohli is hoping to lead India to their first Test series victory in Australia. (Photo by Ryan Pierse – CA/Cricket Australia/Getty Images) Australia and India despise each other. The battles between the two powerhouses have long been contentious and fiery – even downright spiteful and nasty. In the past decade there has been the infamous ‘Monkeygate’ scandal, an ugly spat between Virat Kohli and Mitchell Johnson in 2014-15 and Steve Smith’s DRS saga last year. Contests between the two countries have been marred by bickering and petty behavior. Led by firebrand Kohli, India’s current ge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ben Stokes and Alex Hales prepare to revisit events of Bristol as ECB hearing begins - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25443831/ben-stokes-alex-hales-prepare-revisit-events-bristol-ecb-hearing-begins</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIroAGvA0KIZMadLy91vtO4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 12:43:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25443831/ben-stokes-alex-hales-prepare-revisit-events-bristol-ecb-hearing-begins" target="_blank"&gt;Ben Stokes and Alex Hales prepare to revisit events of Bristol as ECB hearing begins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;English cricket could be forgiven for feeling as if the Ghost of Christmas Past was visiting over the next few days. Events that the game may well have wanted to put behind it - notably, the late-night brawl involving Ben Stokes and Alex Hales in Bristol in September 2017 - will be dragged up once again as the ECB's Cricket Discipline Commission (CDC) considers whether Hales and Stokes have brought the game into disrepute. There is no doubt it has been an ugly episode for the game and the individuals involved. Footage of high-profile players involved in a fight and the headlines that follow...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Lyon's thrift key to Australia pace attack - Hazlewood - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25439715/nathan-lyon-thrift-key-australia-pace-attack-josh-hazlewood</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWhUNRrsiH2PjNaRxyxQKYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:10:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25439715/nathan-lyon-thrift-key-australia-pace-attack-josh-hazlewood" target="_blank"&gt;Lyon's thrift key to Australia pace attack - Hazlewood&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia's chances of thriving against India this summer will rest as much upon the capacity of Nathan Lyon to restrain the touring team's talented batting line-up as on the ability of the "big three" of Mitchell Starc, Josh Hazlewood and Pat Cummins to attack them. Entering a home Test series without the prolific run-making ability of Steven Smith and David Warner, both dominant performers against India at home during their last Australian visit in 2014-15, the capacity of the home side's world-class bowling attack to cover for any resultant lack of runs will be pivotal to the outcome. Bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Mehidy 12-for scripts record Bangladesh win - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18783/report/1153312/bangladesh-vs-west-indies-2nd-test-wi-in-bangladesh-2018-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSc8bDQejFYtNGpeGgVTZ0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 17:38:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18783/report/1153312/bangladesh-vs-west-indies-2nd-test-wi-in-bangladesh-2018-19" target="_blank"&gt;Mehidy 12-for scripts record Bangladesh win&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly five months after being beaten 2-0 in a pace-dominated series in the West Indies, Bangladesh served up revenge on a spinning platter to the same opponents with an innings-and-184-run win in the Dhaka Test to complete a 2-0 series win. The victory was their first innings win in Test cricket. Mehidy Hasan Miraz underscored the supremacy of spinners with his match figures of 12 for 117, surpassing his own record for the best bowling figures for Bangladesh. Mehidy took nine wickets on the third day, the most by a Bangladesh bowler on a single day, and all 40 West Indies wickets fell to t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>'It's time for action': Skipper Paine sick of talk about Aussie cricket - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-02/time-for-action-skipper-paine-sick-of-talk-about-aussie-cricket/10575390</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC4CEcXDo3uKT-xlE-fVxbMqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 04:09:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-02/time-for-action-skipper-paine-sick-of-talk-about-aussie-cricket/10575390" target="_blank"&gt;'It's time for action': Skipper Paine sick of talk about Aussie cricket&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australian captain Tim Paine is sick of all the talk. Paine wants the first Test against India starting on Thursday in Adelaide to be a full-stop on the retrospection, reviews and commentary about the Australian team and its culture. Key points: - Following a year of turmoil, the Australian cricket team begins a four-Test series against India in Adelaide on Thursday - Test skipper Tim Paine says he wants to shift the focus from off-field problems to on-field performance - The team will focus on negating the influence of Indian captain and the world's top batsman, Virat Kohli "There has been...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Jofra Archer to be eligible for England selection next year after ECB change qualification criteria - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/29/jofra-archer-eligible-england-selection-next-year-ecb-change/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOIPuZT8_Ugbx-Iyhd-WMMMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 19:41:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/29/jofra-archer-eligible-england-selection-next-year-ecb-change/" target="_blank"&gt;Jofra Archer to be eligible for England selection next year after ECB change qualification criteria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The England and Wales Cricket Board has staged a dramatic about-turn by relaxing eligibility rules for foreign-born players in what is being viewed as an attempt to increase the national team’s chances at next year’s World Cup. England residency requirements are being slashed from seven years to three and will allow highly-rated fast bowler Jofra Archer to become available for selection within the first quarter of next year. The ECB announcement comes six years after it toughened qualification rules, extending them from four years, to put more emphasis on players being developed through t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Trouble for India with star batsman Prithvi Shaw carried off at SCG - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/trouble-for-india-with-batsman-prithvi-shaw-carried-off-at-scg/10570882</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBQvhzU_AjuRAsUwfm_9pwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:22:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/trouble-for-india-with-batsman-prithvi-shaw-carried-off-at-scg/10570882" target="_blank"&gt;Trouble for India with star batsman Prithvi Shaw carried off at SCG&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prithvi Shaw is in doubt for next week's first Test against Australia after the precocious India opener was carried off the SCG and sent to hospital for scans on an ankle injury. Key points: - Prithvi Shaw rolled his left ankle while fielding against the Cricket Australia XI - Shaw was unable to put any weight on his left leg after sustaining the injury - The 19-year-old has been labelled the next "Sachin Tendulkar" Shaw hurt himself trying to complete a catch on the boundary early on day three of the tour match against a Cricket Australia XI, snaffling the ball then rolling his ankle while...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Ben Stokes receives glowing report from Trevor Bayliss for 'exemplary' behaviour and is first name on coach's teamsheet - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/27/ben-stokes-receives-glowing-report-trevor-bayliss-exemplary/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM35Q2xUyMcRe2pK4WmiRDsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCe8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 18:39:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/27/ben-stokes-receives-glowing-report-trevor-bayliss-exemplary/" target="_blank"&gt;Ben Stokes receives glowing report from Trevor Bayliss for 'exemplary' behaviour and is first name on coach's teamsheet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ben Stokes has been “exemplary” in his behaviour since the night-club incident in September last year cost him his Ashes place, according to England head coach Trevor Bayliss. Stokes faces a Cricket Discipline Commission hearing on Dec 5, along with the England batsman Alex Hales who was also involved in the incident, and Stokes could not have asked for a better character reference. “I hope he’s available for our next game,” said Bayliss, who clearly does not want Stokes to be banned from England’s tour of the West Indies starting on 11 Jan. “Certainly I think he’s certainly learnt a lesson...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>De Kock ton delivers massive win for Blitz - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/ci/content/story/1167575.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHYGdT5cS149ZfDKRTpfFUkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 11:56:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/ci/content/story/1167575.html" target="_blank"&gt;De Kock ton delivers massive win for Blitz&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quinton de Kock sets off for a run © AP Quinton de Kock struck his fourth T20 century - a superlative knock on a night where only two other batsmen made more than 30 - as Cape Town Blitz countered Nelson Mandela Bay Giants' bonus point win on Friday with one of their own. This means that Blitz are now six points clear of the Giants at the top of the table. On the flip side, AB de Villiers' Tshwane Spartans registered their fourth loss in six games, and will wonder how they managed to lose by 60 runs, having reduced Blitz to 101 for 8 at one point after electing to bowl. The pitch had bother...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Michael Clarke denies Australia culture soured under his watch in fierce attack on journalist - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/cricket/australia-cricket-ball-tampering-scandal-michael-clarke-steve-smith-a8657571.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJNAedQ_koLcq2YLES9VX5wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 10:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/cricket/australia-cricket-ball-tampering-scandal-michael-clarke-steve-smith-a8657571.html" target="_blank"&gt;Michael Clarke denies Australia culture soured under his watch in fierce attack on journalist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Clarke has branded a prominent Australian sports journalist a “headline-chasing coward” in a rant on social media after the broadcaster linked the Cape Town ball-tampering scandal with cultural failings during his captaincy. Journalist Gerard Whateley said on his programme on local radio station SEN that Australia had become the “most despised team in world cricket... a scourge that is part of Clarke’s legacy.” Clarke, who led the side from 2011-15, defended his record as captain in a lengthy tirade on Twitter. Australia caught cheating: Cameron Bancroft in ball-tampering scandal - ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Afghanistan to face Ireland in maiden clash of Test cricket's new boys - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25417051/afghanistan-face-ireland-maiden-clash-test-cricket-new-boys</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOYube05jUIc46RkHzV7TXYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 11:18:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25417051/afghanistan-face-ireland-maiden-clash-test-cricket-new-boys" target="_blank"&gt;Afghanistan to face Ireland in maiden clash of Test cricket's new boys&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ireland will begin their first overseas Test match on St Patrick's Day - March 17 - when they take on Afghanistan next year, in what will be a second Test outing for both of the game's newest senior nations. The Test will be the culmination of a nine-match itinerary, which will also include three T20Is on February 23, 24 and 26, and five ODIs on March 2, 4, 7, 9 and 12 - all in the northern India city of Dehradun, Afghanistan's home from home. Both teams made their Test debuts in 2018, with Ireland taking on Pakistan in Malahide in May, before Afghanistan played India at Bangalore in June. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>India opener Prithvi Shaw ruled out of first Test with freakish injury - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/30/india-opener-prithvi-shaw-in-australia-test-series-injury-scare</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHQ_KR1BW-8ToyzRFQJyvlIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:29:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/30/india-opener-prithvi-shaw-in-australia-test-series-injury-scare" target="_blank"&gt;India opener Prithvi Shaw ruled out of first Test with freakish injury&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A shocked India have been forced to rejig their XI for next week’s first Test, with Prithvi Shaw suffering an ankle injury at the SCG. The teenage prodigy hurt himself trying to complete a catch on the boundary early on day three of India’s four-day match, snaffling the ball then rolling his ankle while attempting to stay in the field of play. The 19-year-old’s immediate reaction was one of agony as he grabbed his lower left leg. He was carried from the field and sent to hospital, where scans confirmed there was some ligament damage that will ensure he misses the four-Test series opener at ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Opinion: Australia wants to play nice but India series will show if it's working - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/australia-wants-to-play-nice-against-india-in-cricket-tests/10568024</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMvmhhYtIRZMaizH-UalKuwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 19:08:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/australia-wants-to-play-nice-against-india-in-cricket-tests/10568024" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: Australia wants to play nice but India series will show if it's working&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Offsiders columnist Richard Hinds With two new TV networks broadcasting cricket this summer there will be the customary array of updated technological gadgetry. The latest successors to the long forsaken "player comfort level" and Tony Greig's all-knowing car key will include a battery of quasi-analytical tools intended to enhance your viewing experience and, as importantly, fill the gaps on a slow day in the commentary box. Most optimistically, Fox Sports' armoury includes an algorithmic device with the supposed ability to answer that most infuriating question posed by those TV room int...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>England whitewash Sri Lanka after spinners end long resistance - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/26/sri-lanka-vs-england-third-test-day-four-latest-updates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVTjbrw67-HwwQ9opxs5X8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 14:22:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/26/sri-lanka-vs-england-third-test-day-four-latest-updates/" target="_blank"&gt;England whitewash Sri Lanka after spinners end long resistance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Sri Lanka vs England, third Test scoreboard - ENG 336 &amp; 230 beat SL 240 &amp; 284 by 42 runs - England player ratings from third Test, plus marks for the Sri Lanka series: who was top of the class? - Scyld Berry's verdict: England's strength in spin attack behind historic Sri Lanka clean-sweep Joe Root’s cricketers are turning into rather magnificent young men in their flying machines. It is goggles on and chocks away, lads, and let’s see just how high we can fly. If Root is the pilot, Jos Buttler is a skilful navigator when the flight threatens to be turbulent, while Ben Stokes is the rear-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Jofra Archer could play for England at World Cup after ECB amend eligibility rules - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25407156/jofra-archer-play-england-world-cup-ecb-amend-eligibility-rules</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJDGmCVGPG1TGqzRDwIOPS8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:38:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25407156/jofra-archer-play-england-world-cup-ecb-amend-eligibility-rules" target="_blank"&gt;Jofra Archer could play for England at World Cup after ECB amend eligibility rules&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Miller was saved from a life of drudgery in the City when his car caught fire on the way to an interview. He took this as a sign and fled to Pakistan where he witnessed England's historic victory in the twilight at Karachi (or thought he did, at any rate - it was too dark to tell). He then joined Wisden Online in 2001, and soon graduated from put-upon photocopier to a writer with a penchant for comment and cricket on the subcontinent. In addition to Pakistan, he has covered England tours in Sri Lanka, Bangladesh, South Africa, Australia and New Zealand, as well as the World Cup in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Markram, Ngidi among SA Cricket Annual's Cricketers of the Year - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25408218/markram-ngidi-sa-cricket-annual-cricketers-year</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKjRgA7qKeqczzclG_u6omcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:46:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25408218/markram-ngidi-sa-cricket-annual-cricketers-year" target="_blank"&gt;Markram, Ngidi among SA Cricket Annual's Cricketers of the Year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aiden Markram and Lungi Ngidi are among the five Cricketers of the Year named in the 2018 South African Cricket Annual published on Thursday. Markram scored 1000 runs at an average of 55.55 in his first season of Test cricket, including four hundreds and a top score of 152 in the 492-run victory over Australia in March - the biggest Test win, in terms of runs, by any team since 1934. Markram is also South Africa's leading Test run-scorer in the last year. Fast bowler Ngidi made a sensational start to his Test career by taking 6 for 39 on debut against India. He is also South Africa's leadin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>New and improved Pooran revels in T10 freedom - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25408604/new-improved-nicholas-pooran-revels-t10-freedom</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDVUt8ab8vsMGk8g6dIPerYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:43:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25408604/new-improved-nicholas-pooran-revels-t10-freedom" target="_blank"&gt;New and improved Pooran revels in T10 freedom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicholas Pooran, the West Indies and Northern Warriors batsman, believes the T10 League can further increase scores in both T20s and 50-over cricket, a potential knock-on effect of cricket's shortest format. Pooran has been a revelation this season in Sharjah and following his 43* from 18 balls on Thursday night, now has the tournament's highest score (77), the most sixes this season (24) and is the edition's third-highest run scorer after five games. In contrast, Pooran managed scores of 20 and 1 in his two knock last season. "The T10 League is definitely taking the game to a higher level ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Michael Clarke slammed for 'missing the point' on Australian cricket's new ethos - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-28/michael-clarke-simon-katich-defends-cricket-teams-new-ethos/10562286</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTQqRZ6R0pUtbzGd0FFdA8qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 02:56:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-28/michael-clarke-simon-katich-defends-cricket-teams-new-ethos/10562286" target="_blank"&gt;Michael Clarke slammed for 'missing the point' on Australian cricket's new ethos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simon Katich has defended Australian cricket's new ethos, arguing long-time rival Michael Clarke was "missing the point" when he said Australia was "not going to win shit" if it toned down its traditionally aggressive style. Key points: - Michael Clarke says Australia should not try to be "the most-like team in the world" - Simon Katich claims Australia has no choice but to change its on-field behaviour - Australia coach Justin Langer is frustrated with the focus on the behaviour of his team The recent Ethics Centre report, commissioned by Cricket Australia (CA) following the Cape Town ball...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>England’s Keaton Jennings holds aces to turn match against Sri Lanka - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/24/england-keaton-jennings-short-leg-sri-lanka-test-cricket</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL744Olh6RMQ_7zPzqk9oRMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 14:53:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/24/england-keaton-jennings-short-leg-sri-lanka-test-cricket" target="_blank"&gt;England’s Keaton Jennings holds aces to turn match against Sri Lanka&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may be Angelo Mathews did England an unwitting favour in Galle in the first Test. He swung hard at Jack Leach and the ball thudded into the helmet of Rory Burns at short-leg. It was a disconcerting blow, which caused Burns to leave the field for treatment, and since then Keaton Jennings has been England’s short-leg. And he keeps working his magic there. Related: Adil Rashid magic puts England in control of third Test against Sri Lanka Perhaps Jennings is lucky; perhaps, like a great South African Player (Gary, that is) the harder he practises the luckier he becomes. One of his victims in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Alex Pyecroft impresses on debut as Tasmania take charge - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/8043/report/1150120/day/2/tasmania-vs-south-australia-13th-match-sheffield-shield-2018-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMqV9pvuEteTL3GHeD7xA08qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:42:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/8043/report/1150120/day/2/tasmania-vs-south-australia-13th-match-sheffield-shield-2018-19" target="_blank"&gt;Alex Pyecroft impresses on debut as Tasmania take charge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four wickets to Gabe Bell and three to debutant Alex Pyecroft has given Tasmania the upper hand against South Australia at Bellerive in Hobart. The Redbacks were bowled out for just 136 on day two, with only four players reaching double figures, to concede a first innings deficit of 49 before the Tigers cruised to 3 for 120 in their second innings. Test incumbent Travis Head was the only Redbacks batsman to provide any lengthy resistance making 49, while Jake Lehmann contributed 28. Bell started the rot removing Jake Weatherald and Callum Ferguson with two cracking deliveries as the surface...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>England on brink of whitewash after picking up four late wickets as Sri Lanka stumble in pursuit of 327 - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/25/sri-lanka-vs-england-third-test-day-three-latest-updates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECzrXhq4GfFAshgrDZCId_QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 14:39:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/25/sri-lanka-vs-england-third-test-day-three-latest-updates/" target="_blank"&gt;England on brink of whitewash after picking up four late wickets as Sri Lanka stumble in pursuit of 327&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Sri Lanka vs England, third Test scoreboard So rapid has been England’s growth this autumn, it is easy to forget how only a month ago Sri Lanka were favourites to win this three-Test series. Just as it is easy to forget that umpiring can be as difficult as winning in Sri Lanka. The bottom fell out of Sri Lanka when they were set 327 to win the third Test. England’s spinners, and Ben Stokes with his bouncers, climbed into the home side’s demoralised batsmen to set up the prospect of a 3-0 victory, which only Australia and India have achieved here. The on-field umpiring hit rock bottom too....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Former teammates clash over Australian cricket's non-aggression pact - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/28/former-teammates-clash-over-australian-crickets-non-aggression-pact</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKRY6A4wlzo4F4KZup0OUU8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:19:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/28/former-teammates-clash-over-australian-crickets-non-aggression-pact" target="_blank"&gt;Former teammates clash over Australian cricket's non-aggression pact&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Clarke and Simon Katich famously clashed physically in the dressing room when they were Test players and this week they have become embroiled in a verbal disagreement over Australia’s commitment to be less aggressive on the pitch. Clarke joined a chorus of former players who have criticised the new ethos propagated in the wake of March’s ball tampering scandal, saying Australia’s chances of success would be compromised if their aggressive streak was tempered. Related: Australia to tune up for Ashes with game against their own A team “You don’t need to be best mates with everyone. Au...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Weak opposition, weather factor put India's warm-up under a cloud - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18693/preview/1165591/cricket-australia-xi-vs-indians-tour-match-india-aus-2018-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH8Vx74JvN0HlBX9pOiAcn8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 19:00:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18693/preview/1165591/cricket-australia-xi-vs-indians-tour-match-india-aus-2018-19" target="_blank"&gt;Weak opposition, weather factor put India's warm-up under a cloud&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India begin their only tour game before the Test series in Australia on Wednesday, but they do so in a manner similar to the one in England despite efforts to do it otherwise. They will play a non-first-class fixture against a weak side in a game that might not see more than three days' play. In England, India had asked their only four-day match to be reduced to three days, a game in which every player of the squad played, ridding it of its competitive nature. In Australia, the BCCI seemed to have pulled off a modern coup of sorts, getting a tour game at a venue that will be hosting a Test ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Finch scores 50 ahead of first Test as opener debate fizzles out - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/aaron-finch-peter-handscomb-score-50s-ahead-of-first-test/10559604</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEjgpAtgF2rp3b03FlMAitAqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 07:06:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/aaron-finch-peter-handscomb-score-50s-ahead-of-first-test/10559604" target="_blank"&gt;Finch scores 50 ahead of first Test as opener debate fizzles out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shane Warne's criticism of Victoria not using Aaron Finch as an opener before the first Test against India became a moot point in the Sheffield Shield clash with Queensland at the Gabba. Victoria ignored pleas from Warne, as well as Ricky Ponting, to pick Finch at opener in his only Shield clash before the first Test in Adelaide, sticking with Marcus Harris and Travis Dean. Key points: - Aaron Finch scored a half-century for Victoria batting at number three - Shane Warne and Ricky Ponting argued Finch needed to open with Marcus Harris - Peter Handscomb boosted his Test hopes with a half-cen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Mushfiqur becomes second Bangladesh man to 4000 Test runs - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25415074/mushfiqur-becomes-second-bangladesh-man-4000-test-runs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL5fholvlUil2sFXxCR6INgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:52:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25415074/mushfiqur-becomes-second-bangladesh-man-4000-test-runs" target="_blank"&gt;Mushfiqur becomes second Bangladesh man to 4000 Test runs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mushfiqur Rahim became the second Bangladeshi batsman to reach 4000 Test runs. Needing only eight runs to reach the milestone, he got there against West Indies in the Dhaka Test when he cut legspinner Devendra Bishoo off the back foot in the 65th over. Earlier this year, Tamim Iqbal had become the first to reach the mark in West Indies. Mushfiqur, who made his debut in 2005 as a precocious 16-year old against England in Lord's, has built himself as one of the best batsmen in the team, often spoken of in the same breath as Tamim. He was the first Bangladesh batsman to score a Test double-hun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>CA, ACA attempt to repair fraught relationship - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25389583/ca-aca-attempt-repair-fraught-relationship</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE6HlsMxnDGKGa3B_UVY6PMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:21:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25389583/ca-aca-attempt-repair-fraught-relationship" target="_blank"&gt;CA, ACA attempt to repair fraught relationship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assistant editor Daniel Brettig had been a journalist for eight years when he joined ESPNcricinfo, but his fascination with cricket dates back to the early 1990s, when his dad helped him sneak into the family lounge room to watch the end of day-night World Series matches well past bedtime. Unapologetically passionate about indie music and the South Australian Redbacks, Daniel's chief cricketing achievement was to dismiss Wisden Almanack editor Lawrence Booth in the 2010 Ashes press match in Perth - a rare Australian victory that summer. Australian cricket's governing body and players union ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Sri Lanka seek confidence, England a whitewash - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18602/preview/1140387/sri-lanka-vs-england-3rd-test-eng-in-sl-2018-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO_K69Zfrul1RxcNARG_aYIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 21:13:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18602/preview/1140387/sri-lanka-vs-england-3rd-test-eng-in-sl-2018-19" target="_blank"&gt;Sri Lanka seek confidence, England a whitewash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark Butcher discusses the aggressive batting approach England succeeded with in Sri Lanka and the importance of Joe Root leading from the front. (1:01) What can Sri Lanka salvage from here? They've lost both Tests so far. They are without their captain due to injury. Their best bowler from the previous Test is off in Brisbane, having his action assessed. Having come into the series as mild favourites (they had either won or drawn their three previous series this year), they are now gasping. A battling performance their showing at Pallekele may have been, but there is the very real possibil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>England take control of third Test as Sri Lanka collapse at hands of Adil Rashid - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/24/sri-lanka-vs-england-third-test-day-two-live-score-updates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKcIHmTqqw1I9L0qp5f65ugqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCe8LkF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 14:20:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/24/sri-lanka-vs-england-third-test-day-two-live-score-updates/" target="_blank"&gt;England take control of third Test as Sri Lanka collapse at hands of Adil Rashid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Sri Lanka vs England, third Test scoreboard England took control of the third Test after a monumental Sri Lanka batting collapse on the afternoon of day two. England, continuing their first innings from an overnight score of 321/7, lost the final three wickets cheaply during the first session, bowled out for 336 in less than five overs' play. Sri Lanka battled back with Dimuth Karunaratne and Dhananjaya de Silva building the biggest partnership by any two batsmen in this series. At 173/1 just before tea, the hosts looked in a good position to challenge England's first innings total, and b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>How Jonny Bairstow made his point to England selectors with sublime century - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/23/jonny-bairstow-made-point-england-selectors-sublime-century/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ55yYH8Q96N4avM-SgWmsAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCe8LkF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:43:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/23/jonny-bairstow-made-point-england-selectors-sublime-century/" target="_blank"&gt;How Jonny Bairstow made his point to England selectors with sublime century&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mindset Bristling. That was Jonny Bairstow’s mood as he walked to the crease but crucially he channelled it the right way. Bairstow is at his best when he has a point to prove. He took his chance as keeper when Jos Buttler was dropped three years ago, displaced Alex Hales as England’s one-day opener and the animalistic guttural roar he released when he reached his sixth Test hundred on Friday left no doubt about the personal importance of this innings. Bairstow has had a rough time for a while. It stretches back to Aug 20, the day he fractured his finger keeping wicket at Trent Bridge. Thre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Rashid, Stokes send Sri Lanka crumbling after tea - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18602/report/1140387/sri-lanka-vs-england-3rd-test-eng-in-sl-2018-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAnpm1f_aKfe8r3LqFprd90qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 19:58:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18602/report/1140387/sri-lanka-vs-england-3rd-test-eng-in-sl-2018-19" target="_blank"&gt;Rashid, Stokes send Sri Lanka crumbling after tea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sri Lanka collapsed like an origami skyscraper in a Godzilla attack, losing seven wickets in the space of 53 runs after tea, and 8 for 67 overall, as Ben Stokes delivered a searing spell of short-pitched bowling, and Adil Rashid spun it large from the other end - the pair collecting eight wickets between them in the innings. The hosts had, at one stage of the game, been looking at a score of more than 400, when Dhananjaya de Silva and Dimuth Karunaratne were at the crease. And yet, from the relative safety of 173 for 1, they managed to plunge swiftly, dramatically and at times flamboyantly ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Steve Smith and David Warner could have bans cut short by Cricket Australia - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/19/steve-smith-david-warner-could-have-bans-cut-short-cricket-australia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEISFBWvFGjLx-vfHEV2wJwUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 15:29:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/19/steve-smith-david-warner-could-have-bans-cut-short-cricket-australia/" target="_blank"&gt;Steve Smith and David Warner could have bans cut short by Cricket Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve Smith and David Warner could have their one-year bans from international and state cricket reduced or adjusted after a review by the board of Cricket Australia (CA) this week. Former test captain Smith and vice-captain Warner were handed the bans by CA after the ball-tampering scandal earlier this year and are not scheduled to resume playing at the top level until the end of March 2019. Batsman Cameron Bancroft was handed a nine-month ban for his part in the affair and is scheduled to return to action at the end of December. The Australian Cricketers' Association have always contested...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Uncapped duo named in Australian squad for India Tests - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-22/australia-names-squad-for-opening-india-tests/10521936</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJAuHJZsPOpOcCzIzT948yUqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 01:20:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-22/australia-names-squad-for-opening-india-tests/10521936" target="_blank"&gt;Uncapped duo named in Australian squad for India Tests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Victorian opener Marcus Harris is one of two new names in the Australian squad for the Test series against India, which starts in Adelaide next month. The 26-year-old Harris, who scored an unbeaten 250 against NSW in the Sheffield Shield last month, joins Bushrangers seamer Chris Tremain in the 14-man squad, while Peter Handscomb returns. Queensland batsman Marnus Labuschagne and Victorian spinner Jon Holland are the two players from Australia's last Test against Pakistan in the United Arab Emirates not to be named, along with squad members Matt Renshaw, Michael Neser and Brendan Doggett. "...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Dowrich fancies West Indies' chances in 'even game' - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25354358/shane-dowrich-fancies-west-indies-chances-even-game</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGAYWRZPtxhVygBpL0y_-QwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 23:11:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25354358/shane-dowrich-fancies-west-indies-chances-even-game" target="_blank"&gt;Dowrich fancies West Indies' chances in 'even game'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;West Indies' target on Saturday will be to keep Bangladesh's lead below 200 runs, and they plan on doing that by "going hard at them" in the morning session. Wicketkeeper Shane Dowrich, who battled hard with an unbeaten 63, stated that West Indies will need to pick up early wickets on day three if they are to avoid a tough chase in the fourth innings. Bangladesh are currently leading by 133 runs, with five wickets in hand. Mushfiqur Rahim, unbeaten on 11, and Mehidy Hasan will be West Indies' initial stumbling blocks before Mahmudullah, the last recognised batsman, comes in at No 8. "On thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>England vs Sri Lanka: Stuart Broad to replace rested James Anderson as Trevor Bayliss rotates side - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/cricket/england-vs-sri-lanka-team-news-stuart-broad-james-anderson-rested-third-test-a8644066.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMlkCHMNM3-vN1cgeqvP7ZcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 07:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/cricket/england-vs-sri-lanka-team-news-stuart-broad-james-anderson-rested-third-test-a8644066.html" target="_blank"&gt;England vs Sri Lanka: Stuart Broad to replace rested James Anderson as Trevor Bayliss rotates side&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;James Anderson will be rested for England's third Test against Sri Lanka, with Stuart Broad taking his place. Anderson is the country's record wicket taker but played a relatively minor role in England's victories in Galle and Kandy, taking just one scalp across the two games. The 36-year-old was last rested for a Test in 2012 but will step aside for his long-term new ball partner, who has yet to feature. Player ratings: England vs Sri Lanka second Test - 11 show all Player ratings: England vs Sri Lanka second Test - 1/11 Joe Root - 10 Root had enjoyed a good series as a skipper without tru...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Gabriel brought us back in the game - Warrican - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25348181/shannon-gabriel-brought-us-back-game-jomel-warrican</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGUWjCFKfmqohYcuzVV05gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 22:57:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25348181/shannon-gabriel-brought-us-back-game-jomel-warrican" target="_blank"&gt;Gabriel brought us back in the game - Warrican&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Left-arm spinner Jomel Warrican credited his team-mate Shannon Gabriel for bringing West Indies back into the game on the first day in Chattogram after Bangladesh had reached a "commanding" position earlier. The hosts were cruising on 222 for 3 after opting to bat, but Gabriel's third spell broke the back of Bangladesh's innings with four quick wickets. Gabriel dismissed Mominul Haque, Mushfiqur Rahim, Mahmudullah and Shakib Al Hasan single-handedly to reduce them to 235 for 7 before Bangladesh's lower order "put the momentum back" in their innings. "Obviously Bangladesh were in the command...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Pandya asked to prove fitness in Ranji clash - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25389502/hardik-pandya-asked-prove-fitness-ranji-clash</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO_IS9NNPk8PAHgNIoG_iVwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:13:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25389502/hardik-pandya-asked-prove-fitness-ranji-clash" target="_blank"&gt;Pandya asked to prove fitness in Ranji clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hardik Pandya flaunts some style AP Hardik Pandya won't be a part of the India A squad for the three one-dayers in New Zealand as he is yet to fully recover from a back injury that he picked up at the Asia Cup in September. Selected in the India A squad last month in a bid to give him game time before the second half of the Test series in Australia, Pandya has now instead been asked to rest and continue regaining strength by the medical staff at the National Cricket Academy in Bengaluru. Pandya's next competitive fixture is likely to be the sixth-round Ranji Trophy clash for Baroda against ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>How Michael Clarke proved Australian cricket's critics right while trying to hit back - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-29/clarke-proves-dectractors-point-while-trying-to-hit-back/10566540</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEKfOoMNUFAzo2cHCk-WTDQqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 02:11:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-29/clarke-proves-dectractors-point-while-trying-to-hit-back/10566540" target="_blank"&gt;How Michael Clarke proved Australian cricket's critics right while trying to hit back&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The culture war between the reformists and the traditionalists — all of whom care about the future of Australian cricket — continues apace. This time, Michael Clarke has climbed back onto the pulpit to tee off on Gerard Whateley. Clarke already had his turn earlier this week, taking aim at the new, softer direction suggested after the independent review in Australian cricket, sparked by the horrible scenes of sandpaper-borne ball tampering in South Africa. "Play tough, Australian cricket because — whether we like it or not — that is in our blood," the former skipper told Macquarie Radio. "I...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>The hits and misses from a low-key PSL 2019 player draft - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25332547/the-hits-misses-low-key-psl-2019-player-draft</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAbYEitco2Meq0VM6IR8b5gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 16:37:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25332547/the-hits-misses-low-key-psl-2019-player-draft" target="_blank"&gt;The hits and misses from a low-key PSL 2019 player draft&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Pakistan's fourth-innings implosion against New Zealand on Monday was a poor warm-up, the Pakistan Super League 2019 draft lost much of its sheen to the PCB's case against the BCCI being dismissed by the ICC dispute panel on Tuesday. However, the semblance of attention the draft received, as the glittery ceremony unfolded in Islamabad, came via its most celebrated pick - AB de Villiers - going to Lahore Qalandars, followed by the 'Sixth Team', formerly Multan, snapping up the banned Australia batsman Steven Smith. Aside from de Villiers and Smith, the focus was on veterans Shahid Afridi ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>David Warner and Steve Smith ball-tampering bans stand, Cricket Australia says - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/20/david-warner-and-steve-smiths-ball-tampering-bans-will-stand</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEUcfOWZKvk0OF11HvklMMgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 01:58:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/20/david-warner-and-steve-smiths-ball-tampering-bans-will-stand" target="_blank"&gt;David Warner and Steve Smith ball-tampering bans stand, Cricket Australia says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A definitive line in the sand has been drawn under the ball tampering scandal after Cricket Australia dismissed a submission by the players’ union which asked for amendments to the bans handed to Steve Smith, David Warner and Cameron Bancroft. CA directors discussed the options available to them on Monday, following calls from the Australian Cricketers’ Association to immediately lift the sanctions. Despite the union’s claims the trio had “already been punished enough”, the board of directors unanimously decided the bans were fair, and saw no reason to alter them. Related: Caught on tape: t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Starc replaces injured Stanlake for series decider - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18693/preview/1144992/australia-vs-india-3rd-t20i-india-in-aus-2018-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHo_NeXRMkTZGILVJTbIunMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 14:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/18693/preview/1144992/australia-vs-india-3rd-t20i-india-in-aus-2018-19" target="_blank"&gt;Starc replaces injured Stanlake for series decider&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Should India bring in Yuzvendra Chahal for the deciding T20I in Sydney? Murali Kartik and Shaun Tait discuss (3:23) The rain has followed Australia's T20Is around: the one-off match against South Africa was reduced to a T10, the opening game against India had overs lopped off, and in Melbourne the contest didn't get beyond the first innings as showers teased everyone that they would allow a resumption. On balance, the rain allowed Australia to get away with it in Melbourne and denied India a great opportunity to level the series. Now, the best India can get is a share of the spoils in Sydne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Vijay, Vihari fifties headline drawn encounter against New Zealand A - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/19014/report/1164220/day/4/new-zealand-a-vs-india-a-1st-unofficial-test-india-a-tour-of-nz-2018-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGj1G3xBezkn7ZkwnY78WpoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 14:17:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/series/19014/report/1164220/day/4/new-zealand-a-vs-india-a-1st-unofficial-test-india-a-tour-of-nz-2018-19" target="_blank"&gt;Vijay, Vihari fifties headline drawn encounter against New Zealand A&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of India A's top five batsmen notched up 40-plus scores on the last day against New Zealand A as the first unofficial Test ended in a draw at Mount Maunganui. M Vijay and captain Ajinkya Rahane followed up on their paltry first-innings scores by making 60 and 41 not-out respectively, while Prithvi Shaw and Hanuma Vihari, who made their Test debuts against England earlier this year, brought up half-centuries. India openers Vijay and Shaw had finished with a quick stand of 35 in eight overs on day three after New Zealand's lower order had made India bowlers toil hard earlier. Shaw reached...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>England try fifth No 3 in five matches as Jonny Bairstow steps in for final Sri Lanka Test - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/21/england-try-fifth-no-3-five-matches-jonny-bairstow-steps-final/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAnUGDXjd600iqWxsO_6BYAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCe8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/11/21/england-try-fifth-no-3-five-matches-jonny-bairstow-steps-final/" target="_blank"&gt;England try fifth No 3 in five matches as Jonny Bairstow steps in for final Sri Lanka Test&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come in, number three, your time is up. For the fifth time in five Tests England will change their number three batsman, jettisoning Ben Stokes after one innings and installing Jonny Bairstow for the third and last Test against Sri Lanka. Bairstow will replace Sam Curran, who has a side strain, while Stuart Broad replaces James Anderson on a rest-and-rotation basis. “We’ve still got two seam options, plenty of spin there and, if anything, strengthening that batting should hold us in good stead going into this last game,” Joe Root explained. “I feel it’s a very strong team that gives us a ve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Dinesh Chandimal out of third England Test too - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25337938/dinesh-chandimal-third-england-test-too</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYgPTGXWQGbZyoJxGCNeBQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 01:43:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25337938/dinesh-chandimal-third-england-test-too" target="_blank"&gt;Dinesh Chandimal out of third England Test too&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sri Lanka captain Dinesh Chandimal has been ruled out of the third Test against England, after he failed to sufficiently recover from the groin strain he had sustained during the first Test. Opener Danushka Gunathilaka has been brought into the squad as his replacement. Team management had hoped Chandimal would be available for the SSC Test, after the initial prognosis had been that he would take two weeks to recover. But despite having sat out the second Test in Pallekele, the injury still lingers. "I did a fitness test on Monday, and afterwards there were still symptoms of this injury," C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Sri Lanka vs England: Jonny Bairstow hits defiant century to bat tourists into promising position on day one - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/cricket/sri-lanka-vs-england-score-latest-scorecard-jonny-bairstow-hundred-colombo-a8648371.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOCRv-gCqnvn442pcIDgOSIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/cricket/sri-lanka-vs-england-score-latest-scorecard-jonny-bairstow-hundred-colombo-a8648371.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sri Lanka vs England: Jonny Bairstow hits defiant century to bat tourists into promising position on day one&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jonny Bairstow laid emphatic claim to England's problem position at number three, scoring a wonderful century on an emotionally-charged return to the Test side. Bairstow's red-faced roar as he reached three figures in the broiling heat of Colombo, bat cast aside and fists pumping the air, was one of the most expressive celebrations in recent memory and spoke volumes about the meaning attached to his battling 110. In terms of the third Test against Sri Lanka, and England's hopes of a whitewash, it was a vital innings and formed the spine of a promising stumps score of 312 for seven, but for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Azhar Ali agrees Somerset return in 2019 - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25383413/azhar-ali-agrees-somerset-return-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAw6bgzM8cGQ9DKyxUQe4qAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 02:17:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25383413/azhar-ali-agrees-somerset-return-2019" target="_blank"&gt;Azhar Ali agrees Somerset return in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Somerset have confirmed the return of Pakistan batsman Azhar Ali as overseas player for the whole of the 2019 season. Azhar, 33, will be available to play a full part in the Specsavers Championship and the Royal London Cup. Azhar is currently Pakistan's leading active Test run-scorer, but he retired earlier this month from playing ODIs. With the 2019 summer dominated in part by the World Cup in England, and Pakistan only playing white-ball cricket between January and October, Azhar can throw himself into a full campaign at Taunton. "We are delighted to have secured a player of Azhar's quali...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>CPL keen to host women's T20 tournament - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25399685/cpl-keen-host-women-t20-tournament</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDQHcuTuGcDx_1yMTwtWNCIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:25:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25399685/cpl-keen-host-women-t20-tournament" target="_blank"&gt;CPL keen to host women's T20 tournament&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There could be Women's Caribbean Premier League on the cricket calendar in the near future with the tournament's chief operating officer indicating it is not a question of "if" but "when". Pete Russell was responding to questions raised by West Indies batsman Britney Cooper after her team was knocked out in the semi-finals of the T20 World Cup, when she claimed they could have done better if they could also play as many matches a year as some of the more fancied teams like Australia, England and India. "We need people in the CPL or corporate sponsors to back us and give us that push. We can...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Keaton Jennings puts his body on the line once more at short leg - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25359938/keaton-jennings-puts-body-line-once-more-short-leg</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOo_T_unFk2Vp9zkzYb1hscqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 21:21:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25359938/keaton-jennings-puts-body-line-once-more-short-leg" target="_blank"&gt;Keaton Jennings puts his body on the line once more at short leg&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the third time in the space of two Sri Lanka innings, Jennings pulled off an outstanding catch at short leg (to be scrupulously correct, one of the catches in Kandy was taken by the keeper, Ben Foakes, after Jennings parried to ball to him) to conjure a wicket from pretty much nowhere. He was then back in the action three more times in the innings, combining with Adil Rashid just before tea to remove Dhananjaya de Silva for 73 and break a burgeoning second-wicket stand of 142, before accounting for Dimuth Karunaratne and Roshen Silva after the break, the latter an outstanding sharp one-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item></channel></rss>