<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Uhuru Kenyatta - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREp5YlRWM0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:16:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Kenya adds 1063 megawatts to national grid - Political Analysis South Africa</title><link>https://www.politicalanalysis.co.za/kenya-adds-1063-megawatts-to-national-grid/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiT2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnBvbGl0aWNhbGFuYWx5c2lzLmNvLnphL2tlbnlhLWFkZHMtMTA2My1tZWdhd2F0dHMtdG8tbmF0aW9uYWwtZ3JpZC_SAQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:26:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.politicalanalysis.co.za/kenya-adds-1063-megawatts-to-national-grid/" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya adds 1063 megawatts to national grid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Political Analysis South Africa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Uhuru Kenyatta on Tuesday, 4 December 2018, said his government has added 1063 megawatts of electricity to the national grid, since taking over ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.politicalanalysis.co.za">Political Analysis South Africa</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/fHCLZn17jFqqHWo1DUNGJl20qWK8lCfZR7-TxzlnwTMSFGJKo7JAvuFMeVYW7-YIbDZQ1cl2J8sIaKLDegsU4T3wPXEK2ni9Ofrajzp1_31Rtfx_tNLJCuI4M4udIrHk2cAsx7w=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Kenyatta challenges farmers to adopt modern farming techniques - Political Analysis South Africa</title><link>https://www.politicalanalysis.co.za/kenyatta-challenges-farmers-to-adopt-modern-farming-techniques/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnBvbGl0aWNhbGFuYWx5c2lzLmNvLnphL2tlbnlhdHRhLWNoYWxsZW5nZXMtZmFybWVycy10by1hZG9wdC1tb2Rlcm4tZmFybWluZy10ZWNobmlxdWVzL9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 08:04:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.politicalanalysis.co.za/kenyatta-challenges-farmers-to-adopt-modern-farming-techniques/" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyatta challenges farmers to adopt modern farming techniques&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Political Analysis South Africa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Uhuru Kenyatta on Tuesday, 4 December 2018, challenged farmers in the country to adopt modern farming and livestock production technologies in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.politicalanalysis.co.za">Political Analysis South Africa</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/Hn5aDviRXtOfErzA7HUihATQHBshEiAobhmvkobX0qSDzTAqLXXlixEaLZhro6YwIyCHD_zURVoaraYlcL2rfVI20xddDDTkdySRtnn1kUBj-YUHhwz5Qd8ACPRAyosa8DFD0Ho=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Kenyatta mourns passing of George Herbert Walker Bush - Political Analysis South Africa</title><link>https://www.politicalanalysis.co.za/kenyatta-mourns-passing-of-george-herbert-walker-bush/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiWmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnBvbGl0aWNhbGFuYWx5c2lzLmNvLnphL2tlbnlhdHRhLW1vdXJucy1wYXNzaW5nLW9mLWdlb3JnZS1oZXJiZXJ0LXdhbGtlci1idXNoL9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:33:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.politicalanalysis.co.za/kenyatta-mourns-passing-of-george-herbert-walker-bush/" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyatta mourns passing of George Herbert Walker Bush&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Political Analysis South Africa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Uhuru Kenyatta on Saturday, 1 December 2018, mourned former US President George Herbert Walker Bush who died on Friday aged 94. Kenyatta ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.politicalanalysis.co.za">Political Analysis South Africa</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/tzQOTteN1OvftSHNuhZcZ9eX8nAxARNKTnQPUjJJnh9rqzJHEHyWMB3pGT4oU1TF_Nk4rI30TU8tVM17M0UlX9osCJEVgX4dy6qcOr9XIT1AatdlBvOxFpTGkSrXt3u6mg5LmgHQE686JuaFgwzowE7NNEAYf0vB27I=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Chimamanda let Hillary off. But my father showed how to stand up to power - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/01/writers-power-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-hillary-clinton-pen</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJW9J0pV3xhXu-AC3rasl00qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 09:00:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/01/writers-power-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-hillary-clinton-pen" target="_blank"&gt;Chimamanda let Hillary off. But my father showed how to stand up to power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In June 2015 my father, Ngũgĩ wa Thiong’o, and my writer siblings were on a book tour in Kenya at the invitation of East African Educational Publishers. One of our stops was a meeting with President Uhuru Kenyatta and the opposition leader Raila Odinga (for balance, I assumed). So we went. After going through security we were walked into this room that was arranged, as to be expected, for power to sit at the head of the table. Uhuru walked in and we all stood up. He greeted each one of us and casually sat at the head of the room, one leg draped over his chair’s arm rest. My father was sitti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Beyonce and other stars to perform at Mandela festival - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/33e0fba9a9f14bf297e88b9d413dab66</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG4RghQG5aYoLj5OAHo35sMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 15:40:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/33e0fba9a9f14bf297e88b9d413dab66" target="_blank"&gt;Beyonce and other stars to perform at Mandela festival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Beyonce and other international stars have gathered in South Africa for a charity concert honoring Nelson Mandela, a century after he was born. Pharrell Williams, Trevor Noah and Oprah Winfrey were among those headlining the Global Citizen Festival: Mandela 100 at Johannesburg's FNB Stadium on Sunday. Model Naomi Campbell and singer Bob Geldof, who organized the Live Aid concerts for Africa, are also attending. Global Citizen, an advocacy group, campaigns for an end to extreme poverty and other causes. It says many people won tickets to Sunday's concert through charity w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Rugby team rallies against deportation of gay player to Kenya - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/20/uk/rugby-team-lgbt-deportation-scli-gbr-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE6PSdwlc8zc30PvM4DbiKsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 10:43:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/20/uk/rugby-team-lgbt-deportation-scli-gbr-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rugby team rallies against deportation of gay player to Kenya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An English rugby team is fighting to save a gay teammate from being deported to Kenya, where they fear he will face persecution or imprisonment. Kenneth Macharia, who has lived in the UK since 2009, has had his request for asylum rejected and is now being detained in an immigration center pending deportation, his club has said. His fellow players at the Bristol Bisons, a gay and inclusive rugby club, have set up a petition and launched a social media campaign in an attempt to force the Home Office to reverse the decision. Homosexuality is punishable by up to 14 years' imprisonment in Kenya....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kenyatta: We're focused on putting Kenya first - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/10/29/exp-quest-kenyatta-full-interview.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK_Gq80KbwJBMwJJmp665TcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 13:34:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/10/29/exp-quest-kenyatta-full-interview.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyatta: We're focused on putting Kenya first&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN's Richard Quest sits down with Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta on moving Kenya to the next level and whether he'll seek another term as president. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kenyan ex-sports minister charged over Rio Olympics graft - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-corruption/kenyan-ex-sports-minister-charged-over-rio-olympics-graft-idUSKCN1MT1EF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP4r95jZXpQyu2QeaWEPvYQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:16:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-corruption/kenyan-ex-sports-minister-charged-over-rio-olympics-graft-idUSKCN1MT1EF" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan ex-sports minister charged over Rio Olympics graft&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Kenyan sports minister Hassan Wario was charged in court on Friday with abuse of office over the siphoning off of funds meant for athletes who competed in the 2016 Rio Olympics. Kenya enjoyed its most successful Olympics ever in Rio, winning six gold medals, six silvers and one bronze, all in track and field. But the on-field achievements were blighted by allegations of corruption among Kenyan team leaders and senior government officials. An investigation laid the blame on Wario, the sports minister at the time, and six other former senior officials, according to the East African cou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Botswana’s President Masisi joins the Giants Club - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/campaigns/elephant-campaign/botswana-s-president-masisi-joins-the-giants-club-a8591101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZzAwGYV63RKtDn9PL7N8kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 21:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/campaigns/elephant-campaign/botswana-s-president-masisi-joins-the-giants-club-a8591101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Botswana’s President Masisi joins the Giants Club&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Botswana’s new president Mokgweetsi Masisi became the fourth African Head of State to join the Giants Club when he signed the forum’s declaration at a ceremony attended by fellow African leaders. The Giants Club is an initiative of the international conservation organisation Space for Giants that unites the leaders of African elephant-range states with international financiers, conservationists and celebrities. Together, these individuals combine their exceptional political muscle, extensive financial resources, pioneering scientific expertise, and global reach and influence to fulfil the C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Kenya's Finance Minister Cuts Spending, Money Transfer Taxes to Rise - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-s-finance-minister-cuts-spending-money-transfer-taxes-to-rise-/4578287.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEpfJ-7IBcu501c-_dmPoe0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:35:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-s-finance-minister-cuts-spending-money-transfer-taxes-to-rise-/4578287.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya's Finance Minister Cuts Spending, Money Transfer Taxes to Rise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya's Finance Minister Henry Rotich has cut the government's spending budget by 55.1 billion shillings ($546.90 million), or 1.8 percent, for the fiscal year from July this year, a Treasury document showed on Wednesday. The government is facing a tough balancing act after a public outcry over a new 16 percent value added tax on all petroleum products forced President Uhuru Kenyatta to suggest to parliament to keep the VAT and cut if by half. In the document detailing the new spending estimates, Rotich said the budget had to be adjusted because of the amendments to tax measures brought by ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zimbabwe opposition leader plans mock inauguration in challenge to president - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zimbabwe-politics/zimbabwe-opposition-leader-plans-mock-inauguration-in-challenge-to-president-idUSKCN1LR1UF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPtMIRsP_DFc8JmkHlr4IIMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:26:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zimbabwe-politics/zimbabwe-opposition-leader-plans-mock-inauguration-in-challenge-to-president-idUSKCN1LR1UF" target="_blank"&gt;Zimbabwe opposition leader plans mock inauguration in challenge to president&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zimbabwe's main opposition leader Nelson Chamisa may take a mock presidential oath on Saturday, his spokesman said, three weeks after President Emmerson Mnangagwa was inaugurated following a court decision upholding his disputed election victory. However, a junior minister warned the opposition Movement for Democratic Change (MDC) that any attempt to undermine the government's legitimacy would be dealt with mercilessly. Chamisa, who heads the MDC, has argued that he was cheated of victory by the electoral board, and has rejected last month's constitutional court ruling that declared Mnangag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Kenyan police apologizes over arrest of Chinese journalists - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-immigration/kenyan-police-apologizes-over-arrest-of-chinese-journalists-idUSKCN1LM1AD</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPEd4KLXAK8QjE8yeDZz7b4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 12:04:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-immigration/kenyan-police-apologizes-over-arrest-of-chinese-journalists-idUSKCN1LM1AD" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan police apologizes over arrest of Chinese journalists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenyan police apologized on Thursday for briefly arresting journalists from Chinese state television's international English channel China Global Television Network (CGTN). The incident happened just days after Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta attended a summit in China, which is a crucial partner for the East African nation. President Xi Jinping offered another $60 billion in financing for Africa. Officers on Wednesday raided the CGTN's offices in Nairobi and detained some staff for what they alleged were immigration offences. "The raid on the Chinese state-owned broadcaster was based on fa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>South African rand weakens as economy enters recession - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/south-africa-recession-rand-weak-economy-ramaphosa-a8523341.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJnGqIyNN10mjKYzNEu0LHgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 06:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/south-africa-recession-rand-weak-economy-ramaphosa-a8523341.html" target="_blank"&gt;South African rand weakens as economy enters recession&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa has gone into recession after its economy shrank by 0.8 per cent in the second quarter of the year. A recession is technically defined as when an economy contracts over two consecutive quarters. The main reasons behind the contraction in the second quarter were slowing agriculture, transport and trade sectors, according to Statistics South Africa. In particular, the agriculture market fell back by 29.2 per cent, taking 0.8 per cent off GDP. - Read more Never mind Brexit, the South Africans will love us after May's dancing The main positive contributions came from the mining ind...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Boris Johnson ridiculed by Kenyan president: 'The bicycle guy' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/boris-johnson-kenya-president-bicycle-guy-theresa-may-uhuru-kenyatta-a8514326.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP9IbLilj5AdCCXOfIsxgiYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 11:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/boris-johnson-kenya-president-bicycle-guy-theresa-may-uhuru-kenyatta-a8514326.html" target="_blank"&gt;Boris Johnson ridiculed by Kenyan president: 'The bicycle guy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boris Johnson has been ridiculed by the President of Kenya, who appeared to feign forgetting his name and then referred to the former foreign secretary as “the bicycle guy”. Uhuru Kenyatta was standing next to Theresa May at a live press conference in Nairobi when he derided Mr Johnson on the world stage. The moment came on the final day of Ms May’s tour of Africa, with would-be Conservative leader Mr Johnson said to be planning a challenge against her leadership. - Read more May vows to fight off any leadership challenge from Johnson But while Ms May might have found the president’s commen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>China pledges $60bn for Africa as Xi rejects ‘debt trap’ claims - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e46bf2e2-af90-11e8-99ca-68cf89602132</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVW14CJb3BLJWb-qVrOe_MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 18:36:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e46bf2e2-af90-11e8-99ca-68cf89602132" target="_blank"&gt;China pledges $60bn for Africa as Xi rejects ‘debt trap’ claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xi Jinping, China’s president, has pledged $60bn for African development over the next three years while countering criticism that Beijing is trying to ensnare African governments in a debt trap. At the start of the three-day triennial Forum on China-Africa Co-operation in Beijing, Mr Xi said China would not finance “vanity projects” but would concentrate on commercially viable, sustainable and green investments. Speaking to representatives of 54 African countries — including several heads of state — in the Great Hall of the People, he said: “Only Chinese and African people have a say when ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Trump welcomes president of Kenya to the White House - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/4f361ee9d40643fb9776a64c42364b8c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHk5sdNHduegcyXQKpeBVQIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 02:37:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/4f361ee9d40643fb9776a64c42364b8c" target="_blank"&gt;Trump welcomes president of Kenya to the White House&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump on Monday welcomed the president of Kenya to the White House, where the two leaders talked trade, security — and Trump's accomplishments. Trump hosted President Uhuru Kenyatta as Kenya is emerging from a period of election turmoil. He's the second African leader to meet with Trump at the White House, following a visit by Nigeria's president earlier this year. Trump has been criticized for paying too little attention to the continent and faced demands for an apology earlier this year after his private comments about "shithole countries" in Africa and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Kenyan president rebukes Theresa May on last day of Africa trip - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/aug/30/kenya-president-rebukes-theresa-may-last-day-africa-trip</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE4B523HCtxsl6juntF5ZT4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 11:31:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/aug/30/kenya-president-rebukes-theresa-may-last-day-africa-trip" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan president rebukes Theresa May on last day of Africa trip&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya’s president has complained that no British prime minister has visited the east African country for 30 years, delivering a diplomatic rebuke to Theresa May in a press conference on the final day of her visit to the continent. Uhuru Kenyatta told May he was pleased she had “found time” to visit and went on to struggle to remember Boris Johnson’s surname at the culmination of a three-day trip aimed at boosting Britain’s trade and diplomatic presence in the country. The president began proceedings by saying he was glad May had “honoured our invitation to come and see for yourself our coun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Trump Welcomes President of Kenya to White House - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-welcomes-president-of-kenya-to-white-house/4546482.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBXCTwvjC01g_jXXfVw7PxIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 21:39:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-welcomes-president-of-kenya-to-white-house/4546482.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Welcomes President of Kenya to White House&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump on Monday welcomed the president of Kenya to the White House, where the two leaders talked trade, security — and Trump’s accomplishments. Trump hosted President Uhuru Kenyatta as Kenya is emerging from a period of election turmoil. He’s the second African leader to meet with Trump at the White House, following a visit by Nigeria’s president earlier this year. Trump has been criticized for paying too little attention to the continent and faced demands for an apology earlier this year after his private comments about “shithole countries” in Africa and other regions were...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>PM May says Britain committed to free trade with Kenya after Brexit - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-britain-may/pm-may-says-britain-committed-to-free-trade-with-kenya-after-brexit-idUSKCN1LF139</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPEvkDxcUrbzpLZc42RCq-EqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 12:49:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-britain-may/pm-may-says-britain-committed-to-free-trade-with-kenya-after-brexit-idUSKCN1LF139" target="_blank"&gt;PM May says Britain committed to free trade with Kenya after Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain is committed to free trade with Kenya after it leaves the European Union, British Prime Minister Theresa May said on Thursday on a visit to Nairobi as her government plays up increased trade with non-EU nations as a Brexit selling point. May was speaking on the third stop of a trip to Africa during which she has said she wants Britain to become the biggest investor on the continent out of the world's richest nations. [L8N1VJ180] "As Britain prepares to leave the European Union we are committed to a smooth transition that ensures continuity in our trading relationship with Kenya, ens...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Britain's May in Kenya to boost economic ties amid Brexit - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/ae269b0aa30b46de87dff712204360dc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMczLfnXeTId5ahkrWLEVd8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 17:32:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/ae269b0aa30b46de87dff712204360dc" target="_blank"&gt;Britain's May in Kenya to boost economic ties amid Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya (AP) — British Prime Minister Theresa May on Thursday became the first UK leader to visit Kenya in 30 years, bringing security and development funding to East Africa's commercial hub and neighboring Somalia as Britain seeks to boost economic ties ahead of a bumpy exit from the European Union in March. May met with President Uhuru Kenyatta on the last stop of her three-country Africa tour, which also included South Africa and Nigeria, the continent's top economies. The prime minister was travelling with a large business delegation as Britain wants to push its trade with Africa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Theresa May filmed dancing for second time on African trip - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/theresa-may-dancing-video-kenya-scouts-south-africa-visit-tour-brexit-trade-a8515346.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH2fA0SVjzaiRfyxZMAPj80qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDyxv0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 20:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/theresa-may-dancing-video-kenya-scouts-south-africa-visit-tour-brexit-trade-a8515346.html" target="_blank"&gt;Theresa May filmed dancing for second time on African trip&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May has been filmed dancing for the second time on her tour of Africa as she tries to tie down trade deals ahead of Brexit. The prime minister showed off more of her “Maybot” moves when she met a group of scouts in Kenya on Thursday. In footage shared online, Ms May is seen copying a dance routine being performed by members of the organisation, raising her hands to the sky. Wearing a pair of her trademark leopard print shoes, she then begins shuffling her feet and bobbing to the music. - Read more Theresa May filmed dancing with schoolchildren in South Africa Ms May’s apparent willi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Kenya Deputy Chief Justice arrested over alleged corruption - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/9b04310e5f8846dead94a6e684061813</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFreViRGHGnppLEdLgc0R6AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 16:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/9b04310e5f8846dead94a6e684061813" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Deputy Chief Justice arrested over alleged corruption&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya (AP) — Kenya's deputy chief justice, the country's second highest ranking judicial officer, was arrested Tuesday for alleged abuse of office, tax evasion and taking of bribes. Philomena Mwilu was released on $50,000 bail until Wednesday when she will be asked to answer to the charges. Kenya's director of prosecutions Noordin Haji said he ordered Mwilu's arrest and that the decision was made "independently" but many Kenyans remember that President Uhuru Kenyatta had warned of unspecified action against the judiciary when the Supreme Court nullified his election victory last ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Kenyan President Believes Peace With Opposition Will Hold - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenyan-president-believes-peace-with-opposition-will-hold/4546019.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGq0pdEZ25gCteWM8DsHh8QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 16:09:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenyan-president-believes-peace-with-opposition-will-hold/4546019.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan President Believes Peace With Opposition Will Hold&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta says his meeting Monday with U.S. President Donald Trump at the White House will focus on trade and security issues. In a wide-ranging interview Sunday evening at the Hay-Adams hotel near the White House, Kenyatta told VOA's English to Africa service that he believes his own country can attain domestic peace and security, after several election cycles marred by violence and disputes about the results. He also addressed efforts to bring stability to South Sudan, Ethiopia and Somalia. The following is an edited transcript of his remarks. VOA: "Let's talk about ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenya Charges Top Officials With Fraud Over New $3B Railway - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-charges-top-officials-with-fraud-over-new-3b-railway/4527430.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPUDj2C6uH5dp5W_lzxZndcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 00:30:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-charges-top-officials-with-fraud-over-new-3b-railway/4527430.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Charges Top Officials With Fraud Over New $3B Railway&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Kenyan court on Monday charged the heads of the agency that manages public land and of the state railway with fraud over land allocation for a new $3 billion train line linking the capital with East Africa's biggest port. The line between Nairobi and Mombasa, funded by China, is one of the biggest infrastructure projects of President Uhuru Kenyatta, whose government this year embarked on an anti-graft drive. Mohammed Abdalla Swazuri, chairman of the National Land Commission, Atanas Kariuki Maina, managing director of the Kenya Railways Corporation and 16 other businesspeople and companies...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenyan President Kenyatta to Visit White House - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenyan-president-kenyatta-to-visit-white-house/4515722.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAPMvYf5BTarsmolzKIF_CgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 17:07:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenyan-president-kenyatta-to-visit-white-house/4515722.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan President Kenyatta to Visit White House&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White House announced Monday that Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta would visit August 27. Kenyatta will meet with President Trump to discuss "ways to bolster trade and investment between the two countries, while strengthening security cooperation," according to a White House statement. In June, a U.S. delegation that included undersecretary for Commerce Gilbert Kaplan visited Kenya to attend the inaugural American Chamber of Commerce meeting. Kenyatta attended that gathering. Kaplan told VOA economic development in Africa would benefit the U.S. economy, and that the U.S. was providing re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenya: Officials accused of corruption in flagship rail project - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/08/kenya-officials-accused-corruption-flagship-rail-project-180811130432178.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQGgsWozHCUL4j-UJhwgpEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 16:50:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/08/kenya-officials-accused-corruption-flagship-rail-project-180811130432178.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya: Officials accused of corruption in flagship rail project&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenyan authorities have arrested several senior officials on suspicion of corruption over their management of a flagship $3.2bn railway project. The National Prosecution Authority said in a statement on Saturday that it had agreed to charge 14 civil servants and business people, as well as three companies, over compensation for land purchased for the construction of the Chinese-funded line linking the capital, Nairobi, to the coastal city of Mombasa. Among those indicted were Mohammed Abdalla Swazuri, chairman of the National Land Commission (NLC), and Atanas Kariuki Maina, managing directo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>South Sudan Peace Deal Can Work – if Leaders Can Cooperate - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/south-sudan-peace-deal-can-work-if-leaders-can-cooperate/4515568.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGB8Z8UZ3qTpsYSKVcq3yWIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 15:55:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/south-sudan-peace-deal-can-work-if-leaders-can-cooperate/4515568.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Sudan Peace Deal Can Work – if Leaders Can Cooperate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Sudan leaders agreed to end hostilities Sunday in the latest attempt to end the country’s five-year civil war, which has killed tens of thousands of people. Some analysts say the deal will succeed only if the country's political leaders can finally find a way to work together. South Sudanese leaders have once again agreed to end the war and work towards peace. East African head of states gathered Sunday in Khartoum to witness the signing of a new peace deal between the government of President Salva Kiir, rebel leader Riek Machar and other opposition groups. The sides all agreed to e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Africa Asks UN for Court Opinion on Immunity for Leaders - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/africa-asks-un-court-opinion-immunity-leaders/4510298.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGKDqwc0ctxTPU3-TnXcFEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 02:19:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/africa-asks-un-court-opinion-immunity-leaders/4510298.html" target="_blank"&gt;Africa Asks UN for Court Opinion on Immunity for Leaders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya is asking the United Nations on behalf of African states to request an advisory opinion from the International Court of Justice on immunity for heads of state and government and other senior officials. The request by Kenyan Ambassador Lazarus Ombai Amayo follows a decision by the African Union in January to seek an opinion from the court, the U.N.’s highest judicial body. Some African countries have been highly critical of the International Criminal Court for pursuing the continent’s leaders, including Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir and President Uhuru Kenyatta of Kenya. In a lette...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta Fires Tycoon Chris Kirubi From Plum Job - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mfonobongnsehe/2018/07/16/kenyan-president-uhuru-kenyatta-fires-tycoon-chris-kirubi-from-plum-job/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTkGCmO7sRz0aWX3_Ac_HoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mfonobongnsehe/2018/07/16/kenyan-president-uhuru-kenyatta-fires-tycoon-chris-kirubi-from-plum-job/" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta Fires Tycoon Chris Kirubi From Plum Job&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BERLIN – APRIL 21: U2 lead singer Bono (R) and Global Business Coalition on HIV/AIDS board member Chris Kirubi attend the ‘Global Business Coalition on HIV/AIDS Awards and Dinner’ at the DaimlerChrysler Atrium on April 21, 2004 in Berlin, Germany. (Photo by Sean Gallup/Getty Images) Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta has revoked his appointment of multi-millionaire businessman Chris Kirubi as the Non-Executive Chairperson of the Brand Kenya board. Brand Kenya, is a state agency mandated to coordinate marketing initiatives for the country through distinguishing Kenyan products, services and con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Obama in Kenya for First Visit to Africa Since Leaving White House - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/obama-in-kenya-for-first-visit-to-africa-since-leaving-white-house/4484778.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ23fHRkye7nZVA3jykua80qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 17:24:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/obama-in-kenya-for-first-visit-to-africa-since-leaving-white-house/4484778.html" target="_blank"&gt;Obama in Kenya for First Visit to Africa Since Leaving White House&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former U.S. President Barack Obama arrived in Kenya on Sunday for his first visit to Africa since leaving the White House. On Monday, he spoke at the small village that was his late father's homeland. This is the fifth time that Obama has visited Kenya, his father's birthplace. Upon arriving in Nairobi on Sunday, he held talks with Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta and opposition leader Raila Odinga. On Monday, he inaugurated the Sauti Kuu Foundation, a sports and vocational training center set up by his half-sister in the small western Kenyan town of Kogelo. Kogelo was the hometown of Barack...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Obama praises Kenya's political reconciliation - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/8b0210b2f2294bbbafb88fd8f4c31148</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGqUJvZS7KIygVAkRQ7Mk1kqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 00:25:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/8b0210b2f2294bbbafb88fd8f4c31148" target="_blank"&gt;Obama praises Kenya's political reconciliation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya (AP) — Former U.S. President Barack Obama Monday praised Kenya's president and opposition leader for working together but said this East African country must do more to end corruption. Obama, on his first visit to Africa since stepping down as president, commended President Uhuru Kenyatta and opposition leader Raila Odinga for cooperating following last year's disputed presidential election which were marked by violence. "Despite some of the tumultuous times that seem to attend every election we now have a president and major opposition leader who have pledged to build bridge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Kenya Power CEO under arrest over allegations of economic crimes: police - Reuters</title><link>https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-corruption/kenya-power-ceo-under-arrest-over-allegations-of-economic-crimes-police-idUSKBN1K510V?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK2IBWVWFvywL1749xiLA9IqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 20:24:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-corruption/kenya-power-ceo-under-arrest-over-allegations-of-economic-crimes-police-idUSKBN1K510V?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Power CEO under arrest over allegations of economic crimes: police&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya Power's Chief Executive Officer gave himself up to police on Sunday and was in their custody, police said, a day after the east African country said it wanted to charge him over alleged economic crimes. Kenya has had a new series of scandals involving bogus tenders and suppliers with the alleged theft of hundreds of millions of shillings by state officials from several government bodies. The Directorate of Criminal Investigations said on Twitter that Ken Tarus, the head of the state-run power distributor, was in their custody. Tarus was not immediately reachable for comment. Over the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://internal.www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Kenya Signs Deal to Return Stolen Wealth From Switzerland - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-signs-deal-to-return-stolen-wealth-from-switzerland/4476607.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGREOoAWjSr4uFwYhluRDI0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 17:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-signs-deal-to-return-stolen-wealth-from-switzerland/4476607.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Signs Deal to Return Stolen Wealth From Switzerland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya's President Uhuru Kenyatta and his Swiss counterpart Alain Berset have signed an agreement aimed at helping Kenya recover illegally acquired assets that were stashed in Swiss banks. Kenyatta and Berset signed the agreement Monday during the Swiss president's two-day visit to Kenya. The agreement, known as the Framework for the Return of Assets from Corruption and Crime in Kenya, or FRACCK, creates a mechanism for Kenya to recover money swindled from state coffers by corrupt individuals and hidden in Switzerland. The agreement is the latest move in Kenyatta’s campaign against corruptio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Obama is in Kenya for his sister's project. Then he's off to South Africa - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/15/africa/obama-kenya-south-africa-visit/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWhLzB8ILWmYFtVHxmvx3IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 12:17:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/15/africa/obama-kenya-south-africa-visit/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Obama is in Kenya for his sister's project. Then he's off to South Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former US President Barack Obama arrived in Kenya on Sunday for a quick family visit before he heads to South Africa to attend Nelson Mandela's birthday tribute. This is his first trip to the country of his father's birth since leaving office. Obama met Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta, opposition leader Raila Odinga and other top officials after his arrival. On Monday, he'll attend the inauguration of a sports and vocational center founded by his sister, Auma Obama. "Given that his own mission under the Obama Foundation is to inspire and empower people to change the world, his attendance at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US Delegation Attends Kenya's Inaugural Economic Summit - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-delegation-attends-kenya-inaugural-economic-summit/4459148.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENWe3jCmaKy8fOjJ9erILDsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 22:57:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-delegation-attends-kenya-inaugural-economic-summit/4459148.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Delegation Attends Kenya's Inaugural Economic Summit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A U.S. delegation traveled to Kenya on Thursday to attend the inaugural economic summit of the American Chamber of Commerce, Kenya. About 500 delegates, including Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta and Gilbert Kaplan, U.S. undersecretary of commerce for international trade, other high-ranking government officials from both nations and representatives from nearly 30 major U.S. corporations, gathered at the summit, which was aimed at creating partnerships between the two nations' public and private sectors in order to foster economic growth. AMCHAM economic summit drew more than 500 delegates to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>At least 15 dead in Kenya market blaze - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/28/africa/fire-outbreak-kenya-market/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMvg5CB9ZVLbXZa4YFdjth8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 13:57:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/28/africa/fire-outbreak-kenya-market/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;At least 15 dead in Kenya market blaze&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 15 people, including young children, died after a popular market caught fire early Thursday in Kenya's capital, Nairobi. About 70 people were injured in the fire and 15 homes destroyed,according to the St. John's Ambulance, which has been attending to casualties at the scene. Some of the injured are hospitalized in critical condition, Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta said in a statement. The fire broke out at around 2:30 a.m. local time Thursday and was contained two hours later, the ambulance service said. Gikomba is one of the largest markets in Nairobi, selling everything from ti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>East Africa Agrees to Improve Trade, Security - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/east-africa-agrees-to-improve-trade-and-security/4456937.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECwGDBta6ZVCibDzJGUg07EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 18:09:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/east-africa-agrees-to-improve-trade-and-security/4456937.html" target="_blank"&gt;East Africa Agrees to Improve Trade, Security&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leaders in east Africa have agreed to work together to build a single railroad and highway network to enhance integration in the region. Leaders and representatives of eight countries met in Kenya Tuesday for the 14th time to discuss the northern corridor project aimed at improving trade and tightening security. The representatives stressed the need for better movement of people, goods and services with better joint infrastructure. Kenya got the go-ahead to continue building its standard gauge railways to the Uganda border. Kenya is about to finish the second phase of the rail line between ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Fire sweeps through market in Kenya's capital, killing 15 - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f8eb1a00337f430b9f3de01d063dc2c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0F_djLTctTkCb6MYEjTP8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 13:26:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f8eb1a00337f430b9f3de01d063dc2c0" target="_blank"&gt;Fire sweeps through market in Kenya's capital, killing 15&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya (AP) — A fire swept through one of Nairobi's largest open-air markets early Thursday, killing 15 people and sending 70 injured to hospitals, an official said, as traders who lived there struggled to wake their families and flee. Young children were among the victims, President Uhuru Kenyatta said in a statement, and many of the injured were in critical condition. Gikomba market has burned several times in recent years, and Kenyatta said that "we owe the victims, and the people of Nairobi, a clear, credible plan to end these fires." Nairobi County Commissioner Kangethe Thuku s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Kenya’s President Mandates Lifestyle Audit for Public Servants - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-president-mandates-lifetyle-audit-for-public-servants/4442016.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGIpRXv_Spskk6a8XpRisNkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 20:49:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-president-mandates-lifetyle-audit-for-public-servants/4442016.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya’s President Mandates Lifestyle Audit for Public Servants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya’s President Uhuru Kenyatta has intensified his war on graft by announcing that all public servants will undergo a compulsory lifestyle audit to account for their sources of wealth. This latest announcement follows financial scandals that have rocked the country with revelations that millions of dollars were lost in various government agencies through corrupt deals that involved government officials. Kenyatta offered himself to be the first leader to undergo the audit that seeks to identify corrupt public officials, saying the lifestyle audits would control the misuse of public funds. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>What Jean-Pierre Bemba's acquittal by the ICC means - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/jean-pierre-bemba-acquittal-icc-means-180612121012078.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJox4NVq9eTmfOAdN8HqhBIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 05:52:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/jean-pierre-bemba-acquittal-icc-means-180612121012078.html" target="_blank"&gt;What Jean-Pierre Bemba's acquittal by the ICC means&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 8, the International Criminal Court (ICC) shocked the international justice community and the world by overturning the war crimes conviction of the Democratic Republic of the Congo's former Vice President Jean-Pierre Bemba. Bemba's acquittal is a major event that will have significant consequences for the ICC, the Central African Republic (CAR) and the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC). Bemba had been in custody in The Hague for 10 years and was convicted in 2016 under the command responsibility legal doctrine for having failed to prevent his militia from committing crimes in t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Kenya accounting officials to have anti-corruption vetting - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/b78a8c7f58984061ac28682d685ebade</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEMZVJDYDOsS5lePvKOEWhkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 17:50:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/b78a8c7f58984061ac28682d685ebade" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya accounting officials to have anti-corruption vetting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya (AP) — All procurement and accounting officers in Kenya's ministries and state-owned corporations are to leave their offices for fresh screening, an official announced Monday, as President Uhuru Kenyatta's government grapples with endemic corruption. The officers are to submit personal information including their assets, liabilities and previous record of service by Friday, according to a statement signed by Interior Ministry Spokesman Mwenda Njoka. He said he does not know how many officers will be affected, but some experts say that more than 500 officials will have to step...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Kenyan President orders top officials to take lie-detector tests in corruption crackdown - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/02/africa/kenya-officials-lie-detector-tests/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENeme8JjdMeZ0_zEP8XAo9AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 08:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/02/africa/kenya-officials-lie-detector-tests/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan President orders top officials to take lie-detector tests in corruption crackdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta is ordering top procurement officials in government offices to undergo lie-detector tests as part of a corruption crackdown following a series of scandals. Kenyatta's announcement Friday comes after nearly 9 billion Kenya shillings ( $90 million) vanished from the National Youth Service, a government agency that provides training opportunities for young people. It later emerged that the funds were allegedly stolen through fake invoices for services that were never rendered. Dozens of people have been arrested and are facing charges over the alleged theft. Ken...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kenya Protesters March Against New Corruption Scandal - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-protesters-march-against-new-corruption-scandal/4417698.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJYIEVevGK-zJjYv0HgCWIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 15:46:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-protesters-march-against-new-corruption-scandal/4417698.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Protesters March Against New Corruption Scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protesters marched in Nairobi Thursday after revelations that more than $100 million in public money has been stolen. The protest comes one day after 24 government workers and business people were charged in a Kenyan court over the theft. Dressed in red t-shirts, chanting "we want our money back," protesters took to the streets of the Kenyan capital to register their anger with the runaway corruption in the country's youth agency. It's the second scandal in three years to hit the agency, which provides job training and other services for young people. In both instances, workers in charge of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenya Charges 54 in Graft Investigation - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-charges-54-in-graft-investigation/4413603.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEtlVCVarHhZ4aQDISzISHgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 21:49:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-charges-54-in-graft-investigation/4413603.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Charges 54 in Graft Investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenyan authorities charged 54 people, mainly civil servants, on Monday in an investigation into the theft of nearly $100 million of public funds, a rare move to hold officials to account for graft in a nation where it is widespread. Among the civil servants and businesspeople charged was the head of the National Youth Service, where the corruption allegedly took place, senior accountants at the government agency, and the chief internal auditor at the national treasury, chief prosecutor Noordin Mohamed Haji told a news conference. President Uhuru Kenyatta's pledged to stamp out graft when he...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenya arrests youth service chief after theft of funds: media - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-corruption/kenya-arrests-youth-service-chief-after-theft-of-funds-media-idUSKCN1IT0CA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG7SObojCMFfujSP5C7BMAUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 05:31:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-corruption/kenya-arrests-youth-service-chief-after-theft-of-funds-media-idUSKCN1IT0CA" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya arrests youth service chief after theft of funds: media&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI (Reuters) - Kenyan authorities have arrested the head of the National Youth Service as part of investigations into a $99-million theft of funds, media said on Monday. Despite President Uhuru Kenyatta's pledges to stamp out graft when he was first elected in 2013, critics say he has been slow to pursue top officials, adding that only big-name convictions will break what they call a culture of impunity. Privately-owned Citizen Television and K24 TV said the youth agency official, Richard Ndubai, had been arrested, along with an unspecified number of officials. Kenyan media have said 1...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Kenyan Multi-Millionaire Joshua Kulei, Former President Daniel Moi Look To Acquire 5-Star Hotel - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mfonobongnsehe/2018/05/25/kenyan-multi-millionaire-joshua-kulei-former-president-daniel-moi-look-to-acquire-5-star-hotel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOKEGnr1D4lEmlcGj9l_aoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 15:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mfonobongnsehe/2018/05/25/kenyan-multi-millionaire-joshua-kulei-former-president-daniel-moi-look-to-acquire-5-star-hotel/" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan Multi-Millionaire Joshua Kulei, Former President Daniel Moi Look To Acquire 5-Star Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Portraits of Kenya’s successive Presidents (from right to left), first President Jomo Kenyatta (1964-1978), the second President Daniel Moi (1978-2002), the third President Mwai Kibaki (2002-2013) and the forth incubent President Uhuru Kenyatta, are seen on a wall at the Kasarani Stadium in Nairobi, on May 12, 2018. (Photo by Yasuyoshi CHIBA / AFP/ Getty Images) Sovereign Group, an investment company controlled by Kenyan multi-millionaire tycoon Joshua Kulei, a former Private Secretary to former President Daniel Arap Moi, is set acquire a 33.8% government-owned stake in the 5-star InterCont...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Kenya Approves Controversial Cybercrimes Law - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/critics-kenyan-cyber-crimes-law-to-crush-freedom-of-speech/4396882.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOwuYiuYyyC-JnU6Hv5u04oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 21:00:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/critics-kenyan-cyber-crimes-law-to-crush-freedom-of-speech/4396882.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Approves Controversial Cybercrimes Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya has approved a controversial new cybercrimes law that threatens heavy penalties for people who abuse others via social media – and that some critics contend could be used to stifle freedom of expression. Among other things, the computer and cybercrimes legislation – which President Uhuru Kenyatta signed into law on Wednesday – makes it a crime to publish so-called false information, with hefty fines and prison terms for those found guilty. The law does not define false information, saying only that it's a criminal offense to intentionally publish false, misleading or fictitious data, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenya bans its first Cannes-bound feature film over 'lesbianism' - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-04-28/kenya-bans-1st-cannes-bound-feature-film-over-lesbianism/9707322</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGe_aZkLSNQ4RuZnxW2Cp9wqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDc2g4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 07:52:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-04-28/kenya-bans-1st-cannes-bound-feature-film-over-lesbianism/9707322" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya bans its first Cannes-bound feature film over 'lesbianism'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya has banned its first feature film to premiere at the Cannes Film Festival, accusing it of having "clear intent to promote lesbianism in Kenya contrary to the law." Key points: - The film depicts a love story between two women, debuts at Cannes 2018 - Homosexuality is outlawed in Kenya, gay sex faces up to 14 years in prison - The Kenyan film board said the approved script didn't include romantic scenes between female actors Director Wanuri Kahiu said she is "incredibly sorry" to confirm the ban of "Rafiki", or "Friend" in Swahili, by the Kenya Film Classification Board. Her film depic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Kenyatta rejects role in election violence - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/04/19/amanpour-uhuru-kenyatta.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFvwp81FebFdDiyuAAlBpdsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 15:17:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/04/19/amanpour-uhuru-kenyatta.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyatta rejects role in election violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya's President Uhuru Kenyatta says his govt. had no responsibility for election violence, and assures those affected will have a channel to seek justice. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kenyatta denies ties to Cambridge Analytica - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/04/19/amanpour-kenyatta-cambridge-analytica.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGA0DF6HaxG6jnu35fIgHqUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 15:14:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/04/19/amanpour-kenyatta-cambridge-analytica.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyatta denies ties to Cambridge Analytica&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenyan president Uhuru Kenyatta denies any connection to the controversial data firm Cambridge Analytica. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>President: Gay rights 'of no importance' in Kenya - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/04/20/kenya-uhuru-kenyatta-gay-rights-intv-amanpour-intl.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELQH1mkocuJDHclUvH7uo_QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 14:38:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/04/20/kenya-uhuru-kenyatta-gay-rights-intv-amanpour-intl.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;President: Gay rights 'of no importance' in Kenya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an interview with Christiane Amanpour, President Uhuru Kenyatta claims that homosexuality is not an issue of human rights, but rather of "our own base as a culture." ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kenyan deputy president fiercely criticises stock exchange - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8d5fa36c-43df-11e8-93cf-67ac3a6482fd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHmcB07ftOj6o0qWN7pNCEMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 22:12:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8d5fa36c-43df-11e8-93cf-67ac3a6482fd" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan deputy president fiercely criticises stock exchange&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya’s deputy president has launched a scathing attack on the country’s securities exchange for failing to bring more private sector companies to market. William Ruto told an African Securities Exchanges Association conference in Nairobi that the Nairobi Securities Exchange “was supposed to help us support more companies, especially the big companies, [to] package them so they can go to the stock exchange”. “Unfortunately, good people, we are not there yet,” he said, without naming any companies that should have listed. “You have some homework to consider why we aren’t making as much progr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Kenya Electoral Body in Turmoil After 3 Commissioners Resign - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-electoral-body-turmil-three-commissioners-resign/4350172.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIPVkFm-bTi89Rdg9FySvggqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 18:13:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-electoral-body-turmil-three-commissioners-resign/4350172.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Electoral Body in Turmoil After 3 Commissioners Resign&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tumult continues at Kenya's independent electoral commission (IEBC) nearly seven months after elections ended. Three commissioners quit their jobs Monday, saying the commission is dysfunctional and too vulnerable to meddling The commissioners' complaint echoes concerns raised during last October's contentious polls. Speaking to journalists Monday in Nairobi, Independent Electoral and Boundaries Commission official Margaret Mwachanya said the head of the electoral body has failed. "Given this severe deterioration of confidence in the commission chair, we find our position as commissioners un...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenya electoral board commissioners resign over leadership row - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/04/kenya-electoral-board-commissioners-resign-leadership-row-180416074428585.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECD_UI1KrOZ3fWnBPFNuzpUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 11:29:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/04/kenya-electoral-board-commissioners-resign-leadership-row-180416074428585.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya electoral board commissioners resign over leadership row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Half of Kenya's electoral board has resigned "with immediate effect", as the commissioners cited lack of faith in the organisation's leadership. Vice chair of Kenya's Independent Electoral and Boundaries Commission (IEBC) Connie Nkatha Maina and two commissioners - Margaret Mwachanya and Paul Kurgat - said they left their posts because they have no faith in chair Wafula Chebukati, adding that the organisation is dysfunctional. "The institution has continued to be dysfunctional, with arbitrary decision-making, leaking of internal documents ... and pursuing of personal interests," the three o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Kenyan opposition politician 'detained in airport toilet' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/mar/28/kenyan-opposition-politician-detained-in-airport-toilet</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9t-zr3cxmGWwF6xQQ9ljEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 10:37:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/mar/28/kenyan-opposition-politician-detained-in-airport-toilet" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan opposition politician 'detained in airport toilet'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Kenyan opposition politician says he has been detained in a toilet at the country’s main airport since Tuesday after he refused to be deported. Miguna Miguna was previously deported to Canada on 6 February in a crackdown on politicians who attended a mock inauguration of the opposition leader, Raila Odinga, to protest against the re-election of the Kenyan president Uhuru Kenyatta. Later in February a court ordered that Miguna’s Kenyan passport be restored and he be given safe passage back into the country. When he tried to return on Monday, Miguna was denied entry at Jomo Kenyatta airport...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Kenyan Opposition Politician Deported Again - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-miguna-deportation/4322225.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB6wLJeNIqA12BjHwSYWXJkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 14:02:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-miguna-deportation/4322225.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan Opposition Politician Deported Again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Kenyan opposition politician says authorities drugged and forcibly deported him to Dubai. Miguna Miguna says in a Facebook post that he had been detained in a bathroom at Nairobi's international airport since Monday, when he returned from Canada after being deported last month. Miguna says authorities broke into the bathroom Thursday and injected him with a substance, then dragged him to an Emirates Airline plane. Lawyers for Miguna said their client was deported despite a court order mandating his release. A High Court judge on Wednesday declared the interior minister and national poli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenyan police detain opposition politician at airport in scuffle: lawyer - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-politics/kenyan-government-tries-to-deport-opposition-politician-again-lawyer-idUSKBN1H30FU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOr8Hfn9RyYg3N4zJzdT0-kqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 08:09:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-politics/kenyan-government-tries-to-deport-opposition-politician-again-lawyer-idUSKBN1H30FU" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan police detain opposition politician at airport in scuffle: lawyer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI (Reuters) - The lawyer of an opposition politician of dual Kenyan and Canadian citizenship said on Tuesday his client was detained by police at Nairobi airport during an attempt to force him onto a plane to Canada. Miguna Miguna, a lawyer, was deported by Kenyan authorities in February for his role in a protest by opposition leader Raila Odinga, who maintains he was the winner of an election that returned President Uhuru Kenyatta to power last year. Shortly before his deportation, which came after Odinga enraged the government by staging a symbolic "swearing-in ceremony", Miguna was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Opposition leader 'drugged and deported' from Kenya - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/03/29/opposition-leader-drugged-deported-kenya/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKNhz3SBk6fngr_nBUtmHX0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 20:04:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/03/29/opposition-leader-drugged-deported-kenya/" target="_blank"&gt;Opposition leader 'drugged and deported' from Kenya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A prominent Kenyan opposition figure was in hospital in the United Arab Emirates last night after he was allegedly drugged by security officials at Nairobi’s international airport and forced on to a Dubai-bound flight. Miguna Miguna had earlier been deported from Kenya for the second time in two months, in contravention of a series of court orders, after a 72-hour stand-off at the airport, much of which he claimed to have spent locked in a lavatory. Amid mounting concerns for the rule of law in one of Africa’s most vibrant democracies, a judge found Kenya’s powerful interior minister, its p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Kenyan Opposition Lawyer Detained at Airport on Arrival - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-opposition-lawyer-detained-at-airport-for-more-than-24-hours-after-arrival-in-the-country/4320966.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDsu1rmuopFuGG9b-eH2L1AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 17:58:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-opposition-lawyer-detained-at-airport-for-more-than-24-hours-after-arrival-in-the-country/4320966.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan Opposition Lawyer Detained at Airport on Arrival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Kenyan opposition leader remains detained at Nairobi airport, barred from entering the country despite a judge's order that authorities allow him to appear before the High Court Wednesday. The standoff has called into question the public reconciliation of Kenya's top political rivals earlier this month. Opposition supporters on Wednesday blocked the main highway linking the cities of Kisumu and Kakamega, lighting bonfires. The protesters were demanding the release of high-ranking opposition leader Miguna Miguna. Kenya's High Court on Tuesday ordered that Miguna be released and appear in c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>After 2016 Election, US Poised to Fight Fake News - in Kenya - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/elections-2016-fake-news-kenya/4305025.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENCtLvs3IbP06MVu-1AMiykqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 11:58:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/elections-2016-fake-news-kenya/4305025.html" target="_blank"&gt;After 2016 Election, US Poised to Fight Fake News - in Kenya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just ahead of Kenya's disputed 2017 election, video clips started spreading on social media of a slick-looking CNN broadcast asserting that President Uhuru Kenyatta had pulled far ahead in the polls. But the CNN broadcast was fake, splicing together real coverage from CNN Philippines with other footage with the network's iconic red logo superimposed in the corner. It happened with a BBC video, too, and with a photo purportedly of Kenyan security forces killing protesters that was actually from Tanzania, and with thousands of spurious blog posts and other false reports that flooded the popul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenya Airways ‘optimistic’ mid-turnround - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2beff760-2cdf-11e8-a34a-7e7563b0b0f4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_sIhCrbTp-17ckOiyscy4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 08:20:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2beff760-2cdf-11e8-a34a-7e7563b0b0f4" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Airways ‘optimistic’ mid-turnround&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya Airways continued its financial turnround in 2017 despite a prolonged political crisis in its domestic market, rising fuel costs and a costly restructuring, the airline reported on Wednesday. However Sebastian Mikosz, chief executive, told the Financial Times that while the finances were improving “we still have a big industrial turnround to continue”. Losses before tax were cut to Ks5.97bn ($59.0m) for the nine months to December 2017 from Ks10.2bn for the 12 months to March 2017, while operating profit rose to Ks1.3bn from K897m for the same periods. Kenya Airways reported nine mont...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Kenyatta and Odinga vow to work out differences - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/03/kenyatta-odinga-amends-tillerson-visit-180309172042412.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMhKjIwObTO-BhjM0umCajIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 18:10:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/03/kenyatta-odinga-amends-tillerson-visit-180309172042412.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyatta and Odinga vow to work out differences&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya's feuding political leaders have announced they will meet to resolve their differences. President Uhuru Kenyatta and opposition leader Raila Odinga have been at odds since 2017 elections that saw about 100 people killed in clashes between opposition supporters and security forces. Odinga told national television on Friday "it is time to resolve our differences", as the two politicians made their first public appearance together since the October presidential elections. Kenyatta said they "have a responsibility as leaders to find solutions. Elections come and go but Kenya remains". He ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Kenyan President, opposition leader say feud over after months of tension - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/03/09/africa/kenya-odinga-kenyatta-joint-speech/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_sAb4yBD3e5R0dprrcf4kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 13:17:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/03/09/africa/kenya-odinga-kenyatta-joint-speech/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan President, opposition leader say feud over after months of tension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After months of political tension, Kenyan President Uhuru Kenyatta and longtime opposition rival Raila Odinga made a joint television address Friday, referring to each other as brothers who are no longer feuding. The two have been at odds since the presidential election in August, which the nation's highest court nullified over poll irregularities. Odinga later boycotted the repeat vote in October, saying the electoral commission had not implemented any reforms. The joint appearance Friday is the first time Kenyatta and Odinga have met publicly since the election, Kenyan media reported. It ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Tillerson ‘Not Feeling Well,’ Cancels Saturday Events in Kenya - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/tillerson-says-political-reonciliation-in-kenya-very-positive-step/4288752.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFl7_3GdWLHjoUj4CTmRQDwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:38:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/tillerson-says-political-reonciliation-in-kenya-very-positive-step/4288752.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tillerson ‘Not Feeling Well,’ Cancels Saturday Events in Kenya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. Secretary of State Rex Tillerson cancelled events in Kenya Saturday to seek respite from what has been an extraordinarily busy schedule, according to the State Department. "The secretary is not feeling well after a long couple days working on major issues back home such as North Korea and has cancelled his events for the day," said spokesman Steve Goldstein, who is accompanying Tillerson on his trip to Africa. Goldstein added other Saturday events would proceed without Tillerson while others may be rescheduled and Tillerson was expected to resume his schedule Sunday. After meeting Frid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>U.S.'s Tillerson says Kenya should not stifle media, threaten courts - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-africa-kenya/tillerson-says-kenya-should-not-stifle-media-threaten-courts-idUSKCN1GL2CJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFTU2_-hX3yOos6dbpnSlUgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 21:21:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-africa-kenya/tillerson-says-kenya-should-not-stifle-media-threaten-courts-idUSKCN1GL2CJ" target="_blank"&gt;U.S.'s Tillerson says Kenya should not stifle media, threaten courts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI (Reuters) - U.S. Secretary of State Rex Tillerson said on Friday in Nairobi that he had shared his concerns with Kenya's president about the importance of democracy and said the government should not stifle the media and threaten the courts. The Kenyan government shut down three television channels in January on the day opposition leader Raila Odinga took a symbolic presidential oath, then defied a court order to switch them back on. The stations had planned to live-stream the oath. "We believe that there are actions that need to be taken in Kenya and that they need to correct certa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>On International Women's Day Kenyans celebrated neoliberalism - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/international-women-day-kenyans-celebrated-neoliberalism-180309191622660.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDmO3QqcLz4do1qFlSirAbAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 20:29:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/international-women-day-kenyans-celebrated-neoliberalism-180309191622660.html" target="_blank"&gt;On International Women's Day Kenyans celebrated neoliberalism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, most of the world marked International Women's Day. Some women went on strike demanding better working conditions, others protested violence and oppression, still others debated various issues related to feminism. In Kenya, the mainstream media was preoccupied with discussing the number of women in Kenyan boardrooms, while corporations used the day for cheap PR stunts (McDonalds, for example, turned the M of its logo upside down to read W). But perhaps the most bizarre part of the celebrations was the government's decision to focus on Kenya's First Lady, Margaret Gakuo Kenyatta, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Kenya's president, opposition leader pledge to heal divisions - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-politics-speeches/kenyas-president-opposition-leader-pledge-to-heal-divisions-idUSKCN1GL17U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEELT59bOfKgvArriA43wFGEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 09:50:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-politics-speeches/kenyas-president-opposition-leader-pledge-to-heal-divisions-idUSKCN1GL17U" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya's president, opposition leader pledge to heal divisions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI (Reuters) - Kenya's President Uhuru Kenyatta called opposition leader Raila Odinga "his brother" on Friday and promised "we will begin a process of bringing our people together" after last year's contentious elections. Odinga told national television "it is time to resolve our differences," as the two politicians made their first public appearance together since the Oct. 26 repeat presidential election last year. (Writing by Katharine Houreld; Editing by Hugh Lawson)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>