<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Mike Sonko - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR2RvTmpWc2F4SUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:34:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Switzerland Investigates Possible Crimes by Gambian Ex-Minister - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/switzerland-investigate-possible-crimes-by-gambian-ex-minister/3707868.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHQruJrNyaOfbq26HzNulqsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 14:14:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/switzerland-investigate-possible-crimes-by-gambian-ex-minister/3707868.html" target="_blank"&gt;Switzerland Investigates Possible Crimes by Gambian Ex-Minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gambia's former interior minister who applied for asylum in Switzerland is being investigated for possible crimes against humanity committed in his homeland, Swiss federal prosecutors said Monday. The attorney general's office said in a statement that it's taking over an investigation initially launched by regional authorities in Bern because crimes against humanity would be international offenses that fall under federal jurisdiction. Michael Lauber's office did not specify the suspect by name Monday but cited a complaint filed by Trial International. The watchdog group last month called fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Devolution gives Kenyans a taste of power as they vote governors out - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-election-devolution-idUSKCN1AY1E4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIjpkVpfUwhq2dIdiV-1efQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 13:10:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-election-devolution-idUSKCN1AY1E4" target="_blank"&gt;Devolution gives Kenyans a taste of power as they vote governors out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Katharine Houreld NAIROBI (Reuters) - As disputes raged over the presidential results from Kenya's election last week, a little-noticed democratic revolution blossomed in the layer of government directly underneath. Kenyans sent home 25 out of 47 county governors, upholding a strong anti-incumbency tradition and warning that voters would turf out failing local leaders after power and money devolved to the counties in the last election cycle. Anti-corruption campaigners - and voters - hope the new taste of direct accountability will eventually help curb corruption in East Africa's biggest...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>12 dead babies found stuffed in boxes and plastic bags in a Kenyan hospital - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/18/health/pumwani-babies-found-dead/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMIISk8Y_MG6VN7vWMGmckkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 07:41:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/18/health/pumwani-babies-found-dead/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;12 dead babies found stuffed in boxes and plastic bags in a Kenyan hospital&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The governor of Nairobi has ordered an investigation after he visited a hospital in the Kenyan capital and found 12 dead babies stuffed in boxes and plastic bags. Gov. Mike Sonko said he went to the Pumwani Maternity Hospital on Monday after he received reports of negligence and of employees carrying bodies from hospital rooms. "During the impromptu visit, I uncovered 12 bodies of infants who died at the hospital mysteriously and their bodies hidden in boxes and paper bags inside a room," Sonko said in a statement. The visit was captured on video In a confrontation Sonko captured on video a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Nairobi governor orders investigation into deaths of 12 babies at maternity hospital - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-hospital-babies/nairobi-governor-orders-investigation-into-deaths-of-12-babies-at-maternity-hospital-idUSKCN1LX28V</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBmT6gUoIREnGCJ4hr3TCZsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 18:46:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-hospital-babies/nairobi-governor-orders-investigation-into-deaths-of-12-babies-at-maternity-hospital-idUSKCN1LX28V" target="_blank"&gt;Nairobi governor orders investigation into deaths of 12 babies at maternity hospital&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The governor of Nairobi found the bodies of 12 infants in the mortuary of a hospital in the capital - an unusually high figure even amid declining standards of health care in Kenya - when he made a surprise visit to the facility at the weekend. Governor Mike Sonko on Monday ordered an investigation into the matter and suspended senior staff, his office said. It was not immediately clear what had killed the babies at the Pumwani Maternity Hospital or what had happened to their mothers. But the incident reflected declining public health care in Kenya, with patients often complaining about neg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>