<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Gulf Cooperation Council - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZuT0RkbkVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:43:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>UAE says Gulf Arab bloc still strong despite Qatar row - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar/uae-says-gulf-arab-bloc-still-strong-despite-qatar-row-idUSKBN1O50F1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJFAPHfdDXB11X4VTiWs700qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 06:37:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar/uae-says-gulf-arab-bloc-still-strong-despite-qatar-row-idUSKBN1O50F1" target="_blank"&gt;UAE says Gulf Arab bloc still strong despite Qatar row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Arab Emirates said on Thursday the Gulf Cooperation Council remained valid despite a bitter row with Qatar that has fractured the bloc ahead of an annual summit next week. Saudi Arabia, the UAE, Bahrain and non-GCC member Egypt have imposed a diplomatic and economic boycott on Qatar since June 2017 over allegations Doha supports terrorism. Qatar denies the charges and says the boycott aims to curtail its sovereignty. "The main success of the council is in its economic aspects and the creation of a Gulf common market," UAE Minister of State for Foreign Affairs Anwar Gargash tweete...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Saudi king extends invitation to Qatari emir to attend GCC summit - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/saudi-king-extends-invitation-qatari-emir-attend-gcc-summit-181204193515224.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDpLxk8xnkR9T1alkJZaRdYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 06:17:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/saudi-king-extends-invitation-qatari-emir-attend-gcc-summit-181204193515224.html" target="_blank"&gt;Saudi king extends invitation to Qatari emir to attend GCC summit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia's King Salman has invited Qatar's Emir Sheikh Tamim bin Hamad Al Thani to attend the upcoming Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) summit set to take place in Riyadh on December 9, the official Qatar News Agency reported. The announcement on Tuesday follows Qatar's decision a day earlier to withdraw from the Organisation of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC), a move seen by some analysts as deeply symbolic given Qatar's modest oil output. Qatar News Agency (QNA) said in a tweet the emir received "an invitation from the King of Saudi Arabia" for the meeting. The invitation was deliv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>US senators introduce resolution blaming MBS for Khashoggi murder - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/senators-introduce-resolution-blaming-mbs-khashoggi-murder-181206035658278.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAhcuDciw1qKGYk2GTZ97acqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 04:55:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/senators-introduce-resolution-blaming-mbs-khashoggi-murder-181206035658278.html" target="_blank"&gt;US senators introduce resolution blaming MBS for Khashoggi murder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six top US senators from across party lines have introduced a scathing resolution to hold the Saudi crown prince accountable for the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi more than two months ago. The proposal, which was introduced on Wednesday, says the Senate "has a high level of confidence" that Mohammed bin Salman "was complicit in the murder". If approved by the Senate, it would officially condemn Prince Mohammed, also known as MBS, for the killing of Khashoggi in the kingdom's consulate in the Turkish city of Istanbul in October. "This resolution - without equivocation - definitively ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Qatar’s Emir Receives Invite from Saudi King to Attend Gulf Arab Summit - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/qatar-s-emir-receives-invite-from-saudi-king-to-attend-gulf-arab-summit-/4686851.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPrTKMpYJKGIaADRCkGIdmgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:57:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/qatar-s-emir-receives-invite-from-saudi-king-to-attend-gulf-arab-summit-/4686851.html" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar’s Emir Receives Invite from Saudi King to Attend Gulf Arab Summit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar’s emir, Sheikh Tamim bin Hamad Al Thani, has received a written invitation from Saudi Arabia’s King Salman to attend an annual Gulf Arab summit being held in Riyadh on Dec. 9, the Qatar News Agency said on Tuesday. Qatar is locked in a bitter dispute with Saudi Arabia that has fractured the six-nation Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) and it has not said what level of representation it will send to the gathering of heads of state seen by analysts as unlikely to bring a diplomatic breakthrough. Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain and non-GCC member Egypt have imposed diplomati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Qatar’s emir invited to attend Gulf Arab summit in Saudi Arabia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/f02f15ba-f864-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKLaqurvYPLEIsh7_GKdvQgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:10:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f02f15ba-f864-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar’s emir invited to attend Gulf Arab summit in Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar’s emir has received an invitation to attend the Gulf Co-operation Council meeting in Saudi Arabia on Sunday, raising the prospect of a thaw in a damaging spat that has divided the Gulf nations. It is unclear whether Sheikh Tamim bin Hamad Al Thani will accept the invitation for the annual meeting of the six GCC heads of state. Saudi Arabia led four Arab nations in imposing a trade and travel embargo on Qatar in June 2017, accusing the country of sponsoring terrorism. Doha vigorously denied the allegations. The overture comes a day after Qatar announced that it would leave Opec, a surp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia refuses to engage in WTO dispute brought by Qatar - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/saudi-arabia-refuses-engage-wto-dispute-brought-qatar-181204141931031.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHI9ghCVpA8IQ3L6cTVN7nUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:44:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/saudi-arabia-refuses-engage-wto-dispute-brought-qatar-181204141931031.html" target="_blank"&gt;Saudi Arabia refuses to engage in WTO dispute brought by Qatar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia told the World Trade Organization on Tuesday that national security concerns meant it "simply will not engage in dispute settlement procedures" regarding an intellectual property complaint by Qatar. Qatar launched the dispute in October, saying Saudi Arabia was blocking Qatari-owned broadcaster beIN and refusing to take effective action against the piracy of its content by a sophisticated operation called "beoutQ". 170722144955060 BeoutQ, a 10-channel system broadcasting to the Middle East on the Arabsat satellite operator, is allegedly being transmitted from Saudi Arabia. The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Qatar’s exit from Opec deepens rift with Saudi Arabia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/f33b64de-f710-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE2vDuAi8BOIgUTNQZFPuY4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:04:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f33b64de-f710-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar’s exit from Opec deepens rift with Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar has made a shock decision to quit Opec after 57 years of membership, billing its move as an apolitical attempt to refocus on expanding its natural gas exports. But its withdrawal has stoked suspicion that Qatari leaders are seeking to irritate their regional rival Saudi Arabia and curry favour with US President Donald Trump. Saad al-Kaabi, Qatar’s minister of state for energy affairs, said the decision would enable “focused efforts” on gas production. But it created shockwaves, making Qatar the first Middle Eastern country to abandon the producer group and further fracturing Opec’s mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Gulf states 'rebuff bid to ease humanitarian impact' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/gulf-states-rebuff-bid-ease-humanitarian-impact-170719130425057.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM12Qa0g-P2WOLY_ZXC2GNMqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 21:26:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/gulf-states-rebuff-bid-ease-humanitarian-impact-170719130425057.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gulf states 'rebuff bid to ease humanitarian impact'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doha, Qatar - The head of Qatar's National Human Rights Committee (NHRC) says his efforts to ease the humanitarian impact of the blockade on Qatari and other citizens have been rebuffed by human-rights groups in neighbouring Arab Gulf states. Ali bin Smaikh al-Marri, the NHRC chairman, disclosed in Doha on Wednesday that he had sent letters to his counterparts in Saudi Arabia, UAE and Bahrain asking them to appeal to their governments to spare Gulf citizens the humanitarian, social and economic consequences of the dispute. "We either got no response or have been attacked by our colleagues w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Tillerson expresses hope over Saudi-Qatar dispute - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/de5b146e-6635-11e7-8526-7b38dcaef614</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGo3ItuhVcBUcur6rGF78fQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 15:18:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/de5b146e-6635-11e7-8526-7b38dcaef614" target="_blank"&gt;Tillerson expresses hope over Saudi-Qatar dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rex Tillerson said he was hopeful about the chances of resolving the dispute between Qatar and its neighbours despite a renewed war of words between the Gulf states. Saudi Arabia led the quartet of Arab nations that last month imposed an embargo on Qatar, accusing Doha of backing terrorism and cosying up to Iran, Riyadh’s regional rival. Doha, which denies supporting militant groups, says it is willing to discuss issues related to security but will not accept limits on its sovereignty. The US secretary of state, arriving in Qatar from Kuwait, on Tuesday described Qatar’s stance as “reasonab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>War 'stopped' between Qatar, blockading Arab nations - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/war-stopped-qatar-blockading-arab-nations-170908012658804.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAaA6tRwxoCTFJk9IIjgnuEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 01:45:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/war-stopped-qatar-blockading-arab-nations-170908012658804.html" target="_blank"&gt;War 'stopped' between Qatar, blockading Arab nations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The emir of Kuwait says the threat of war between Qatar and Arab nations blockading it for the past three months has been neutralised. Sheikh Sabah al-Ahmad Al Sabah, the main mediator in the Gulf dispute, spoke in Washington, DC on Thursday at a joint press conference with US President Donald Trump. While both sides in the dispute have ruled out the use of armed force, some ordinary Qataris say they worry about the possibility of military action, given the ferocity of the criticism their country has received from media in the four Arab states. "What is important is that we have stopped any...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>UAE Holds Out Prospect Of Qatar Being Ejected From Gulf Bloc - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2017/07/17/qatar-ejection-from-gcc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENoCU189m38mD2B3G0BmcHMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2017/07/17/qatar-ejection-from-gcc/" target="_blank"&gt;UAE Holds Out Prospect Of Qatar Being Ejected From Gulf Bloc&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar risks being effectively thrown out of the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) as a result of the current diplomatic crisis with Saudi Arabia and the UAE. Since early June, Riyadh and Abu Dhabi have cut off diplomatic and economic ties with Doha. Bahrain and Egypt have acted in concert with the two powerful Gulf countries, and a host of others around the region have also either broken diplomatic ties or downgraded them. At the heart of the dispute is allegations by the UAE and Saudi Arabia that Qatar has been offering financial and other support to terrorists and other extremist groups. The...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Qatar takes complaint of ‘illegal siege’ to WTO - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b52e9ade-7634-11e7-90c0-90a9d1bc9691</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE021QQ3JsAPHIJh9vqn4-oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 21:27:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b52e9ade-7634-11e7-90c0-90a9d1bc9691" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar takes complaint of ‘illegal siege’ to WTO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar has lodged a formal complaint with the World Trade Organisation against the “illegal siege” imposed by four Arab neighbours that have accused the Gulf state of sponsoring terrorism. The complaint, lodged with the WTO’s dispute-settlement body, described the embargo as “unprecedented”, accusing Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Egypt and Bahrain of “violating the WTO’s core laws and conventions on trade of goods and services, and trade-related aspects of intellectual property,” the ministry of economy and commerce said in a statement on Monday. On June 5, the quartet of Arab alli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>IMF cuts Qatar growth in wake of regional embargo - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e4f465e6-8d9a-11e7-a352-e46f43c5825d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM2d6DfP2JfM5jc_DcCMmvoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 18:54:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e4f465e6-8d9a-11e7-a352-e46f43c5825d" target="_blank"&gt;IMF cuts Qatar growth in wake of regional embargo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Monetary Fund has cut its growth forecast for Qatar after its neighbours imposed a land, sea and air embargo on the gas-rich state. The fund said Qatar’s non-hydrocarbon growth would fall from 5.6 per cent in 2016 to 4.6 per cent this year “due to the ongoing fiscal consolidation and trade diversion”. The fund had been forecasting growth of 5.7 per cent in 2017. Qatar has been enduring a regional blockage since Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain and Egypt cut transport and diplomatic links to the country in June, accusing Doha of sponsoring terrorism. The meas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>GDP per head declines sharply in United Arab Emirates - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2b687a72-71ed-11e7-93ff-99f383b09ff9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMFJmnMvB0tBB7CytUhwdd4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 03:03:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2b687a72-71ed-11e7-93ff-99f383b09ff9" target="_blank"&gt;GDP per head declines sharply in United Arab Emirates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Arab Emirates is widely viewed as the most successful Gulf economy, having successfully diversified away from its fossil fuel-driven past to become a regional hub for finance, commerce, tourism and air travel. A strong pro-business agenda means it ranked 26 out of 190 countries in this month’s annual World Bank report on ease of doing business, well ahead of the next highest-placed Gulf state, Bahrain, in 63rd. Yet, in terms of long-run real income per person at least, the UAE has performed far worse than any of its five Gulf Cooperation Council peers. Since 1980, when the IMF be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Call for GCC dialogue as Trump speaks to Qatar's emir - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/call-gcc-dialogue-trump-speaks-qatar-emir-170908132013870.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHuOIlMIjRGu0HS7h14gJJIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 14:20:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/call-gcc-dialogue-trump-speaks-qatar-emir-170908132013870.html" target="_blank"&gt;Call for GCC dialogue as Trump speaks to Qatar's emir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shortly after calling for unity and offering to mediate in a diplomatic crisis between Qatar and its neighbours, US President Donald Trump has held a phone conversation with the Qatari emir to discuss the latest developments in the Gulf. The call on Thursday followed a White House meeting between Trump and the emir of Kuwait, who is mediating in the dispute since June 5, when a Saudi-led group announced it was cutting ties with Qatar, accusing it of supporting "terrorism". Dona denies the allegations. During his conversation with Trump, Qatari Emir Sheikh Tamim bin Hamad Al Thani welcomed T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Tillerson Travels to Kuwait in Hopes of Brokering Qatar Deal - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/tillerson-qatar-crisis-kuwait/3934509.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOpqkP3AlHBMvtJ33ZQxI9cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 06:59:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/tillerson-qatar-crisis-kuwait/3934509.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tillerson Travels to Kuwait in Hopes of Brokering Qatar Deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. Secretary of State Rex Tillerson travels to Kuwait Monday to try to help broker a deal between Qatar and its Gulf neighbors. Kuwait has tried to mediate a resolution between the small monarchy on the Arabian Peninsula and its neighbors, but has been unsuccessful so far. Tillerson met with top Qatari and Kuwaiti officials late last month in an effort to end the escalating standoff, but he is apparently taking a more hands-on role in the negotiations with his trip to Kuwait. The secretary of state has emphasized the need for all parties to exercise restraint to allow for productive diplo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The U.S. Charges Head-On Into the Gulf Crisis - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/stratfor/2017/07/13/the-u-s-charges-head-on-into-the-gulf-crisis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAW1s-aN7RigEaKSNB_jRKcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 13:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/stratfor/2017/07/13/the-u-s-charges-head-on-into-the-gulf-crisis/" target="_blank"&gt;The U.S. Charges Head-On Into the Gulf Crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article was originally published at Stratfor.com. The crisis in the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) has reached a turning point. U.S. Secretary of State Rex Tillerson signed an agreement on counterterrorism with the Qatari government July 11, the second day of a trip designed to diffuse the tension in the bloc. Though the content of the deal is vague, its message is clear: The United States has had enough of the feud between Qatar on one side and Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates on the other. Riyadh and Abu Dhabi will have to reassess their position in the dispute with Doha, mu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Sergey Lavrov calls for dialogue to resolve Gulf crisis - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/sergey-lavrov-calls-dialogue-resolve-gulf-crisis-170830113114395.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEElRkHXj8BwFXNpGnr103BgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 14:03:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/sergey-lavrov-calls-dialogue-resolve-gulf-crisis-170830113114395.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sergey Lavrov calls for dialogue to resolve Gulf crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doha, Qatar - Russian Foreign Minister Sergey Lavrov has expressed Moscow's support for Kuwait's mediation efforts to defuse a three-month long diplomatic crisis in the Gulf. Lavrov made the comments in Qatar's capital, Doha, on Wednesday, at the end of a three-nation tour of the region that also included stops in Kuwait and the United Arab Emirates (UAE). "We welcome all initiatives to resolve the Gulf crisis, and we support the Kuwaiti efforts in that direction," Lavrov said during a joint press conference with his Qatari counterpart, Sheikh Mohammad bin Abdelrahman Al Thani. OPINION: GCC...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Qatar says no sign Arab states willing to negotiate over boycott - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-russia-idUSKCN1BA1OT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGjCUPMtrUnqePwlJKtm39UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 13:27:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-russia-idUSKCN1BA1OT" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar says no sign Arab states willing to negotiate over boycott&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DOHA (Reuters) - Qatar's foreign minister said on Wednesday that his country was willing to negotiate an end to a Gulf diplomatic rift but had seen no sign that Saudi Arabia and other countries imposing sanctions on Doha were open to mediation. Kuwait and the United States are trying to heal a bitter dispute between Qatar and four Arab countries that has damaged business ties and disrupted travel for thousands of citizens in the six-nation Gulf Cooperation Council. Egypt, Saudi Arabia, Bahrain and the United Emirates severed political and trade ties with the small gas-rich country on June 4...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Arab states rap 'negative' Qatari reply to demands but no new sanctions - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-idUSKBN19Q0YY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1pcq91z_Sic_-BKnkhtwQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 01:10:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-idUSKBN19Q0YY" target="_blank"&gt;Arab states rap 'negative' Qatari reply to demands but no new sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Ahmed Aboulenein and Karin Strohecker CAIRO/LONDON (Reuters) - Four Arab states refrained on Wednesday from slapping further sanctions on Qatar but voiced disappointment at its "negative" response to their demands and said their boycott of the tiny Gulf nation would continue. Qatar earlier in the day accused Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain, and Egypt of "clear aggression" and said the accusations cited when they severed ties a month ago "were clearly designed to create anti-Qatar sentiment in the West". The four Arab nations accuse Qatar of supporting terrorism and allyin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>US military halts exercises over Qatar-Gulf crisis - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/military-halts-exercises-qatar-gulf-crisis-171006064515792.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO47QEkP196O8oQ8V7Pf750qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 09:00:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/military-halts-exercises-qatar-gulf-crisis-171006064515792.html" target="_blank"&gt;US military halts exercises over Qatar-Gulf crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US military has halted some exercises with its Gulf Arab allies over the ongoing diplomatic crisis targeting Qatar, trying to use its influence to end the months-long dispute, authorities told The Associated Press. While offering few details, the acknowledgement by the US military's Central Command shows the concern it has over the conflict gripping the Gulf, home to the US Navy's Fifth Fleet and crucial bases for its campaign against the Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant group, as well as the war in Afghanistan. The Gulf crisis began June 5, when Bahrain, Egypt, Saudi Arabia and the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>UAE denies Washington Post report it orchestrated Qatar hack - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/07/17/middleeast/uae-qatar-report/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVLImQmGSYuQMd2LHugHxMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 16:12:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/07/17/middleeast/uae-qatar-report/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;UAE denies Washington Post report it orchestrated Qatar hack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Arab Emirates has denied a Washington Post report that claims the country orchestrated a hack of Qatari state news and social media websites in May, an incident that triggered the region's worst diplomatic crisis in decades. Saudi Arabia and its allies -- the UAE, Bahrain and Egypt -- accused Qatar of supporting terrorism and led a group of Muslim-majority nations to cut ties with Doha. That came after Qatar's emir, Sheikh Tamim bin Hamad Al Thani, was quoted online calling Iran -- a key rival to Saudi Arabia -- an Islamic power and describing Qatari relations with Israel as good...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Iran's Javad Zarif and Sheikh Tamim hold talks in Doha - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/iran-javad-zarif-sheikh-tamim-hold-talks-doha-171003153132194.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIYFC_FDrZ8RbYdMaF1OrJAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 20:06:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/iran-javad-zarif-sheikh-tamim-hold-talks-doha-171003153132194.html" target="_blank"&gt;Iran's Javad Zarif and Sheikh Tamim hold talks in Doha&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mohammad Javad Zarif, Iran's foreign minister, has met Qatar's Emir Sheikh Tamim bin Hamad Al Thani for talks on relations and strengthening "cooperation" between the two countries after almost four months of a blockade against Qatar. The visit is Zarif's first to Doha since four Arab countries - Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain, and Egypt - cut diplomatic ties with Qatar on June 5 and imposed a land, air and sea blockade. "During the meeting, they reviewed relations of cooperation between the two countries in various fields as well as exchanged views on the current situation...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: The secret documents that help explain the Qatar crisis - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/07/10/politics/secret-documents-qatar-crisis-gulf-saudi/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBg5YxVEKKVI45oL4Q2eg6IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 07:51:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/07/10/politics/secret-documents-qatar-crisis-gulf-saudi/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: The secret documents that help explain the Qatar crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar made a series of secret agreements with its Gulf neighbors in 2013 and 2014 barring support for opposition and hostile groups in those nations, as well as in Egypt and Yemen. The existence of the agreements has been known, but both the content and the documents themselves were kept secret due to the sensitivity of the issues involved and the fact that they were agreed in private by heads of state. The agreements were exclusively obtained by CNN from a source from the region with access to the documents. The Gulf countries have accused Qatar of not complying with the two agreements, wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Isolated Qatar is defiant. What happens next? - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2017/07/12/news/economy/arab-states-qatar-isolation/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENn58PX3VviP4XCEfYrPGssqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:02:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2017/07/12/news/economy/arab-states-qatar-isolation/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Isolated Qatar is defiant. What happens next?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arab countries boycotting Qatar aren't planning to end its isolation anytime soon, and could step up the pressure. Saudi Arabia, United Arab Emirates, Bahrain and Egypt said Tuesday that sanctions on the Gulf nation will continue until it accepts the "just and full demands that will ensure that terrorism is addressed and stability and security are established in the region." The four countries cut diplomatic ties and transport links with Qatar last month, accusing it of funding terrorism. They also ordered Qataris to leave, and their citizens to return home indefinitely, and presented the s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Top U.S. diplomat begins tough Gulf talks on easing Qatar row - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-idUSKBN19X0WM</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHbIxr4kGmCwCNSo18FeMZkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:00:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-idUSKBN19X0WM" target="_blank"&gt;Top U.S. diplomat begins tough Gulf talks on easing Qatar row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JEDDAH, Saudi Arabia (Reuters) - U.S. Secretary of State Rex Tillerson began talks with four Arab states on Wednesday in efforts to ease a boycott of Qatar after the countries labeled a U.S.-Qatar terrorism financing accord an inadequate response to their concerns. Any resolution of the dispute must address all the key issues for Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain and Egypt, including Doha's undermining of regional stability, a senior UAE official said ahead of the talks in Saudi Arabia. His comments shed light on Tillerson's uphill challenge. The four countries imposed sanctio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tillerson Ends Persian Gulf Trip With No Breakthrough on Qatar Blockade - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/top-us-diplomar-heads-back-to-qatar-but-impasse-grinds-on/3942540.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDztMnUlDCKnPCq40Uldhs4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:47:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/top-us-diplomar-heads-back-to-qatar-but-impasse-grinds-on/3942540.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tillerson Ends Persian Gulf Trip With No Breakthrough on Qatar Blockade&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. Secretary of State Rex Tillerson left Qatar Thursday with little apparent progress in his shuttle diplomacy aimed at ending Doha's diplomatic standoff with four Arab countries. Tillerson declined questions after a final meeting with Qatar's emir, Sheikh Tamim bin Hamad al-Thani, before leaving for Washington. The emir's brother, Sheikh Mohammad bin Hamad al-Thani, told Tillerson, "Hope to see you again under better circumstances." Tillerson spoke with Qatari leaders after spending Wednesday in the Saudi Red Sea city of Jeddah meeting with diplomats from Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Bahrain and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>World-beating wealth props up Qatar against Arab sanctions - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-economy-idUSKBN19R1WA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPEHB7YhxcbKzpMtjjllx04qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 14:12:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-economy-idUSKBN19R1WA" target="_blank"&gt;World-beating wealth props up Qatar against Arab sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Andrew Torchia and Tom Finn DUBAI/DOHA (Reuters) - A month after Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain and Egypt severed diplomatic, trade and transport ties with Qatar, accusing it of backing terrorism, it is suffering from isolation but is nowhere near an economic crisis. The alliance against it, meanwhile, may not have options to inflict further damage.(For a graphic on Qatar's economy click tmsnrt.rs/2sinDGg) As the world's top liquefied natural gas exporter, Qatar is so rich -- at $127,660, its gross domestic product per capita in purchasing power terms is the highest of a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Qatar: UN should play a role in resolving Gulf crisis - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/qatar-play-role-resolving-gulf-crisis-170727223916633.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHAXPGtgqqnIHoR04PUk_fIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 01:14:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/qatar-play-role-resolving-gulf-crisis-170727223916633.html" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar: UN should play a role in resolving Gulf crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar's foreign minister called on Thursday for the United Nations to help resolve the crisis in the Persian Gulf and accused the four Arab countries that have imposed a blockade on Doha of violating international law. Sheikh Mohammed bin Abdulrahman Al Thani told reporters that Saudi Arabia, Egypt, United Arab Emirates and Bahrain are showing "stubbornness" and have not taken any steps to solve the crisis. He vowed that Qatar will spare no effort to overcome what he called "violations" of international law and said "the United Nations is the right platform to start from". Mohammed bin Abdu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Iranian foreign minister urges regional cooperation after returning from Oman, Qatar - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-gulf-zarif/iranian-foreign-minister-urges-regional-cooperation-after-returning-from-oman-qatar-idUSKCN1C82C6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC4NT9zeG_3_W-_-NqWukRAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 18:18:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-gulf-zarif/iranian-foreign-minister-urges-regional-cooperation-after-returning-from-oman-qatar-idUSKCN1C82C6" target="_blank"&gt;Iranian foreign minister urges regional cooperation after returning from Oman, Qatar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIRUT (Reuters) - Iranian Foreign Minister Mohammad Javad Zarif made an appeal for greater regional cooperation on Tuesday after returning to Tehran from a two-day visit to Oman and Qatar. Zarif's visit came with Qatar in the midst of a row with fellow Gulf Cooperation Council members Saudi Arabia, Bahrain and the United Arab Emirates. Together with Egypt, they accuse Qatar of supporting terrorism, a charge it denies. "We have repeatedly suggested a system of dialogue in the Persian Gulf, but unfortunately this has not been acknowledged by some countries, who see their future through tensi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Theresa May, the Arsène Wenger of politics — but without the wins - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d1ebf9fc-8e33-11e7-9084-d0c17942ba93</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGzTQI3z20rflY0c3zBf-FIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 15:37:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d1ebf9fc-8e33-11e7-9084-d0c17942ba93" target="_blank"&gt;Theresa May, the Arsène Wenger of politics — but without the wins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By chance, Theresa May’s unexpected declaration that she wants to stay on as UK prime minister through to the next election came just hours before the end of English football’s transfer deadline day. This day has become a particular torture for many fans, not least supporters of Arsenal, a once all-conquering team which, like the government, has lost its way and its place in the European elite. Like Mrs May, Arsenal’s manager, Arsène Wenger, has also faced growing calls to step aside from fans who believe there is no prospect of a fresh start under his leadership. The parallels are not perf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Qatar burns almost $40bn of reserves to live through blockade – Moody’s - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/business/403416-qatar-reserve-fund-blockade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHpfTim9s8DRfSIwZobSSW0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwroQo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 09:42:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/business/403416-qatar-reserve-fund-blockade/" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar burns almost $40bn of reserves to live through blockade – Moody’s&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar has spent over 11 percent of its reserves in just three months after its Gulf neighbors led by Saudi Arabia imposed a blocked over Qatar’s alleged support of terrorism, Moody’s reports. According to the report, Doha used $38.5 billion, or 23 percent of GDP, to prop up the economy and financial system in June and July. It is more than 11 percent of its $340 billion financial reserves. On June 5, Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain, Egypt and other countries severed all diplomatic and transport links with Qatar, accusing the state of backing terrorism. Qatar has denied the a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>The blockade against Qatar damages all sides - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/213cfae6-6e28-11e7-bfeb-33fe0c5b7eaa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAmP-iYvOi6-ctKGovOv9qMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 17:50:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/213cfae6-6e28-11e7-bfeb-33fe0c5b7eaa" target="_blank"&gt;The blockade against Qatar damages all sides&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With help from President Donald Trump, Riyadh and its Arab allies have painted themselves into a corner at a precarious moment for the Gulf. It is seven weeks since Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Egypt and Bahrain clubbed together to impose a blockade on Qatar in an attempt to bend the gas-rich emirate’s rulers to their will. There are few signs that US and regional mediation is making progress towards breaking the impasse, even though it is clear that the dispute is damaging all concerned. In effect, Saudi Arabia and its allies have asked Qatar to volunteer for vassal status as th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>All GCC countries to attend Riyadh summit: Kuwaiti minister - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/gcc-countries-attend-riyadh-summit-kuwait-minister-181118195939047.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARiGUqT2MaKchxo5GqWposqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 09:03:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/gcc-countries-attend-riyadh-summit-kuwait-minister-181118195939047.html" target="_blank"&gt;All GCC countries to attend Riyadh summit: Kuwaiti minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All member countries of the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC), which includes Qatar, are expected to attend its next summit in the Saudi capital, Riyadh, according to Kuwait's Deputy Foreign Minister Khaled Al-Jarallah. "I am optimistic that the level of representation is expected to be high and reflects the keenness of GCC leaders to maintain this pioneering experience," the minister said in press statements carried by Kuwaiti news agency KUNA. Jarallah said the summit, scheduled to be held in December, offers a ray of hope in reviving efforts to resolve more than one-year-old Gulf dispute. K...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Saudi move will force region into 'further discord' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/saudi-move-force-region-discord-170713131117232.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJWoV7UzFF2QvhZfI4l-xqYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 15:38:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/saudi-move-force-region-discord-170713131117232.html" target="_blank"&gt;Saudi move will force region into 'further discord'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia's and its Arab allies' move to impose a political and economic blockade on Qatar has "plunged the Middle East into further discord", a leading foreign policy magazine published by the US-based Council on Foreign Relations said. In an article published on Wednesday, Foreign Affairs magazine said the "missteps" committed by the Saudi-led group pushed Doha "directly into Iran and Turkey's hands", noting that the many of its demands "were based on false premises". "The blockade is unlikely to result in Qatar returning to the GCC [Gulf Cooperation Council] fold. Rather, it will esse...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>GCC crisis: Why is Kuwaiti mediation not working? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/08/gcc-crisis-kuwaiti-mediation-working-170807093244546.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENCIzRTYPh0VC9s1M9hP1roqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 08:46:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/08/gcc-crisis-kuwaiti-mediation-working-170807093244546.html" target="_blank"&gt;GCC crisis: Why is Kuwaiti mediation not working?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kuwait has long played a constructive role in the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) by bringing opposing parties together. It also enjoys strong relations with both Saudi Arabia and Qatar. So when Saudi Arabia, United Arab Emirates (UAE), Egypt and Bahrain cut ties to Qatar in early June, Kuwait was seen as an acceptable mediator that can mend the latest rift within the GCC. Sheikh Sabah Al-Sabah served for 40 years as foreign minister (1963-2003), and then as prime minister before becoming the emir of Kuwait in 2006. The vast experience he had in these positions and the intensity of his invol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>HRW condemns crackdown of rights activists in Gulf - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/hrw-condemns-crackdown-rights-activists-gulf-170713063810420.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIjSx89kRXVqJwSQ6gq_ZnkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 09:08:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/hrw-condemns-crackdown-rights-activists-gulf-170713063810420.html" target="_blank"&gt;HRW condemns crackdown of rights activists in Gulf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The governments of Gulf nations continued a crackdown on critics during the first half of 2017, Human Rights Watch (HRW) said. In a statement on Wednesday, the international rights organisation condemned the suppression of free speech by the Gulf states amid the ongoing rift between Qatar and three of its GCC neighbours - Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain. HRW's report listing "targeted" dissidents comes after a Bahraini court sentenced human rights activist Nabeel Rajab to two years in prison on charges of "broadcasting false news" over tweets on July 10. READ MORE: Nabeel Ra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>IMF Says Transport, Food Costs Are Up in Qatar After Rift - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/international-monetary-fund-says-transport-food-costs-increased-qatar/4007593.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSnVDxi4aEUFcj_jkPyWHwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 22:17:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/international-monetary-fund-says-transport-food-costs-increased-qatar/4007593.html" target="_blank"&gt;IMF Says Transport, Food Costs Are Up in Qatar After Rift&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Monetary Fund said Wednesday that transportation and food costs in Qatar had "edged up" because of a diplomatic rift that led four Arab countries to cut ties with the small Gulf state. An IMF team visited the capital, Doha, this week, saying in a statement that Qatar's government was able to soften the immediate impact of trade disruptions, but that some costs had gone up as a result of delays caused by rerouting trade. Non-oil growth is projected to shrink to 4.6 percent this year, down 1 percentage point. In June, Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain and Egypt...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Middle East madness engulfs Iran, Qatar and US - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/07/opinions/qatar-us-chaos-opinion-ghitis/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMjcKGUhL4O0V1Mbv5gBW_YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 16:26:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/07/opinions/qatar-us-chaos-opinion-ghitis/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Middle East madness engulfs Iran, Qatar and US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frida Ghitis is a world affairs columnist for The Miami Herald and World Politics Review, and a former CNN producer and correspondent. The views expressed in this commentary are her own. In the turbulent Middle East, there seems no limit on the number of conflicts that can occur at once. On Wednesday morning, residents of Tehran experienced a series of coordinated attacks, with at least a dozen people killed as gunmen and a suicide bomber assaulted the Parliament building and the mausoleum housing the tomb of the Islamic republic's founder, Ayatollah Khomeini. ISIS quickly claimed responsib...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Israeli government moves to impose ban on al-Jazeera news network - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/aug/06/israeli-government-impose-ban-al-jazeera-news-network</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKjY2cvG63HwpVAwHity1qYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 14:48:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/aug/06/israeli-government-impose-ban-al-jazeera-news-network" target="_blank"&gt;Israeli government moves to impose ban on al-Jazeera news network&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel has moved to ban al-Jazeera from operating in the country and in the occupied territories, joining a boycott by Jordan, Egypt, the United Arab Emirates and Saudi Arabia which have all accused the network of sponsoring terrorism. The communications minister, Ayoob Kara, said press cards for al-Jazeera reporters would be revoked. His announcement follows a vow the prime minister, Benjamin Netanyahu, made in July to close the Jerusalem office of the Qatari state-funded news network. Related: Al-Jazeera: the Qatar broadcaster at centre of diplomatic crisis The move had been foreshadowed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UAE accused of hacking Qatar state media and publishing comments which sparked diplomatic crisis - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/07/17/uae-accused-hacking-qatar-state-media-publishing-comments-sparked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJPe1lpP3c9UeC1K8Fv8cpYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 13:50:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/07/17/uae-accused-hacking-qatar-state-media-publishing-comments-sparked/" target="_blank"&gt;UAE accused of hacking Qatar state media and publishing comments which sparked diplomatic crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Arab Emirates has been accused of hacking Qatar’s state news agency and planting a fake news story that helped spark the current diplomatic crisis engulfing the region. Senior members of the UAE government had discussed a plan to hack Qatari state media sites on May 23, according to US intelligence officials discussing newly-analysed information. Later that day, the official Qatar News Agency quoted Qatar’s emir, Sheikh Tamim bin Hamad al-Thani. as criticising US "hostility" towards Iran, describing it as an "Islamic power that cannot be ignored", and praising Hamas, a ideologica...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>IUMS urges Saudi Arabia to free Muslim scholars - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/iums-urges-saudi-arabia-free-muslim-scholars-170912134235564.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO7NNRclprMxTau4DJmiwTYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 04:43:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/iums-urges-saudi-arabia-free-muslim-scholars-170912134235564.html" target="_blank"&gt;IUMS urges Saudi Arabia to free Muslim scholars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Union of Muslim Scholars, a Doha-based body, has condemned the reported arrest of Muslim preachers and scholars in Saudi Arabia, urging Saudi King Salman bin Abdulaziz to order their release. Salman al-Audah, a prominent Muslim preacher and member of the IUMS's board of trustees, and more than 20 others were arrested on Sunday, according to social media postings. The IUMS said in a statement on Monday that the scholars "should not be used as pawns in political disputes", referring to the crisis between Qatar and four other Arab states - Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Russia urges dialogue to solve Gulf crisis - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-russia/russia-urges-dialogue-to-solve-gulf-crisis-idUSKCN1BL0IK</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIuw9EEgHik3GR7sjwjTelcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 14:01:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-russia/russia-urges-dialogue-to-solve-gulf-crisis-idUSKCN1BL0IK" target="_blank"&gt;Russia urges dialogue to solve Gulf crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Stephen Kalin JEDDAH (Reuters) - Arab countries and Qatar should enter into direct talks to solve a diplomatic dispute, Russia's foreign minister said on a trip to Saudi Arabia on Sunday, urging all parties to restore regional unity. Saudi Arabia, Bahrain, the United Arab Emirates and Egypt severed ties with Qatar on June 5, accusing it of supporting terrorist groups - a charge it denies. "We have confirmed our position (that we are) in favor of settling the disagreements by means of negotiations, by directly expressing concerns and achieving solutions which would take into account the c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>ICC prosecutor voices regret over anti-Qatar blockade - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/icc-prosecutor-expresses-regret-anti-qatar-siege-170709192916957.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMV-7b4MXHgeqy3O8AIw4PkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 20:37:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/icc-prosecutor-expresses-regret-anti-qatar-siege-170709192916957.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC prosecutor voices regret over anti-Qatar blockade&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court's (ICC) chief prosecutor has expressed regret over the blockade imposed by Saudi Arabia and three other Arab states against Qatar. On Sunday, ICC's Fatou Bensouda met Qatar's Emir Sheikh Tamim bin Hamad Al Thani in Doha and discussed the violations of international accords as well as human rights abuses committed by the four blockading countries. QNA, Qatar's state news agency, reported that Bensouda praised Doha's mature handling of the crisis. The meeting also dealt with fields of cooperation between Qatar and the ICC, QNA reported. Earlier on Sunday, Bens...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Qatar presses UN to take action against blockade - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/qatari-fm-doha-ready-dialogue-blockade-170911111044486.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEB_0ujlxDv5kxE_7y5yOMQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 15:20:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/qatari-fm-doha-ready-dialogue-blockade-170911111044486.html" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar presses UN to take action against blockade&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar's foreign minister says the blockade by neighbouring Gulf countries violates international law and human rights and the United Nations needs to take action against the Saudi-led bloc. Speaking at a UN Human Rights Council session in Geneva on Monday, Sheikh Mohammed bin Abdulrahman Al Thani said Qatar faced numerous challenges because of the "illegal imposition" by Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Egypt and Bahrain after accusing Doha of funding "terrorism". Qatar has vehemently rejected the allegations. The foreign minister said there are currently about 26,000 cases filed wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>How will Qatar-Gulf crisis shape the region's economy? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/07/qatar-gulf-crisis-shape-region-economy-170722113437953.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ9-n-F-CCEfHshCTUnq1QgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 07:10:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/07/qatar-gulf-crisis-shape-region-economy-170722113437953.html" target="_blank"&gt;How will Qatar-Gulf crisis shape the region's economy?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a now widely discredited 1990s-era theory of international relations, New York Times columnist Thomas Friedman advanced the argument that no two countries with a McDonald's would go to war with one another. The logic behind the so-called "Golden Arches Theory" suggested that states with economies that were strong and stable enough to support investment by multinational corporations like McDonald's would be constrained from launching destructive conflicts against one another. The theory was roundly criticised and disproved with numerous examples, including wars between India and Pakistan,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>The turning point of the GCC crisis - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/07/turning-point-gcc-crisis-170707074800456.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBIo8eY1ARtbzRc4tCFw0MMqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 11:56:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/07/turning-point-gcc-crisis-170707074800456.html" target="_blank"&gt;The turning point of the GCC crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A flurry of diplomacy this week marks the first possible turning point in the five-week-old standoff between a defiant Qatar and four Saudi Arabia-led Arab states that have tried to bring it to its knees, accusing it of promoting terrorism and threatening their security. While accusations and denials continue to fly around, we may be facing a turning point towards a possible negotiated diplomatic resolution that satisfies the legitimate minimum demands of both sides - if all concerned respond maturely to the new positive developments. The heart of this possible shift is a list of six "princ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>France Urges Qatar, Arab Neighbors to Resolve Diplomatic Standoff - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/france-qatar/3945483.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKo9UUpwVgpsVXveB19MreMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 13:06:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/france-qatar/3945483.html" target="_blank"&gt;France Urges Qatar, Arab Neighbors to Resolve Diplomatic Standoff&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France's foreign minister has expressed concern about the deterioration of relations between Qatar and its Arab neighbors and called for sanctions that target Qatari nationals to be lifted. Jean-Yves Le Drian spoke to reporters after talks with his Qatari counterpart, Sheikh Mohammed bin Abdulrahman Al-Thani, in Doha on Saturday. A group of nations that includes Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain and Egypt accuses Qatar of supporting terrorism and has given Doha a 13-point list of demands after severing diplomatic ties in early June. Qatar has said it is willing to negotiate bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Tillerson to travel to Kuwait in bid to resolve Qatar crisis - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-07-07/qatar-rex-tillerson-to-travel-to-kuwait-to-resolve-arab-dispute/8687424</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJSKEteU3rGZ_1iXP_cmEhoqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:24:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-07-07/qatar-rex-tillerson-to-travel-to-kuwait-to-resolve-arab-dispute/8687424" target="_blank"&gt;Tillerson to travel to Kuwait in bid to resolve Qatar crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;United States Secretary of State Rex Tillerson will travel to Kuwait next week to seek a resolution to the ongoing impasse over Qatar. Key points: - Qatar is denying accusations that it sponsors terrorist organisations - The row is problematic for the US because of the nation's close ties with Saudi Arabia - US Defence Secretary concerned the dispute "could drag on for months" Arab nations involved in the boycott of the tiny Gulf state say its refusal of their demands is proof of its links to terrorist groups, and they are planning political, economic and legal steps. Qatar denies sponsorin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Qatar rift: Saudi, UAE, Bahrain, Egypt cut diplomatic ties - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/05/middleeast/saudi-bahrain-egypt-uae-qatar-terror/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIhjz5OLpAcuUqZSpk-j8noqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 16:09:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/05/middleeast/saudi-bahrain-egypt-uae-qatar-terror/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar rift: Saudi, UAE, Bahrain, Egypt cut diplomatic ties&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia, Bahrain, Egypt and the United Arab Emirates broke off relations with Qatar in the worst diplomatic crisis to hit Gulf Arab states in decades. The three Gulf countries and Egypt accused Qatar of supporting terrorism and destabilizing the region. Qatar -- which shares its only land border with Saudi Arabia -- has rejected the accusations, calling them "unjustified" and "baseless." Yemen and the Maldives also cut ties with Qatar. Qatari citizens have been told they have 14 days to leave Saudi Arabia, Bahrain and the UAE, and those countries also banned their own citizens from ent...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>UAE social media users 'showing sympathy' for Qatar could face jail time - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/07/middleeast/uae-social-media-qatar/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELS_C3XU6BbJsbkPmrc9AesqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 16:04:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/07/middleeast/uae-social-media-qatar/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;UAE social media users 'showing sympathy' for Qatar could face jail time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social media users in the United Arab Emirates who "show sympathy" for Qatar could face up to 15 years of jail time, UAE Public Prosecutor Hamad al-Shamsi said in a statement on Wednesday. The announcement follows a major diplomatic rift between Qatar, the UAE, Saudi Arabia and Bahrain, all members of the powerful Gulf Cooperation Council over allegations that the small, but wealthy peninsula state supports terrorism. Qatar has rejected the charge as "unjustified" and "baseless." "Inclination or favoritism" towards Qatar by social media users in the UAE is punishable by three to 15 years in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>'Qatar is rich enough to face threats of the blockade' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/rich-face-threats-blockade-170707132243176.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPVdKl4D8VGKHHZOArAncX8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 14:29:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/rich-face-threats-blockade-170707132243176.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Qatar is rich enough to face threats of the blockade'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar's finance minister has said that the economic fundamentals of his country were in a better position than its rivals and that Doha was rich enough to face threats of the blockade. Saudi Arabia, Bahrain, the United Arab Emirates and Egypt cut ties to Qatar a month ago, accusing it of funding "terrorism" and spreading unrest. Qatar has denied allegations and refused to comply in whole with a list of demands. Speaking to The Times newspaper, Ali Sharif al-Emadi, said the state's huge financial reserves, built on the sale of natural gas over decades meant it could withstand sanctions. READ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Gulf Disunity On Display Once More, As Plans For Introduction Of VAT Diverge - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2017/08/15/gulf-disunity-vat-tax/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAerw8qEQT1BGV9ENtbW_5UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 15:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2017/08/15/gulf-disunity-vat-tax/" target="_blank"&gt;Gulf Disunity On Display Once More, As Plans For Introduction Of VAT Diverge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea of Gulf unity has taken another knock, after a senior UAE official acknowledged that the six countries of the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) will probably not introduce a value-added tax (VAT) at the same time, as originally planned. Khalid Al Bustani, director general of the UAE’s Federal Tax Authority, has said the UAE and Saudi Arabia are likely to push ahead with the new tax in January 2018, but other Gulf countries would only follow later in the year. “The UAE and Saudi Arabia will be implementing VAT starting 2018 January, and the rest could implement until the end of 2018,” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>France calls for swift lifting of sanctions on Qatari nationals - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-france-idUSKBN1A00EI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOLBkNylVCle-0530lsKaAwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 19:34:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-gulf-qatar-france-idUSKBN1A00EI" target="_blank"&gt;France calls for swift lifting of sanctions on Qatari nationals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DOHA (Reuters) - France called on Saturday for a swift lifting of sanctions that target Qatari nationals in an effort to ease a month-long rift between the Gulf country and several of its neighbors. Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain and Egypt imposed sanctions on Qatar on June 5, accusing it of financing extremist groups and allying with the Gulf Arab states' arch-foe Iran. Doha denies the accusations. "France calls for the lifting, as soon as possible, of the measures that affect the populations in particular, bi-national families that have been separated or students," French...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Will the GCC crisis be resolved soon? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/07/gcc-crisis-resolved-170721193141148.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdAy7BU48ziQN01OhY7_UEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 13:02:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/07/gcc-crisis-resolved-170721193141148.html" target="_blank"&gt;Will the GCC crisis be resolved soon?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A string of rapid-fire developments this weekend in Qatar, the United States, and the United Arab Emirates will likely mark this as the turning point that nudged the seven-week-old GCC crisis towards a resolution. A combination of public statements, practical policy measures, and a veritable armada of foreign mediators should prompt indirect negotiations in the coming week, leading to direct talks soon after that. The bitter conflict that saw Saudi Arabia, the UAE, Bahrain and Egypt impose a land, sea, and air siege of Qatar on June 5 now appears to be solvable, due to three critical new de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Qatar questions timing of Riyadh agreement leak - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/qatar-questions-timing-riyadh-agreement-leak-170711170435958.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtyuHh5tYOHmpP_HaLMHY0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 04:40:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/qatar-questions-timing-riyadh-agreement-leak-170711170435958.html" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar questions timing of Riyadh agreement leak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar's foreign minister has questioned the timing of the leak of a set of agreements made between Gulf countries between 2013 and 2014 and insisted that his country was abiding by the accords. After CNN on Monday published a set of documents known as the "Riyadh agreements," Qatari officials said the leak aimed to weaken mediation efforts in the region. The documents were published just as US Secretary of State Rex Tillerson arrived in the Gulf for shuttle diplomacy between Jeddah, Doha and Kuwait City. "These are clear efforts to diminish … the mediation by Kuwait, and the efforts of the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Arab states issue 13 demands to end Qatar-Gulf crisis - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/arab-states-issue-list-demands-qatar-crisis-170623022133024.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEJo_BswpZuapV2KNqnWs7QqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 04:57:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/arab-states-issue-list-demands-qatar-crisis-170623022133024.html" target="_blank"&gt;Arab states issue 13 demands to end Qatar-Gulf crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia and other Arab countries that have cut ties to Qatar have reportedly issued a list of demands to end a major Gulf crisis, insisting that Qatar shut down the Al Jazeera network, close a Turkish military base and scale down ties with Iran. In the 13-point list, the countries also demand that Qatar sever all alleged ties with the Muslim Brotherhood and with other groups, including Hezbollah, al-Qaeda and ISIL (also known as ISIS). Associated Press and Reuters news agencies reported they obtained the list from unnamed officials from one of the countries involved in isolating Qatar....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia 'detains' more preachers - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/saudi-arabia-detains-preachers-170912210153172.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8RVIYea3NEnii3xoDgjFAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 13:30:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/saudi-arabia-detains-preachers-170912210153172.html" target="_blank"&gt;Saudi Arabia 'detains' more preachers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia has detained more preachers and scholars, activists said, two days after the reported arrest of more than 20 individuals, including prominent Saudi intellectuals. The reports come as Saudi state news agency SPA said authortities were uncovering "intelligence activities for the benefit of foreign parties" by an unamed group of people. It did not comment on the reported arrests. On Sunday, online activists said up to 20 influential Saudi preachers and religious scholars had been arrested, including some of the kingdom's most influential preachers. Activists dedicated to monitorin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Iran and Oman agree to boost ties amid Gulf crisis - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/iran-oman-agree-boost-ties-gulf-crisis-170712140618904.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAbMmXWeKX1YWz3173Rd9E4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/iran-oman-agree-boost-ties-gulf-crisis-170712140618904.html" target="_blank"&gt;Iran and Oman agree to boost ties amid Gulf crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran and Oman have agreed to work on boosting bilateral ties as a diplomatic crisis persists in the Gulf. "Iran and Oman have for years had fraternal relations and the best must be made of these good relations to reinforce them," Iranian President Hassan Rouhani said on Wednesday as he met Oman's foreign minister. The Iranian government's website reported Foreign Minister Yussef Bin Alawi as replying: "Omani leaders believe our ties should be developed". The meeting comes as Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain and Egypt severed ties with Qatar, accusing it of backing terrorism a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Trump urges GCC to find diplomatic solution to crisis - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/trump-urges-gcc-find-diplomatic-solution-crisis-170831041806499.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBmdukuUyoSiIbAowL3g6-QqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 07:55:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/trump-urges-gcc-find-diplomatic-solution-crisis-170831041806499.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump urges GCC to find diplomatic solution to crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump urged the countries embroiled in a regional dispute with Qatar to find a diplomatic resolution to the ongoing rift. The White House said Trump discussed the issue on Wednesday in a telephone conversation with Saudi Arabia's King Salman. Trump told King Salman that a diplomatic resolution would fulfil a commitment - made when Trump visited Riyadh - to maintain unity while fighting "terrorism". Analyst say the Trump administration is concerned about Qatar's growing relationship with Iran as a result of the ongoing crisis. "We need to see this within the context of Qatar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Qatar faults 'disorganised' conduct by Saudi-led group - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/qatar-faults-disorganised-conduct-saudi-led-group-170719202407648.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDny874aIvm-lCfT6RkstnAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 04:30:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/qatar-faults-disorganised-conduct-saudi-led-group-170719202407648.html" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar faults 'disorganised' conduct by Saudi-led group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A government official in Qatar said on Wednesday that the four Arab countries blockading the country have acted dangerously and in a "disorganised manner" after apparently changing their demands. Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates, Egypt and Bahrain said Tuesday that Qatar should commit to six principles on combatting terrorism and negotiate a plan to implement them. The four countries had initially made 13 sweeping demands, including shuttering Al Jazeera, which Qatar dismissed as an infringement on its sovereignty. Sheikh Saif bin Ahmed Al Thani, director of the Qatari government's co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Donald Trump’s dream of an Arab Nato is a fantasy - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/265d9cc8-e75e-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDrUJ-GLLn_XKqMAFZEV3vMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 16:35:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/265d9cc8-e75e-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3" target="_blank"&gt;Donald Trump’s dream of an Arab Nato is a fantasy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before his visit to Saudi Arabia in May last year, Donald Trump and his entourage talked portentously about creating an “Arab Nato” to counter the regional ambitions of Iran. What happened next takes more than a tweet to describe. Mr Trump was delighted to boast of $110bn in arms sales to the Saudis. Eighteen months later Riyadh has made good on about a tenth of that exaggerated sum. Before some 50 Sunni Arab and African heads of state, the US president launched a Saudi-led Sunni alliance against Shia Iran. But Saudi Arabia, urged on by the hawkish United Arab Emirates, instead decided to b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Gulf economies recovering but still vulnerable to oil volatility — IMF - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/6e26c84a-e718-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJGOyn9_G86iWf0loXl5DEQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 08:04:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6e26c84a-e718-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3" target="_blank"&gt;Gulf economies recovering but still vulnerable to oil volatility — IMF&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arab Gulf economies are expected to bounce back to modest levels of growth on higher oil prices and production this year, the International Monetary Fund said while warning against any complacency in pushing through economic reforms amid crude price volatility. Growth among the six-member Gulf Cooperation Council states should reach 2.4 per cent this year and 3 per cent in 2019 after a 0.4 contraction in 2017 as state investment projects increase, the IMF said in its autumn regional economic outlook report. Over the past two years, oil prices have increased by around 60 per cent, helping GC...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Going Their Separate Ways: How A Qatari Children's Hospital Has Coped With The Economic Boycott - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/11/08/going-their-separate-ways-how-a-qatari-childrens-hospital-has-coped-with-the-economic-boycott/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAqpxZXz1R3-bXcbYEffZ58qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/11/08/going-their-separate-ways-how-a-qatari-childrens-hospital-has-coped-with-the-economic-boycott/" target="_blank"&gt;Going Their Separate Ways: How A Qatari Children's Hospital Has Coped With The Economic Boycott&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the western outskirts of Qatar’s capital Doha, a series of 14 striking bronze sculptures by the British artist Damian Hirst glisten in the sun. Showing the development of human life from conception to birth, the installation – called the Miraculous Journey – is a surprising sight in the socially conservative country of Qatar. Alongside the art works sits Sidra Medicine, a vast new women and children’s hospital which has also been making its mark. In early October, two conjoined twins were successfully separated during a nine-hour operation at the hospital. The two boys, Tamim and Hamad, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Qatar rejects accusations of meddling in Bahrain internal affairs - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/qatar-rejects-accusations-meddling-bahrain-internal-affairs-181105063352350.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGHigrT0uOjEORdYbrjTtpUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 09:12:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/qatar-rejects-accusations-meddling-bahrain-internal-affairs-181105063352350.html" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar rejects accusations of meddling in Bahrain internal affairs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar rejects accusations of meddling in Bahrain's political disputes and internal conflicts, Qatar's foreign ministry said on Monday. Three senior members of Bahrain's opposition movement were sentenced to life in prison on Sunday over charges of spying for Qatar. ''The State of Qatar condemns that its name was mentioned in Bahrain's internal conflicts,'' the ministry said in statement. The verdict against Sheikh Ali Salman, who headed the now-outlawed al-Wefaq movement, as well as Sheikh Hassan Sultan and Ali al-Aswad came months after their acquittal by the high criminal court in June. S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Indonesia protests Saudi execution of domestic worker - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/indonesia-protests-saudi-execution-domestic-worker-181031094812124.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIIJIYnNXyoP284Fk9g4-rwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:41:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/indonesia-protests-saudi-execution-domestic-worker-181031094812124.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia protests Saudi execution of domestic worker&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia has filed an official protest with Saudi Arabia after the kingdom executed an Indonesian domestic worker without notifying her family or consular staff. Tuti Tursilawati was executed on Monday in the city of Taif, Indonesia's foreign ministry said, seven years after she was sentenced to death for killing her employer in an act she claimed was self-defence from sexual abuse. President Joko Widodo criticised the decision on Wednesday, saying the government has officially protested to Riyadh and demanded better protection of Indonesian workers in the country. Lalu Muhammad Iqbal, dir...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item></channel></rss>