<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Bob Menendez - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRE16WkROd0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:50:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Senators wrestle with rebuke of Saudis - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zQQeDaGyYE0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOb128UnPGPkTS-cmNdZiAoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6OVAw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:42:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zQQeDaGyYE0" target="_blank"&gt;Senators wrestle with rebuke of Saudis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(6 Dec 2018) Senators are considering multiple pieces of legislation to formally rebuke Saudi Arabia for the slaying of journalist Jamal Khashoggi. Momentum is building for a resolution that would call the Saudi crown prince "complicit" in the killing. (Dec. 6) Subscribe for more Breaking News: http://smarturl.it/AssociatedPress Website: https://apnews.com Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP Facebook: https://facebook.com/APNews Google+: https://plus.google.com/115892241801867723374 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/ ​ You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchiv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Bob Corker’s Final Act: A Middle Finger to Trump’s Foreign Policy - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bob-corkers-final-act-a-middle-finger-to-trumps-foreign-policy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEuua5D2Vljih4NGVhAzIngqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:09:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/bob-corkers-final-act-a-middle-finger-to-trumps-foreign-policy" target="_blank"&gt;Bob Corker’s Final Act: A Middle Finger to Trump’s Foreign Policy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast Bob Corker (R-TN) has just a few weeks left as a United States senator, and he’s determined to use that time to deliver one final rebuke to President Donald Trump. Corker, the chairman of the powerful Senate Foreign Relations Committee, is cobbling together a coalition of Republicans and Democrats in an attempt to force the Trump administration to do something that would undermine a key tenet of its foreign policy: acknowledge that Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman was complicit in the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi. “I know he did it. I want...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Senators wrestle with rebuke of Saudis for Khashoggi killing - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/0455566e183945beb7946ea7a04fde8b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKgIva6mXQofSNrSXuxPEYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:18:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/0455566e183945beb7946ea7a04fde8b" target="_blank"&gt;Senators wrestle with rebuke of Saudis for Khashoggi killing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Senators are considering multiple pieces of legislation to formally rebuke Saudi Arabia for the slaying of journalist Jamal Khashoggi, with momentum building for a resolution to call Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman complicit in the killing. Senate Foreign Relations Committee Chairman Bob Corker said Thursday that senators are looking at moving three measures — a resolution to condemn the crown prince for Khashoggi's murder, a bill to suspend arms sales to the kingdom and a resolution to call on President Donald Trump's administration to pull back U.S. help for the S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Senate set to rebuke White House's handling of Saudi Arabia after Khashoggi murder - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/congress-khashoggi-yemen-saudi-arabia-reaction/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMHw9tc6h6Swcvr1ecZF4-AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:51:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/congress-khashoggi-yemen-saudi-arabia-reaction/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senate set to rebuke White House's handling of Saudi Arabia after Khashoggi murder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Senate is preparing to confront the White House over its support for Saudi Arabia in the aftermath of journalist Jamal Khashoggi's killing, moving toward a floor vote next week to curtail US involvement in the Saudi-led war in Yemen, while a powerful committee prepares to deliver a swift rebuke to the kingdom's crown prince over his alleged role in the murder. But the moves may end up amounting to little more than a symbolic rebuke to Saudi Arabia and the White House. GOP leaders are navigating complicated Senate procedures and may limit next week's floor debate to focus narrowly on the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Menendez warns Treasury against lifting sanctions on Russian firms - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/menendez-treasury-russia-sanctions/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELzh9q3lUw4YgEMhZ-8hdqwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:38:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/menendez-treasury-russia-sanctions/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Menendez warns Treasury against lifting sanctions on Russian firms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A top Democratic senator on Wednesday urged the Trump administration not to lift sanctions on two Russian firms, including the world's second-largest aluminum maker, until Russian billionaire Oleg Deripaska fully divests his stake in both companies. "I see no reason to remove sanctions against Mr. Deripaska, and until he divests from and relinquishes control of RUSAL and EN+, there is no justification to remove the sanctions on those companies," New Jersey Sen. Bob Menendez, ranking member of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, wrote in a letter to Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin. In ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Senator Rips Mnuchin for Backpedaling on Manafort-Linked Russia Sanctions - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/senator-rips-mnuchin-for-backpedaling-on-manafort-linked-russia-sanctions</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDNSiMa79kKPJizvrfDjS6AqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/senator-rips-mnuchin-for-backpedaling-on-manafort-linked-russia-sanctions" target="_blank"&gt;Senator Rips Mnuchin for Backpedaling on Manafort-Linked Russia Sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alex Wong/Getty The top Democrat on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee is blasting Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin for entertaining the idea of lifting sanctions on a Russian aluminum company with ties to former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort. In a letter sent Wednesday, Sen. Bob Menendez (D-NJ) urged Mnuchin to maintain the sanctions that were slapped on Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska in April, arguing that they are a necessary aspect of U.S. efforts to punish Russian President Vladimir Putin and his inner circle for Moscow’s interference in the 2016 election. “I welcomed thes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Menendez: Trump making wrong calculation - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/04/khashoggi-briefing-bob-menendez-erin-burnett-intv-ebof.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIC07VZdv0gMagNl1SaUa_IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:27:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/04/khashoggi-briefing-bob-menendez-erin-burnett-intv-ebof.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Menendez: Trump making wrong calculation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top Democrat on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee Bob Menendez (D-NJ) said after a CIA briefing on the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi that the administration was making the "wrong calculation" in declining to blame the de facto Saudi leader. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Menendez says U.S. sanctions on Russia's Deripaska should remain - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions/menendez-says-sanctions-on-russias-deripaska-should-remain-idUSKBN1O42DU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDB0mXiUN0IJ9X3EqLI2joUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:36:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions/menendez-says-sanctions-on-russias-deripaska-should-remain-idUSKBN1O42DU" target="_blank"&gt;Menendez says U.S. sanctions on Russia's Deripaska should remain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top Democrat on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee on Wednesday urged the Trump administration not to waive or remove sanctions on Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska or two companies he controls. In a letter to U.S. Treasury Secretary Steve Mnuchin, Senator Bob Menendez cited unspecified reports that Treasury was considering such a move and noted the department's own analysis says the oligarch is accused of crimes from blackmail to murder. "I see no reason to remove sanctions against Mr. Deripaska, and until he divests from and relinquishes control of Rusal and EN+, there is no justifi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Top Senate Democrat Warns Trump Not to Lift Sanctions Against Russian Billionaire - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/top-senate-democrat-warns-trump-not-to-lift-sanctions-against-russian-billionaire-/4688948.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAQDyn5dFE6mS-q77F0xwFMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:45:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/top-senate-democrat-warns-trump-not-to-lift-sanctions-against-russian-billionaire-/4688948.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top Senate Democrat Warns Trump Not to Lift Sanctions Against Russian Billionaire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key Democratic senator is warning the Trump administration not to lift sanctions against a Russian oligarch or the companies he controls. Oleg Deripaska holds large stakes in the Russian aluminum giant Rusal and the automobile conglomerate GAZ Group. FILE - Oleg Deripaska attends an agreement signing ceremony with the Krasnoyarsk region's government in Moscow, Russia, Dec. 12, 2017. New Jersey's Bob Menendez, the top Democrat on the Foreign Relations Committee, wrote in a letter to the Treasury Department that it would face strong opposition in Congress if it waives sanctions against Deri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Menendez after CIA's Khashoggi briefing: Trump, Mattis, Pompeo making 'wrong calculation' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/politics/bob-menendez-khashoggi-cnntv/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEx2IRJu49LBkt9eucFI4CgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:30:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/politics/bob-menendez-khashoggi-cnntv/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Menendez after CIA's Khashoggi briefing: Trump, Mattis, Pompeo making 'wrong calculation'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top Democrat on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee said after a CIA briefing on murdered journalist Jamal Khashoggi that the administration was making the "wrong calculation" in declining to blame the de facto Saudi leader. "I think they're making a wrong calculation," New Jersey Democratic Sen. Bob Menendez said Tuesday on CNN's "Erin Burnett OutFront." Members of both parties who attended a briefing on Tuesday with CIA Director Gina Haspel left the session doubling down on their criticism of President Donald Trump, Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and Defense Secretary James Mattis....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Top senators slam Trump’s INF treaty pullout, call it ‘gift to Russia’ - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445556-senators-blast-trump-quitting-inf/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEE_a0ey4g0fki9tjthLzpIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:58:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445556-senators-blast-trump-quitting-inf/" target="_blank"&gt;Top senators slam Trump’s INF treaty pullout, call it ‘gift to Russia’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A trio of top Senators criticized Donald Trump’s decision to walk away from the 1987 INF treaty, saying the move, which lacks “strategic forethought,” would spell the end of other arms control treaties. Trump’s decision to withdraw from the milestone Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces Treaty (INF) came out of the blue for American lawmakers – senators Bob Menendez, Jack Reed, and Mark Warner, who wrote an open letter to the US president. There were multiple opportunities to explain the rationale behind the pullout, but it turns out that the administration “provided no indication that a decis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Top senators briefed by CIA blame Saudi prince for Khashoggi death - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-cia/top-senators-briefed-by-cia-blame-saudi-prince-for-khashoggi-death-idUSKBN1O32BR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECGUzSjOxao4B3L_RiqGjLYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:50:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-cia/top-senators-briefed-by-cia-blame-saudi-prince-for-khashoggi-death-idUSKBN1O32BR" target="_blank"&gt;Top senators briefed by CIA blame Saudi prince for Khashoggi death&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senior U.S. senators said on Tuesday they were more certain than ever that Saudi Arabia's crown prince, Mohammed bin Salman, was responsible for the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi after receiving a CIA briefing on the matter. "You have to be willfully blind not to come to the conclusion that this was orchestrated and organized by people under the command of MbS," Republican Senator Lindsey Graham told reporters after the meeting with Central Intelligence Agency Director Gina Haspel, referring to the crown prince by his initials. In his bid to pressure the Trump administration to cond...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Menendez slams Trump on Khashoggi response - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/11/28/bob-menendez-saudi-arabia-trump-khashoggi-response-nr-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFRc2UJEZ9W4nTrXUvYE6cUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:38:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/11/28/bob-menendez-saudi-arabia-trump-khashoggi-response-nr-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Menendez slams Trump on Khashoggi response&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Bob Menendez (D-NJ) says the Trump administration's response to journalist Jamal Khashoggi's murder sends a signal to other world leaders they can get away with anything. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Menendez: Trump 'can't find spine' with Putin - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/11/29/sen-bob-menendez-intv-trump-putin-g20-meeting-argentina-confront-sot-ath-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIMr3v5333ZZpaAS7tu3n4wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:09:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/11/29/sen-bob-menendez-intv-trump-putin-g20-meeting-argentina-confront-sot-ath-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Menendez: Trump 'can't find spine' with Putin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an interview with CNN's Poppy Harlow, Sen. Bob Menendez (D-NJ) says that President Donald Trump canceling his meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin because the Ukrainian sailors have not been released is Trump avoiding the problem instead of confronting Putin. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Senate defied Trump on Saudi ties, but may falter in next steps - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-usa/senate-defied-trump-on-saudi-ties-but-may-falter-in-next-steps-idUSKCN1NZ18T</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGDTX_yjJgvDQag8zWsF9lkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 13:18:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-usa/senate-defied-trump-on-saudi-ties-but-may-falter-in-next-steps-idUSKCN1NZ18T" target="_blank"&gt;Senate defied Trump on Saudi ties, but may falter in next steps&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Congress will have a difficult time undermining the Trump administration's close ties with Saudi Arabia, despite a Senate vote this week to consider a resolution that would end support for the Saudi-led war in Yemen. On Wednesday, 14 of President Donald Trump's fellow Republicans, who hold a slim majority in the Senate and rarely defy his wishes, joined Democrats to vote 63-37 to advance the measure, paving the way for a possible vote to pass it next week. The unusual result underscored lawmakers' frustration with what they see as the Trump administration's inadequate response to t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pompeo: No 'direct' evidence linking MBS to Khashoggi killing - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/pompeo-downgrading-ties-saudi-arabia-mistake-181128162020009.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcEqK_jjVhdWu-LjlB79zQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 18:51:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/pompeo-downgrading-ties-saudi-arabia-mistake-181128162020009.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pompeo: No 'direct' evidence linking MBS to Khashoggi killing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said on Wednesday there was no direct evidence connecting Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman to the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi last month in Istanbul. Pompeo spoke to reporters after he and Defense Secretary Jim Mattis told the Senate behind closed doors that weakening US-Saudi ties over the killing would hurt national security. "There is no direct reporting connecting the crown prince to the order to murder Jamal Khashoggi," Pompeo said. His comments come despite reports that the CIA concluded that Prince Mohammed must have at least known abo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>US Lawmakers Seethe Ahead of Briefing on Saudi Arabia - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-lawmakers-seethe-briefing-saudi-arabia-jamal-khashoggi/4677039.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB5Z5S_S9yoNW3YM6W2lQpsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:55:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-lawmakers-seethe-briefing-saudi-arabia-jamal-khashoggi/4677039.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Lawmakers Seethe Ahead of Briefing on Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still seething over the death of journalist Jamal Khashoggi, U.S. senators on Tuesday demanded the Trump administration share all it knows about who ordered last month's killing of the Saudi dissident and U.S. resident at the kingdom's consulate in Turkey. Lawmakers of both parties blasted CIA Director Gina Haspel's exclusion from Wednesday's scheduled classified briefing on Saudi Arabia, in which Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and Defense Secretary Jim Mattis are to speak with the full Senate behind closed doors. "I want the CIA — I want somebody from the intelligence community to brief th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>U.S. Cabinet members defend close Saudi ties, lawmakers unconvinced - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-usa/us-cabinet-members-defend-close-saudi-ties-lawmakers-unconvinced-idUSKCN1NX1ZV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECn89r5EZ5GoVV_w3WGV8t8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 04:29:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-usa/us-cabinet-members-defend-close-saudi-ties-lawmakers-unconvinced-idUSKCN1NX1ZV" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. Cabinet members defend close Saudi ties, lawmakers unconvinced&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two senior U.S. Cabinet members urged senators on Wednesday not to downgrade ties with Saudi Arabia over the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi, but lawmakers from both parties said they could not turn a blind eye to reports that the country's de facto ruler was involved in last month's killing. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and Defense Secretary Jim Mattis said there was no hard evidence that the powerful Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman was behind the killing, seemingly contradicting an assessment by the CIA about Khashoggi's death in the Saudi consulate in Istanbul. "We have no smokin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Senators demand 'determination' on Khashoggi - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/aea1800302ba4d6092274528c3a173b9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB8wgBiPdCuaQzrinIZhFm0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 04:23:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/aea1800302ba4d6092274528c3a173b9" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Senators demand 'determination' on Khashoggi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on U.S. response to the murder of Saudi columnist Jamal Khashoggi (all times local): 6:50 p.m. The chairman and ranking member of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee have written to the president demanding that his administration "make a determination" about whether Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman was responsible for the killing Jamal Khashoggi. Sens. Bob Corker, R-Tenn., and Bob Menendez, D-N.J., wrote the letter to President Donald Trump on Tuesday, asking for an investigation under the Global Magnitsky Human Rights Accountability Act. The act requir...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Khashoggi murder: Trump urged to investigate whether Saudi crown prince bin Salman responsible for consulate killing - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/khashoggi-murder-trump-bin-salman-saudi-arabia-consulate-istanbul-sanctions-magnitsky-act-a8644121.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK6EpHBTgZfD5Qsngn4-1y0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/khashoggi-murder-trump-bin-salman-saudi-arabia-consulate-istanbul-sanctions-magnitsky-act-a8644121.html" target="_blank"&gt;Khashoggi murder: Trump urged to investigate whether Saudi crown prince bin Salman responsible for consulate killing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senators have demanded that Donald Trump investigate what role, if any, Saudi crown prince Mohammed bin Salman played in the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi. Two senior senators invoked the Magnitsky Act in an attempt to force the president to determine whether the prince was involved in the Washington Post columnist’s death at the Saudi consulate in Istanbul. The law, named after slain Russian tax lawyer Sergei Magnitsky, allows the US government to impose sanctions against a foreign person determined to have been responsible for human rights violations. Bob Menendez, a Democrat, wrot...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Congress aims to push Trump into getting tough on Saudi Arabia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/12983fca-edaf-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGvBQDU5XfIzWTtF0P8fL9QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 18:44:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/12983fca-edaf-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Congress aims to push Trump into getting tough on Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US lawmakers are pressing the White House into taking a harder line against Saudi Arabia after Donald Trump said he would stand by the kingdom’s royal family following the killing of Jamal Khashoggi. House Democrats are preparing their own moves after senior Republican and Democratic senators ordered the White House to determine whether Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman was behind the murder. According to Democratic aides, whose party will take control of the House of Representatives next year, lawmakers are considering using their powers to push for tougher sanctions on Riyadh and to initia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>US politicians accuse Trump of putting 'Saudi Arabia first' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/politicians-accuse-trump-putting-saudi-arabia-181120210819431.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKH5lijbzGvqAZoCQoYLZykqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 15:11:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/politicians-accuse-trump-putting-saudi-arabia-181120210819431.html" target="_blank"&gt;US politicians accuse Trump of putting 'Saudi Arabia first'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States senators have accused President Donald Trump of putting "Saudi Arabia first" by his decision to not take punitive measures against the kingdom or Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman over the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi. Trump's decision is "yet another fawning prostration to a foreign authoritarian", Democratic Senator Tim Kaine tweeted on Tuesday. "It's only a matter of time until actions like this one by the president directly threaten our security," he added. In a statement issued by the White House, Trump said the US intends to remain a "steadfast partner" of Sau...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Senate Demands Answers On Khashoggi Murder After Trump Stands By Saudis - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/senate-answers-khashoggi-murder_us_5bf53516e4b0eb6d9309e784</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB_hv1mHql14gNfrhmjOhBAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 11:37:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/senate-answers-khashoggi-murder_us_5bf53516e4b0eb6d9309e784" target="_blank"&gt;Senate Demands Answers On Khashoggi Murder After Trump Stands By Saudis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Members of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee on both sides of the aisle voiced their opposition to President Donald Trump’s proclamation of support for the Saudis, demanding answers into Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman’s (MBS) specific involvement in the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi. Sens. Bob Corker (R-Tenn.) and Bob Menendez (D-N.J.) penned a letter to Trump on Tuesday asking the administration to do more to clarify what happened to Khashoggi. Specifically, they want an answer within 120 days into whether MBS is responsible. “In light of recent developments, including the Sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Senate advances bill to end US military involvement in Yemen war - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/senate-advances-bill-military-involvement-yemen-war-181128233238224.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB7cJO8cblnlOISn2OZtI5wqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:21:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/senate-advances-bill-military-involvement-yemen-war-181128233238224.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senate advances bill to end US military involvement in Yemen war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Washington, DC - The US Senate, angered by the murder of writer Jamal Khashoggi, voted 63-37 on Wednesday to take up a war powers resolution that would curtail the Trump administration's military backing for Saudi Arabia's bombing campaign in Yemen. The procedural vote signals a break between leading Senate Republicans and President Donald Trump. It sets up a highly public legislative fight beginning next week over the US role in the Yemen civil war and by extension, the US's strategic partnership with Saudi Arabia in the war. Timing of the Senate vote was prompted by the killing of Khashog...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Trump Thanks Saudi Arabia For Low Gas Prices After Jamal Khashoggi's Killing - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-saudi-arabia-oil-prices_us_5bf55699e4b0eb6d930a2d28</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKtXLthiEYzlwOVXbLe6zXoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 13:51:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-saudi-arabia-oil-prices_us_5bf55699e4b0eb6d930a2d28" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Thanks Saudi Arabia For Low Gas Prices After Jamal Khashoggi's Killing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump on Wednesday thanked Saudi Arabia for the declining price of oil, one day after he said the United States would back the country even if Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman ordered the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi. “Oil prices getting lower. Great! Like a big Tax Cut for America and the World. Enjoy! $54, was just $82,” Trump said in a tweet. “Thank you to Saudi Arabia, but let’s go lower!” Oil prices getting lower. Great! Like a big Tax Cut for America and the World. Enjoy! $54, was just $82. Thank you to Saudi Arabia, but let’s go lower! — Donald J. Trum...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Senators move to act against Saudi Arabia - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/539fae4ff328419bb118da5354b7a04a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJbQmUtY5OGOzKFGaifgWzUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 02:57:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/539fae4ff328419bb118da5354b7a04a" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Senators move to act against Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the U.S. response to the killing of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi (all times local): 4:35 p.m. Senators are sending a strong signal that they want to punish Saudi Arabia for its role in the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi, voting to move forward with legislation that would end U.S. involvement with a Saudi-led war in Yemen. The 63-37 vote was to consider a bipartisan resolution to halt U.S. support for the war, a rebuke to Saudi Arabia and President Donald Trump's administration, which had issued a veto threat. The procedural vote sets up the beginnin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Senators ask Trump to investigate if was MbS responsible for Khashoggi's death - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/444504-senate-asks-investigate-crown-prince/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHxGvm5kr96nP8JrTSeTZRwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 04:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/444504-senate-asks-investigate-crown-prince/" target="_blank"&gt;Senators ask Trump to investigate if was MbS responsible for Khashoggi's death&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a rare bipartisan effort, the senior Republican and Democrat on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee have both asked President Donald Trump to launch a human rights probe into Saudi Crown Prince Mohamed bin Salman. In a letter penned by the outgoing chairman of the committee, Senator Bob Corker (R-Tenn.) and ranking member Bob Menendez (D-N.J.), lawmakers urge Trump to determine whether Mohamed bin Salman (MbS) bears responsibility for the torture and brutal murder of Washington Post columnist and Saudi citizen Jamal Khashoggi in the Saudi consulate in Turkey in October. New: @SenBobCo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>White House denies Haspel prevented from briefing Senate on Khashoggi murder - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/27/jamal-khashoggi-murder-senate-briefing-saudi-arabia-gina-haspel-white-house</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGy4o1Nk3LDKGmetlfv790wqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 18:04:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/27/jamal-khashoggi-murder-senate-briefing-saudi-arabia-gina-haspel-white-house" target="_blank"&gt;White House denies Haspel prevented from briefing Senate on Khashoggi murder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White House has denied preventing the CIA director, Gina Haspel, from briefing the Senate on the murder of Saudi dissident and Washington Post columnist, Jamal Khashoggi. The secretary of state, Mike Pompeo, and the defence secretary, James Mattis, are due to give a briefing on US relations with Saudi Arabia to the entire Senate behind closed doors on Wednesday, ahead of a vote that could cut off US support for Riyadh’s military campaign in Yemen. Related: Who are the Houthis and why are they fighting the Saudi coalition in Yemen? On a national security issue of such importance, it woul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Key Senate Republican says Trump's Saudi response 'took our nation to a very low level,' demands Hill briefing - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/21/politics/bob-corker-saudi-arabia-comments/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHcafN3CCpBMefE9ouiWpP8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 19:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/21/politics/bob-corker-saudi-arabia-comments/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Key Senate Republican says Trump's Saudi response 'took our nation to a very low level,' demands Hill briefing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senate Foreign Relations Chairman Bob Corker told CNN that top administration officials need to immediately brief lawmakers about the situation in Saudi Arabia, while saying President Donald Trump's handling of the situation "took our nation to a very low level." The Tennessee Republican, who is retiring at year's end, said in a phone interview that Secretary of Defense James Mattis, CIA Director Gina Haspel and Secretary of State Mike Pompeo need to brief the full Senate as soon as next week about the situation in Yemen and the circumstances behind the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Bernie Sanders Is Forcing A Vote On Support For Saudi Arabia. Here's His Path To Victory. - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bernie-sanders-is-forcing-a-senate-vote-on-american-support-for-saudi-arabia-heres-his-path-to-victory_us_5bfde5fde4b030172fa80593</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMteqC32IQPiZdxSQ8RIhbMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 02:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bernie-sanders-is-forcing-a-senate-vote-on-american-support-for-saudi-arabia-heres-his-path-to-victory_us_5bfde5fde4b030172fa80593" target="_blank"&gt;Bernie Sanders Is Forcing A Vote On Support For Saudi Arabia. Here's His Path To Victory.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― After months ofglobal controversy over Saudi Arabia for its role in the devastation in Yemen and the murder of Jamal Khashoggi, Congress could issue the longtime American partner’s biggest U.S. rebuke this week ― if a handful of senators agree. The Senate will soon vote on a bill from Sens. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.), Chris Murphy (D-Conn.) and Mike Lee (R-Utah) that would end American support for a Saudi-led military campaign in Yemen that has killed thousands of civilians and pushed millions to the brink of starvation. Sanders and his allies already introduced the legislation ear...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump officials face frustrated senators on Khashoggi - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/8368e1a4acc9462db752d1dad8e380b1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPPIf7M4f-Zf3Yejr4EfDoAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 00:00:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/8368e1a4acc9462db752d1dad8e380b1" target="_blank"&gt;Trump officials face frustrated senators on Khashoggi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Senators who have grown increasingly uneasy with the U.S. response to Saudi Arabia after the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi are set to grill top administration officials Wednesday at a closed-door briefing that could determine how far Congress goes in punishing the longtime Middle East ally. Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell says "some kind of response" is needed from the United States for the Saudis' role in the gruesome death. While President Donald Trump has equivocated over who is to blame, the Senate is considering a vote as soon as this week to halt U.S. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Mississippi senator apologies for ‘hanging’ remark | Navarro reportedly will be excluded from Trump-Xi event - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/mississippi-senator-apologies-for-hanging-remark-lindsey-graham-other-republicans-disagree-with-trumps-move-to-stand-with-saudis-2018-11-21</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIB2auTPykIKN6DynGjcq_QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/mississippi-senator-apologies-for-hanging-remark-lindsey-graham-other-republicans-disagree-with-trumps-move-to-stand-with-saudis-2018-11-21" target="_blank"&gt;Mississippi senator apologies for ‘hanging’ remark | Navarro reportedly will be excluded from Trump-Xi event&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Victor Reklaitis Lindsey Graham, other Republicans disagree with Trump’s move, while GOP Rep. Mia Love loses her re-election bid Republican Sen. Cindy Hyde-Smith has apologized for her remark about public hanging. Getty Images Mississippi senator facing runoff apologizes for joke about public hanging: Sen. Cindy Hyde-Smith, a Mississippi Republican, has apologized after a video surfaced showing her praising someone by saying: “If he invited me to a public hanging, I’d be on the front row.” “For anyone that was offended by my comments, I certainly apologize. There was no il...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>US senators seek to stop weapons sales to Saudi Arabia over Yemen war, Khashoggi murder - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/444128-saudi-arms-ban-bill/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO32EwClF-sceGMjA7coZDAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 22:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/444128-saudi-arms-ban-bill/" target="_blank"&gt;US senators seek to stop weapons sales to Saudi Arabia over Yemen war, Khashoggi murder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A newly proposed bill in the US Senate would suspend the sale of weapons to Saudi Arabia and block refueling of Saudi warplanes bombing Yemen, as punishment for the death of a Washington Post columnist. A group of senators on the Foreign Relations Committee, led by Bob Menendez (D-New Jersey) and Lindsey Graham (R-South Carolina) introduced the “Saudi Arabia Accountability and Yemen Act of 2018.” It was sponsored by three Democrats and two Republicans. Menendez, who is the top Democrat on the committee, said that sanctions against 17 Saudi nationals introduced earlier on Thursday by the Tru...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>US lawmakers aim to hold China accountable for Uyghur abuses - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/politics/congress-uyghur-legislation/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFv8xBjha5rm__S83bC3VxIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 08:23:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/politics/congress-uyghur-legislation/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;US lawmakers aim to hold China accountable for Uyghur abuses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bipartisan group of lawmakers are pushing legislation aimed at holding China accountable for reported human rights abuses against its Uyghur population. The legislation, introduced by Sens. Marco Rubio (R-FL) and Bob Menendez (D-NJ) in the Senate and by Reps. Chris Smith (R-NJ) and Thomas Suozzi (D-NY) in the House, condemns the "gross human rights violations of ethnic Turkic Muslims in Xinjiang, and calling for an end to arbitrary detention, torture, and harassment of these communities inside and outside China." Both House and Senate bills have a broad swath of bipartisan cosponsors. As ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US Senate blocks plan to stop an arms sale to Bahrain – one of the countries bombing Yemen - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/444120-us-senate-arms-bahrain-yemen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ1SdybAQNRhX3h3RpH9IGUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 20:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/444120-us-senate-arms-bahrain-yemen/" target="_blank"&gt;US Senate blocks plan to stop an arms sale to Bahrain – one of the countries bombing Yemen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US senate has rejected an effort by Kentucky Senator Rand Paul to block a major arms sale to Bahrain – more proof that if there’s one thing that unites Democrats and Republicans, it’s selling weapons to Middle Eastern allies. The senate voted 77-21 on Thursday to table the resolution, which would have blocked the $300 million arms sale to the Persian Gulf nation, which is a member of the Saudi-Arabia led coalition currently bombing Yemen. In recent weeks, US lawmakers have publicly professed concern over the war in Yemen and its growing civilian death toll but, when faced with the oppor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Senate lets Bahrain weapon sale proceed; Yemen unease grows - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/75a9feb0f6a548fba4455e8e8a823621</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAt1RRfIHvQR-OrsknDCfO4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 23:28:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/75a9feb0f6a548fba4455e8e8a823621" target="_blank"&gt;Senate lets Bahrain weapon sale proceed; Yemen unease grows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Senate rejected an effort Thursday to block $300 million in weapon sales to Bahrain, but there's growing unease in Congress about the U.S. role supporting the Saudi Arabia-led coalition's military campaign in Yemen. Sen. Rand Paul, R-Ky., forced the vote to send a message to President Donald Trump that the United States is "done with the war in Yemen." Facing a veto threat from the White House, the resolution failed 77-21. But Paul, who remains close to Trump, is not alone in raising concern about the toll the war is taking in Yemen. In the House, Democratic lawmakers ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>U.S. senators seek clampdown on Saudis over Yemen, journalist's murder - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-usa-senate/u-s-senators-seek-clampdown-on-saudis-over-yemen-journalists-murder-idUSKCN1NK347?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=politicsNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL46vmKQn3a_X53m8qXbGLMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 23:07:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-usa-senate/u-s-senators-seek-clampdown-on-saudis-over-yemen-journalists-murder-idUSKCN1NK347?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=politicsNews" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. senators seek clampdown on Saudis over Yemen, journalist's murder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican and Democratic U.S. senators introduced legislation on Thursday seeking to strike back at Saudi Arabia over the death of a Saudi journalist at a consulate in Turkey and for its role in Yemen's devastating civil war. If it were to become law, the bill would suspend weapon sales to Saudi Arabia and prohibit U.S. refueling of Saudi coalition aircraft for Riyadh's campaign in Yemen against the Houthis, Shi'ite Muslim fighters that Yemen's neighbors view as agents of Iran, the lawmakers said. It also would impose sanctions on anyone blocking humanitarian access in Yemen and anyone sup...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>U.S. measure to urge possible China sanctions over Xinjiang crackdown - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xinjiang-usa-idUSKCN1NI2VW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEr8Y4JUaXcbydtNHhj_LSEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 08:47:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xinjiang-usa-idUSKCN1NI2VW" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. measure to urge possible China sanctions over Xinjiang crackdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. lawmakers will introduce legislation on Wednesday urging a stronger response by the Trump administration to China's crackdown on minority Muslims, including possible sanctions against a senior official, a move China decried as hypocrisy. The legislation will also ask President Donald Trump to condemn China's actions in its western region of Xinjiang, call for a new "special coordinator" of U.S. policy on the issue and seek consideration of a ban on export of U.S. technology Beijing could use in surveillance and mass detention of ethnic Uighurs, according to a copy of the measure seen b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Democratic Sen. Bob Menendez Avoids Upset And Wins Re-election In New Jersey - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bob-menendez-new-jersey-senate_us_5bd7404fe4b0a8f17efab075</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGHi5Gl41vfMP63FxmazrKAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ3knAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 01:32:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bob-menendez-new-jersey-senate_us_5bd7404fe4b0a8f17efab075" target="_blank"&gt;Democratic Sen. Bob Menendez Avoids Upset And Wins Re-election In New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey Democrat Bob Menendez overcame lingering doubts about his integrity and a stronger-than-expected challenge from Republican Bob Hugin to win re-election on Tuesday. New Jersey hasn’t elected a Republican to the Senate in 46 years, but the ethical cloud that hovered over Menendez put his bid for another term in doubt this year. He was indicted in 2015 on charges including bribery and fraud stemming from allegations that he engaged in a quid pro quo relationship with a friend ― advancing the man’s business interests and in return accepting an array of gifts, including luxury trips a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>US voters re-elect lawmakers facing criminal indictments &amp; corruption charges, because why not? - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/443362-collins-hunter-menendez-corruption-midterms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJbSYbzotrrlTUOCBZPIgacqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 15:37:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/443362-collins-hunter-menendez-corruption-midterms/" target="_blank"&gt;US voters re-elect lawmakers facing criminal indictments &amp; corruption charges, because why not?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Embarrassing social media photos could easily sink a congressional campaign, but several lawmakers have shown that you can be charged with corruption and embezzlement and still win re-election. American voters took partisan politics to a whole new level on Tuesday, after Republican congressmen Duncan Hunter and Chris Collins – both of whom face federal indictments for crimes including embezzlement and securities fraud – won re-election. As long as the Democrats don’t win, right? Another big takeaway tonight: Being under federal indictment is no bar to winning re-election! Just ask Chris Col...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Two GOP congressman facing indictment win re-election, CNN projects - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/07/politics/duncan-hunter-chris-collins-bob-menendez/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL-6i05CXPCxhqol5qzXuhIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 14:29:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/07/politics/duncan-hunter-chris-collins-bob-menendez/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Two GOP congressman facing indictment win re-election, CNN projects&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican Reps. Chris Collins and Duncan Hunter, who are both facing federal indictments, were re-elected to Congress Tuesday night, CNN projects. Both men were early supporters of President Donald Trump, who blasted the Justice Department earlier this year for investigating the two Republicans. Despite the federal charges against him, which he calls "meritless," Collins has been actively campaigning to keep his seat in New York's 27th Congressional District. Collins, the first House member to endorse Trump's 2016 campaign, has been charged with securities fraud, wire fraud and false state...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Facing long Senate odds, Democrats must first secure New Jersey - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-new-jersey/facing-long-senate-odds-democrats-must-first-secure-new-jersey-idUSKCN1NA16D</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAo8qml3YwiL5h8llzW0cXwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 18:10:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-new-jersey/facing-long-senate-odds-democrats-must-first-secure-new-jersey-idUSKCN1NA16D" target="_blank"&gt;Facing long Senate odds, Democrats must first secure New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Democrats, Tuesday's New Jersey U.S. Senate election should have been a breeze. Bob Menendez, 64, has held the seat for more than a decade in a state that has not elected a Republican to the U.S. Senate in 46 years. But June's Democratic nominating contest exposed his potential weakness following his federal corruption trial last year: 40 percent voted for a virtually unknown challenger who spent zero dollars in the race. Menendez is locked in a tough and expensive race with a Republican who has hammered Menendez as unethical, former pharmaceutical executive Bob Hugin, also 64. Top Demo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>InfoWars, Newsmax and the Wingnut Media Declare Victory Over CNN - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/infowars-newsmax-and-the-wingnut-media-declare-victory-over-cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN8ldVZKk9MvD5fAB6MeyCIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 09:30:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/infowars-newsmax-and-the-wingnut-media-declare-victory-over-cnn" target="_blank"&gt;InfoWars, Newsmax and the Wingnut Media Declare Victory Over CNN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast “AAAAAAAARRRRGGHHH!” Alex Jones shrieked at around 9 p.m. Tuesday night, as it started to look as though Ted Cruz might actually fall to Rep. Robert “Beto” O’Rourke in the epically expensive Senate race in Texas. “If we lose this, oh my God!” Jones ranted—not that his worries proved justified: Cruz ultimately prevailed. And while the Democrats, as widely predicted, took the majority in the House of Representatives—positioning them to cause major heartburn for President Donald Trump—they did so than many in the party had hoped, and the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>'Split decision': How US newspapers reacted to the midterm elections - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/07/split-decision-us-newspapers-reacted-midterm-elections/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ5ZoP0fV3gr317XdWRSnMQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 20:31:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/07/split-decision-us-newspapers-reacted-midterm-elections/" target="_blank"&gt;'Split decision': How US newspapers reacted to the midterm elections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democrats took back the House but the Republicans strengthened their majority in the Senate - a mixed bag of results that were reflected on the country's front pages on Wednesday. Ending eight years of Republican control that began with the tea party revolt of 2010, Democrats picked off more than two dozen GOP-held districts in suburbs across the nation on the way to securing the 218 seats needed for a majority. As of early Wednesday, two dozen races had yet to be decided, meaning the majority could grow still larger. With the Republicans keeping control of the Senate, the outcome in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Bob Menendez Fights for His Political Life as National Dems Watch on in Horror - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bob-menendez-fights-for-his-political-life-as-national-dems-watch-on-in-horror</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-mF3DTHUn9ZsB4GuzpELEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 09:29:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/bob-menendez-fights-for-his-political-life-as-national-dems-watch-on-in-horror" target="_blank"&gt;Bob Menendez Fights for His Political Life as National Dems Watch on in Horror&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg via Getty WEST ORANGE, New Jersey—In October 2002, Sen. Robert Torricelli (D-NJ), dogged by an ethics scandal, dropped his bid for re-election just weeks before the vote, saying that he didn’t want to cause further harm to his party and imperil its control of the chamber. He was replaced by former Sen. Frank Lautenberg (D-NJ), who won the race like all New Jersey Senate Democrats have since 1972. Sixteen years later, Sen. Bob Menendez (D-NJ), who has served in public office since 1986, is facing the toughest reelection campaign of his life, due exclusively to an indi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>This newspaper wants you to know both Senate candidates in New Jersey are completely terrible - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/30/politics/menendez-new-jersey-hugin-endorsement/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOlaAsSqQBtQACOE-hTS-bQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 19:44:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/30/politics/menendez-new-jersey-hugin-endorsement/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;This newspaper wants you to know both Senate candidates in New Jersey are completely terrible&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Newark Star-Ledger's editorial board wanted to make two things very clear in their endorsement of Sen. Bob Menendez's (D) re-election bid: 1. They felt compelled to endorse someone. 2. Both Menendez and Republican Senate nominee Bob Hugin are truly awful. In an op-ed headlined "Choke it down, and vote for Menendez" (I told you it was bad!), the editorial board writes: "This year's U.S. Senate race presents the most depressing choice for New Jersey voters in a generation, with two awful candidates whose most convincing argument is that the other guy is unfit to serve." Democracy! Love it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Health care actually isn't the top issue in every key race - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/politics/most-important-issue-state/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOJOAYlp392HuZdriepgo-IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 10:02:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/politics/most-important-issue-state/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Health care actually isn't the top issue in every key race&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The issue of health care is currently dominating national polls and it is the issue likely voters say is the most important issue to their vote in November. Democrats in particular have built their 2018 pitch around health care. While it is clearly the top issue in the country as a whole, most state polls, especially those in some key battleground states, show health care has competition from the economy, and in some areas, immigration. Texas is one state where residents are more concerned with the issue of immigration, perhaps due to their geographical proximity to the border. According to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Midterm Elections Could Impact America's Global Engagement - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/local-midterms-global-impact/4623399.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJvQwlPWTf5fn5QbEkkRA2YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 10:33:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/local-midterms-global-impact/4623399.html" target="_blank"&gt;Midterm Elections Could Impact America's Global Engagement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While domestic concerns dominate much of the political debate ahead of next month’s U.S. midterm elections, Democratic lawmakers say they are eager to assert themselves on foreign affairs and, when necessary, provide a check on the Trump administration if they win control of at least one chamber of Congress in November. From trade to refugee quotas to regional concerns spanning the globe, a newly empowered Democratic majority would work energetically to hold the administration to account on its policies and potentially wield the power of the purse in areas of disagreement. Republicans, who ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Democrats, Menendez facing tough fight in blue New Jersey - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f957bd8531fb4892b4088ced474c8b62</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENsASnCMrWqRE4eI_Giq_TkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 22:39:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f957bd8531fb4892b4088ced474c8b62" target="_blank"&gt;Democrats, Menendez facing tough fight in blue New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HACKENSACK, N.J. (AP) — In deep blue New Jersey, Sen. Bob Menendez is in a brutal political fight against his GOP rival, putting Democrats — who are pouring cash into the race— on the defensive as they seek to hold onto imperiled seats in red states. Menendez is seeking his third term against wealthy former pharmaceutical CEO Bob Hugin, who has tapped his own wallet for $24 million to finance a TV-ad-heavy campaign in New Jersey, where Democrats have more than 900,000 additional registered voters than Republicans. Polls show the race has closed from a double-digit lead for Menendez to singl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Top Democratic Super PAC Comes To Bob Menendez’s Rescue In New Jersey - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bob-menendez-senate-democratic-super-pac_us_5bc5f739e4b0d38b5871ed43</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPHOs9QAiPRTRTbz3VZQNoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ3knAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 16:48:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bob-menendez-senate-democratic-super-pac_us_5bc5f739e4b0d38b5871ed43" target="_blank"&gt;Top Democratic Super PAC Comes To Bob Menendez’s Rescue In New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democratic Sen. Bob Menendez's recent corruption trial has dogged his bid for re-election in bright blue New Jersey. The Senate Democrats’ leading super PAC is set to spend $3 million in bright blue New Jersey in an effort to save Sen. Bob Menendez, who has struggled to put away a Republican challenger after facing a corruption trial last year. Senate Majority PAC, which is controlled by allies of Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer (D-N.Y.), will use the cash to air a statewide ad attacking Menendez’s opponent, former pharmaceutical executive Bob Hugin, as an ally of President Donald Trum...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Why New Jersey might shake up the Senate map - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/16/politics/new-jersey-senate-shake-up/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKrGeaN8g_4MHiV6Q4CMfNIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 23:39:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/16/politics/new-jersey-senate-shake-up/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why New Jersey might shake up the Senate map&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, something interesting -- and important -- happened in the battle for the Senate. Senate Majority PAC, the chief super PAC of Senate Democrats, dumped $3 million worth of TV ads into the New Jersey Senate race, where Democratic Sen. Bob Menendez is facing a surprisingly strong challenge from wealthy Republican businessman Bob Hugin. The first ad from the super PAC seeks to link Hugin with President Donald Trump, who is not particularly popular in the Garden State. That the Senate Democratic establishment -- and make no mistake, that's what Senate Majority PAC is -- is spending mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia, Turkey have no US ambassadors amid crisis - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/e8884bf35487416c87e6f7185c16f987</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHFhnd9UU5FTEEk4867X6AIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 07:36:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/e8884bf35487416c87e6f7185c16f987" target="_blank"&gt;Saudi Arabia, Turkey have no US ambassadors amid crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The disappearance of journalist and U.S. resident Jamal Khashoggi after visiting a Saudi consulate in Turkey has thrown the large number of diplomatic vacancies under President Donald Trump into the spotlight — notably in Turkey and Saudi Arabia. It's a gap the administration says it has been trying to fix but with limited success. Khashoggi's case and the fact that there are no American ambassadors in either Ankara or Riyadh have prompted concerns about dozens of unfilled senior State Department positions almost two years into Trump's presidency. And, those concerns have ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Paul Ryan warns of 'green wave' of money for Democrats - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/17/politics/paul-ryan-campaign-trail-new-jersey/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGHwJtqUULa7jxCFOwPYO-cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 22:37:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/17/politics/paul-ryan-campaign-trail-new-jersey/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Ryan warns of 'green wave' of money for Democrats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;House Speaker Paul Ryan pointed to a "green wave" of money that Democrats have infused into the midterm elections, telling a crowd of Republican supporters on Wednesday that "this is our challenge." "You're seeing the money spigot being opened by the left to try and drown us out," said the Wisconsin Republican who's leaving Congress at the end of his term in January. While campaigning for GOP candidate Jay Webber in New Jersey's 11th Congressional district, Ryan pointed to Michael Bloomberg's recent pledge to contribute $20 million in the final stretch to Election Day to help Democrats. Tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Menendez: 'Growing sentiment' against Saudi arm sales - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/10/11/bob-menendez-amanpour-khashoggi.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8GPSaDHkHxHXHBjWt5RokqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 18:36:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/10/11/bob-menendez-amanpour-khashoggi.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Menendez: 'Growing sentiment' against Saudi arm sales&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bob Menendez, ranking Democrat on the House Foreign Relations Commitee, says he believes more and more senators would now oppose arms sales to Saudi Arabia. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump: missing journalist no reason to stop Saudi investments - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-politics-dissident-report/trump-missing-journalist-no-reason-to-stop-saudi-investments-idUSKCN1ML2BY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENVN6Hlcvs-A8CHvs9-gc3MqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 20:06:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-politics-dissident-report/trump-missing-journalist-no-reason-to-stop-saudi-investments-idUSKCN1ML2BY" target="_blank"&gt;Trump: missing journalist no reason to stop Saudi investments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump said on Thursday he saw no reason to block Saudi Arabian investments in the United States despite concern over a missing Saudi journalist, saying the Gulf nation would then just move its money into Russia and China. Trump, speaking to reporters at the White House, also said the United States was expecting a report soon on the journalist, Jamal Khashoggi, but gave no other details. "They're (the Saudis) spending $110 billion on military equipment and on things that create jobs ... for this country. I don't like the concept of stopping an investment of $110 billion...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Senators warn Congress may block Trump's Saudi arms deals - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/11/politics/senators-congress-could-block-saudi-arms-deals/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELrBhRjLZeGjuk5vx9F0sPoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 20:17:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/11/politics/senators-congress-could-block-saudi-arms-deals/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senators warn Congress may block Trump's Saudi arms deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump said Thursday he wants to move forward with major arms deals with Saudi Arabia, but senators from both parties are warning that Congress may block these accords from going forward. New Jersey Sen. Bob Menendez, the top Democrat on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, announced in June he would place a hold on a proposed arms sale on thousands of precision-guided munition kits that would be used by Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates. On Thursday, Menendez warned he would not back off in light of the disappearance of journalist Jamal Khashoggi. "Right now, it'...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>U.S. senators trigger human rights probe over missing Saudi journalist - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-politics-dissident-senate/u-s-senators-trigger-human-rights-probe-over-missing-saudi-journalist-idUSKCN1MK2U0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECtpP5f7YMB8DPlyr4TXqdwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:51:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-politics-dissident-senate/u-s-senators-trigger-human-rights-probe-over-missing-saudi-journalist-idUSKCN1MK2U0" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. senators trigger human rights probe over missing Saudi journalist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twenty-two U.S. senators on Wednesday forced a U.S. investigation of whether human rights sanctions should be imposed over the disappearance of Jamal Khashoggi, a Saudi journalist last seen as he entered the Saudi consulate in Turkey on Oct. 2. In a letter, the senators said they had triggered a provision of the Global Magnitsky Human Rights Accountability Act requiring the president to determine whether a foreign person is responsible for a gross human rights violation. "Our expectation is that in making your determination you will consider any relevant information, including with respect ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Senators demand Magnitsky Act probe, sanctions on Saudi Arabia over Khashoggi disappearance - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/440922-trump-letter-senators-khashoggi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELuyou2tVlpeTB_dCaXVhXkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/440922-trump-letter-senators-khashoggi/" target="_blank"&gt;Senators demand Magnitsky Act probe, sanctions on Saudi Arabia over Khashoggi disappearance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of Republican and Democrat senators united to demand an investigation into the disappearance of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi at a consulate in Turkey. Ankara has accused Saudi Arabia of murdering Khashoggi. Senators Bob Corker (R-Tennessee) and Bob Menendez (D-New Jersey), chairman and ranking member of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, and Lindsey Graham (R-South Carolina) and Patrick Leahy (D-Vermont), chairman and ranking member of the Appropriations Subcommittee on State, Foreign Operations, and Related Programs, sent a letter to President Donald Trump on Wednesday dem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Why Sen. Bob Menendez is still favored to win in New Jersey - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/03/politics/bob-menendez-new-jersey-still-favored/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBEOB0u8Xjl6pl29BdPdQZUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 22:53:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/03/politics/bob-menendez-new-jersey-still-favored/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why Sen. Bob Menendez is still favored to win in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Republican winning a US Senate race in deep blue New Jersey? It hasn't happened since 1972. Yet new polls show Democratic Sen. Bob Menendez in trouble against Republican Bob Hugin. Three high-quality polls released over the last two days give Menendez a lead of anywhere from just 2 to 11 points. Indeed, it's plausible that Menendez does lose. He is, however, strongly favored to win re-election, even at this point. There are two factors competing against each other: voter dislike for Menendez and voter dislike for President Donald Trump. The latter is likely to carry the day. Following a f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>CNN Key Races: A blue state complicates Democrats' Senate math - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/02/politics/new-jersey-senate-bob-menendez/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELZf63XXNX9iurE6tf4dOMgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 18:19:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/02/politics/new-jersey-senate-bob-menendez/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;CNN Key Races: A blue state complicates Democrats' Senate math&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Democrats want to take control of the Senate after the midterm elections -- and they very much want to -- they're going to need to defend nearly all of their current seats, knock off at least two vulnerable Republicans and maybe strike deep into red territory. What they can't afford is to play defense in blue states. But that's exactly the position of trial-tainted Sen. Robert Menendez, who survived federal corruption charges in New Jersey with a mistrial and now wants to hold onto his job in the Senate. A number of factors conspired to make CNN slide the New Jersey Senate race from Like...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Florida Sen. Bill Nelson says he is banned from Cuba - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/04/politics/florida-bill-nelson-cuba-ban/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBdc6hsnmO358OVUXrkRw4cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 20:31:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/04/politics/florida-bill-nelson-cuba-ban/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Florida Sen. Bill Nelson says he is banned from Cuba&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a quick moment in the first debate of the 2018 Florida Senate race and if you weren't listening closely you might've missed it: Sen. Bill Nelson, the incumbent Democrat locked in a tight race with Governor Rick Scott, revealed that he was barred from entry into Cuba. It came after Scott accused Nelson of appeasing the Castro regime for supporting President Obama's efforts to normalize relations with the Communist-run Island Nation just 90 miles of the coast of the United States. "Indeed, we've got a problem in this hemisphere, not only with Maduro and Chavez before him, but also with...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>For Democrats To Flip The Senate, The N.J. Race Shouldn’t Be In Doubt. But It Is. - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bob-menendez-hugin-new-jersey_us_5ba40175e4b0375f8f9b6272</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMZZTXGZ-S7qi7VzpOa3LTcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 09:45:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bob-menendez-hugin-new-jersey_us_5ba40175e4b0375f8f9b6272" target="_blank"&gt;For Democrats To Flip The Senate, The N.J. Race Shouldn’t Be In Doubt. But It Is.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Democrats have any chance of winning the Senate in November’s elections, they need to focus their time and energy on flipping traditionally safe GOP seats, like in Tennessee, while defending vulnerable incumbents in red states such as Indiana, West Virginia and North Dakota ― a daunting task even with a historically unpopular president in the Oval Office. What they shouldn’t be doing is worrying about a deep blue state like New Jersey, where Sen. Bob Menendez (D-N.J.) seeks his third term. But Menendez, whose political career in the Garden State began when he won a school board race at ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>US Officials Express Doubts on Future of Nuke Pact with Russia - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-officials-express-doubts-on-future-of-nuke-pact-with-russia-/4576979.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFlJE0fUA3nSUD9_76f3qdsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 19:30:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-officials-express-doubts-on-future-of-nuke-pact-with-russia-/4576979.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Officials Express Doubts on Future of Nuke Pact with Russia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian arms control violations and other malign activities are eroding the confidence and trust required to extend a critical nuclear agreement between Washington and Moscow that expires in 2021, U.S. officials told lawmakers on Tuesday. "Russia continues to violate a series of arms control obligations that undermine the trust of the United States can place in treaties, including some that have served U.S. and allied security interests for years," Under Secretary of State for Arms Control Andrea Thomson said in testimony before the Senate Foreign Relations Committee. "The bottom line is th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>U.S. to sharply limit refugee flows to 30,000 in 2019 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-pompeo/us-to-sharply-limit-refugee-flows-to-30000-in-2019-idUSKCN1LX2HS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJma-Rh7T7IisoiRvYsHeR8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 01:22:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-pompeo/us-to-sharply-limit-refugee-flows-to-30000-in-2019-idUSKCN1LX2HS" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. to sharply limit refugee flows to 30,000 in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said on Monday the United States would cap the number of refugees allowed into the country at 30,000 for fiscal-year 2019, a sharp drop from a limit of 45,000 it set for 2018. "We proposed resettling up to 30,000 refugees under the new refugee ceiling as well as processing more than 280,000 asylum seekers," Pompeo said in an announcement at the State Department, calling the United States "the most generous nation in the world when it comes to protection-based immigration." "This year's proposed refugee ceiling must be considered in the context of the many...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Indicted Congressmen Collins and Hunter try to do what no one has done since 1990 - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/indicted-congressmen-collins-and-hunter-try-to-do-what-no-one-has-done-since-1990-2018-09-17</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHaraQ7mG62meCyjd1gLS5QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/indicted-congressmen-collins-and-hunter-try-to-do-what-no-one-has-done-since-1990-2018-09-17" target="_blank"&gt;Indicted Congressmen Collins and Hunter try to do what no one has done since 1990&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Jeffry Bartash Lawmakers facing charges almost always resign or lose reelection Rep. Chris Collins (R-NY) walks out of a New York court house after being charged with insider trading in August. He now says he will stay on the ballot and seek reelection Getty Images Congressmen Chris Collins and Duncan Hunter are trying to do something no one has done in 28 years: Win reelection under indictment. Collins on Monday indicated he would resume his campaign despite facing federal charges of insider trading. He was indicted last month. New York law doesn’t make it easy to replace...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Senate OKs Trump choice for IRS head over Democrats' protest - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/1c767be8e9b0475c967892ff5b201e0f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBzdmVV7tne5NIFicVekEukqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:17:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/1c767be8e9b0475c967892ff5b201e0f" target="_blank"&gt;Senate OKs Trump choice for IRS head over Democrats' protest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Over the protests of many Democrats, the Senate on Wednesday evening approved President Donald Trump's choice to become the new head of the IRS. Democrats opposed the nomination because of a new Trump administration policy allowing some groups involved in politics to hide their donors' identities. The Senate voted 64-33 to confirm Beverly Hills tax attorney Charles Rettig as Internal Revenue Service commissioner. Democrats who voted against him did so even though they considered him qualified for the job. Still, 15 Democrats voted with the Republicans to approve Rettig. Wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>CNN Key Race Alert: This is the narrow path to a Democratic Senate - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/09/politics/cnn-key-races-senate-update-early-september/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELOJ-5mB4QAwVWLg-ITDHrAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 11:41:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/09/politics/cnn-key-races-senate-update-early-september/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;CNN Key Race Alert: This is the narrow path to a Democratic Senate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are two months until the midterm elections in November and Democrats still have a narrow path to the Senate majority despite a map that favors Republicans and includes 10 Democratic incumbents running in states President Donald Trump won, five of them by double-digit margins. The President carried Indiana and Missouri by 19 points each, but a pair of new polls released this week by NBC News/Marist show Democratic Sens. Joe Donnelly and Claire McCaskill waging competitive re-election fights. In a two-way contest, Donnelly leads Republican Mike Braun 49% to 43% in the Hoosier State, whi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>U.S. senators introduce bill to help Taiwan keep its allies - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-taiwan/us-senators-introduce-bill-to-help-taiwan-keep-its-allies-idUSKCN1LL2PW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM2A6j-5ofqq9tQJ5qTKKysqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 18:22:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-taiwan/us-senators-introduce-bill-to-help-taiwan-keep-its-allies-idUSKCN1LL2PW" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. senators introduce bill to help Taiwan keep its allies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican and Democratic U.S. senators introduced legislation on Wednesday to discourage Taiwan's few remaining allies from switching their allegiance to China, after El Salvador became the third country this year to move toward Beijing. The legislation, introduced by Republican Senators Cory Gardner and Marco Rubio and Democrats Ed Markey and Bob Menendez, would authorize the State Department to downgrade U.S. relations with any government that shifts away from Taiwan, and to suspend or alter U.S. assistance. It also requires a U.S. strategy to engage with governments to support Taiwan's ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>