<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Xi Jinping - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRFptWmpZd0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:20:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Trump-Xi meet, a turning point in global trade war? - EWN</title><link>https://ewn.co.za/2018/12/02/trump-xi-meet-a-turning-point-in-global-trade-war</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDX527NqG0oPBIlXMfoU9lcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowgdKhCTCd8pYCMO3KkQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:37:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://ewn.co.za/2018/12/02/trump-xi-meet-a-turning-point-in-global-trade-war" target="_blank"&gt;Trump-Xi meet, a turning point in global trade war?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;EWN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The state-run 'China Daily' newspaper said any deal was unlikely to be a comprehensive solution to the impasse due to 'diverging demands and agendas'.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://ewn.co.za">EWN</source></item><item><title>China exports weaken ahead of US trade talks - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/e42afc33d5894ac6b79aa4a984822e2e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFS4_iH5mBjPN2VaRwJdz18qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:00:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/e42afc33d5894ac6b79aa4a984822e2e" target="_blank"&gt;China exports weaken ahead of US trade talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China's export growth sank in November as global demand weakened, adding to pressure on Beijing ahead of trade talks with Washington. Exports rose 5.4 percent over a year ago to $227.4 billion, a marked decline from the previous month's 12.6 percent increase, customs data showed Saturday. Imports rose 3 percent to $182.7 billion, a sharp reversal from October's 20.3 percent surge. That adds to signs a slowdown in the world's second-largest economy is deepening as Chinese leaders prepare for negotiations with President Donald Trump over Beijing's technology policy and other ir...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Chinese executive facing US extradition appears in court - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/fb8df477588343918f6b5cfbef0a0472</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEPu-0obI-6UNwqh5iNXEJYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:00:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/fb8df477588343918f6b5cfbef0a0472" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese executive facing US extradition appears in court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VANCOUVER, British Columbia (AP) — A Canadian prosecutor urged a Vancouver court to deny bail to a Chinese executive at the heart of a case that is shaking up U.S.-China relations and worrying global financial markets. Meng Wanzhou, the chief financial officer of telecommunications giant Huawei and daughter of its founder, was detained at the request of the U.S. during a layover at the Vancouver airport last Saturday — the same day that Presidents Donald Trump and Xi Jinping of China agreed over dinner to a 90-day ceasefire in a trade dispute that threatens to disrupt global commerce. The U...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>China's Xi urges North Korea, United States to meet halfway - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-northkorea/chinas-xi-urges-north-korea-united-states-to-meet-halfway-idUSKBN1O60RV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECP1CP9wPHjkiCYXRyZnw1IqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:10:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-northkorea/chinas-xi-urges-north-korea-united-states-to-meet-halfway-idUSKBN1O60RV" target="_blank"&gt;China's Xi urges North Korea, United States to meet halfway&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping on Friday told North Korea's foreign minister that he hoped North Korea and the United States could meet each other halfway and address each other's reasonable concerns, China's foreign ministry said. China is the North's most important economic and diplomatic backer, despite anger over its neighbour's nuclear and missile programmes. Ties have warmed in the last year as Pyongyang's relations with both Seoul and Washington have also improved. At a landmark June summit in Singapore, the North's leader, Kim Jong Un, and U.S. President Donald Trump pledged to work t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>What does Meng Wanzhou's arrest mean for US-China conflict - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/meng-wanzhou-arrest-means-china-conflict-181208010817198.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOCWIGTWHPNRcW8XwSKGID4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:32:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/meng-wanzhou-arrest-means-china-conflict-181208010817198.html" target="_blank"&gt;What does Meng Wanzhou's arrest mean for US-China conflict&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the day global attention zeroed in on a highly-anticipated meeting between Donald Trump and Xi Jinping in the Argentine capital, thousands of kilometres away, on Canada's western coast, a new, dramatic front was opening in the US-China trade war - one that would reignite fears over the viability of a vague and fragile trade war truce between the world's two largest economies. It wasn't until Wednesday that the world learned that Meng Wanzhou, chief financial officer of Chinese telecoms giant Huawei, had been arrested on Saturday in Canada at the behest of US authorities. Hours before her...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Huawei awaits 'right conclusion' in CFO's arrest - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/0e5bd92a91624a34a153d6bb4c21fd97</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM8HgyqH5_pMcITI8PG74vwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 04:45:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/0e5bd92a91624a34a153d6bb4c21fd97" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Huawei awaits 'right conclusion' in CFO's arrest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the arrest of an executive of Chinese telecoms equipment maker Huawei Technologies (all times local): 11:45 p.m. Chinese telecommunications giant Huawei says it has "every confidence that the Canadian and U.S. legal systems will reach the right conclusion" over the arrest of one of its top executives in Canada. Huawei released a brief statement Saturday in China following a bail hearing in Vancouver for Meng Wanzou, its chief financial officer and the daughter of its founder. She faces possible extradition to the U.S, where officials allege that Huawei used a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Explainer: How does extradition to the U.S. work? - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei-tech-explainer/explainer-how-does-extradition-to-the-us-work-idUSKBN1O528Y</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGpFTkPi4fu4AkOloijKuBwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 03:29:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei-tech-explainer/explainer-how-does-extradition-to-the-us-work-idUSKBN1O528Y" target="_blank"&gt;Explainer: How does extradition to the U.S. work?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The arrest in Canada of a top Chinese technology executive for possible extradition to the United States has roiled markets and cast doubt on a recent U.S.-China trade truce. Huawei Technologies Co Ltd Chief Financial Officer Meng Wanzhou, who is also the daughter of the telecommunications company's founder, was detained on Saturday while changing planes in Vancouver. A person familiar with the matter told Reuters she faces extradition on charges related to U.S. sanctions violations. Chinese authorities have criticized the United States and Canada, saying they did not explain why Meng was a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump Seeks To Calm Markets Over China Trade - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/charleswallace1/2018/12/07/trump-seeks-to-calm-markets-over-china-trade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFOBSD-C52Dp-1mbDgmUy5kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/charleswallace1/2018/12/07/trump-seeks-to-calm-markets-over-china-trade/" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Seeks To Calm Markets Over China Trade&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump said talks with China are going well. (AP Photo/Evan Vucci) President Trump brushed aside worries about trade with China on Friday, saying talks with Beijing are going well despite a blast of criticism from official Chinese sources over the arrest of a Chinese tech executive. Trump issued a tweet Friday morning saying only “China talks are going very well,” without providing any details. The tweet came in response to a rocky week on Wall Street, with markets see-sawing over fears that the two sides were at an impasse following Trump’s description of himself as “Mr. Ta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Trump said to express irritation over Wall Street's negative review of China deal - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/trump-stock-market-china-irritation/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPITHX3hnLnD8P_YreJkwIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:51:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/trump-stock-market-china-irritation/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump said to express irritation over Wall Street's negative review of China deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump has expressed anxiety about a dismal streak for the stock market over the past several days, telling advisers he is surprised a tentative deal he struck with Chinese President Xi Jinping hasn't gone over well with Wall Street, according to a person who has spoken with him. Ahead of Trump's meeting with Xi, held on Saturday evening in Argentina, some of Trump's top advisers told him the shaky markets were partly due to unease over a brewing trade war with China. That left Trump hungry to strike some sort of deal with Xi, people familiar with the matter said. When the t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>North Korea’s top diplomat arrives in China as countries seek breakthrough in nuclear crisis - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/north-korea-china-ri-yong-ho-visit-beijing-kim-jong-un-nuclear-crisis-wang-yi-a8670601.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGJGW0VVJAUdN9xcsKu-BwMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/north-korea-china-ri-yong-ho-visit-beijing-kim-jong-un-nuclear-crisis-wang-yi-a8670601.html" target="_blank"&gt;North Korea’s top diplomat arrives in China as countries seek breakthrough in nuclear crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;North Korea’s foreign minister arrived in China on Thursday for the start of a hastily-arranged three-day official visit, as all sides gear up for a new round of leaders’ summits aimed at solving the nuclear crisis on the Korean peninsula. Ri Yong Ho’s trip was only announced on Tuesday, a few days after the Chinese president Xi Jinping held one-on-one talks with Donald Trump at the G20 summit in Argentina. The timing of Mr Ri’s visit has led to speculation that North Korea’s top diplomat will be briefed on Mr Xi and Mr Trump’s discussions. The US president said after the meeting that Mr Xi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>German president reminds young Chinese of 'havoc' caused by Marxism - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-germany/german-president-reminds-young-chinese-of-havoc-caused-by-marxism-idUSKBN1O60YS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENo1b7sj2C5OLxPH9ehOweoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:17:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-germany/german-president-reminds-young-chinese-of-havoc-caused-by-marxism-idUSKBN1O60YS" target="_blank"&gt;German president reminds young Chinese of 'havoc' caused by Marxism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;German President Frank-Walter Steinmeier told Chinese students on Friday that "havoc" was wrought in the name of Karl Marx in Germany and eastern Europe, but that Marx also stood for things like freedom of the press. Marx is lauded in China, and in May President Xi Jinping said the decision of the ruling Communist Party to stick with his political theories remained "totally correct", in a speech to coincide with the 200th anniversary of the German philosopher's birth. Xi's speech came near the end of a week-long propaganda blitz by state media, with chat shows saying "Marx was Right" and ca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Arresting Huawei exec is a case of spectacularly bad timing - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/opinions/arresting-huawei-exec-is-a-case-of-spectacularly-bad-timing-andelman/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEADGn8FFnqwPioIb4tWhfd0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:31:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/opinions/arresting-huawei-exec-is-a-case-of-spectacularly-bad-timing-andelman/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Arresting Huawei exec is a case of spectacularly bad timing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;David A. Andelman, visiting scholar at the Center on National Security at Fordham Law School and director of its Red Lines Project, is a contributor to CNN, where his columns won the Deadline Club Award for Best Opinion Writing. Author of "A Shattered Peace: Versailles 1919 and the Price We Pay Today," he was formerly a foreign correspondent for The New York Times and Paris correspondent for CBS News. Follow him @DavidAndelman. The views expressed in this commentary are his own. View more opinion on CNN. Imagine for a moment that Ivanka Trump steps off a plane at Chek Lap Kok Airport and is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>White House, Trudeau seek to distance themselves from Huawei move - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei-tech/white-house-trudeau-seek-to-distance-themselves-from-huawei-move-idUSKBN1O604J</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHUSVOaxg_47Kvqu9mo0FKoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:40:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei-tech/white-house-trudeau-seek-to-distance-themselves-from-huawei-move-idUSKBN1O604J" target="_blank"&gt;White House, Trudeau seek to distance themselves from Huawei move&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump did not know about plans to arrest a top executive at Chinese telecoms giant Huawei in Canada, two U.S. officials said on Thursday, in an apparent attempt to stop the incident from impeding crucial trade talks with Beijing. Huawei Technologies Co Ltd's chief financial officer, Meng Wanzhou, the 46-year-old daughter of the company's founder, was detained in Canada on Dec. 1, the same day Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping dined together at the G20 summit in Buenos Aires. A White House official told Reuters Trump did not know about a U.S. request for her extradition...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China's Xi hopes North Korea, U.S. address each others' concerns - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-northkorea-xi/chinas-xi-hopes-north-korea-us-address-each-others-concerns-idUSKBN1O60YN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK77gBYelWdTcVvFvryBxukqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:10:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-northkorea-xi/chinas-xi-hopes-north-korea-us-address-each-others-concerns-idUSKBN1O60YN" target="_blank"&gt;China's Xi hopes North Korea, U.S. address each others' concerns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping told North Korea's foreign minister on Friday that he hoped North Korea and the United States could meet each other halfway and address each others' legitimate concerns, state news agency Xinhua said. (Reporting by Ben Blanchard and Lushan Zhang; Editing by Clarence Fernandez)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Donald Trump and Xi Jinping have brokered peace. It will be sorely tested - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/05/donald-trump-xi-jinping-trade-buenos-aires</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKB82XpoIOSAvdVyPzMVCo4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:39:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/05/donald-trump-xi-jinping-trade-buenos-aires" target="_blank"&gt;Donald Trump and Xi Jinping have brokered peace. It will be sorely tested&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What Donald Trump and Xi Jinping did in Buenos Aires was buy time. Three months, in fact. Which is good when measured against the alternative: which was a full-blown trade and broader economic war between the two countries. Which in turn had the potential to trigger a further collapse in global market sentiment, particularly coming on the back of other negative trends emerging in both the US and Chinese domestic economies. Related: Donald Trump and Xi Jinping declare trade truce at G20 But a word of caution to markets, even from those of us who have been arguing publicly that on balance a d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>North Korea tells China it's committed to denuclearization - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/b9a26cf5f0b74def8ff6b4015bd66121</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMzWOux2DkoLSyfkkuw5KsMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:41:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/b9a26cf5f0b74def8ff6b4015bd66121" target="_blank"&gt;North Korea tells China it's committed to denuclearization&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (AP) — North Korea's foreign minister said his country remains committed to ending its nuclear weapons program in talks Friday with his Chinese counterpart, according to China's foreign ministry. The talks in Beijing between Ri Yong Ho and Wang Yi came amid a lack of progress in international efforts to persuade North Korea to reverse its drive to build a nuclear arsenal. China is North Korea's most important ally, but has agreed to increasingly strict United Nations economic sanctions over its programs to develop nuclear weapons and the ballistic missiles to deliver them. Ri told W...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Inside China's audacious global propaganda campaign - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/dec/07/china-plan-for-global-media-dominance-propaganda-xi-jinping</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECQsfQG6qCNT1L3TUhTCvYYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:00:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/news/2018/dec/07/china-plan-for-global-media-dominance-propaganda-xi-jinping" target="_blank"&gt;Inside China's audacious global propaganda campaign&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As they sifted through resumes, the team recruiting for the new London hub of China’s state-run broadcaster had an enviable problem: far, far too many candidates. Almost 6,000 people were applying for just 90 jobs “reporting the news from a Chinese perspective”. Even the simple task of reading through the heap of applications would take almost two months. For western journalists, demoralised by endless budget cuts, China Global Television Network presents an enticing prospect, offering competitive salaries to work in state-of-the-art purpose-built studios in Chiswick, west London. CGTN – as...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Sell-off due to fragile trade truce could spur M&amp;A turning point - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a0fc41de-f828-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN7RVfcyxPr-Kz5tkDdiLFgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a0fc41de-f828-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Sell-off due to fragile trade truce could spur M&amp;A turning point&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FT premium subscribers can click here to receive Due Diligence every day by email. Market volatility is the topic du jour, and not just for investors, but bankers and lawyers who sew up the trillions of dollars of takeover transactions each year. Increasingly, sources tell DD, the first question from their clients (whether lunching at Avra in Midtown Manhattan or Cecconi’s in London) is what the market swings mean. Their answer: it can inject uncertainty. And as Frank Aquila, a corporate lawyer at Sullivan &amp; Cromwell, explains it, “uncertainty ultimately is what kills all deals”. The latest...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Huawei finance chief Meng Wanzhou to appear in court as Chinese media react furiously to arrest - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/huawei-finance-chief-meng-wanzhou-in-court-chinese-media-reaction-arrest-a8672006.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIKIuXSYUsFSyCXQrd9iuGAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRxP0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/huawei-finance-chief-meng-wanzhou-in-court-chinese-media-reaction-arrest-a8672006.html" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei finance chief Meng Wanzhou to appear in court as Chinese media react furiously to arrest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei’s finance chief is set to appear at a bail hearing in Vancouver on Friday amid a backlash in Chinese media over her detention. Chief financial officer Meng Wanzhou, daughter of Huawei founder Ren Zhengfei, was arrested by Canadian authorities on Saturday at the request of the US government which is seeking extradition. No official reason has been given but it is thought to be linked to alleged violations of US sanctions on Iran. Stock markets calmed on Friday following a tumultuous session on Thursday as news of Ms Meng’s detention prompted fears of a new front on the US-China trade ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Trump Today: President touts meeting with Xi and slams former lawyer Michael Cohen - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-today-president-touts-meeting-with-xi-and-slams-former-lawyer-michael-cohen-2018-12-03</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHECdjESkbOG8-Htnp1XQHIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 20:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-today-president-touts-meeting-with-xi-and-slams-former-lawyer-michael-cohen-2018-12-03" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Today: President touts meeting with Xi and slams former lawyer Michael Cohen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRUMP TODAY By Robert Schroeder Roger Stone has ‘guts,’ Trump tweets President Donald Trump. Getty Images President Donald Trump on Monday touted his meeting with Chinese President Xi Jinping, as he ripped his former lawyer Michael Cohen and said he was looking forward to being with the Bush family to mourn former President George H.W. Bush. POST-MEETING TWEETS Trump tweeted out what he said were the benefits of his meeting with Xi at the Group of 20 summit in Argentina over the weekend. He said farmers would be a “BIG and FAST beneficiary of our deal with China,” and that Beijing intends t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>China hails Trump-Xi summit, but offers no new details - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china/china-hails-trump-xi-summit-but-offers-no-new-details-idUSKBN1O502D</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIHBdmsfgtW4DwZF7uiX28qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 01:26:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china/china-hails-trump-xi-summit-but-offers-no-new-details-idUSKBN1O502D" target="_blank"&gt;China hails Trump-Xi summit, but offers no new details&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The summit between President Xi Jinping and his U.S. counterpart Donald Trump in Argentina was "friendly and candid" and would help to avoid further trade tensions, a senior Chinese diplomat said on Thursday, but offered no new details on the talks. The two leaders held high stakes discussions on the sidelines of the G20 meeting in Buenos Aires last week and agreed to a ceasefire in their trade war. State Councillor Wang Yi, the Chinese government's top diplomat, said the talks about trade frictions had been extremely positive and constructive, helping reach a consensus that worked for both...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China hails 'mutual respect' as it loops Portugal into belt initiative - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-portugal-china-xi/china-hails-mutual-respect-as-loops-portugal-into-belt-initiative-idUSKBN1O41RK</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGkElNI1IVuwtLMtFTp9MEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:43:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-portugal-china-xi/china-hails-mutual-respect-as-loops-portugal-into-belt-initiative-idUSKBN1O41RK" target="_blank"&gt;China hails 'mutual respect' as it loops Portugal into belt initiative&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China will always stick to "mutual respect" in its efforts to deal with global challenges, President Xi Jinping said on Wednesday in Lisbon, where he signed agreements to link Portugal to Beijing's belt and road initiative. Portugal was Xi's last stop on a trip that included a meeting of G20 leaders in Buenos Aires, where China and the United States agreed to negotiate a solution to their trade war. "Even though the world is facing many challenges, China will always adhere to mutual respect and peaceful development, promote peace and stability," Xi said in a short speech. He said that durin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>10-year U.S. government bond yield pushes below 3% as stocks come off highs - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/treasury-yields-rise-as-trade-tensions-fade-in-wake-of-trump-xi-meeting-2018-12-03</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEuSnv595POzZ_PQj0sQ42kqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 21:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/treasury-yields-rise-as-trade-tensions-fade-in-wake-of-trump-xi-meeting-2018-12-03" target="_blank"&gt;10-year U.S. government bond yield pushes below 3% as stocks come off highs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOND REPORT By Sunny Oh Sifma recommends the bond market close on Wednesday Treasury yields broke below key psychological levels on Monday as stocks gave up a chunk of their opening gains. The rally in government debt, which drove Treasury prices higher and rates down, came in late-morning action after fading euphoria around a tentative deal with President Donald Trump and China’s leader Xi Jinping this weekend to delay a further increase in tariffs. The 10-year Treasury note yield (BX:TMUBMUSD10Y) was down 2.4 basis points to 2.990%, around a three month low, after trading as high as 3.050...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Trade war truce: markets jump as Trump says China will halt new car tariffs - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/03/trade-war-china-trump-markets-jump-car-tariffs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELOv_H7lbhfsOUQOsQfm2BwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 06:13:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/03/trade-war-china-trump-markets-jump-car-tariffs" target="_blank"&gt;Trade war truce: markets jump as Trump says China will halt new car tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global stock markets rallied on Monday after the US and China agreed a 90-day truce in their trade war at a weekend meeting of the G20 nations in Argentina. The outcome of the two-and-a-half-hour dinner meeting between Donald Trump and Xi Jinping in Buenos Aires, following months of escalating tensions on trade and other issues, boosted financial markets around the world. The FTSE 100 index in London rose more than 2%, while Germany’s Dax jumped 2.6%, France’s CAC gained 2%, Spain’s Ibex rose 1.8% and Italy’s FTSE MiB gained 1.9%. In Asia, the benchmark Shanghai Composite index led the way ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Trump says he believes China's Xi is sincere on trade - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-trump/trump-says-he-believes-chinas-xi-is-sincere-on-trade-idUSKBN1O41P1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELrObf7b7LvSb_Opr-HO7BUqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:36:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-trump/trump-says-he-believes-chinas-xi-is-sincere-on-trade-idUSKBN1O41P1" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says he believes China's Xi is sincere on trade&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump on Wednesday said he believed Chinese President Xi Jinping was being sincere at their meeting on trade and that Beijing had been sending "strong signals" since then. "Very strong signals being sent by China once they returned home from their long trip, including stops, from Argentina. Not to sound naive or anything, but I believe President Xi meant every word of what he said at our long and hopefully historic meeting. ALL subjects discussed!" Trump tweeted. (Reporting by Susan Heavey; Editing by Doina Chiacu)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Chinese state media says U.S. trying to 'stifle' Huawei with arrest - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei-media/chinese-state-media-says-us-trying-to-stifle-huawei-with-arrest-idUSKBN1O607R</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMZXlzczaOxaTxJzi0ZYHMcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:27:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei-media/chinese-state-media-says-us-trying-to-stifle-huawei-with-arrest-idUSKBN1O607R" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese state media says U.S. trying to 'stifle' Huawei with arrest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States is trying to "stifle" Chinese technology company Huawei and curb its global expansion with the arrest of a top executive, Chinese state media said on Friday. Huawei Technologies Co Ltd's chief financial officer, Meng Wanzhou, the 46-year-old daughter of the company's founder, was detained in Canada on Dec. 1, the same day U.S. President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping dined together at the G20 summit in Buenos Aires. Trump did not know about plans to arrest a top executive at the Chinese telecoms giant in Canada, two U.S. officials said on Thursday, in an app...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Dollar softens after U.S.-China temporary cease-fire - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dollar-softens-after-us-china-cease-fire-2018-12-03</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJaP1exAANcG1VPQeDGxzl4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 20:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dollar-softens-after-us-china-cease-fire-2018-12-03" target="_blank"&gt;Dollar softens after U.S.-China temporary cease-fire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CURRENCIES By Anneken Tappe Commodity-linked currencies rally on higher oil prices Getty Images The U.S. dollar was weaker on Monday as risk appetite across financial markets increased in the wake of a trade-war cease-fire between the U.S. and China. Higher oil prices also boosted commodity currencies, weighing on greenback. The ICE U.S. Dollar Index (DXY) was 0.2% weaker at 97.047. So-called risk currencies strengthened on the back of a detente that came on the sidelines of the G-20 summit in Argentina. The standoff between the two largest economies in the world has been momentarily halte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>If Brunei Takes China’s Energy Deal, Neighbors May Follow - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/if-brunei-takes-china-energy-deal-neighbors-may-follow/4690627.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMuDHuFids7IuV68N0irlQcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:40:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/if-brunei-takes-china-energy-deal-neighbors-may-follow/4690627.html" target="_blank"&gt;If Brunei Takes China’s Energy Deal, Neighbors May Follow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brunei, an oil-rich nation in Southeast Asia, watched with near horror as world energy prices fell from 2014 to 2016. Reserves were running out. Its lifeblood of 80 years at stake, the tiny, wealthy country is looking for other sources of prosperity. China is offering to be a source, and it’s China that stands to prosper politically. Chinese President Xi Jinping agreed to support joint exploration with Brunei for oil and gas, likely in a rectangular block of the South China Sea extending from the Bruneian coastline on the island of Borneo. That’s Brunei’s exclusive economic zone, but China ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>New Zealand China Scholar 'Targeted' by Beijing - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/new-zealand-china-scholar-targeted-by-beijing/4690536.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJwXk_aG_0FslRI9GKps5AoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:43:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/new-zealand-china-scholar-targeted-by-beijing/4690536.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand China Scholar 'Targeted' by Beijing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An academic who has been exposing the back-door methods of the Chinese seeking to influence New Zealand politics as well as the country's media and universities says she is being targeted and harassed by Beijing. Professor Anne-Marie Brady has asked for government protection after suffering what she describes as a yearlong campaign of intimidation by Beijing, saying she fears for her security and the safety of her family. And more than 150 China experts from universities and think tanks around the world are supporting her appeal for protection, urging New Zealand's government to assign a se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>China-US feud threatens Canada as Huawei executive due in court - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/07/huawei-meng-wanzhou-arrest-canada-china-response-relations</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHiUptzZHafgEhrEzpMJrrMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:00:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/07/huawei-meng-wanzhou-arrest-canada-china-response-relations" target="_blank"&gt;China-US feud threatens Canada as Huawei executive due in court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The feud between China and the United States sparked by the arrest of a senior Huawei telecoms executive in Vancouver appears poised to inflict collateral damage on Canada, which has sought to build closer ties with Beijing amid an increasingly unpredictable trade relationship with its southern neighbour. Related: John Bolton says he knew in advance Huawei executive would be arrested Meng Wanzhou, Huawei’s global chief financial officer, will appear at a bail hearing on Friday morning, following her arrest last Saturday. She is sought for extradition to the US for allegedly violating US san...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>China's Xi seeks deeper cooperation with EU, Portugal - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-portugal-china/chinas-xi-seeks-deeper-cooperation-with-eu-portugal-idUSKBN1O32CB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED2BF55RHgWZ0gseu84NRcgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:40:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-portugal-china/chinas-xi-seeks-deeper-cooperation-with-eu-portugal-idUSKBN1O32CB" target="_blank"&gt;China's Xi seeks deeper cooperation with EU, Portugal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China wants to deepen cooperation with the European Union, China's President Xi Jinping said on Tuesday during a visit to Portugal, a country he said was an important link to Europe. "Chinese-Portuguese relations are entering their best period in history," Xi said in a speech after meeting Portuguese President Marcelo Rebelo de Sousa. Xi said the two countries could benefit from Beijing's belt and road initiative, to build business partnerships, including in third countries along the old silk road from China to Europe. Xi said that having Portugal as a partner, "we will deepen our ... strat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump Tries to Calm Global Markets After Stocks Drop Sharply - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-tries-to-calm-global-markets-after-stocks-drop-sharply-in-response-to-us-china-trade-war/4687911.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECLDCnqp6TX5y_rfTNGYaJAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:43:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-tries-to-calm-global-markets-after-stocks-drop-sharply-in-response-to-us-china-trade-war/4687911.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Tries to Calm Global Markets After Stocks Drop Sharply&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump, who rattled global markets Tuesday after declaring himself "a Tariff Man," predicted in a series of tweets Wednesday the United States and China would negotiate a new trade deal. Trump said China is planning to resume buying U.S. soybeans and natural gas, which he said confirms his claims that China had agreed to start "immediately" buying U.S. products." Trump said he believes "President Xi (Jinping) meant every word of what he said" at their meeting recently in Argentina, including "his promise to me to criminalize the sale of deadly Fentanyl coming into the U...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>After Huawei Arrest, White House Sticks With Hard Line on Trade Talks - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/after-huawei-arrest-white-house-sticks-with-hard-line-on-trade-talks/4689821.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELTFQXyZGDjZTiagQT1tvhcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:15:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/after-huawei-arrest-white-house-sticks-with-hard-line-on-trade-talks/4689821.html" target="_blank"&gt;After Huawei Arrest, White House Sticks With Hard Line on Trade Talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Top White House officials are continuing to take a hard line on U.S.-China trade talks, even after the arrest of a prominent Chinese tech executive that some fear could derail a trade truce between Washington and Beijing. In an interview with VOA, White House trade and economic adviser Peter Navarro repeatedly refused to comment on the record about the arrest of Meng Wanzhou, chief financial officer of Huawei, whose company is at the heart of trade tensions between the U.S. and China. But Navarro said that the Trump administration is "demanding not asking" that China make fundamental change...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Unravelling US-China trade truce threatens deal wave - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8ee1cbde-f816-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHjPPsE97Pb3hFWcpbTVMr0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:00:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8ee1cbde-f816-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Unravelling US-China trade truce threatens deal wave&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market sell-off triggered by fears that the US-China trade truce could unravel has created fresh uncertainty for companies on the hunt for acquisitions, threatening a five-year global takeover wave, dealmakers say. Jumping volatility creates several problems for advisers who have helped broker more than $18tn of deals since the start of 2014. Swinging share prices can spoil a deal, as buyers and sellers struggle to agree on a value to clinch a transaction, and can also weigh on board and chief executive confidence. If an economic slowdown materialises, as some market barometers suggest,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>China ‘confident’ trade agreement with US can be reached within 90 days – official - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/business/445727-china-us-tariffs-ceasefire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFxF3Mp2QeIHg3yAMtSKDjAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwroQo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/business/445727-china-us-tariffs-ceasefire/" target="_blank"&gt;China ‘confident’ trade agreement with US can be reached within 90 days – official&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beijing wants to strike a trade deal with Washington within three months, China’s commerce ministry announced Thursday in its first comment on US-China trade negotiations since presidents Xi and Trump met in Argentina. “We are confident in reaching an agreement (with the US) within the next 90 days,” China's commerce ministry spokesman Gao Feng said in a weekly briefing on Thursday. The official added that both sides have been communicating and cooperating since the two countries’ leaders, US President Donald Trump and China’s Xi Jinping, met at the G20 summit in Buenos Aires. Trump agreed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Trump changes his tone on China deal after market slide - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/trump-xi-china-markets-trade/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIRCERmlklZar_66Eb0WFUsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 04:38:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/trump-xi-china-markets-trade/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump changes his tone on China deal after market slide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After President Donald Trump helped send markets tanking by feeding doubts about his trade deal with China, he stepped in Wednesday to pump up optimism in a series of early-morning tweets. The US President cited "very strong signals" overnight from Beijing, including recognition of a 90-day clock for talks -- a key point that had been omitted in readouts from Beijing after Trump's Saturday night dinner meeting with his Chinese counterpart Xi Jinping in Buenos Aires. The Chinese Ministry of Commerce also reaffirmed Beijing's pledge to "implementing already-agreed-on specific points as quickl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm says China comment will not revive NXP deal - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nxp-semicondtrs-m-a-qualcomm/qualcomm-says-china-comment-will-not-revive-nxp-deal-idUSKBN1O20BG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBsGCval8asZ6MxxZaOUMxMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 23:43:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nxp-semicondtrs-m-a-qualcomm/qualcomm-says-china-comment-will-not-revive-nxp-deal-idUSKBN1O20BG" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm says China comment will not revive NXP deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. chipmaker Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) said on Monday it was not looking to revive its abandoned $44 billion acquisition of Dutch peer NXP Semiconductors NV (NXPI.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), a day after the White House said China would reconsider clearing a deal if it was attempted again. Qualcomm, the world's biggest smartphone-chip maker, walked away from its agreement to buy NXP in July, after failing to secure Chinese regulatory approval. The planned deal was first agreed between the two companies in October 2016. Qualcomm, headquartered...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China demands Canada release executive of tech giant Huawei - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/214994bccf3f442db8169cba138d970d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMHg0Zpa0NhgtG6esz6LMwgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:46:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/214994bccf3f442db8169cba138d970d" target="_blank"&gt;China demands Canada release executive of tech giant Huawei&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China on Thursday demanded that Canada release an executive of Chinese tech giant Huawei who was arrested in a case that compounds tensions with the U.S. and threatens to complicate trade talks. Meng Wanzhou, chief financial officer of Huawei Technologies Ltd., faces possible extradition to the United States, according to Canadian authorities. The Globe and Mail newspaper, citing law enforcement sources, said she is suspected of trying to evade U.S. trade curbs on Iran. Huawei, the biggest global supplier of network gear used by phone and internet companies, has been the targ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>China Demands Release of Telecom Executive Arrested in Canada - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/china-demands-release-of-top-telecom-executive-arrested-in-canada/4690017.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6DzvN7kENVwtWf3SGi5yIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:52:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/china-demands-release-of-top-telecom-executive-arrested-in-canada/4690017.html" target="_blank"&gt;China Demands Release of Telecom Executive Arrested in Canada&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China is demanding Canada immediately free a top executive of a giant telecom firm arrested last Saturday on a U.S. warrant. The charges against Meng Wanzhou are unclear. But Canada's Globe and Mail newspaper says she is suspected of trying to evade U.S. sanctions against Iran — something U.S. officials have been suspecting about her company, Huawei, for the last two years. Police arrested Meng at the Vancouver airport. She faces possible extradition to the United States after a bail hearing on Friday. A Chinese statement said Meng did not break any U.S. or Canadian laws and that Beijing ex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Trump praises death penalty for Chinese fentanyl 'distributors and pushers' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/donald-trump-opioids-fentanyl-death-penalty/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFLA2A1Hu03GfCJNnmd5PLcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:28:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/donald-trump-opioids-fentanyl-death-penalty/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump praises death penalty for Chinese fentanyl 'distributors and pushers'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump on Wednesday praised the potential for capital punishment in China against "distributors and pushers" of fentanyl -- an opioid 50 to 100 times more powerful than morphine. "One of the very exciting things to come out of my meeting with President Xi of China is his promise to me to criminalize the sale of deadly Fentanyl coming into the United States. It will now be considered a 'controlled substance.' This could be a game changer on what is [...] considered to be the worst and most dangerous, addictive and deadly substance of them all," Trump tweeted. "Last year over ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Huawei CFO Arrested in Canada, Faces Extradition to US - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/huawei-cfo-arrested-in-canada-faces-extradition-to-us/4688934.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKm8hWnXJeiaM_6mKD9LJEIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 01:56:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/huawei-cfo-arrested-in-canada-faces-extradition-to-us/4688934.html" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei CFO Arrested in Canada, Faces Extradition to US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canada has arrested Huawei’s global chief financial officer in Vancouver, where she is facing extradition to the United States, Canada’s Department of Justice said Wednesday. The arrest is related to violations of U.S. sanctions, a person familiar with the matter said. Reuters was unable to determine the precise nature of the violations. Meng Wanzhou, who is one of the vice chairs on the Chinese technology company’s board and the daughter of company founder Ren Zhengfei, was arrested Dec. 1 and a court hearing has been set for Friday, a Canadian Justice Department spokesman said. Huawei con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>China confident on U.S. trade pact, Trump cites Xi's 'strong signals' - Reuters</title><link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-deal/china-says-confident-it-can-implement-trade-deal-with-u-s-idUKKBN1O401H</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKweXIOXpNlMmYSxgnQLLowqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:36:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-deal/china-says-confident-it-can-implement-trade-deal-with-u-s-idUKKBN1O401H" target="_blank"&gt;China confident on U.S. trade pact, Trump cites Xi's 'strong signals'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China expressed confidence on Wednesday that it can reach a trade deal with the United States, a sentiment echoed by U.S. President Donald Trump a day after he warned of more tariffs if the two sides could not resolve their differences. The remarks, by the Chinese Commerce Ministry, follow a period of relative quiet from Beijing after Trump and Chinese leader Xi Jinping reached a temporary truce in their trade war at a meeting over dinner in Argentina on Saturday. In a brief statement, the ministry said China would try to work quickly to implement specific items already agreed upon, as both...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://uk.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Arrest triggers fresh doubts about Trump's ability to deliver on China deal - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/trump-huawei-china-trade/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEORNMRZOtldMNWx23SvdnL4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:27:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/trump-huawei-china-trade/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Arrest triggers fresh doubts about Trump's ability to deliver on China deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The arrest of a top Chinese technology executive should have been a triumphant moment for the Trump administration. Instead, the detention of Chinese tech giant Huawei's chief financial officer, Meng Wanzhou, in Vancouver, British Columbia, triggered a market meltdown Thursday amid uncertainty about whether President Donald Trump can strike a lasting trade deal with Beijing. The volatility put a spotlight on doubts about Trump's ability to deliver on his promises with China -- and exposed a clash between his policy goals in China and his efforts to crack down on technology companies and oth...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>China promises action on US trade deal but gives no details - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/328d929b6c7e4c20af6519179a07233f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELii_Qp5UlvmQkeDdp7go2kqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:55:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/328d929b6c7e4c20af6519179a07233f" target="_blank"&gt;China promises action on US trade deal but gives no details&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China issued an upbeat but vague promise Wednesday to carry out a tariff cease-fire with Washington but gave no details that might dispel confusion about what Presidents Xi Jinping and Donald Trump agreed to in Argentina. China has yet to confirm Trump's claim that Beijing committed to cut auto tariffs and buy more American farm exports. That, coupled with conflicting statements by Trump and U.S. officials, helped trigger a tumble in U.S. stock prices Tuesday amid doubt about the chances for a lasting settlement of a battle over technology that threatens to chill global econo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Market rally reaches Wall Street after US-China trade war truce - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4647f286-f6b8-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIohKqXfHTt2ukgVKRUvR1IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 21:49:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4647f286-f6b8-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Market rally reaches Wall Street after US-China trade war truce&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A global stock rally reached Wall Street on Monday, as investors breathed a sigh of relief that Washington and Beijing had refrained from escalating their trade war at the G20 talks. The market rise was particularly pronounced in technology and automotive stocks, on hopes for relief from current and threatened tariffs, while the wider market has been fretting for months that US-China brinkmanship would smother already faltering global growth. The S&amp;P 500 closed up 1.1 per cent and the Nasdaq Composite up 1.5 per cent, a little off the day’s highs. The rally came after gains across European ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>US-China trade war: Here’s what the Trump-Xi talks mean and how we got here - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/us-china-trade-war-explainer-trump-xi-jinping-soybeans-cars-tariffs-a8665596.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcUiux2ddgLAghfhoVDTkMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/us-china-trade-war-explainer-trump-xi-jinping-soybeans-cars-tariffs-a8665596.html" target="_blank"&gt;US-China trade war: Here’s what the Trump-Xi talks mean and how we got here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has suggested he has no fear of imposing more tariffs on China at the end of a 90-day ceasefire in their ongoing trade war that has disrupted markets and kept investors up at night over the past year. With just a month until yet another planned tariff increase, Donald Trump and his Chinese counterpart Xi Jinping agreed over dinner in Argentina at the annual G20 summit last week to a delay on any tax increases in hopes a lasting deal could be negotiated in that time. Mr Trump said via Twitter on Tuesday that negotiations had started, but if no "real deal" with Beijing could be f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Trump says if no China trade deal possible, 'I am a Tariff Man' - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-idUSKBN1O31U0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMX15XC7cLvsQXAbSv_RN4EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:30:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-idUSKBN1O31U0" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says if no China trade deal possible, 'I am a Tariff Man'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump on Tuesday held out the possibility of an extension of the 90-day trade truce with China but warned he would revert to tariffs if the two sides could not resolve their differences. Trump said his team of trade advisers led by China trade hawk U.S. Trade Representative Robert Lighthizer would determine whether a "REAL deal" with Beijing was possible. "If it is, we will get it done," Trump wrote in a Twitter post. "But if not remember, I am a Tariff Man." The threat of an escalating trade war between the world's two largest economies has loomed large over financial...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Huawei exec's arrest opens a new front in the US-China trade war - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/business/huawei-us-china-trade-war/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAgrHnPo76P8dcYAmSZ3e4wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:28:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/business/huawei-us-china-trade-war/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei exec's arrest opens a new front in the US-China trade war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The conflict between the United States and China over trade and technology is expanding. The arrest of a top executive at Chinese tech giant Huawei at the request of the US government has angered Beijing, alarmed investors and raised new doubts about the fragile truce that the leaders of the world's top two economies reached just days ago. "You have to see this as a significant escalation in the trade war," said Christopher Balding, a China expert at the Fulbright University Vietnam in Ho Chi Minh City. Viewed by US intelligence agencies as a national security threat, Huawei is one of China...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump calls trade truce with China a big step forward - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-trump/trump-calls-trade-truce-with-china-a-big-step-forward-idUSKBN1O21DO</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMcnkxPVHIeHtXA4BGFji2wqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:10:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-trump/trump-calls-trade-truce-with-china-a-big-step-forward-idUSKBN1O21DO" target="_blank"&gt;Trump calls trade truce with China a big step forward&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday said U.S.-China relations had taken a big step forward over the weekend after he and Chinese President Xi Jinping agreed to hold off on new tariffs, and urged Beijing to finalize a trade deal with Washington. "My meeting in Argentina with President Xi of China was an extraordinary one. Relations with China have taken a BIG leap forward! Very good things will happen. We are dealing from great strength, but China likewise has much to gain if and when a deal is completed. Level the field!" Trump tweeted. (Reporting by Susan Heavey and Lisa Lambert; Editing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Four big differences that could endanger Trump and Xi's trade deal - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/politics/china-us-trump-xi-deal-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEMhl1nZGlE8Ycbx1EWYIOsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 02:34:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/politics/china-us-trump-xi-deal-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Four big differences that could endanger Trump and Xi's trade deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stock markets across the world rose Monday after the United States and China agreed to a temporary truce in their trade war, negotiated over dinner in Argentina on Saturday. But stark differences in the language used by Washington and Beijing in announcing the deal could spell trouble as both countries begin negotiations aimed at striking a permanent end to trade tensions. US President Donald Trump and Chinese leader Xi Jinping met for more than two hours on the sidelines of the G20 meeting after months of tough talk on trade and tariffs on hundreds of billions of dollars of goods. Followin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Optimism in China after US trade thaw but hard work just starting - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/optimism-china-trade-thaw-hard-work-starting-181206061705235.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDcYTiOSiNp6vxGAwgJ33AqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:21:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/optimism-china-trade-thaw-hard-work-starting-181206061705235.html" target="_blank"&gt;Optimism in China after US trade thaw but hard work just starting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beijing, China - A sense of relief spread across China as President Xi Jinping and his United States counterpart, Donald Trump, agreed over the weekend to a 90-day halt to new tariffs as the world's two leading economies engage in new negotiations aimed at reaching a broader deal. The smiles and friendly handshakes exchanged between the two leaders on the sidelines of a Group of 20 meeting in Argentina contrasted sharply with the testy exchanges and thinly-veiled animosity that had for months defined the US-China relations amid a bitter tit-for-tat trade dispute. The news of the ceasefire, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>China vulnerable in war with US over computer chips - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4a8553a6-f3b2-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEtaFAHUUxqB8rJQRXJjg84qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 22:00:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4a8553a6-f3b2-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;China vulnerable in war with US over computer chips&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xi Jinping, the Chinese president, visited a memory chip plant in the city of Wuhan earlier this year. In a white lab coat, he made an unexpectedly sentimental remark, comparing a computer chip to a human heart: “No matter how big a person is, he or she can never be strong without a sound and strong heart”. China’s ambitions to be a leader in next-generation technology, such as artificial intelligence, rest on whether or not it can design and manufacture cutting-edge chips, and Mr Xi has pledged $150bn to build up the sector. But China’s plan has alarmed the US, and chips, or semiconductors...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Hong Kong: an experiment under strain - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/43a34a48-f16e-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQVzG_qxP8VIiJeaa4FvlkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 04:59:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/43a34a48-f16e-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;Hong Kong: an experiment under strain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Chinese agents abducted a bookseller critical of Beijing and a politically connected tycoon from semi-autonomous Hong Kong, many foreign investors said privately that they were thorns in Beijing’s side who would inevitably have trouble with the authorities. As the Hong Kong government ratcheted up the pressure on the city’s democracy movement, prosecuting activists, blocking opposition politicians from running in elections and banning a political party, investors said that local politics did not impact business. Corporate executives have looked the other way as Beijing has emphasised i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Trump says China will cut tariffs on American cars - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/business/trump-china-auto-tariffs/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ8x72NWoJr2ukD3_lPd_voqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 20:56:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/business/trump-china-auto-tariffs/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says China will cut tariffs on American cars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US President Donald Trump says China has agreed to cut tariffs on cars it imports from the United States. Trump made the announcement in a tweet late Sunday in the United States, saying Beijing will "reduce and remove" the tariffs, which currently stand at 40%. He didn't specify when the change would happen or what the new tariff level would be. White House adviser Larry Kudlow, director of the National Economic Council, said Monday that no agreement had been reached on what the new tariff would be, but he expected levies to plummet. "We don't yet have specific agreement on that," Kudlow to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US Lawmakers Seek Details of Trump's Trade Breakthrough With China - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-lawmakers-seek-details-of-trump-s-trade-breakthrough-with-china/4686462.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENxXFMV4H2Ktv6mrpu2iRNMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:54:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-lawmakers-seek-details-of-trump-s-trade-breakthrough-with-china/4686462.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Lawmakers Seek Details of Trump's Trade Breakthrough With China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conflicting White House messaging about a reported breakthrough on U.S.-Chinese trade disputes, coupled with relative silence from Beijing, left many American lawmakers unsure where, precisely, trade matters stand between the two economic giants. For days, President Donald Trump has hailed agreements he says he reached with his Chinese counterpart, Xi Jinping, at the G-20 summit in Argentina, from a 90-day deferment of additional tariffs on each other's exports to a Chinese commitment to purchase U.S. agricultural products to a reduction of China's duties on American automobiles. "I think i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Opinion: The true story about China's economy isn't as rosy as we think - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-03/china-xi-jinping-donald-trump-chinese-military-economic-power/10568398</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAsfhdeWa9drzW49zxff3FwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 19:03:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-03/china-xi-jinping-donald-trump-chinese-military-economic-power/10568398" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: The true story about China's economy isn't as rosy as we think&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Kori Schake China's rise has been spectacular — hundreds of millions of people lifted out of poverty by their hard work. Participation in the global order has provided the capital investment, market access, and technology that have fuelled China's prosperity. But the country has been rising for more than 40 years, unaccompanied by effective public pressure for reform. It opted in to the liberal order without liberalising. Despite President Jinping Xi's expansive statements about preserving the liberal order, China undercuts it politically, economically, and militarily. The irony is that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>US-China trade truce gives global stocks and oil a big lift - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/f9fa8956cc394d24935ac65e607de024</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENkDuN-COGlLZvfesOwNPAUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:38:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/f9fa8956cc394d24935ac65e607de024" target="_blank"&gt;US-China trade truce gives global stocks and oil a big lift&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON (AP) — Shares around the world and oil prices surged Monday after the U.S. and China struck a 90-day truce in a trade dispute that has rattled investors for months. KEEPING SCORE: In Europe, Germany's DAX climbed 2.4 percent to 11,511 and France's CAC 40 was up 1.1 percent at 5,057. Britain's FTSE 100 advanced 1.8 percent to 7,104. Wall Street was poised for a buoyant day too, with Dow futures and the broader S&amp;P 500 futures up 1.5 percent. G-20 SUMMIT: President Donald Trump and his Chinese counterpart Xi Jinping dined together at the G-20 summit over the weekend and called a cease-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Huawei's chief financial officer arrested in Canada, facing extradition to US - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-06/huawei-cfo-arrested-in-canada-for-violating-us-sanctions-on-iran/10588464</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJX29jdFGDF71o6DTauPa-IqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 23:25:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-06/huawei-cfo-arrested-in-canada-for-violating-us-sanctions-on-iran/10588464" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei's chief financial officer arrested in Canada, facing extradition to US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China is demanding the immediate release of Huawei's global chief financial officer, who was arrested in Canada and is facing extradition to the United States amid reports she violated US sanctions against Iran. Canada has arrested Huawei's global chief financial officer in Vancouver, where she is facing extradition to the United States on suspicion she violated US sanctions against Iran, Canadian officials and reports say. Key points: - Canadian and US officials refuse to provide specifics of case - China demands Meng Wanzhou's immediate release - Huawei says it's unaware of any wrongdoing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Fast Europe Open: Turkey inflation, European manufacturing PMIs - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ae060e30-f6bd-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDSpgkk2SuYZ_fqbVlGD2gcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 05:53:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ae060e30-f6bd-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Fast Europe Open: Turkey inflation, European manufacturing PMIs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump, the US president, and Xi Jinping, China’s president, are facing hurdles in building on the fragile truce they reached in their trade war, after the two countries left many thorny issues unresolved and offered different interpretations of the agreement. In a much-anticipated working dinner in Buenos Aires following the G20 summit, Mr Trump and Mr Xi agreed on Saturday to a temporary ceasefire, in which the US president suspended his decision to impose higher tariffs on Chinese imports next year. But the bare-bones agreement will trigger a new round of talks over the coming mon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Washington may bluster but cannot stifle the Chinese economy - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d47b2e40-f6ec-11e8-a154-2b65ddf314e9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELazGuGHE7xVPj2xWSl6QegqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:38:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d47b2e40-f6ec-11e8-a154-2b65ddf314e9" target="_blank"&gt;Washington may bluster but cannot stifle the Chinese economy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Presidents Xi Jinping and Donald Trump reached an agreement at the G20 meeting in Argentina at the weekend on a framework for trade dialogue that will delay the previously announced imposition of new American tariffs on January 1. While surely better than the alternative, this step does not address any of the fundamental tensions in the economic relationship between US and China. Few observers doubt that China needs to make significant changes in areas such as intellectual property, rights of foreign investors and subsidies to state-owned companies if it is to meet international norms. Anti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>US-China trade war: truce shows who holds the upper hand - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2635fa64-f6d7-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELNu5FK9JpH5MkISZR2HG_EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 09:36:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2635fa64-f6d7-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;US-China trade war: truce shows who holds the upper hand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A truce has been struck in the US-China trade war but the terms of that ceasefire make clear who holds the upper hand when hostilities inevitably resume. In exchange for the US not imposing higher tariffs on about half of Chinese exports from January 1, Beijing has agreed to discuss a long list of concessions that would, if fully implemented, fundamentally alter the very nature of the Chinese system. According to a White House summary of the dinner meeting between Donald Trump and Xi Jinping at the G20 summit in Buenos Aires, China has agreed in the short term to buy a “very substantial amo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>U.S., China agree on trade war ceasefire after Trump, Xi summit - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-g20-argentina/u-s-china-agree-trade-war-ceasefire-after-trump-xi-summit-idUSKCN1O031C</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKl0PWH8vKKoPnqRG7oTrDsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 18:23:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-g20-argentina/u-s-china-agree-trade-war-ceasefire-after-trump-xi-summit-idUSKCN1O031C" target="_blank"&gt;U.S., China agree on trade war ceasefire after Trump, Xi summit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China and the United States agreed to a ceasefire in their bitter trade war on Saturday after high-stakes talks in Argentina between U.S. President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping, including no escalated tariffs on Jan. 1. Trump will leave tariffs on $200 billion worth of Chinese imports at 10 percent at the beginning of the new year, agreeing to not raise them to 25 percent "at this time", the White House said in a statement. "China will agree to purchase a not yet agreed upon, but very substantial, amount of agricultural, energy, industrial, and other product from the United...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The US and China are in a tech war, not a trade war - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ddbe9522-f878-11e8-a154-2b65ddf314e9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJzFUsNELcbQuURHTVCcTesqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:19:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ddbe9522-f878-11e8-a154-2b65ddf314e9" target="_blank"&gt;The US and China are in a tech war, not a trade war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Confucius, in the Analects, argued that if names are not correct and “language is not in accord with the truth of things, affairs cannot be carried out successfully”. The US-China trade dispute is a case in point. Two misnomers must be corrected if we are to understand what the future is likely to bring. First, this is not a trade war. The fight over trade is merely a skirmish in a larger technology war, which itself is a component of a long struggle between a global hegemon — the US — seeking to maintain its dominance, and an ascending challenger — China — that feels it has a moral right t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Asia Stocks Rally After US-China Truce on Tariffs - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-china-trade-truce/4684224.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE18DOkuF7XUvDT-KNzhZo4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 08:42:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-china-trade-truce/4684224.html" target="_blank"&gt;Asia Stocks Rally After US-China Truce on Tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asia stocks rallied Monday on the news that the United States and China, the world’s two largest economies, would not impose any new tariffs during a 90-day grace period, during which the two sides are to negotiate a detailed agreement. In early trading Monday China’s main market index (the Shanghai Composite) jumped 2.7 percent and the Hang Seng in Hong Kong added 2.8 percent. Japan's Nikkei 225 index climbed 1.4 percent. The U.S. pre market indexes - Dow and S&amp;P futures contracts - were 1.9 percent and 1.8 percent higher respectively, indicating a strong start on Wall Street once the New ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Trump 'likes' North Korean leader and will 'fulfil Chairman Kim's wishes' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/02/trump-likes-north-korea-fulfil-chairman-kims-wishes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBGccgfdRbJpbRX_4bqP0uoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 20:25:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/02/trump-likes-north-korea-fulfil-chairman-kims-wishes" target="_blank"&gt;Trump 'likes' North Korean leader and will 'fulfil Chairman Kim's wishes'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump wants Kim Jong-un to know he likes him and will fulfil his wishes, South Korean president Moon Jae-in said on Sunday, a day after meeting the US president at the G20 summit in Argentina. Related: Donald Trump and Xi Jinping declare trade truce at G20 Moon, who is hoping to host Kim on the first ever trip to Seoul by a North Korean leader, as agreed earlier this year, said Trump had asked him to pass on a message. “The message is that President Trump has very favourable views toward Chairman Kim and he likes him,” Moon told reporters on a flight to New Zealand, where he started ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Trade truce: Will China lower tariffs on US cars? - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4068ca08-f784-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHVUMJIlAFu2uBXnmBKrHvcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 07:47:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4068ca08-f784-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Trade truce: Will China lower tariffs on US cars?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After announcing a 90-day deadline for a new round of trade talks with China, Donald Trump tweeted that Beijing would “reduce and remove” tariffs on US-made cars and “immediately” resume large-scale purchases of US agricultural products. The Chinese government, however, has not acknowledged the three-month talks deadline, after which the US president has said he would impose tariff hikes originally scheduled for January 1. Nor has Beijing confirmed any moves related to auto tariffs or agricultural purchases. Is Mr Trump lying? Probably not. The Chinese government selectively reports informa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>White House intensifies confusion and fear on US-China deal - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/8123f436d5904310bb76b4c7cd34fb30</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEnUtMCCTa4XZZ03JAR2eIAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:05:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/8123f436d5904310bb76b4c7cd34fb30" target="_blank"&gt;White House intensifies confusion and fear on US-China deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration raised doubts Tuesday about the substance of a U.S.-China trade cease-fire, contributing to a broad stock market plunge and intensifying fears of a global economic slowdown. Investors had initially welcomed the truce that the administration said was reached over the weekend in Buenos Aires between Presidents Donald Trump and Xi Jingping — and sent stocks up Monday. But on Tuesday, after a series of confusing and conflicting words from Trump and some senior officials, stocks tumbled, with the Dow Jones shedding about 800 points, or 3.1%. White House...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Will Cosmetic Changes To China Trade War Be Enough? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kenrapoza/2018/12/05/will-cosmetic-changes-to-china-trade-war-be-enough/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAIn3teFADnDanhyer9ssXIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kenrapoza/2018/12/05/will-cosmetic-changes-to-china-trade-war-be-enough/" target="_blank"&gt;Will Cosmetic Changes To China Trade War Be Enough?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shanghai’s stock market lifted after the first 48 hours of a ceasefire in the China-U.S. trade war. Photographer: Qilai Shen/Bloomberg The G20 is behind us. The trade truce is upon us. Analysts have had a change to pine over all of this, what little is actually known regarding the $1.2. trillion in trade items Treasury said China agreed on, and the initial reaction is this: it’s good, but cosmetically good. Let’s see what it all looks like in the morning. The metaphorical morning comes sometime in early-March, when a 90-day cease-fire in the Trump-led trade war expires. “The White House has...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fifty years on, China ramps up 'ping-pong diplomacy' in South Pacific - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-pacific-diplomacy/fifty-years-on-china-ramps-up-ping-pong-diplomacy-in-south-pacific-idUSKBN1O22PU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECE2nd9NyRGjXA85efoiuAAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:54:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-pacific-diplomacy/fifty-years-on-china-ramps-up-ping-pong-diplomacy-in-south-pacific-idUSKBN1O22PU" target="_blank"&gt;Fifty years on, China ramps up 'ping-pong diplomacy' in South Pacific&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inside a Chinese-funded facility perched on a steep hill overlooking Port Moresby's sparkling harbor, Papua New Guinea's best table tennis players are honing techniques picked up months earlier on a sponsored trip to Shanghai. China's backing is helping the sport, also known as ping-pong, establish an unlikely foothold in the Pacific nation better known for its love-affair with rugby league. Although the number of Papua New Guinea (PNG) enthusiasts is small, table tennis' prestige is on the rise. Its governing organization believes its players could soon start qualifying for the Olympics, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China-US Tariff Truce is Opportunity with Tight Time Frame - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/china-us-tariff-truce-is-opportunity-with-tight-time-frame/4684282.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIi-f9wXDvbMowidveAZ81UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 11:52:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/china-us-tariff-truce-is-opportunity-with-tight-time-frame/4684282.html" target="_blank"&gt;China-US Tariff Truce is Opportunity with Tight Time Frame&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China and the United States have agreed to put tariffs on hold and give negotiations a chance. But the short 90-day period the two have to finish negotiations, which includes major holidays both in Washington and Beijing, will require quick steps, analysts say. China’s pledges to purchase what the White House calls “substantial” amounts of agricultural, energy, industrial and other products are relatively straightforward. What will be more difficult are the other items that Washington said the two agreed on. Those include the pledge to immediately begin negotiations on structural changes su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>