<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>New Jersey - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFZtYW1ZU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:44:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Trump's history of hiring undocumented workers - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/john-avlon-reality-check-victorina-morales-bedminster-trump-employee-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDbq7YfF3Ol8uWHMcPZEy-cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:13:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/john-avlon-reality-check-victorina-morales-bedminster-trump-employee-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's history of hiring undocumented workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While President Donald Trump has pushed hardline immigration policies and vilified undocumented immigrants, his private club in New Jersey has employed people who managers allegedly knew were in the country illegally, The New York Times reported Thursday. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New York Times: Trump's Bedminster club hired undocumented immigrants, two workers claim - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/trump-bedminster-club-undocumented-workers/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPIGiaASmahufabReEnAHN4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:53:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/trump-bedminster-club-undocumented-workers/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;New York Times: Trump's Bedminster club hired undocumented immigrants, two workers claim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While President Donald Trump has pushed hardline immigration policies and vilified undocumented immigrants, his private club in New Jersey has employed people who managers allegedly knew were in the country illegally, The New York Times reported Thursday. The Times found two women who say they entered the United States unlawfully but were employed at the Trump National Golf Club in Bedminster, New Jersey. Victorina Morales, a native of Guatemala, told the newspaper she had crossed into the US illegally in 1999 and was hired at the club in 2013 as a housekeeper using phony documentation. Ano...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Teacher sacked by school for telling six-year-old children Father Christmas is not real - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/teacher-santa-not-real-father-christmas-new-jersey-cedar-hill-school-montville-a8668021.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH5zHRxmc1pM50ENzNc2KUMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/teacher-santa-not-real-father-christmas-new-jersey-cedar-hill-school-montville-a8668021.html" target="_blank"&gt;Teacher sacked by school for telling six-year-old children Father Christmas is not real&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A substitute teacher has been reportedly been sacked from a New Jersey school after telling a class of young children Father Christmas does not exist. Parents said first grade children at Cedar Hill Elementary School in Montville, had to be consoled after the incident, which was sparked when one pupil asserted Santa Claus was real. The child’s statement is thought to have prompted an outburst from the teacher in question, who then reportedly went on to debunk several other myths including the Tooth Fairy and the Easter Bunny. Myra Sansone-Aboyoun, a mother of one child in the class, said sh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Trump golf club employed illegal immigrants: report - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-golf-club-employed-illegal-immigrants-report-2018-12-06</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChqOqLCoyu_qXukLMV3phEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-golf-club-employed-illegal-immigrants-report-2018-12-06" target="_blank"&gt;Trump golf club employed illegal immigrants: report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Victor Reklaitis Undocumented housekeeper says she has worked for Bedminster club for more than 5 years President Donald Trump speaks in August at a dinner at Trump National Golf Club in Bedminster, N.J. Reuters The Trump National Golf Club has employed a housekeeper who is an illegal immigrant as well as other undocumented workers, according to a New York Times report published Thursday. The undocumented housekeeper, Guatemala native Victorina Morales, 45, said she has worked at the Bedminster, N.J., club for more than five years, cleaning President Donald Trump’s toilet,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Miss America terminates agreements with NJ, NY and FL - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/a60f36cd4af648028b598f48c78f75b9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGA-hAvTtkZVoiSo-jIrKIEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:58:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/a60f36cd4af648028b598f48c78f75b9" target="_blank"&gt;Miss America terminates agreements with NJ, NY and FL&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. (AP) — There they go. Miss America state groups in three more states have had their licenses revoked by the Miss America Organization following a bitter, high-stakes clash between state pageants and the national leadership headed by former Fox News host Gretchen Carlson. The Miss America Organization sent termination letters Friday to New Jersey, New York and Florida. The Associated Press obtained two of the letters, and confirmed with leaders of the third state that it, too, had been revoked. So far, the parent organization has sent termination letters to seven states, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Teacher who spoiled Santa will not return to school - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/ea3139e7c89543089f0077bb54377656</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELSJougSukJ8gh0NoYTjXfgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwwKudAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:25:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/ea3139e7c89543089f0077bb54377656" target="_blank"&gt;Teacher who spoiled Santa will not return to school&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MONTVILLE, N.J. (AP) — School officials say a substitute teacher who told first-grade students in New Jersey that Santa Claus isn't real will not be returning to the school. NJ.com reports Montville Schools Superintendent Rene Rovtar confirmed Tuesday the teacher will no longer work in the district after the incident Thursday at Cedar Hill School. Rovtar declined further comment, saying the issue is a personnel matter. Officials say the teacher debunked other holiday characters, including the Easter Bunny, the Tooth Fairy and Elf on a Shelf. Rovtar previously said she was disheartened by th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Senator Rips Mnuchin for Backpedaling on Manafort-Linked Russia Sanctions - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/senator-rips-mnuchin-for-backpedaling-on-manafort-linked-russia-sanctions</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDNSiMa79kKPJizvrfDjS6AqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/senator-rips-mnuchin-for-backpedaling-on-manafort-linked-russia-sanctions" target="_blank"&gt;Senator Rips Mnuchin for Backpedaling on Manafort-Linked Russia Sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alex Wong/Getty The top Democrat on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee is blasting Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin for entertaining the idea of lifting sanctions on a Russian aluminum company with ties to former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort. In a letter sent Wednesday, Sen. Bob Menendez (D-NJ) urged Mnuchin to maintain the sanctions that were slapped on Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska in April, arguing that they are a necessary aspect of U.S. efforts to punish Russian President Vladimir Putin and his inner circle for Moscow’s interference in the 2016 election. “I welcomed thes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>High school adds a free laudromat for students bullied over wearing dirty clothes. - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/08/20/iyw-high-school-laundromat-trnd.wcbs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAC7edIwmAzDqdhnRk98SecqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:27:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/08/20/iyw-high-school-laundromat-trnd.wcbs" target="_blank"&gt;High school adds a free laudromat for students bullied over wearing dirty clothes.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some students in Newark, New Jersey, would often skip school rather than endure bullying for wearing dirty clothes. Their principal was determined to change that. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Pathway Through Yellow - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/285156039/pathway-through-yellow-by-joe-matzerath</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSwohGVfLziFYgnfy2u14oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:33:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/285156039/pathway-through-yellow-by-joe-matzerath" target="_blank"&gt;Pathway Through Yellow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite places that we make sure to get to every fall. At Whittemore Community, Cultural and Conservation Center in Tewksbury, NJ.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>A family massacre disguised as a massive fire in New Jersey - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/us/new-jersey-mansion-fire-wrap/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHZaTrCfTBP-OIwn8quuUQIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 16:42:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/us/new-jersey-mansion-fire-wrap/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;A family massacre disguised as a massive fire in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was more than a brotherly bond between Paul and Keith Caneiro. They shared a business, vacationed together and settled about 11 miles from each other in the suburbs of New Jersey. But two days before Thanksgiving, a horrific chain of events would forever tear them apart. Even more horrific is the identity of the alleged perpetrator of those events. Paul Caneiro, 51, is accused of killing his younger brother, his sister-in-law and their children in their modern Colts Neck Township mansion in the early morning darkness on November 20 and then setting their home on fire -- an attempt, au...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Man accused of murdering family and torching mansion intends to plead not guilty - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/us/new-jersey-mansion-fire-paul-caneiro-court/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKl4W-ZaBVIEEfB_eNMoh_kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 13:53:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/us/new-jersey-mansion-fire-paul-caneiro-court/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Man accused of murdering family and torching mansion intends to plead not guilty&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A New Jersey man accused of setting fire to two homes to cover up the killings of his brother's family intends to plead not guilty to murder charges, his attorneys indicated in court Friday. Paul Caneiro, 51, was charged Thursday with four counts of murder, one count of aggravated arson, one count of illegal possession of a firearm and one count of illegal possession of a knife in the deaths of his younger brother, Keith Caneiro, his sister-in-law and their two children last week. Their deaths were followed by a large fire at their mansion in Colts Neck Township. Caneiro was ordered to rema...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>CDC: Here Is Where The Asian Longhorned Tick Has Spread Since 2017 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/11/30/cdc-here-is-where-the-asian-longhorned-tick-has-spread-since-2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXIgYcDvBDmx0LjJFZVrIkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 02:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/11/30/cdc-here-is-where-the-asian-longhorned-tick-has-spread-since-2017/" target="_blank"&gt;CDC: Here Is Where The Asian Longhorned Tick Has Spread Since 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Haemaphysalis longicornis tick has now appeared in 9 states. (Photo: Getty Images) Tick, tick, tick. It was only a matter of time before this tick would spread from New Jersey to other states. Just 7 months ago, I wrote for Forbes about how the Asian longhorned tick (Haemaphysalis longicornis) had made its first real appearance in America in 2017 in the Garden State. On August 1, 2017, a sheep farmer visited the Hunterdon County Health Office along with some new companions. Not just some, but thousands of Asian longhorned ticks covering her body. That’s when state officials went “oh, sh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Rhode Island governor becomes chair of Democratic group - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/b11486ea25aa4828ae96c628d1f83433</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIA1It1oaLpgUc32Yrjmv4MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 15:42:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/b11486ea25aa4828ae96c628d1f83433" target="_blank"&gt;Rhode Island governor becomes chair of Democratic group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Weeks after an election that boosted its membership, the Democratic Governors Association selected Rhode Island Gov. Gina Raimondo as its new chairwoman on Saturday. She was elected by her peers during the group's annual meeting in New Orleans, taking over for Washington Gov. Jay Inslee. New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy was elected vice-chair, putting him in line to lead the group in 2020, the next presidential election year. In November's midterm elections, Democrats flipped seven seats to their control without losing any governor's offices currently held by the party. Raimon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>As 1 brother thrived, the other struggled before slayings - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/1b6a428261094a8dbae559fb3ce0a5c7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC195QkjHWpQwPT307CCbMMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:07:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/1b6a428261094a8dbae559fb3ce0a5c7" target="_blank"&gt;As 1 brother thrived, the other struggled before slayings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FREEHOLD, N.J. (AP) — A New Jersey businessman was financially sound and had no reason to kill his brother's family, defense lawyers said Friday, but an emerging picture of their lives suggests their bond as business partners could have frayed as one thrived and the other struggled years after a serious car accident. Paul Caneiro, 51, limped into court Friday to plead not guilty to killing Keith Caneiro, 50; Keith's wife, Jennifer; and their two young children two days before they were to host Thanksgiving at their sleek $1.5 million mansion in Colts Neck. He also pleaded not guilty to arso...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>States eye sports betting, wrestle with regulatory details - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/922420cc9c6b44cbb0dee83b7df31ab1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEArjhO8iokXEEDCOQXDV7KkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:51:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/922420cc9c6b44cbb0dee83b7df31ab1" target="_blank"&gt;States eye sports betting, wrestle with regulatory details&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Numerous U.S. states are considering jumping on the legal sports betting bandwagon, even as they struggle with the details of regulating it. How much to tax it, and how to regulate mobile betting on phones are emerging as thorny issues for states. So far, seven states offer legal sports betting: Nevada, New Jersey, Delaware, West Virginia, Mississippi, Pennsylvania and Rhode Island. And although New Mexico has not passed a sports betting law, the Santa Ana Star Casino &amp; Hotel started taking sports bets last month through a tribal gambling compact. At a sports betting confere...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>New Jersey man charged with killing his brother and his entire family, then setting their mansion on fire - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/us/nj-mansion-fire-murder-caneiro/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK3sDrhpwuW_kr7ucP1zxxYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:38:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/us/nj-mansion-fire-murder-caneiro/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey man charged with killing his brother and his entire family, then setting their mansion on fire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A New Jersey man repeatedly shot his brother, shot and stabbed his brother's wife and stabbed their two young children, then set their mansion on fire in a quadruple homicide, Monmouth County Prosecutor Christopher Gramiccioni said Thursday. The suspect, Paul Caneiro, also is accused of setting his own Ocean Township home on fire with his family inside in an attempt todestroy evidence and create an illusion that the entire family was being targeted, the prosecutor said. Paul Caneiro, 51, was charged with four counts of murder, one count of aggravated arson, one count of illegal possession o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Brother charged with family mansion deaths, fire - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/58084b8626414a45bec86fca09a40a2e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHI--Zx-JlFq9DAo67t7XgsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/58084b8626414a45bec86fca09a40a2e" target="_blank"&gt;Brother charged with family mansion deaths, fire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FREEHOLD, N.J. (AP) — A New Jersey technology executive was charged Thursday with killing his brother and the brother's family over a business dispute, and then setting fire to their mansion and his own house in an attempt to cover up the crimes. Paul Caneiro, 51, was charged with four counts of murder, as well as arson and two weapons violations, in the death of his 50-year-old brother, Keith, along with Keith's wife, Jennifer, and their two children, at their Colts Neck estate, about 50 miles south of New York City. They were shot, stabbed or both. "This one is the most brutal case I've s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Paul Caneiro Charged With Murder After Allegedly Burning Down His Brother’s Family Mansion - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/paul-caneiro-who-allegedly-set-fire-to-brothers-new-jersey-mansion-killing-four-faces-murder-charges</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMbaxE0Efxc1-uoWLW7baDYqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMIv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 13:28:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/paul-caneiro-who-allegedly-set-fire-to-brothers-new-jersey-mansion-killing-four-faces-murder-charges" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Caneiro Charged With Murder After Allegedly Burning Down His Brother’s Family Mansion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tom Mihalek / Reuters A New Jersey business owner allegedly set fire to his own house in an “elaborate ruse to cover his tracks” of murdering his brother, his sister-in-law, and their two young children before torching their mansion, authorities announced Thursday. Before allegedly setting fire to his own home in Ocean Township, Paul Caneiro, 52, shot and killed his brother and business partner Kevin Caneiro, 50, outside of his Colts Neck mansion. Then, authorities said, Caneiro allegedly entered the house, stabbed to death his sister-in-law, Jennifer, 45, and their two children, Jesse, 11,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>2018 Surge In Measles In Europe And US Show Importance Of Herd Immunity - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/11/24/2018-surge-in-measles-in-europe-and-us-show-importance-of-herd-immunity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOxuw-plYoYbVSCQRL3B02cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 23:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/11/24/2018-surge-in-measles-in-europe-and-us-show-importance-of-herd-immunity/" target="_blank"&gt;2018 Surge In Measles In Europe And US Show Importance Of Herd Immunity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pictured here is the measles virus, paramyxoviridae from the Morbillivirus family. (Photo by: BSIP/UIG via Getty Images) This is what happens when you tell people to not get the measles vaccine without providing a viable alternative. In just the first 6 months of 2018, the World Health Organization (WHO) European Region had over 41,000 measles cases, which has already made 2018 the worst year for measles in the decade by far. The previous high was 23,927 for all of 2017. During the first 6 months of 2018, at least 37 people in Europe have died from the disease. Expect these number to be hig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Untitled - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/284690901/untitled-by-taylor-regina</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECL3PmKF2_4ZykYxxFzeXcMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:22:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/284690901/untitled-by-taylor-regina" target="_blank"&gt;Untitled&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BAYONNE PORT ENTRANCE... COUNTRY BASQUE... FRANCE....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Facing An Uptick In Gun Violence, A Small City Takes Matters Into Its Own Hands - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/elizabethmacbride/2018/11/30/facing-an-uptick-in-gun-violence-a-small-city-takes-matters-into-its-own-hands/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPP_uZbk-cLPC-x3eaVw704qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 03:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/elizabethmacbride/2018/11/30/facing-an-uptick-in-gun-violence-a-small-city-takes-matters-into-its-own-hands/" target="_blank"&gt;Facing An Uptick In Gun Violence, A Small City Takes Matters Into Its Own Hands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officer J. Antoine, Cindy Pitts and Captain Frank Balles of Pleasantville, N.J. . Early in my career, when I was covering the police beat in Lancaster, Pa., I often spoke to business owners about how helpless they felt in the face of rising crime. In the 1990s, they were watching their businesses downtown dwindle. Drugs were flowing in via the highways from Philadelphia and New York, and it seemed like there was nothing anyone could do to stop the small city’s decline. That’s in part why I was interested when I heard that the community in Pleasantville, N.J. took an usual step this fall: Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Menendez slams Trump on Khashoggi response - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/11/28/bob-menendez-saudi-arabia-trump-khashoggi-response-nr-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFRc2UJEZ9W4nTrXUvYE6cUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:38:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/11/28/bob-menendez-saudi-arabia-trump-khashoggi-response-nr-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Menendez slams Trump on Khashoggi response&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Bob Menendez (D-NJ) says the Trump administration's response to journalist Jamal Khashoggi's murder sends a signal to other world leaders they can get away with anything. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Suspect in New Jersey Family’s Torching Is Brother and Business Partner to Victim - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/paul-canerio-arrested-for-arson-after-four-die-in-separate-blaze-at-new-jersey-mansion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE3OnilwmzNKyonHInRmg_8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 14:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/paul-canerio-arrested-for-arson-after-four-die-in-separate-blaze-at-new-jersey-mansion" target="_blank"&gt;Suspect in New Jersey Family’s Torching Is Brother and Business Partner to Victim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WABC via AP Authorities suspect the brother and business partner of a man who was killed along with his family in fire at a New Jersey mansion was behind their deaths. Paul Caneiro is being investigated for his role in the fire on Tuesday afternoon that police are investigating as a homicide, the Monmouth County Sheriff's Office told The Daily Beast. Found dead at the residence in nearby Colts Neck were Kevin Caneiro, 51, his wife, Jennifer, 45, and their two kids under age 10, neighbors said. Authorities said believe there is a connection between between the two fires, though they did not ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Honeywell to move headquarters to Charlotte, N Carolina - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1b6d8b96-f4b7-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOwbrtkbmB57WfUoVTIMvAEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:57:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1b6d8b96-f4b7-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Honeywell to move headquarters to Charlotte, N Carolina&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US industrial conglomerate Honeywell on Friday said it is moving its headquarters from the Garden State for the Tar Heel state. Honeywell, which is currently headquartered in Morris Plains, New Jersey, said it expects to bring total employment in Charlotte, North Carolina, to 750 by the end of 2024. The company, whose products range from thermostats to jet engines, is also moving the headquarters of its Safety and Productivity Solutions (SPS) business from Fort Mill, South Carolina, to Charlotte. About 150 to 200 New Jersey-based senior management positions and about 100 South Carolina-base...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>N.J. man faces murder charges in mansion fire - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/29/nj-man-faces-murder-charges-in-mansion-f?videoId=486701672</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOjZoDE8iMekXxe-9l-Qt4kqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 20:02:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/29/nj-man-faces-murder-charges-in-mansion-f?videoId=486701672" target="_blank"&gt;N.J. man faces murder charges in mansion fire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Caneiro is charged with four counts of murder for allegedly killing his brother, his brother's wife and their two young children before setting their Colts Neck Township, N.J. home on fire on November 20th, according to Monmouth County Prosecutor Christopher Gramiccioni. Authorities say Caneiro also set his own Ocean Township home on fire in an attempt to destroy evidence. Rough Cut (no reporter narration).&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Authorities Find 44 Dead Dogs in New Jersey Woman’s Squalid Home - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/authorities-find-44-dead-dogs-in-new-jersey-womans-squalid-home</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFWg02FsxJiTYFRijsqC0zgqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 21:23:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/authorities-find-44-dead-dogs-in-new-jersey-womans-squalid-home" target="_blank"&gt;Authorities Find 44 Dead Dogs in New Jersey Woman’s Squalid Home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey State Police, New Jersey police arrested a 65-year-old woman after 44 dead dogs were found in freezers inside her home and over 100 others were found living in squalor, WABC reports. Donna Roberts now faces charges of animal cruelty after she allegedly kept “all the animals in deplorable and inhumane conditions in and around her” in her Shamong Township home. When police arrived at the home with officials from the Burlington County Health Department, the smell of “animal feces and ammonia” was reportedly potent enough to cause “dizziness and nausea” among authorities. , Forty-fou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Family of four killed, mansion set on fire - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2018/11/22/nj-family-killed-arson-mansion-fire-casarez-vpx.hln</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGHL32wLy4pyeIS9PdZylQcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:30:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2018/11/22/nj-family-killed-arson-mansion-fire-casarez-vpx.hln" target="_blank"&gt;Family of four killed, mansion set on fire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors say a family of four found dead at their mansion in Colts Neck, New Jersey, were the victims of homicide and their house was subsequently set on fire. CNN's Jean Casarez reports. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Correction: Mansion Fire-Deaths story - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/64fe78dd1b1748f892b4eded9db6dd16</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSy3BJgwfdWhEy3HACc6eoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:24:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/64fe78dd1b1748f892b4eded9db6dd16" target="_blank"&gt;Correction: Mansion Fire-Deaths story&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;COLTS NECK, N.J. (AP) — In some versions of a story Nov. 21 about the death of a family of four, The Associated Press misspelled the last name of a man charged with setting fire to his own home. He is Paul Caneiro, not Caniero. A corrected version of the story is below: 4 in New Jersey mansion fire killed by 'homicidal violence' Authorities: Four people found dead after mansion fire were killed before blaze By WAYNE PARRY Associated Press COLTS NECK, N.J. (AP) — A family of four whose remains were found at the burned-down ruins of their New Jersey mansion was slain before the home was set a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Storms, Rising Sea Levels Threaten Historic Lighthouses - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/storms-rising-sea-levels-threaten-historic-lighthouses/4670613.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPsaiqphOvlJe1fTy1HZABoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 01:54:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/storms-rising-sea-levels-threaten-historic-lighthouses/4670613.html" target="_blank"&gt;Storms, Rising Sea Levels Threaten Historic Lighthouses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rising seas and erosion are threatening lighthouses around the U.S. and the world. Volunteers and cash-strapped governments are doing what they can, but the level of concern, like the water, is rising. New Jersey’s East Point Lighthouse has been lighting up Delaware Bay for the better part of two centuries. But those same waters that the lighthouse helped illuminate might bring about its demise. With even a moderate-term fix likely to cost $3 million or more, New Jersey officials are considering what to do to save the lighthouse. Nancy Patterson, president of the Maurice River Historical So...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>New Jersey fire: Four dead in shooting and 'suspicious' mansion blaze - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/new-jersey-mansion-fire-colts-neck-nj-shooting-dead-update-latest-a8643836.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKnhrc5b38DLLTQQuRp2_4IqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/new-jersey-mansion-fire-colts-neck-nj-shooting-dead-update-latest-a8643836.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey fire: Four dead in shooting and 'suspicious' mansion blaze&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police are investigating an apparent shooting and "suspicious" fire that ripped through a New Jersey mansion Tuesday afternoon. One person was found dead with a gunshot wound outside of the mansion located in Colts Neck, New Jersey, as numerous other fatalities were reported inside of the building. The Monmouth County Prosecutor’s Office confirmed “multiple fatalities” had occurred in a tweet, but did not immediately release their identities or causes of death. On Tuesday afternoon, police said the fatalities included two children and two adults, and the fire was being treated as arson. - R...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Deplorable And Inhumane': Police Find 44 Dead Dogs In Woman's Freezer - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-dead-dogs-freezer_us_5bed0266e4b09f4670068a34</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGFO46DLqRczv_q6VdqxPB0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 07:33:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-dead-dogs-freezer_us_5bed0266e4b09f4670068a34" target="_blank"&gt;'Deplorable And Inhumane': Police Find 44 Dead Dogs In Woman's Freezer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A New Jersey woman has been charged with animal cruelty after 44 deceased dogs were discovered stored in freezers throughout her home. State police allege Donna Roberts, 65, also kept 130 living dogs in “deplorable and inhumane conditions in and around her home,” according to a statement posted to Facebook. Detectives and officials from the Burlington County Health Department visited Roberts’ home on Tuesday to carry out an inspection. Once there, they “observed evidence of animal cruelty inflicted upon various breeds of dogs on the property.” The odor of animal feces and ammonia permeated ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Major East Coast bridge closed by chemical leak has reopened - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/20410d1678684398821267daa17b9af7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL2CaZzstrtCALdGjAMixwMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:59:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/20410d1678684398821267daa17b9af7" target="_blank"&gt;Major East Coast bridge closed by chemical leak has reopened&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PENNSVILLE, N.J. (AP) — A gas leak that shut down the Delaware Memorial Bridge in both directions Sunday evening, bringing traffic on a major East Coast artery to a standstill on one of the busiest travel days of the year, has reopened. The Delaware Department of Transportation tweeted late Sunday that the bridge was "REOPENED to traffic" and urged travelers to drive safely. The leak stemmed from the Delaware chemical production facility Croda Atlas Point, located near the twin suspension bridges on a major route between Washington and New York City, Holloway Terrace Fire Company Public Inf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>N.J. mansion fire investigated as homicide: officials - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/21/nj-mansion-fire-investigated-as-homicide?videoId=484482489</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMG82w6HMGYjsZ_lkFYBgAsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 23:32:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/21/nj-mansion-fire-investigated-as-homicide?videoId=484482489" target="_blank"&gt;N.J. mansion fire investigated as homicide: officials&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monmouth County Prosecutor Chris Gramiccioni said the mansion fire in Colts Neck, New Jersey on Tuesday was being investigated as a homicide in addition to arson after Keith Caneiro, his wife and two kids were found dead. Rough Cut (no reporter narration).&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Adenovirus Outbreak At New Jersey Medical Center Leaves 11 Children Dead - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/adenovirus-outbreak-medical-center-new-jersey_us_5bf17622e4b0b84243e317e3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6frfLvE4zGdr2beUFXN4UqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 18:31:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/adenovirus-outbreak-medical-center-new-jersey_us_5bf17622e4b0b84243e317e3" target="_blank"&gt;Adenovirus Outbreak At New Jersey Medical Center Leaves 11 Children Dead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An 11th child has died in connection with an adenovirus outbreak at a health care facility in New Jersey that has sickened 23 others, state health officials said on Friday. The child was a resident of the Wanaque Center for Nursing and Rehabilitation in Haskell, roughly 30 miles west of Manhattan, where a new adenovirus case was confirmed on Thursday night, the New Jersey Department of Health announced. All of the children associated with the outbreak at the facility have severely compromised immune systems and other serious medical issues, making them more susceptible to the infection. The...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Finger pointing, frustration in eastern US storm's aftermath - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/eb0260b7d233463396a02be653d764ae</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO0NVTGxXogogCeWnUFe2YIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 23:03:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/eb0260b7d233463396a02be653d764ae" target="_blank"&gt;Finger pointing, frustration in eastern US storm's aftermath&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — Exhausted commuters pointed fingers and demanded answers Friday, a day after a modest snowstorm stranded motorists on slippery roads for hours, paralyzed the public transit network serving New York City and its suburbs and even forced some New Jersey children to stay overnight in their schools. How, they asked, could a few inches of snow in a region used to this sort of weather lead to such chaos? "Clearly we could have done better and we will do better," New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy said. New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio promised a "full review." "We're all unhappy wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>11th child dies in viral outbreak at NJ facility - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/19/11th-child-dies-in-viral-outbreak-at-nj?videoId=483945401</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECg6R_jwvYb9Q69GKbRzBywqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 14:23:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/19/11th-child-dies-in-viral-outbreak-at-nj?videoId=483945401" target="_blank"&gt;11th child dies in viral outbreak at NJ facility&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An 11th child has died in less than four weeks at a New Jersey rehabilitation center, one of 34 young patients with compromised immune systems to have been infected by a viral outbreak. Linda So reports.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Stung by Amazon's rejection, cities look on the bright side - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/6df0bab693c54d9b8ffd82191f5d0cba</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKaE7GJ5rQi1nfWGjBiBDFYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 23:10:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/6df0bab693c54d9b8ffd82191f5d0cba" target="_blank"&gt;Stung by Amazon's rejection, cities look on the bright side&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes losing is winning. Or at least that's what some of the 18 North American cities passed up by Amazon for its new headquarters are telling themselves. After 14 agonizing months of wooing and then waiting for the online retail giant to make up its mind, the finalists learned that instead of Amazon picking one location for its new offices, it would split them between Long Island City in Queens, New York, and Arlington, Virginia, in suburban Washington, sending an estimated 25,000 jobs to each. The places that didn't make the cut are bearing the rejection with a mixture of reflection, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Blue-state Republicans embraced the 2017 tax cuts. It may have cost them. - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/blue-state-republicans-embraced-the-2017-tax-cuts-it-may-have-cost-them-2018-11-16</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED9RfKM3KrWQt_VHMTUSylYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/blue-state-republicans-embraced-the-2017-tax-cuts-it-may-have-cost-them-2018-11-16" target="_blank"&gt;Blue-state Republicans embraced the 2017 tax cuts. It may have cost them.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Andrea Riquier Is it a reversal of the 2010 response to the Obamacare vote? A real estate agent shows a property in Newport Beach, California. Bloomberg News/Landov Last December, as negotiations over the final outline of the Republican-led tax bill advanced, the Wall Street Journal profiled Congresswoman Mimi Walters. The Orange County Republican had voted for the draft GOP tax overhaul, and as a vote on a final version loomed, Walters was scrambling to find a way to mitigate its impacts on her constituents, many of whom depended on the ability to deduct the full amount o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Newcomer Andy Kim beats GOP Rep. MacArthur in New Jersey - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/5066a2bf74e54e6ba62b634e5c5c9de8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC_FnfVyvJRADch8Qb3mU6wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 01:08:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/5066a2bf74e54e6ba62b634e5c5c9de8" target="_blank"&gt;Newcomer Andy Kim beats GOP Rep. MacArthur in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — Democrat Andy Kim, a political newcomer and former national security aide in the Obama administration, defeated Republican Rep. Tom MacArthur in a tight race in which the incumbent's vote to roll back the Affordable Care Act was a hot issue. Kim upset MacArthur in the hotly contested southern New Jersey district, widening the Democrats' edge in the House. He declared victory last week, but MacArthur did not concede at the time as mail-in and provisional ballots continued to be counted. The Associated Press called the race Wednesday. The U.S. House historian's database s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Andy Kim Declared Winner Over GOP Rep. Tom MacArthur In New Jersey - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andy-kim-tom-macarthur-new-jersey-third-district_us_5bec7d8be4b0a2569fd13c90</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELpG5X87XbYwhZyRNm2VFCQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 21:59:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andy-kim-tom-macarthur-new-jersey-third-district_us_5bec7d8be4b0a2569fd13c90" target="_blank"&gt;Andy Kim Declared Winner Over GOP Rep. Tom MacArthur In New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― Andy Kim, a national security adviser to President Barack Obama who returned home to suburban New Jersey to challenge the biggest Donald Trump supporter in the Garden State’s congressional delegation, has won a tight race against GOP Rep. Tom MacArthur and made history in the process. The Associated Press called the race on Wednesday afternoon, more than a week after the polls closed. Kim will become is the first Korean-American Democrat to serve in Congress, which hasn’t had a lawmaker of Korean descent since 1999. (Republican Young Kim is locked in a too-close-to-call race in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Homeless Samaritan tale raised $400K. Police say it's a lie - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/d9ebdfa756054ee68d180072c6fb066d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAOYmDDKdcXz-zPTvDpc51sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 23:49:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/d9ebdfa756054ee68d180072c6fb066d" target="_blank"&gt;Homeless Samaritan tale raised $400K. Police say it's a lie&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOUNT HOLLY, N.J. (AP) — A feel-good tale of a homeless man using his last $20 to help a stranded New Jersey woman buy gas was actually a complete lie, manufactured to get strangers to donate more than $400,000 to help the down-and-out good Samaritan, a prosecutor said Thursday. Burlington County prosecutor Scott Coffina announced criminal charges against the couple who told the story to newspapers and television stations along with the homeless man who conspired with them to tell the story. Coffina said the money, donated to homeless Marine veteran Johnny Bobbitt, will be refunded to peopl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>How Democrats Won In Trump Country - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-democrats-midterms-election_us_5bf2dba7e4b0b84243e4ae2d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1tOLYRexfGCcAjg399Yx0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ3knAY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 19:31:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-democrats-midterms-election_us_5bf2dba7e4b0b84243e4ae2d" target="_blank"&gt;How Democrats Won In Trump Country&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this May 10, 2018 file photo, Kendra Horn speaks during a forum for Oklahoma 5th Congressional District seat Democratic candidates in Edmond, Okla. Horn defeated Republican Rep. Steve Russell. (AP Photo/Sue Ogrocki, File) WASHINGTON ― Democrats didn’t simply win in places they expected to on Nov. 6. They also managed to flip districts Donald Trump won easily in the 2016 presidential election, as well as some districts that have been held by Republicans for decades. The secret to their success was a fairly conventional, but somewhat surprising, campaign strategy during an election year th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Snowstorm slows evening commute in New York City - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/81d03dc52ef94a4391ad941c6faa831e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAfpqCEOddRhjyeFD8BOcmwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 04:21:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/81d03dc52ef94a4391ad941c6faa831e" target="_blank"&gt;Snowstorm slows evening commute in New York City&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The first snowstorm of the season to hit the New York City area brought several inches of snow, slowing Thursday's evening commute to a crawl, after contributing to at least seven deaths as it swept across the country. From St. Louis to the South and into the Northeast, snow, freezing rain, and in some parts, sleet, made driving tricky and closed schools Thursday. In New York City, the wet snowfall and wind gusts Thursday downed numerous tree branches. Police advised people to stay indoors and avoid the roads. Commuters also were advised to avoid the Port Authority Bus Termi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Snowstorm slams Eastern US, killing 8 and knocking out power - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/us/snow-storm-northeast-southeast-wxc/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-x3Lv83P4LplGpheguA5EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 01:14:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/us/snow-storm-northeast-southeast-wxc/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Snowstorm slams Eastern US, killing 8 and knocking out power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A strong wintry storm still was dumping snow Friday in far northern New England after creating traffic havoc that claimed at least eight lives across the country's eastern half and knocked out power for tens of thousands of people. A mix of rain, snow and ice that initially hit the Midwest caused headaches from the South to the Northeast, leaving up to a foot of snow in some parts of the latter and widespread freezing rain and ice accumulations elsewhere. Conditions prompted school closures, hours-long delays for commuters and hundreds of flight cancellations. Track the storm here About 200...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Couple, homeless man accused of setting up GoFundMe campaign 'predicated on a lie' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/15/us/couple-homeless-man-gofundme/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDsFwBvU0VmwGjCkcuGq-h8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 14:41:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/15/us/couple-homeless-man-gofundme/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Couple, homeless man accused of setting up GoFundMe campaign 'predicated on a lie'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A New Jersey couple and a homeless man have been accused of making up a feel-good story that raised more than $400,000 through GoFundMe. The couple, Kate McClure and Mark D'Amico, and the man, Johnny Bobbitt Jr., face charges of second-degree theft by deception and conspiracy to commit theft by deception, Burlington County Prosecutor Scott Coffina said Thursday. The couple had said they met Bobbitt when he gave his last $20 to McClure, who was stranded on Interstate 95 in Philadelphia, so she could put gas in her car, then started the GoFundMe campaign as a way to thank him. "The paying-it-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Science Of Why A Modest Snowstorm Caused Havoc On The East Coast - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/marshallshepherd/2018/11/17/the-science-of-why-a-modest-snowstorm-caused-havoc-on-the-east-coast/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOao9lH4I1Ajo0Ytdo_BRmsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 14:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/marshallshepherd/2018/11/17/the-science-of-why-a-modest-snowstorm-caused-havoc-on-the-east-coast/" target="_blank"&gt;The Science Of Why A Modest Snowstorm Caused Havoc On The East Coast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week was truly one of “fire and ice.” The nation continued to watch the tragedy of the California wildfires. CNN is now reporting a statewide death toll of 74 people and over 1000 people missing from the Camp Fire and Woolsey Fire, respectively. As that disaster continued to play out, a relatively “modest” snowstorm caused significant mayhem in the mid-Atlantic and Northeast on Thursday, and everyone’s finger pointing in the aftermath. New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio and New Jersey Governor Phil Murphy called for full assessments of what went wrong. How could a storm with only 6 or ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Launches Extensive Tax Amnesty Program - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyphillipserb/2018/11/15/new-jersey-launches-extensive-tax-amnesty-program/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHa5ZFU9IyZLtnT28ecb1CQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 15:57:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyphillipserb/2018/11/15/new-jersey-launches-extensive-tax-amnesty-program/" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Launches Extensive Tax Amnesty Program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=1] The holiday season might be a little more bright for some taxpayers: The New Jersey Division of Taxation has announced the launch of their Tax Amnesty program. The program is intended to provide individuals and businesses with the opportunity to pay back taxes or file past returns with no penalties and reduced interest. “We are pleased to offer taxpayers a chance at compliance and a fresh start through the New Jersey Tax Amnesty program,” said John Ficara, Acting Director of the Division of Taxation. “Since Tax Amnesty is offered for a limited time, we’re encouraging taxpayers to tak...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Opinion: These U.S. states are putting their bond investors in a world of hurt - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/these-us-states-are-putting-their-bond-investors-in-a-world-of-hurt-2018-11-14</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ1X5tllD3cY8Pw8jrMDgL8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/these-us-states-are-putting-their-bond-investors-in-a-world-of-hurt-2018-11-14" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: These U.S. states are putting their bond investors in a world of hurt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OUTSIDE THE BOX By Robert Pozen Illinois, New Jersey, Hawaii, and Connecticut are precariously stretched to fund their debt obligations Getty Images Investors in state bonds, beware. Four U.S. states — Illinois, New Jersey, Hawaii, and Connecticut — are sitting on time bombs. Between 35% and 51% of their annual revenues are likely to be needed to meet their total annual payment obligations on existing debt, retirement plans, and retiree healthcare. Yet the general obligation (GO) bonds of New Jersey, Hawaii, and Connecticut have a single A-rating from both Moody’s and S&amp;P Global; the GO bon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Democrats pick up two more House seats as Denham, MacArthur concede - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/politics/jeff-denham-concedes-josh-harder-california-10th-house-race/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFsexlC7DuterMe4kERKD54qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 12:30:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/politics/jeff-denham-concedes-josh-harder-california-10th-house-race/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Democrats pick up two more House seats as Denham, MacArthur concede&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democrats picked up two more House seats on Wednesday as Republican Reps. Jeff Denham of California and Tom MacArthur of New Jersey acknowledged they'd been defeated. The two Democratic victories give Democrats a total of 32 net pickups in the House, bringing the current balance of power come January in Washington to 227 Democrats and 200 Republicans. Eight House races remain undecided. Denham, who represented the 10th District in the state's Central Valley, said in a statement he'd met in person with Democratic challenger Josh Harder. "It has been an absolute honor to serve our community a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Democrat Andy Kim And Rep. Tom MacArthur Neck And Neck In New Jersey’s 3rd District - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andy-kim-tom-macarthur-new-jersey_us_5bcf88b8e4b0d38b587d6e6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIgHcVkG3kvvgo-sTMWZnZ4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 04:51:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andy-kim-tom-macarthur-new-jersey_us_5bcf88b8e4b0d38b587d6e6c" target="_blank"&gt;Democrat Andy Kim And Rep. Tom MacArthur Neck And Neck In New Jersey’s 3rd District&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― Democrat Andy Kim, a former Obama administration official who returned to his home district to challenge New Jersey’s strongest Donald Trump ally on Capitol Hill, was running neck and neck with Rep. Tom MacArthur as of Tuesday evening. With 99 percent of precincts reporting, the gap between Kim and MacArthur was less than half a percentage point. Neither side declared victory. Voters in New Jersey’s 3rd Congressional District, a sprawling, largely white district that spans the state from the Philadelphia suburbs to the Jersey Shore, were nearly evenly divided on Trump in 2016. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>South Jersey Conservative Democrat Fends Off Republican The GOP Thought Was Too Racist - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/seth-grossman-loses-new-jersey_us_5be2467de4b0e8438891109b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDryiUe_aSKNPhvkTcxJWN0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 05:54:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/seth-grossman-loses-new-jersey_us_5be2467de4b0e8438891109b" target="_blank"&gt;South Jersey Conservative Democrat Fends Off Republican The GOP Thought Was Too Racist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― A conservative Democrat in New Jersey’s 2nd Congressional District narrowly defeated a right-wing Republican who called diversity “un-American,” railed against illegal immigrants and was abandoned by national Republicans because of his bigotry. Democrat Jeff Van Drew, a dentist and state senator, declared victory over Republican Seth Grossman on Tuesday evening. Van Drew received 52 percent of the vote compared with Grossman’s 46 percent. Both were running to replace former Rep. Frank LoBiondo, a Republican who decided to retire after 24 years in office. New Jersey’s 2nd Distri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Patterson throws 3 TDs, No. 4 Michigan beats Rutgers 42-7 - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/0d96074a500e4eca91e5f959cefed675</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOwfSM7CxLHw6jixN9Bozh0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwnZidAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 01:32:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/0d96074a500e4eca91e5f959cefed675" target="_blank"&gt;Patterson throws 3 TDs, No. 4 Michigan beats Rutgers 42-7&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PISCATAWAY, N.J. (AP) — Shea Patterson has stamped Michigan a national title contender. Patterson threw for 260 yards and three touchdowns, Karan Higdon ran for a pair of 1-yard scores and the fourth-ranked Wolverines routed Rutgers 42-7 on Saturday for their ninth straight win. Patterson threw darts in swirling winds in front of thousands of fans bundled in Michigan colors. Up ahead, another week with national title hopes in the Big House. "The one thing I think we do a really good job of is not getting distracted by where we are now," Patterson said, "and don't let that distract us from w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Multiple children dead from virus in New Jersey - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/health/2018/10/23/new-jersey-adenovirus-outbreak-children-gupta-nr-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM5gifqpj0AnqWy81E2SE5AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 22:47:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/health/2018/10/23/new-jersey-adenovirus-outbreak-children-gupta-nr-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Multiple children dead from virus in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple children have died as a result of a flu-like adenovirus at the Wanaque Center for Nursing and Rehabilitation in Haskell, New Jersey. CNN's Dr. Sanjay Gupta reports. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Tom Malinowski, Former Obama Human Rights Official, Defeats 5-Term Republican - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/tom-malinowski-wins-new-jersey-house_us_5be20ca1e4b0769d24c63160</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDP05LfuvXjcTNxiFQAE6DkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 04:28:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/tom-malinowski-wins-new-jersey-house_us_5be20ca1e4b0769d24c63160" target="_blank"&gt;Tom Malinowski, Former Obama Human Rights Official, Defeats 5-Term Republican&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tom Malinowski, a long-time human rights activist and former State Department official, defeated Rep. Leonard Lance (R-N.J.) Tuesday night in the contest for New Jersey’s 7th Congressional District, joining other Democrats who managed to win traditionally GOP-held seats in the Northeast. By beating Lance, Malinoswki ended 37 years of Republican control of the district. Lance, a former state lawmaker, had been in office since 2009 and won re-election in 2016 by 11 percentage points. Voters in the district, a suburban-rural mix that hosts one of President Donald Trump’s beloved golf courses i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>How Tom Malinowski unseated 5-term GOP incumbent - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/11/09/intv-amanpour-tom-malinowski.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIzdXBhm5g-ce3PLDW9FrfAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 19:14:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/11/09/intv-amanpour-tom-malinowski.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;How Tom Malinowski unseated 5-term GOP incumbent&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. House Democrat-elect Tom Malinowski discusses his win in New Jersey's 7th District and what the flip in the House might mean going forward. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>FanDuel Partnering with NHL, New Jersey Devils--What It Means - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jppelzman/2018/11/05/fanduel-partnering-with-nhl-new-jersey-devils-what-it-means/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIIsW7GP50e5SM0zbSyGuJ0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 00:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jppelzman/2018/11/05/fanduel-partnering-with-nhl-new-jersey-devils-what-it-means/" target="_blank"&gt;FanDuel Partnering with NHL, New Jersey Devils--What It Means&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daily fantasy and sports betting company FanDuel announced Monday it is partnering with both the NHL and the New Jersey Devils. FanDuel will be the exclusive daily sports fantasy partner of the league, and an official betting partner. FanDuel also is the third sports betting partner to join forces with the Devils, who previously announced arrangements with Caesars and William Hill. Both the Devils and the NHL appear to be following the model of English Premier League soccer teams, in which clubs partner with multiple betting operators at the same time. The NHL previously announced a multi-y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Democratic Sen. Bob Menendez Avoids Upset And Wins Re-election In New Jersey - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bob-menendez-new-jersey-senate_us_5bd7404fe4b0a8f17efab075</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGHi5Gl41vfMP63FxmazrKAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ3knAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 01:32:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bob-menendez-new-jersey-senate_us_5bd7404fe4b0a8f17efab075" target="_blank"&gt;Democratic Sen. Bob Menendez Avoids Upset And Wins Re-election In New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey Democrat Bob Menendez overcame lingering doubts about his integrity and a stronger-than-expected challenge from Republican Bob Hugin to win re-election on Tuesday. New Jersey hasn’t elected a Republican to the Senate in 46 years, but the ethical cloud that hovered over Menendez put his bid for another term in doubt this year. He was indicted in 2015 on charges including bribery and fraud stemming from allegations that he engaged in a quid pro quo relationship with a friend ― advancing the man’s business interests and in return accepting an array of gifts, including luxury trips a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Facing long Senate odds, Democrats must first secure New Jersey - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-new-jersey/facing-long-senate-odds-democrats-must-first-secure-new-jersey-idUSKCN1NA16D</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAo8qml3YwiL5h8llzW0cXwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 18:10:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-new-jersey/facing-long-senate-odds-democrats-must-first-secure-new-jersey-idUSKCN1NA16D" target="_blank"&gt;Facing long Senate odds, Democrats must first secure New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Democrats, Tuesday's New Jersey U.S. Senate election should have been a breeze. Bob Menendez, 64, has held the seat for more than a decade in a state that has not elected a Republican to the U.S. Senate in 46 years. But June's Democratic nominating contest exposed his potential weakness following his federal corruption trial last year: 40 percent voted for a virtually unknown challenger who spent zero dollars in the race. Menendez is locked in a tough and expensive race with a Republican who has hammered Menendez as unethical, former pharmaceutical executive Bob Hugin, also 64. Top Demo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>A New Jersey U.S. House Race Shows How Trump’s Hard-Right Turn Is Leaving GOP Moderates Vulnerable - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-new-jersey-us-house-race-shows-how-trumps-hard-right-turn-is-leaving-gop-moderates-vulnerable</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEwxphEpfF_PNlNSsDDssgYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 15:55:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-new-jersey-us-house-race-shows-how-trumps-hard-right-turn-is-leaving-gop-moderates-vulnerable" target="_blank"&gt;A New Jersey U.S. House Race Shows How Trump’s Hard-Right Turn Is Leaving GOP Moderates Vulnerable&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tom Williams President Donald Trump’s explicitly racialized closing argument in support of Republicans up for election has put even the man behind the infamous Willie Horton campaign ad to blushing shame. But while thousands of troops laying miles of barbed concertina wire along the U.S. southern border may motivate Trump’s base to show up to the polls on Tuesday, the GOP’s full-throated embrace of hard-right nationalist messaging could seal the fate of moderate suburban Republicans. Once-safe red congressional seats, like the one held by New Jersey Rep. Leonard Lance, are now up for grabs ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Sen. Booker on racist attack ads: Bring it - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/11/06/racist-ads-response-cory-booker-cpt-sot-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAeT4u8ErwqLu79e-preXsgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/11/06/racist-ads-response-cory-booker-cpt-sot-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Sen. Booker on racist attack ads: Bring it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Cory Booker (D-NJ) tells those who push racist attack ads to "bring it," claiming those ads "reveal your true colors." ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Law Allows Cory Booker To Run For Both President And Senator In 2020 - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-cory-booker-2020_us_5bdc32e1e4b01ffb1d012be2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELCxNVj1sLP171yUqLPR1F4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 12:29:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-cory-booker-2020_us_5bdc32e1e4b01ffb1d012be2" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Law Allows Cory Booker To Run For Both President And Senator In 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy (D) on Thursday signed a bill that would allow Sen. Cory Booker (D-N.J.), who has expressed interest in a 2020 presidential bid, to run for both senator and president simultaneously. The law affirms that Booker, who is up for re-election in 2020, can appear on the ballot as both a Senate and presidential candidate, if he decides to jump into the presidential race. New Jersey laws don’t explicitly prohibit people from running for multiple offices, only from holding multiple offices. The new law “clarifies” that anyone running for U.S. House or Senate can also appe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Parents Call for Closure of NJ Care Site Where 10 Kids Have Died - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/parents-call-for-closure-of-nj-care-site-where-10-kids-have-died</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHkICSdsVGryblP5EeTmdukqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 15:31:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/parents-call-for-closure-of-nj-care-site-where-10-kids-have-died" target="_blank"&gt;Parents Call for Closure of NJ Care Site Where 10 Kids Have Died&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philippe Huguen/AFP/Getty, The New Jersey rehabilitation facility where 10 children have died of an adenovirus outbreak in recent weeks remains open, despite calls from parents of the deceased to close its doors. NorthJersey.com reports Friday that those parents include Ocroimy Dolcin and Modeline Auguste, who lost their four-year-old daughter, Dorcase, to the adenovirus on Oct. 22. “It is negligence because they don’t take full responsibility for what happened over there,” Dolcin said, noting that they had concerns about negligence at the facility even before their daughter fell ill. “They...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>10th child dies from adenovirus outbreak in New Jersey - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/01/health/adenovirus-outbreak-new-jersey-mother/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIJgFIXdk9LPRmCEHfQYzpsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:37:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/01/health/adenovirus-outbreak-new-jersey-mother/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;10th child dies from adenovirus outbreak in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ten children have died and 18 others have become sick in connection with an adenovirus outbreak at a New Jersey health care facility, the state's Department of Healthannounced Thursday. The patients are children with serious medical issues, many of whom require assistance to breathe and function, at the Wanaque Center for Nursing and Rehabilitation in Haskell, New Jersey. The confirmed cases became ill between September 26 and October 30, according to the health department. The number of illnesses has risen from 18 cases, including six deaths, announced last week by the health department. "...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Andy Kim Is A South Jersey Boy. The GOP Calls Him 'Not One Of Us.' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andy-kim-tom-macarthur-nj-3rd-district_us_5bbcd8c5e4b01470d055d5eb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHil0nRVCHMni_7zqVhFwOQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 09:45:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andy-kim-tom-macarthur-nj-3rd-district_us_5bbcd8c5e4b01470d055d5eb" target="_blank"&gt;Andy Kim Is A South Jersey Boy. The GOP Calls Him 'Not One Of Us.'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOUNT LAUREL, N.J. ― Andy Kim really wants you to know he’s from New Jersey. The man he’s trying to unseat, Rep. Tom MacArthur (R-N.J.), is trying to convince voters otherwise. MacArthur and his allies have attacked Kim, a son of South Korean immigrants and a former national security aide to President Barack Obama, as a D.C. elitist and an outsider. The New Jersey Republican Party described him in campaign mailers as “Real Fishy” ― the text printed in a typeface called Chop Suey ― next to a photo of dead fish on ice. So Kim makes sure to remind voters in the state’s sprawling, largely white...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>10th patient dies at pediatric facility in viral outbreak - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/413bd927be874826b5f8b2cb7ed9a692</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFfzmlrBMJIsSAZrnbQ-rPUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6udAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 21:06:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/413bd927be874826b5f8b2cb7ed9a692" target="_blank"&gt;10th patient dies at pediatric facility in viral outbreak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — A 10th person died amid a viral outbreak at a pediatric care center while a different strain of the virus was found at another facility in the state, New Jersey health officials said Thursday. The state Health Department confirmed in a statement the "medically fragile child" at the Wanaque Center for Nursing and Rehabilitation had the adenovirus infection. There have been 28 cases associated with the respiratory virus at the center, where the affected children had severely compromised immune systems. One death was a young adult. "The loss of these young lives is heartbr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Goodwill workers in NJ find original 1774 'rebel' newspaper - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/0be8910e4060486ca2f8f93d70f738d6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDOmZU2MgB2nYlbf9Obmh44qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwwKudAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 20:34:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/0be8910e4060486ca2f8f93d70f738d6" target="_blank"&gt;Goodwill workers in NJ find original 1774 'rebel' newspaper&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BELLMAWR, N.J. (AP) — A quick eye by Goodwill workers in southern New Jersey turned up framed pages from an original 1774 Philadelphia newspaper with an iconic "Unite or Die" snake design on the masthead. The frayed Dec. 28, 1774, edition of the "Pennsylvania Journal and the Weekly Advertiser" boasts three items signed by John Hancock, then president of the Provincial Congress, who pleads for the Colonies to fight back "enemies" trying to divide them. A jumble of small advertisements offer rewards for a lost horse or runaway apprentice, while another insists the poster will no longer pay hi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Bookmaker opens sports lounge in Devils hockey arena - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/fecf6afb2c484badb595b87ba1f876a1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHnEYhgwAbezwa95eNzBobAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwnZidAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 18:31:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/fecf6afb2c484badb595b87ba1f876a1" target="_blank"&gt;Bookmaker opens sports lounge in Devils hockey arena&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. (AP) — New Jersey's rapidly growing sports betting market is extending its reach into a professional hockey arena, even as it adds a seventh Atlantic City casino to the fold. Bookmaker William Hill US said it plans to open a sports lounge Thursday night at Newark's Prudential Center, where the NHL's New Jersey Devils play. The viewing center will feature large video screens and constantly updated odds on sporting events in case fans with mobile betting apps on their phones want to wager. But it can't accept in-person cash bets; those are restricted to New Jersey casinos ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item></channel></rss>