<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>South Africa national rugby sevens team - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNR0kxWXpGakVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:21:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Check out BlitzBokke #Madiba100 jersey for Cape Town 7s - CapeTalk</title><link>http://www.capetalk.co.za/articles/329984/check-out-blitzbokke-madiba100-jersey-for-cape-town-7s</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYGh0dHA6Ly93d3cuY2FwZXRhbGsuY28uemEvYXJ0aWNsZXMvMzI5OTg0L2NoZWNrLW91dC1ibGl0emJva2tlLW1hZGliYTEwMC1qZXJzZXktZm9yLWNhcGUtdG93bi03c9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.capetalk.co.za/articles/329984/check-out-blitzbokke-madiba100-jersey-for-cape-town-7s" target="_blank"&gt;Check out BlitzBokke #Madiba100 jersey for Cape Town 7s&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CapeTalk&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saru has partnered with Asics to create a special Blitzbokke jersey to celebrate Nelson Mandela's 100th birthday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.capetalk.co.za">CapeTalk</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/0DQFDaxwrVeqccReOvZkePpbbhxh7c54wy1JaFS1-HokXD9S17Ofgd5UXzKWdUBO5bfABniTorqe9gdQGVZNjmZIQhkigKVL1AJY-ccEH2GhpMkWdgk8JOYiOxdMs3fQXDGqdtK8YSMEY6jLGXq2NkG26ytvkmHQtRMAcO__21FPwkkuFg5bMh7m=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Blitzbokke to feed off Cape Town crowd's energy - Jacaranda FM</title><link>https://www.jacarandafm.com/news/sport/blitzbokke-feed-cape-town-crowds-energy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780127241957</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.jacarandafm.com/news/sport/blitzbokke-feed-cape-town-crowds-energy/" target="_blank"&gt;Blitzbokke to feed off Cape Town crowd's energy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Jacaranda FM&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thesouthafrican.com/exclusive-cape-town-sevens-cecil-afrika-qa/" target="_blank"&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Cape Town Sevens - Cecil Afrika Q&amp;A&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The South African&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://supersport.com/rugby/sevens/news/181206_Powell_names_unchanged_lineup_for_CT_Sevens" target="_blank"&gt;Powell names unchanged line-up for CT Sevens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SuperSport&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=McXW_uKhkUI" target="_blank"&gt;Blitzboks ready for the World Rugby's Sevens Cape Town leg&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SABC Digital News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://ewn.co.za/2018/12/05/snyman-blitzboks-playing-for-50-million-south-africans" target="_blank"&gt;Snyman: Blitzboks playing for 50 million South Africans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;EWN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpsamZHbGpZQU1FWGtxVUJYZUowaldLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.jacarandafm.com">Jacaranda FM</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/kHscSuqOuK0SgZnP7CmXFriZyegCvNxzlQ4bSCmw5ugH6vqpAQ-VIEggm8YXnyffm32NsigTFbhQqsEuBLAUxu8vhmUf-JKz0Qh2LC-TXwQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Cape Town Sevens: Blitzboks to wear jersey to honor Nelson Mandela - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/06/sport/south-africa-blitzboks-mandela-jersey-south-africa-cape-town-sevens-spt-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjiTpCBsUNamsKwvdxmihMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:47:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/06/sport/south-africa-blitzboks-mandela-jersey-south-africa-cape-town-sevens-spt-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cape Town Sevens: Blitzboks to wear jersey to honor Nelson Mandela&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa's rugby sevens team will wear a special jersey at this weekend's tournament in Cape Town to pay tribute to former President Nelson Mandela, who would have turned 100 this year. Captains from each country visited Robben Island ahead of the Sevens World Series tournament, the site where Mandela served 18 of his 27 years in prison. "It's a great honor and privilege to wear this jersey and just to pay tribute to Nelson Mandela, the father figure of this country," said Blitzboks captain Phil Snyman. Visit CNN/com/sport for more news, features and videos "We can go out as a team and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sevens World Series: Blitzboks hit Vegas jackpot - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2017/03/06/sport/rugby-sevens-world-series-las-vegas-blitzboks-win-fiji/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbHcK2qlbsXA8DKSm40fTAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 14:33:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2017/03/06/sport/rugby-sevens-world-series-las-vegas-blitzboks-win-fiji/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sevens World Series: Blitzboks hit Vegas jackpot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa's Blitzboks hit the jackpot in rugby sevens party capital Las Vegas as they secured a fourth victory in five HSBC Sevens World Series events. The men in green are the side to beat in this year's series and Sunday's triumph means they now command a 24-point lead atop the overall standings, adding to wins in Wellington, Sydney and Dubai. "We're happy with how it's been going the last few tournaments and the guys are believing in a system and working for each other," said head coach Neil Powell. After conceding an early try against Fiji in Sunday's closely fought final, Powell's s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>England seal Cape Town sevens after South Africa miss final-kick conversion - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2016/dec/11/england-sevens-south-africa-australia-cape-town</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK2e1Sm3BaTjdOOgHnDlKZcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 22:40:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2016/dec/11/england-sevens-south-africa-australia-cape-town" target="_blank"&gt;England seal Cape Town sevens after South Africa miss final-kick conversion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;England beat South Africa 19-17 in Cape Town to win the second round of the 2016-17 World Rugby Sevens Series after Justin Geduld missed a conversion for the hosts with the last kick of the final. Chris Dry got the Blitzboks off to a flyer, finishing off a fine move from halfway to touch down in the corner. Branco du Preez missed the conversion. England hit back through Richard de Carpentier, who covered half the pitch to score under the posts. Tom Mitchell’s conversion gave England a 7-5 lead. Dan Norton then touched down out wide for his 225th career try as Simon Amor’s men extended their...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>London Sevens: Scotland upsets hosts England in season finale - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2017/05/21/sport/scotland-rugby-england-london-sevens-hsbc-sevens-world-series/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM8h3E5IcTQlCJPk5kggp0gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 19:38:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2017/05/21/sport/scotland-rugby-england-london-sevens-hsbc-sevens-world-series/" target="_blank"&gt;London Sevens: Scotland upsets hosts England in season finale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a final between two of rugby's greatest rivals, Scotland upset home favorites England 12-7 to win back-to-back London Sevens titles at Twickenham Stadium. Having lost to South Africa in the final of the Paris Sevens last week, Scotland went one step further in London thanks to second-half tries from Hugh Blake and Scott Riddell. The Blitzboks, meanwhile, had the chance to lift the championship trophy that was secured with last week's victory in Paris. Despite the loss, England managed to secure second place in the overall standings -- the side's best finish since 2007. READ: Anorexia and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rugby Sevens: Blitzboks tighten grip on series in Sydney - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2017/02/05/sport/rugby-sevens-south-africa-england-sydney-world-series/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMvXHSShyhcYP9IHrnuBv5kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 18:36:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2017/02/05/sport/rugby-sevens-south-africa-england-sydney-world-series/" target="_blank"&gt;Rugby Sevens: Blitzboks tighten grip on series in Sydney&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa tightened its grip on rugby's 2016-17 Sevens World Series, beating England 29-14 in Sunday's Sydney final. England had seen off New Zealand 12-5 in the semifinal, but proved no match for the blistering Blitzboks in the the decider, as unanswered tries from captain Philip Snyman, Seabelo Senatla and Justin Geduld ended the contest before the first half was up. England did fight back, as captain Tom Mitchell and Dan Norton gave the scoreline a look of respectability But, determined to avenge their defeat to England in December's Cape Town final, this was a match South Africa neve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Paris Sevens: South African 'Blitzboks' seal overall title - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2017/05/14/sport/paris-rugby-sevens-blitzboks-scotland/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGX9hfc-59qgrYXdwo_JQicqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 16:58:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2017/05/14/sport/paris-rugby-sevens-blitzboks-scotland/" target="_blank"&gt;Paris Sevens: South African 'Blitzboks' seal overall title&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The South Africa 'Blitzboks' were crowned HSBC World Rugby Sevens champions Sunday as they claimed the Paris title with a 15-5 victory over Scotland in the final. The overall series win had been sealed by South Africa's 26-5 semifinal win over New Zealand, combined with England's 19-17 defeat to the Scots at the same stage. It meant England was unable to overhaul the Blitzboks ahead over the final round of the series in London next weekend. Sevens all-time leading try scorer Dan Norton crossed three times for England, but it could not overhaul a 19-5 lead for its arch-rival, topped by a fin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Australia stifled at Sydney Sevens with defeat to South Africa in semi-finals - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2017/feb/05/australia-stifled-at-sydney-sevens-with-defeat-to-south-africa-in-semi-finals</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFsI8K7YALDfeRWMMxd9avUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 07:55:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2017/feb/05/australia-stifled-at-sydney-sevens-with-defeat-to-south-africa-in-semi-finals" target="_blank"&gt;Australia stifled at Sydney Sevens with defeat to South Africa in semi-finals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia’s hopes of securing their home rugby sevens tournament were ended by a rampant South Africa side in the semi-finals in Sydney, with the hosts eventually settling for fourth place following defeat to New Zealand in the bronze-medal match. South Africa went on to claim the title at this leg of the Sevens World Series with an even more dominant display in the final, opening up a 24-0 lead over England before sealing a 29-14 win. Against Australia, the Blitzboks took full advantage of an indisciplined performance by the hosts to post a comfortable 26-12 win at a hot, sticky and packed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Wellington Sevens: Blitzboks thrash Olympic champion Fiji in final - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2017/01/29/sport/rugby-sevens-wellington-blitzboks-fiji/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBc-5XCbUzLbbzIgY6njO-4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 12:42:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2017/01/29/sport/rugby-sevens-wellington-blitzboks-fiji/" target="_blank"&gt;Wellington Sevens: Blitzboks thrash Olympic champion Fiji in final&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa's Blitzboks thrashed Olympic champion Fiji 26-5 to win the Wellington Sevens Sunday and extend its lead in the World Series. Runner-up twice in the last three years, a rampant South Africa team made no mistake this time after dominating the two-day tournament with 174 points in its six matches and only 22 conceded. Victory in the final was the second of the weekend over Fiji, having beaten the Pacific Islanders by 31-12 in pool play Saturday. After three rounds of the series, the Blitzboks hold a 12-point lead on defending champion Fiji, with England in third place. WATCH: Janu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sevens World Series: Vancouver victory caps stellar weekend for English rugby - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2017/03/13/sport/rugby-sevens-world-series-vancouver-england-south-africa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI4khjazzuU7yjp4Pi5MvUoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 14:37:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2017/03/13/sport/rugby-sevens-world-series-vancouver-england-south-africa/" target="_blank"&gt;Sevens World Series: Vancouver victory caps stellar weekend for English rugby&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As weekends go, it was a pretty good one for English rugby. A record-equaling 18th consecutive win for the test side, a 64-0 hammering of Scotland for the women's team, and to cap it all off, victory at the Rugby Sevens World Series event in Vancouver, Canada. England's 19-7 defeat of South Africa in Sunday's final means Simon Amor's side is still the only team to overcome the Blitzboks this season, having also beaten the men in green in the Cape Town title match. "We've played well at times this season and haven't come away with wins so it's nice to get reward for our efforts," said Englan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Dubai Sevens: South Africa stuns Olympic champion Fiji - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2016/12/03/sport/dubai-sevens-fiji-south-africa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBMsjKPJ4eSPSTDZUP1Ln7IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 18:04:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2016/12/03/sport/dubai-sevens-fiji-south-africa/" target="_blank"&gt;Dubai Sevens: South Africa stuns Olympic champion Fiji&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The South African Blitzboks upset Olympic champion Fiji to win the opening tournament of the HSBC Sevens World Series in Dubai Saturday. South Africa, so impressive over the two days of the competition, won a thrilling final 26-14 as late tries from man of the match Chris Dry and the prolific Seabelo Senatla took them clear of the Fijians. It was the fifth Dubai title for South Africa, which finished second to Fiji in the last two World Series and took bronze at the Rio Olympics. Boks captain Philip Snyman said confidence was now high heading into the side's home round in Cape Town next wee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Hong Kong Sevens: England's Dan Norton breaks all-time try-scoring record - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2017/04/10/sport/hong-kong-sevens-dan-norton-england-fiji-rugby/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMayUdX2ihxAIYrxdtDR5CUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:42:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2017/04/10/sport/hong-kong-sevens-dan-norton-england-fiji-rugby/" target="_blank"&gt;Hong Kong Sevens: England's Dan Norton breaks all-time try-scoring record&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;England's Dan Norton made history at the Hong Kong Sevens by breaking the sport's all-time try-scoring record. When he out-sprinted South Korea's defence to collect his own chip ahead, the 29-year-old scored the 245th try of his sevens career and surpassed the tally he had previously shared with Kenya's Collins Injera. Fiji won the Hong Kong Sevens for the third consecutive year, convincingly beating South Africa's Blitzboks 22-0 in front of a sell-out crowd at the Hong Kong Stadium. The victory lifts last year's Olympic champion above England to second in the overall standings. It was Fiji...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>HSBC London Sevens: England set up quarter-final against Sevens Series champions the Blitzboks - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/05/21/hsbc-london-sevens-england-set-quarter-final-against-sevens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEnv1G1BopnX3hHe4u7VlFEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 07:42:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/05/21/hsbc-london-sevens-england-set-quarter-final-against-sevens/" target="_blank"&gt;HSBC London Sevens: England set up quarter-final against Sevens Series champions the Blitzboks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;England’s trio of victories, gained from three increasingly-challenging pool games in the HSBC London Sevens on Saturday – against Spain (28-7), Australia (19-12), and Samoa (24-19) – earned the Twickenham hosts a devilish quarter-final clash with newly-crowned series champions South Africa. At 11.42am Simon Amor’s side will tackle the Blitzboks, whose HSBC World Rugby Sevens Series title was confirmed last Sunday in Paris, moments before they claimed their fifth tournament win in the 10-stop season. England, though, are also on high, as their pool-topping performance guaranteed a second-pl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Bryan Habana: The excitement of sevens - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/sports/2016/12/09/bryan-habana-south-africa-rugby-sevens-world-series-cape-town-intv.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB71vS-FVC1T-MWpVbQXcKgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 13:49:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/sports/2016/12/09/bryan-habana-south-africa-rugby-sevens-world-series-cape-town-intv.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Bryan Habana: The excitement of sevens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South African rugby star Bryan Habana reflects on his time as a sevens player last season and looks ahead to the Cape Town round of the 2016-17 World Series. ©2016 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Blitzboks buzzing after Dubai success - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/sports/2016/12/08/philip-snyman-south-africa-springbok-rugby-sevens-dubai-final-christina-macfarlane-intv.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOZ4EFZb5z_PgXACDGoesNkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 17:44:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/sports/2016/12/08/philip-snyman-south-africa-springbok-rugby-sevens-dubai-final-christina-macfarlane-intv.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Blitzboks buzzing after Dubai success&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New captain Philip Snyman talks to CNN's Christina Macfarlane after South Africa's win over Olympic rugby champion Fiji in the Dubai Sevens final. ©2016 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Portia Woodman: Black Ferns star breaks new ground in rugby rankings - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/01/sport/portia-woodman-rugby-sevens-new-zealand-black-ferns-rugby-world-spt-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC9Ar_MuF_NlbnR1TEOV_-8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 16:05:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/01/sport/portia-woodman-rugby-sevens-new-zealand-black-ferns-rugby-world-spt-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Portia Woodman: Black Ferns star breaks new ground in rugby rankings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Victory for South Africa and a fifth-place finish for Fiji saw the Blitzboks take the 2017-18 Sevens World Series title by just two points. Steve Bardens/Getty Images Europe/Getty Images A runner-up finish for Australia in Paris was enough to secure the overall women's title ahead of rivals New Zealand. Steve Bardens/Getty Images Europe/Getty Images Portia Woodman bagged two tries in the Paris final, which ended 33-7 in favor of the Black Ferns. Despite three tournament wins, however, they couldn't defend their championship title. GEOFFROY VAN DER HASSELT/AFP/AFP/Getty Images Fiji's Josua T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Warren Weir: Jamaican sprinter set to electrify rugby sevens - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/07/10/sport/warren-weir-jamaica-rugby-sevens-cac-games-olympics-spt-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK6W9F474BZJBPdCPFmQ0DoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 14:07:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/07/10/sport/warren-weir-jamaica-rugby-sevens-cac-games-olympics-spt-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Warren Weir: Jamaican sprinter set to electrify rugby sevens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Victory for South Africa and a fifth-place finish for Fiji saw the Blitzboks take the 2017-18 Sevens World Series title by just two points. Steve Bardens/Getty Images Europe/Getty Images A runner-up finish for Australia in Paris was enough to secure the overall women's title ahead of rivals New Zealand. Steve Bardens/Getty Images Europe/Getty Images Portia Woodman bagged two tries in the Paris final, which ended 33-7 in favor of the Black Ferns. Despite three tournament wins, however, they couldn't defend their championship title. GEOFFROY VAN DER HASSELT/AFP/AFP/Getty Images Fiji's Josua T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>World Rugby Sevens series wrap - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/sports/2018/06/21/world-rugby-sevens-series-wrap-2018-fiji-south-africa-paris-spt-intl.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELjD-8p4PAiRVBpUxv4Jyc0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 16:09:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/sports/2018/06/21/world-rugby-sevens-series-wrap-2018-fiji-south-africa-paris-spt-intl.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;World Rugby Sevens series wrap&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christina Macfarlane wraps the 2018 Rugby Sevens series from Las Vegas to Hong Kong to Paris, from Fiji to the Blitzboks of South Africa. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>London Sevens: Fiji takes command of series with victory over South Africa - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/06/03/sport/london-sevens-fiji-south-africa-rugby-intl-spt/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECpmI4gplPmKCrW5DDpVIpIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 19:08:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/06/03/sport/london-sevens-fiji-south-africa-rugby-intl-spt/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;London Sevens: Fiji takes command of series with victory over South Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiji's Josua Tuisova looks for an offload in the final of the London Sevens against South Africa. His side ran out 21-19 victors to take control of the series. Jordan Mansfield/Getty Images Europe/Getty Images New Zealand's Black Ferns inflicted the heaviest ever series defeat on Australia in the final of the Canada Sevens, scoring eight tries in a 46-0 demolition of their rivals. DON MACKINNON/AFP/AFP/Getty Images Fiji moved to the top of the standings with a tense victory over Australia in Singapore. ROSLAN RAHMAN/AFP/AFP/Getty Images New Zealand's Black Ferns backed up Commonwealth gold ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Zambia relishes 'once in a lifetime' game against All Blacks - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/21/sport/zambia-rugby-sevens-commonwealth-games/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM75FjcGpu3ZTSDHaxcySB0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 12:05:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/21/sport/zambia-rugby-sevens-commonwealth-games/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia relishes 'once in a lifetime' game against All Blacks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiji overturned a first-half deficit against South Africa to claim its first title of the season in Hamilton -- the first time the town has hosted a Sevens World Series tournament after the New Zealand leg was moved from Wellington. MICHAEL BRADLEY/AFP/AFP/Getty Images Australia's women continued their storming start to the season in Sydney. Tim Walsh's side became the first team ever to go a whole tournament without conceding a point. MARK EVANS/AFP/AFP/Getty Images There was more good news to come for home fans that weekend. The men eased past South Africa 29-0 in the final, with Ben O'Do...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Hamilton Sevens: Fiji overturns South Africa in final - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/05/sport/hamilton-rugby-sevens-fiji-south-africa/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECJLPEQHB2Su9lgSopKaR8AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 16:33:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/02/05/sport/hamilton-rugby-sevens-fiji-south-africa/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hamilton Sevens: Fiji overturns South Africa in final&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiji overturned a first-half deficit against South Africa to claim its first title of the season in New Zealand. MICHAEL BRADLEY/AFP/AFP/Getty Images Australia's women enjoyed a storming start to the season. In Sydney, Tim Walsh's side became the first team ever to go a whole tournament without conceding a point. MARK EVANS/AFP/AFP/Getty Images There was more good news to come for home fans. The men eased past South Africa 29-0 in the final, with Ben O'Donnell (pictured) grabbing a brace. Jason McCawley/Getty Images AsiaPac/Getty Images for HSBC The All Blacks claimed a first tournament vic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Hobbits, Hamilton and heavy lifting - behind the scenes with England men's Sevens team in New Zealand - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-sevens/2018/02/06/hobbits-hamilton-heavy-lifting-behind-scenes-england-mens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJUZrOIt0Y7rI7J7NFnIsFAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 14:50:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-sevens/2018/02/06/hobbits-hamilton-heavy-lifting-behind-scenes-england-mens/" target="_blank"&gt;Hobbits, Hamilton and heavy lifting - behind the scenes with England men's Sevens team in New Zealand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch an exclusive behind the scenes diary from the England men's Sevens team as they head to Hamilton in New Zealand, with the giants of the rugby world getting ready for the weekend by spending some time in a rather smaller environment - the world of the hobbits. Video block text&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>New Zealand Sevens round-up: Southern Hemisphere domination continues with Fiji victory - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-sevens/2018/02/05/new-zealand-sevens-round-up-southern-hemisphere-domination-continues/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHFi8NDA4s-EWKqU_oUH4-sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 14:06:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-sevens/2018/02/05/new-zealand-sevens-round-up-southern-hemisphere-domination-continues/" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand Sevens round-up: Southern Hemisphere domination continues with Fiji victory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trend of Southern Hemisphere domination in the HSBC Sevens World Series this season continued as Fiji were crowned winners of the New Zealand Sevens. The flying Fijians followed South Africa, New Zealand and Australia in winning tournaments since the World Series season kicked off in Dubai in December. As they had done in Sydney last week, England fell at the quarter-final stages despite pushing New Zealand close. Ruaridh McConnochie, who will move to XVs with Bath next season, put England ahead against the All Blacks Sevens. The hosts crossed twice before McConnochie got his second sco...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Sydney Sevens: Double delight for Australia as women make history - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/29/sport/sydney-australia-rugby-sevens-world-series/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFny84ugJjNr3UJRh_eGvlEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 16:27:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/29/sport/sydney-australia-rugby-sevens-world-series/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sydney Sevens: Double delight for Australia as women make history&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia's women enjoyed a storming start to the season. In Sydney, Tim Walsh's side became the first team ever to go a whole tournament without conceding a point. MARK EVANS/AFP/AFP/Getty Images There was more good news to come for home fans. The men eased past South Africa 29-0 in the final, with Ben O'Donnell (pictured) grabbing a brace. Jason McCawley/Getty Images AsiaPac/Getty Images for HSBC The All Blacks claimed a first tournament victory since March 2016 in South Africa, toppling Argentina in the final. RODGER BOSCH/AFP/AFP/Getty Images Having finished second to New Zealand in las...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ben Ryan: Fiji's rugby sevens hero - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2017/01/05/sport/gallery/ben-ryan-fiji-rugby-sevens/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHe0N8qDM2WC926xKdxUuqEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 15:02:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2017/01/05/sport/gallery/ben-ryan-fiji-rugby-sevens/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ben Ryan: Fiji's rugby sevens hero&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ben Ryan spent a golden three years with Fiji's sevens team. PATRICK HAMILTON/AFP/AFP/Getty Images/file Ryan moved to the Pacific Islands with his interest in the game at its lowest ebb after being disillusioned by his job with the English RFU. Chris McGrath/Getty Images AsiaPac/Getty Images Fiji won two successive men's Sevens World Series titles, and backed that up to take Olympic gold at Rio 2016. JOHN MACDOUGALL/AFP/AFP/Getty Images Ryan built up an amazing rapport with his team, but opted to walk away from the role after the Olympics when his contract expired. PHILIPPE LOPEZ/AFP/AFP/Ge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Australia Women's 7s agree deal that ensures pay parity with male counterparts in historic first - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-sevens/2018/01/26/australia-womens-7s-agree-deal-ensures-pay-parity-male-counterparts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLxIIi0J-Aj4ao4bcjgVL4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:18:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-sevens/2018/01/26/australia-womens-7s-agree-deal-ensures-pay-parity-male-counterparts/" target="_blank"&gt;Australia Women's 7s agree deal that ensures pay parity with male counterparts in historic first&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Happy Australia Day. This year’s celebration was particularly momentous for the Australian Women’s Sevens team as they ran out on the opening day of the HSBC Sydney 7s - not only did they become the first side to strike Olympic sevens gold, they have just achieved another historic first with an agreement that ensures pay parity with their male counterparts. The deal is the first of its kind in rugby and also includes a pregnancy policy - another first. This comes after Norway’s football federation agreed in October that male and female players would be paid the same when on international du...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The secret to South Africa Sevens' success and how country has embraced rugby's short form - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/12/09/secret-south-africa-sevens-success-country-has-embraced-rugbys/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL853msfEL9autREGzlc7EAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 12:29:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/12/09/secret-south-africa-sevens-success-country-has-embraced-rugbys/" target="_blank"&gt;The secret to South Africa Sevens' success and how country has embraced rugby's short form&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many would say that the Springboks are in ill health. After finishing third in the Rugby Championship and losing to Ireland and Wales during the autumn international period, South Africa are currently sitting in sixth place in the World Rugby rankings. Yet it is far from doom and gloom for South African rugby as the Springboks' younger sibling the Blitzbok is fighting fit. South Africa Sevens are current holders of the HSBC World Series and they have started their defence in emphatic form sealing victory at the Dubai 7s last weekend. Further testimony to the Blitzboks’ strength is a sold ou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Magnificent Sevens: Who to look out for in the 2017/18 World Series - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/08/sport/rugby-sevens-ones-to-watch-2018-world-series-mens-womens/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPFMiQzIf1ZOe2DiXTjISFcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 16:20:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/08/sport/rugby-sevens-ones-to-watch-2018-world-series-mens-womens/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Magnificent Sevens: Who to look out for in the 2017/18 World Series&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest event of the Rugby Sevens World Series takes place at the 55,000-capacity Cape Town Stadium this weekend. Can the Blitzboks continue their fine start on home soil after storming to victory in Dubai? Or will England silence the crowd as they did in South Africa last time out? CNN Sport profiles seven men and women to watch for the 2017/2018 campaign below. Perry Baker (USA) David Rogers/Getty Images South America/Getty Images/file The only American selected for the 2016 World Series Dream Team, Baker crossed the line more often than any other player last season, racking up 57 trie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sevens World Series: South Africa storm to victory in Dubai - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/04/sport/rugby-sevens-world-series-dubai-round-one-south-africa/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOWR8ZFux1Kdyg-hEXPvoC4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 14:16:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/04/sport/rugby-sevens-world-series-dubai-round-one-south-africa/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sevens World Series: South Africa storm to victory in Dubai&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New season, same result. South Africa won the opening leg of the HSBC World Rugby Sevens Series in Dubai at the weekend, picking up where they left off last year. The Blitzboks produced an electrifying display of attacking rugby at the Sevens Stadium, topping their pool undefeated before overcoming Fiji, Samoa and finally New Zealand in the knockout stages to lift the trophy. First half tries from captain Philip Snyman, Player of the Final Kwagga Smith and the prolific Seabelo Senatla helped South Africa to a 24-12 win against the Kiwis in the gold medal match. The victory means the reignin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rugby Sevens: Blitzboks and Black Ferns aiming for clean sweep in 2018 - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/01/sport/world-rugby-sevens-season-preview/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4WeHsLGYAgxHuDzWNs4zgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:32:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2017/12/01/sport/world-rugby-sevens-season-preview/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rugby Sevens: Blitzboks and Black Ferns aiming for clean sweep in 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stage is set for an epic battle of speed, stamina and strength as some of the world's most talented rugby players embark upon a momentous sevens season. This weekend sees the return of the HSBC World Rugby Sevens Series with both the men's and women's competitions kicking off in Dubai. The tournament -- the first of 10 for the men and five for the women -- marks the start of a grueling eight months with many teams battling for silverware on three fronts. In addition to the Sevens Series, the top teams will be competing at the Commonwealth Games in Gold Coast, Australia next April. Then ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item></channel></rss>