<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>United States Environmental Protection Agency - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNR2N3YkdnU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:31:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Ex-EPA chief Scott Pruitt used personal email for government work - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/08/epa-chief-scott-pruitt-personal-emails</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJpZ8rzZND0Y1oBIrk7Qg3sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/08/epa-chief-scott-pruitt-personal-emails" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-EPA chief Scott Pruitt used personal email for government work&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump’s first Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) administrator repeatedly violated agency policy to use personal email for government business, according to newly released public records. Scott Pruitt – who left the administration this summer after months of controversy over his spending, travel and ties with industry – used his private email account for work over a period of months, according to records recently made available to the Sierra Club. Someone forwarded the emails to Pruitt’s government account on the day he resigned. EPA policy requires employees to do so within 20 da...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>NT's largest land-clearing permit faces legal challenge over climate change - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/nt-land-clearing-climate-change-legal-stoush-supreme-court/10590808</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGB3_s8Yrz7aCBgtW9QdKg4qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:16:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/nt-land-clearing-climate-change-legal-stoush-supreme-court/10590808" target="_blank"&gt;NT's largest land-clearing permit faces legal challenge over climate change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potential greenhouse gas emissions from the Northern Territory's largest-ever land-clearing project were not weighed because their impact on global warming could not be measured, the head of an environmental watchdog says. Key points: - A permit was approved in 2017 to clear more than 20,000 hectares of native vegetation at Maryfield Station - The EPA did not request an environmental impact assessment before awarding the permit - This decision is facing a legal challenge over potential climate change impacts Paul Vogel gave evidence this week in a landmark challenge brought against the EPA'...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Landmark environmental protections being rolled back - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/b313482683f14439b78d985b758b51e1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZNKIiyLHvIubKOqN384IsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:32:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/b313482683f14439b78d985b758b51e1" target="_blank"&gt;Landmark environmental protections being rolled back&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — One after another, landmark U.S. protections for climate, air and land are in the crosshairs of the Trump administration as his agency leaders move past early fumbles and scandals to start delivering on a succession of promised environmental rollbacks. On Thursday, the Interior Department proposed easing rules on oil and gas drilling for millions of acres of range in the West. And as soon as next week, the Environmental Protection Agency is expected to unveil its proposed rewrite of a major 2015 Obama rule that extended federal protections to thousands of waterways and wet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>EPA rolls back coal rule despite climate change warnings - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/epa-coal-announcement/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGr69cND3d07SFMt-gbloqoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:47:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/epa-coal-announcement/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;EPA rolls back coal rule despite climate change warnings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration will reverse an Obama-era coal emissions rule as part of its effort to loosen restrictions on the coal industry, just days after a US government report warned that aggressive action is needed to curb greenhouse gases and ease the impact of global warming. The reversal won't lead to the immediate construction of new coal-fired power plants, but it does send an immediate political signal that the Trump administration is intent on shoring up the coal industry and other energy interests. "We are rescinding unfair burdens on America's energy providers and leveling the pl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>🇺🇸Trump EPA makes it easier to open new coal plants l Al Jazeera English - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VGqRjSSzxuM</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPpggW4U9IirOk6j4f1ia0YqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwkOgB</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:49:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VGqRjSSzxuM" target="_blank"&gt;🇺🇸Trump EPA makes it easier to open new coal plants l Al Jazeera English&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As climate negotiators from around the world gather in Poland to try to strengthen measures to limit carbon emissions, the US Environmental Protection Agency has just made it easier to open new coal-fired plants. The Trump administration has rolled back an Obama-era regulation designed to reduce CO2 emissions. Al Jazeera's Kristen Saloomey reports. - Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe - Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish - Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera - Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/ #AlJazeeraEnglish #Coal #Climate...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>EPA Moves To Roll Back Coal Plant Rule In A Stunning Rebuke Of Global Climate Talks - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/epa-coal_us_5c096995e4b0b6cdaf5d16ba</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBkVBQRjiMnNK056lkhymJ0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:58:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/epa-coal_us_5c096995e4b0b6cdaf5d16ba" target="_blank"&gt;EPA Moves To Roll Back Coal Plant Rule In A Stunning Rebuke Of Global Climate Talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Environmental Protection Agency on Thursday proposed gutting an Obama-era rule requiring coal-fired power plants to reduce carbon dioxide emissions, defying increasingly desperate international negotiations to scale down planet-warming gases. At a press conference at the agency’s headquarters, Acting Administrator Andrew Wheeler Administrator Andrew Wheeler called the Obama administration’s rule was too strict, calling it “disingenuous” and “not adequately demonstrated,” and said the new proposal would “set high yet achievable standards that are rooted in reality.” “To put it in clear a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>EPA Proposes Rollback on Coal Emissions Regulation - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/epa-proposes-rollback-on-coal-emissions-regulation/4689971.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIy8jBWy2nLllg4mFVJkImsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:54:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/epa-proposes-rollback-on-coal-emissions-regulation/4689971.html" target="_blank"&gt;EPA Proposes Rollback on Coal Emissions Regulation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency has proposed rolling back a regulation for coal plants that would allow new plants a lower standard on carbon emissions. The EPA made the announcement Thursday regarding the Obama-era ruling requiring new coal plants to produce no more than 1,400 pounds of carbon per megawatt-hour. The change would allow new plants to produce up to 1,900 pounds of carbon per megawatt-hour. Under the Obama regulation, plants were to cut their carbon emissions by using some natural gas, installing some carbon-capture equipment, or change to more efficient technology th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Trump's EPA proposes looser carbon limits on new coal plants - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-coal-idUSKBN1O519C</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHcWEkgUwtx8D0Ev4QnQEVsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:28:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-coal-idUSKBN1O519C" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's EPA proposes looser carbon limits on new coal plants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration on Thursday proposed rolling back an Obama-era rule requiring new U.S. coal plants to slash carbon emissions, a move that could crack open the door in coming years for new plants fired by the fossil fuel. The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency's acting administrator, Andrew Wheeler, a former coal lobbyist, announced the proposal. It would allow new coal plants to emit up to 1,900 pounds (862 kg) of carbon dioxide per megawatt-hour of electricity, up from 1,400 pounds now. The move to revive the ailing coal industry, whose share in the U.S. energy mix has been in d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump EPA acts to roll back control on climate-changing coal - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/c9f226034f05432b9a00f975e15815bf</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAt7HnoY3GOAYCNPCcLZsFcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:11:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/c9f226034f05432b9a00f975e15815bf" target="_blank"&gt;Trump EPA acts to roll back control on climate-changing coal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Environmental Protection Agency acted again Thursday to ease rules on the sagging U.S. coal industry, this time scaling back what would have been a tough control on climate-changing emissions from any new coal plants. The latest Trump administration targeting of legacy Obama administration efforts to slow climate change comes in the wake of multiplying warnings from the agency's scientists and others about the accelerating pace of global warming. In a ceremony Thursday at the agency, acting EPA administrator Andrew Wheeler signed a proposal to dismantle a 2015 rule tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The weedkiller in our food is killing us - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/the-weedkiller-in-our-food-is-killing-us</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJNVNPimh7yJ0La_8mzJfM8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:30:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/the-weedkiller-in-our-food-is-killing-us" target="_blank"&gt;The weedkiller in our food is killing us&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a recent Saturday afternoon, in an estuary near Tampa Bay, Florida, I watched airboats move up and down the river banks, spraying massive plumes of weedkiller on to the vegetation. The state of Florida was trying to control and kill off scores of plant species. Nearby, children were lying out in the sun, though they knew better than to swim in the water, which has recently been blooming with toxic algae. Mists of weedkiller drifted downwind toward them. The main active ingredient in that mist, and in the weedkiller being sprayed throughout Tampa Bay, is glyphosate, one of the most widely...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>EPA Cuts Livestream of Press Conference on Future of Coal as Q&amp;A Begins - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/epa-cuts-livestream-of-press-conference-on-future-of-coal-as-qanda-begins</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_Iwo0z3PQf0wh4ixpBOosqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:58:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/epa-cuts-livestream-of-press-conference-on-future-of-coal-as-qanda-begins" target="_blank"&gt;EPA Cuts Livestream of Press Conference on Future of Coal as Q&amp;A Begins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ting Shen/Reuters, At an Environmental Protection Agency press conference Thursday announcing new relaxed coal regulations, an EPA official signaled for the video live feed to end just as Acting Administrator Andrew Wheeler began to take questions from reporters. The new regulations will loosen CO2 emissions standards for new coal-fired power plants, making it cheaper to build new coal plants in the United States. The roll-out eliminates Obama-era restrictions on new coal plants that required them to include carbon capture systems. Wheeler, a former coal lobbyist, argued that the systems, w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Trump targets two Obama-era green rules in boost to coal and oil industries despite warnings over climate change - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/donald-trump-coal-plants-oil-climate-change-epa-sage-grouse-habitat-global-warming-a8671531.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAzs6LVgPXgGxvXST1L28lEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/donald-trump-coal-plants-oil-climate-change-epa-sage-grouse-habitat-global-warming-a8671531.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump targets two Obama-era green rules in boost to coal and oil industries despite warnings over climate change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump’s administration has announced proposals to roll back two Obama-era environmental polices to boost the coal and oil industries - despite increasingly dire warnings about the effects of climate change. First, the Environmental Protection Agency's (EPA) acting administrator, Andrew Wheeler, a former coal lobbyist, announced that new coal plants could be allowed emit up to 1,900 pounds (862 kg) of carbon dioxide per megawatt-hour of electricity, up from 1,400 pounds now. The current rules for new plants, put in place by former President Barack Obama, required technology to capture...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Trump EPA to strike blow against climate rules, reports say - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/climate-epa-coal-power-plants/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPhLDbP-rqr4ggwvmn_hSN8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:12:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/climate-epa-coal-power-plants/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump EPA to strike blow against climate rules, reports say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration is set to roll back Obama-era rules on climate change regulation that will make it easier to build new coal plants, according to reports in Axios and The New York Times. Environmental Protection Agency acting Administrator Andrew Wheeler, a former coal industry lobbyist, is expected to make the announcement Thursday. The move is another indication of the Trump administration's determination to buck both global consensus about the need to act on climate change and market trends, as the President courts what he calls the "beautiful, clean coal" industry. Thursday's ro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump targets pair of Obama-era green rules to boost oil, coal - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-energy-trump/trump-targets-pair-of-obama-era-green-rules-to-boost-oil-coal-idUSKBN1O52L7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELksT9A31uzqYGP4p3AkLRQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:56:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-energy-trump/trump-targets-pair-of-obama-era-green-rules-to-boost-oil-coal-idUSKBN1O52L7" target="_blank"&gt;Trump targets pair of Obama-era green rules to boost oil, coal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration took aim at two Obama-era environmental policies on Thursday to boost the oil and coal industries, proposing to open up a bird's wildlife habitat to drilling and mining and remove hurdles to new coal-fired power plant construction. The moves, part of a broader agenda by U.S. President Donald Trump to revive the ailing coal industry and ramp up domestic energy production, come amid increasingly urgent warnings from within his own government about climate change, and as world leaders gather at a United Nations conference to combat planetary warming. Announced separate...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Emails: EPA Staffers Freaked When Pruitt Tried to Stage Climate Change Debate - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/emails-epa-staffers-freaked-when-pruitt-tried-to-stage-climate-change-debate</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECiEvSVYJHN2u9ZTLyp2qIAqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:24:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/emails-epa-staffers-freaked-when-pruitt-tried-to-stage-climate-change-debate" target="_blank"&gt;Emails: EPA Staffers Freaked When Pruitt Tried to Stage Climate Change Debate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Kelly Caminero/The Daily Beast Officials at the Environmental Protection Agency were privately aghast in early 2017 as their boss, former EPA chief Scott Pruitt, embraced hosting a public debate over the scientific premise of human-caused climate change. In private emails, top scientists and officials at EPA expressed serious concern that Pruitt’s gambit could set back the cause of combating global warming by legitimizing politically motivated skeptics. Mostly, however, they thought the idea of a red team-blue team debate was a gargantuan waste of time with potential t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Ex-EPA head reports single, $50,000 gift to defense fund - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/4577c21bf46444c094588cda52f247e1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIX0dHzdrVfENZs4g3c5drUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:06:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/4577c21bf46444c094588cda52f247e1" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-EPA head reports single, $50,000 gift to defense fund&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Environmental Protection Agency says a Republican donor gave $50,000 for Scott Pruitt's defense fund before he left the agency. The former EPA chief reported the gift in a legally required financial disclosure released Thursday. The report lists the $50,000 contribution to Pruitt from Wisconsin businesswoman Diane Hendricks. Pruitt left the agency in July amid increasing investigations into his spending and other conduct. He earlier acknowledged creating a fund to help him with his growing legal bills. EPA ethics officials note in the report that they believe the $50,0...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Special Report: Little lab on the prairie clears path to big 'clean coal' profits - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-coal-labs-specialreport/special-report-little-lab-on-the-prairie-clears-path-to-big-clean-coal-profits-idUSKBN1O31Q7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMnGDigE9DXMatdNo1cSnX4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:14:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-coal-labs-specialreport/special-report-little-lab-on-the-prairie-clears-path-to-big-clean-coal-profits-idUSKBN1O31Q7" target="_blank"&gt;Special Report: Little lab on the prairie clears path to big 'clean coal' profits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Clean” coal is a rich vein for American investors to mine, thanks to a lucrative subsidy offered by the U.S. government. For many producers of the fuel, the path to profit leads through a laboratory at the University of North Dakota. The school’s Energy and Environmental Research Center reported earning about $5 million in fiscal 2015-16 performing laboratory tests that qualify clean-coal producers for the subsidy. On any given day, EERC technicians take a sample of up to one ton of the coal from a producer and burn it in a miniature boiler to determine whether it reduces a specific pollut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Congress, reverse the EPA's assault on our environment and health - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/opinions/congress-protect-american-health-environment-mikulka/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzSeuVTkNkiGkfyj1Fx5SoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:25:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/opinions/congress-protect-american-health-environment-mikulka/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Congress, reverse the EPA's assault on our environment and health&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Mikulka is president of the American Federation of Government Employees Local 704, representing workers in the Environmental Protection Agency's Region 5, and spokesman for the Save the US EPA Campaign, an effort to have a fully staffed and fully funded EPA protect public health and environment. The views expressed in this commentary are his own. View more opinion on CNN. When the 116th Congress is sworn in, it must immediately reverse course from the Trump administration's two-year assault on environmental and public health protections. To do so, Congress must strengthen the Enviro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump's pick for EPA already rolling back climate change protections - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/politics/epa-wheeler-climate-protections/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENWRU0MS23e-yo8DqWrnZQAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 03:44:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/politics/epa-wheeler-climate-protections/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's pick for EPA already rolling back climate change protections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Wheeler, the former coal lobbyist who is now acting administrator of the Environmental Protection Agency, was a "driving force" behind the agenda of Sen. James Inhofe, who called climate change a "hoax," according to people familiar with Wheeler's work for the senator. President Donald Trump has said he intends to nominate Wheeler as the head of the EPA, and in the past five months as acting administrator, Wheeler has moved aggressively to roll back key environmental regulations, prompting critics and environmentalists to say he is fast confirming their worst fears for the agency's f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Anger mounts over handling of waste re-use scheme - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/anger-mounts-over-nsw-governments-handling-of-waste-reuse-scheme/10558124</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL_Als-2ceF7vYEG8kAJOowqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 05:10:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/anger-mounts-over-nsw-governments-handling-of-waste-reuse-scheme/10558124" target="_blank"&gt;Anger mounts over handling of waste re-use scheme&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Farmers and waste operators in New South Wales are calling for the resumption of a scheme that allowed them to use treated household waste to improve soil quality. The scheme, which used treated waste from red-lid bins on farms and mine rehabilitation sites, was suspended on environmental grounds in late October. A report prepared for the Environmental Protection Authority (EPA) found the material "had highly visible plastic and glass components" and provided limited agricultural benefit. But now farmers have slammed the NSW Government's handling of the issue, saying that he risks have been...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Trump Administration May Reshape Next Federal Climate Report: EPA Chief - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-administration-wheeler-climate-change-study_us_5bfeebcde4b0388c1770ce67</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGd4hhxdUpVfndwN6_-FWgIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 22:48:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-administration-wheeler-climate-change-study_us_5bfeebcde4b0388c1770ce67" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Administration May Reshape Next Federal Climate Report: EPA Chief&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Environmental Protection Agency acting Administrator Andrew Wheeler said Wednesday that the Trump administration may step in to change the way the government drafts its next National Climate Assessment. The suggestion that politicians might influence a report from more 300 federal scientists at 13 agencies came at an event in Washington, where reporters pressed the agency chief on the authors’ dire projections about devastating climate change. Speaking at a Washington Post Live event, Wheeler accused former President Barack Obama of telling “the report’s authors to take a look at the worst-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Chevron granted waiver from U.S. biofuel laws at Utah plant - source - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biofuels-chevron-exclusive/exclusive-chevron-granted-waiver-from-u-s-biofuel-laws-at-utah-plant-source-idUSKCN1NP2E6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPHMQjFceqh39s57uaw2yFcqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:10:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biofuels-chevron-exclusive/exclusive-chevron-granted-waiver-from-u-s-biofuel-laws-at-utah-plant-source-idUSKCN1NP2E6" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Chevron granted waiver from U.S. biofuel laws at Utah plant - source&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency granted oil major Chevron Corp a 2017 hardship waiver from U.S. biofuel laws for its Utah refinery earlier this year, according to a source familiar with the company's operations. Chevron, which reported a net income of $9.2 billion in 2017, becomes the largest known company to be awarded a hardship waiver from the Renewable Fuel Standard (RFS), which requires refiners to blend biofuels like ethanol into their fuel pool or buy compliance credits from competitors that do. The waivers, which have grown significantly under the Trump administration, have...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>EPA Office: Pruitt's Resignation Left Ethics Probes Inconclusive - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/epa-office-pruitt-s-resignation-left-ethics-probes-inconclusive-/4682385.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBC9w_1Bc5ZTwYIR6F6wu4sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 02:12:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/epa-office-pruitt-s-resignation-left-ethics-probes-inconclusive-/4682385.html" target="_blank"&gt;EPA Office: Pruitt's Resignation Left Ethics Probes Inconclusive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The internal watchdog at the Environmental Protection Agency has closed two probes into the conduct of former Administrator Scott Pruitt as inconclusive because investigators were unable to interview him before he resigned. EPA Acting Inspector General Charles Sheehan said in a report sent to Congress this week that Pruitt's departure left his investigators unable to complete reviews into Pruitt's bargain-rate rental of Capitol Hill condo from the wife of an industry lobbyist and efforts by Pruitt's government staff to pursue business opportunities for his wife, including seeking a Chick-fi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: EPA refinery biofuel waiver program on hold pending review - sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biofuels-waivers-exclusive/exclusive-epa-refinery-biofuel-waiver-program-on-hold-pending-review-sources-idUSKCN1NX1D9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKWtRsRjmB7k276oSLwTElEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:41:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biofuels-waivers-exclusive/exclusive-epa-refinery-biofuel-waiver-program-on-hold-pending-review-sources-idUSKCN1NX1D9" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: EPA refinery biofuel waiver program on hold pending review - sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump Administration has temporarily frozen a program meant to exempt small oil refineries in financial distress from the U.S. biofuels law, as it reviews the scoring system to evaluate applications, according to two sources familiar with the matter. The review means changes are likely to the program, which has become a lightning rod of controversy between the rival oil and corn industries since the Environmental Protection Agency vastly increased the number of waivers for last year. Under the U.S. Renewable Fuel Standard, oil refiners must increasingly blend biofuels like corn-based et...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>EPA Watchdog Closes 2 Of The Many Probes Into Former Chief Scott Pruitt - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/scott-pruitt-epa-investigations-closed_us_5c00c322e4b0d04f48b29eb3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMW9kOT-C6UGxkjFFwqNfikqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 05:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/scott-pruitt-epa-investigations-closed_us_5c00c322e4b0d04f48b29eb3" target="_blank"&gt;EPA Watchdog Closes 2 Of The Many Probes Into Former Chief Scott Pruitt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Environmental Protection Agency’s inspector general’s office has closed two of its investigations into former Administrator Scott Pruitt, saying it couldn’t complete them because he resigned before he was able to talk to investigators. In a report to Congress on Thursday, the EPA’s watchdog said it wasn’t able to finish investigations into a sweetheart condo rental deal Pruitt made with a lobbyist or another probe into whether he abused his position and mismanaged members of his staff. “Mr. Pruitt resigned prior to being interviewed by investigators. For that reason, the OIG deemed that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Fox disciplines employees who set up Trump aide appearance - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/3a255b3a63e14309b7fb3c2a17e4dd86</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECyZr32ov_vOh0aHlmLDGCoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 02:37:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/3a255b3a63e14309b7fb3c2a17e4dd86" target="_blank"&gt;Fox disciplines employees who set up Trump aide appearance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fox News Channel said Tuesday that it is disciplining employees involved in an email exchange with an aide to President Trump's former EPA administrator Scott Pruitt to craft a "Fox &amp; Friends" interview with the environmental chief last year. The emails showed one of Pruitt's aides suggesting the interview, passing along "talking points" and given the chance by a Fox producer to approve a script written to introduce Pruitt. The messages were uncovered through a Freedom of Information Act request by the Sierra Club and first reported by The Daily Beast. It's another example o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>'Fox &amp; Friends' Fed Interview Questions To Trump's EPA Chief Scott Pruitt In Advance - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/fox-and-friends-scott-pruitt-questions_us_5bfd7404e4b0771fb6beb13b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGR9LikRU2jUF4KSa6gI7XgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 20:50:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/fox-and-friends-scott-pruitt-questions_us_5bfd7404e4b0771fb6beb13b" target="_blank"&gt;'Fox &amp; Friends' Fed Interview Questions To Trump's EPA Chief Scott Pruitt In Advance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Fox &amp; Friends,” a cable news show known for its friendly coverage of President Donald Trump’s administration, sent interview questions in advance to Scott Pruitt’s staffers on multiple occasions before the then-Environmental Protection Agency head appeared on the show. Pruitt’s team also approved topics of discussion and reviewed at least one script sent by “Fox &amp; Friends” producers ahead of Pruitt’s on-air interviews, according to emails first reported by The Daily Beast and obtained by HuffPost. As noted by The Daily Beast, cable news producers often discuss possible interview topics wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Pruitt escaped multiple EPA IG investigations by resigning, report says - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/politics/pruitt-epa-investigations/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN0l0kD-MfqCXEXwvFGUQusqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:32:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/politics/pruitt-epa-investigations/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pruitt escaped multiple EPA IG investigations by resigning, report says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Pruitt's resignation as Environmental Protection Agency administrator thwarted multiple investigations into his conduct in office, according to an inspector general report obtained by CNN. The investigations included: the "Administrator renting a room in a townhouse owned by a lobbyist's wife"; that Pruitt "had subordinates at the EPA assist him in finding personal housing; that he used his official position and EPA staff to seek a 'business opportunity' for his wife with Chick-fil-A, a fast-food restaurant chain; that he enlisted subordinates at the EPA to secure a mattress for his p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>‘Fox &amp; Friends’ Fed Interview Script to Trump’s EPA Chief, Emails Show - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fox-and-friends-fed-interview-script-to-trumps-epa-chief-emails-show</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECUc1hKeHmN-vPXdkbEA304qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMNCZmAI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 10:00:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/fox-and-friends-fed-interview-script-to-trumps-epa-chief-emails-show" target="_blank"&gt;‘Fox &amp; Friends’ Fed Interview Script to Trump’s EPA Chief, Emails Show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Environmental Protection Agency administrator Scott Pruitt was clearly taken aback last year when occasional Fox &amp; Friends fill-in host Ed Henry grilled him about a number of ethical scandals facing his administration. And Pruitt had a good reason to be surprised. In past interviews with President Trump’s favorite cable news show, the then-EPA chief’s team chose the topics for interviews, and knew the questions in advance. In one instance, according to emails revealed in a Freedom of Information Act request submitted by the Sierra Club and reviewed by The Daily Beast, Pruitt’s team e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Trump EPA Official Who Fought Coal Cleanup Arrested On Criminal Ethics Charges - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-epa-official-trey-glenn-ethics-charges_us_5bee4848e4b0510a1f2f53af</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMh72kOXkamtUl4_bTD8OV4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 09:11:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-epa-official-trey-glenn-ethics-charges_us_5bee4848e4b0510a1f2f53af" target="_blank"&gt;Trump EPA Official Who Fought Coal Cleanup Arrested On Criminal Ethics Charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Environmental Protection Agency official appointed by the Trump administration was arrested on Thursday for multiple criminal ethics violations. Onis Trey Glenn, 47, was charged with crimes reportedly linked to a scheme that took place when he worked as a lobbyist for the Drummond Company. At the time, Glenn helped the coal mining firm dodge a bill for an EPA-mandated cleanup of neighborhoods in Birmingham and Tarrant, Alabama, that were contaminated by emissions from smokestacks owned by a subsidiary, AL.com reported. Last year, Glenn became the Region 4 administrator of the EPA in char...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>For 10 years, a chemical not EPA approved was in their drinking water - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/11/health/denmark-sc-water-chemical-not-epa-approved/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELmd3AExUY6Mz8TkcO9oaHkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:11:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/11/health/denmark-sc-water-chemical-not-epa-approved/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;For 10 years, a chemical not EPA approved was in their drinking water&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For 10 years, some residents in Denmark, South Carolina, have been suspicious of the rust-colored water coming from their taps. They've been collecting samples in jars and using bottled or spring water, even though the local and state government assured them it was safe. But through a Freedom of Information Act request and a one-year investigation, CNN has found new information that may cast doubts on those assurances. The state government was adding a substance to one of the city's four wells, trying to regulate naturally occurring iron bacteria that can leave red stains or rust-like depos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump dismantling US climate efforts as warnings grow dire - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/ba2468b9739d41c489def4011d6199f3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANPM9v38q93E-cp4Oa6hfYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 23:54:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/ba2468b9739d41c489def4011d6199f3" target="_blank"&gt;Trump dismantling US climate efforts as warnings grow dire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has moved steadily to dismantle Obama administration efforts to rein in coal, oil and gas emissions, even as warnings grow — from his own administration and others — about the devastating impact of climate change on the U.S. economy as well as the Earth. Trump has dismissed his administration's warnings about the impact of climate change, including a forecast released Friday that it could lead to economic losses of hundreds of billions of dollars a year by the end of the century. "As to whether or not it's man-made and whether or not the effects that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump announces Wheeler as EPA nominee - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/politics/epa-andrew-wheeler/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELg4r-y_OlKNCzamQC7ecDIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 20:14:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/politics/epa-andrew-wheeler/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump announces Wheeler as EPA nominee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump announced Friday he plans to nominate the acting chief of the Environmental Protection Agency, Andrew Wheeler, to permanently lead the agency. Trump announced the move during a Medal of Freedom ceremony at the White House, where he introduced Wheeler along with other top administration officials in attendance. "Acting administrator -- who, I will tell you, is going to be made permanent," Trump said. "He's done a fantastic job. And I want to congratulate him. EPA, Andrew Wheeler." Wheeler took over the agency after Trump's first EPA administrator, former Oklahoma Attor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: EPA will not reallocate waived biofuel volumes to 2019 - official - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biofuels-exclusive/exclusive-epa-will-not-reallocate-waived-biofuel-volumes-to-2019-official-idUSKCN1NW221</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHHQYkAEimnfySKPqvbhbtQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 18:22:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biofuels-exclusive/exclusive-epa-will-not-reallocate-waived-biofuel-volumes-to-2019-official-idUSKCN1NW221" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: EPA will not reallocate waived biofuel volumes to 2019 - official&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) has rejected requests from the corn lobby to reallocate biofuel volumes waived under its small refinery exemption program into its 2019 mandate, an agency official told Reuters on Tuesday. The move is likely to infuriate the powerful corn lobby and top officials in the U.S. Department of Agriculture, who have complained for months that an expansion of the EPA's refinery waiver program under the Trump administration threatens demand for crucial farm products like corn-based ethanol. Under the U.S. Renewable Fuel Standard, oil refiners must blend...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump Says Will Name EPA's Acting Chief to Post Permanently - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-says-will-name-epa-s-acting-chief-to-post-permanently/4662209.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELZbP3N29jpyG6IMnRvCqkoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 21:23:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-says-will-name-epa-s-acting-chief-to-post-permanently/4662209.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Says Will Name EPA's Acting Chief to Post Permanently&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Wheeler, a former lobbyist who has led the Environmental Protection Agency since his scandal-plagued predecessor resigned earlier this year, got President Donald Trump's nod Friday for the permanent job. Trump made the announcement almost in passing at a White House ceremony for Presidential Medal of Freedom honorees. Singling out Cabinet members in the audience at the ceremony, Trump got to Wheeler, "acting administrator, who I will tell you is going to be made permanent." "He's done a fantastic job and I want to congratulate him, EPA, Andrew Wheeler. Where's Andrew?" Trump continue...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>This town is like thousands that are vulnerable to contaminated water, with no fix in sight - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/health/enterprise-louisiana-water/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO6u_zJ0O4BbZyFRFo4oYOQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:52:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/health/enterprise-louisiana-water/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;This town is like thousands that are vulnerable to contaminated water, with no fix in sight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Virginia Tech engineering Professor Marc Edwards watched as water flowed from a garden hose in Enterprise, Louisiana. As he moved a jar to catch a sample, the color changed from clear to brown. "When mine comes out, it comes out black," Enterprise resident John Tiser said as he watched Edwards work. Tiser, Enterprise's newly appointed water board president, was giving Edwards a tour around this rural community in central Louisiana, where residents have struggled with water problems. He says his wife drives 20 miles each direction to do laundry in a town with clear water. Concerned about the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>EPA official arrested on felony ethics charges in Alabama - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/09473e52d1c9438cb93d44af80800741</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEdkHatmNMi0-Mi9cU9csbsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 23:05:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/09473e52d1c9438cb93d44af80800741" target="_blank"&gt;EPA official arrested on felony ethics charges in Alabama&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration's top environmental official for the Southeast was arrested Thursday on criminal ethics charges in Alabama reported to be related to a scheme to help a coal company avoid paying for a costly toxic waste cleanup. Trey Glenn, 47, was briefly booked into a county jail in Birmingham before being released on a $30,000 bond. Glenn was appointed in August 2017 to serve as chief of the Environmental Protection Agency's regional office in Atlanta, which oversees operations in eight states stretching from the Carolinas to Mississippi. A grand jury indicted G...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump says will make acting EPA head Wheeler permanent - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-epa/trump-says-will-make-acting-epa-head-wheeler-permanent-idUSKCN1NL2CL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBeLukXA-lOglnH1GxQbEKsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:40:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-epa/trump-says-will-make-acting-epa-head-wheeler-permanent-idUSKCN1NL2CL" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says will make acting EPA head Wheeler permanent&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he would nominate the acting head of the Environmental Protection Agency, Andrew Wheeler, to take on the position permanently. Wheeler, a long-time Washington insider known to shun the spotlight, took the reins at the EPA in July after former Administrator Scott Pruitt resigned. Pruitt faced a slew of ethics controversies that included his first-class travel, round-the-clock security detail, and expensive office equipment. Wheeler has done a "fantastic job, and I want to congratulate him," Trump said as he announced his decision during a Medal of F...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump says will name EPA's acting chief to post permanently - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/c5e63d08a3d24190bf4cc00be21ba2fd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP87qKgjAEHeOC_2rtcx1aYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 01:59:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/c5e63d08a3d24190bf4cc00be21ba2fd" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says will name EPA's acting chief to post permanently&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Andrew Wheeler, a former congressional aide and lobbyist who has led the Environmental Protection Agency since his scandal-plagued predecessor resigned earlier this year, got President Donald Trump's nod Friday for the permanent job. Wheeler's promotion from acting to permanent EPA chief would keep him as a methodical and effective agent in Trump's mission of rolling back environmental regulations that the administration regards as burdensome to business. Environmental groups quickly voiced their opposition. Trump announced his plans for Wheeler almost in passing Friday at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Air Pollution Is Killing Kids, But Trump's EPA Doesn't Seem To Care - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-epa-pollution-health_us_5bf41da3e4b01909c809a8f5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMtQAlKlOB5fAW9dywC-jckqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMIiW7QU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-epa-pollution-health_us_5bf41da3e4b01909c809a8f5" target="_blank"&gt;Air Pollution Is Killing Kids, But Trump's EPA Doesn't Seem To Care&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a fourth-year medical student and future family medicine provider, I have a moral obligation ― as does any doctor ― to keep my current and future patients healthy and thriving. It’s for that reason I must speak out against acting Environmental Protection Agency Administrator Andrew Wheeler’s pending proposal, misleadingly named the “Affordable Clean Energy Rule,” to dismantle the Obama-era 2015 Clean Power Plan, which set the first and only federal limits on carbon pollution from power plants. I’ve seen firsthand how air pollution harms our communities’ most vulnerable populations. Durin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Dozens plead with Trump administration to keep air rules - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/74220483f16a43a7a817a64228036f4f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM7qSI8FF48mJkWpLVrg3DsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:11:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/74220483f16a43a7a817a64228036f4f" target="_blank"&gt;Dozens plead with Trump administration to keep air rules&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DENVER (AP) — Dozens of people who live near oil and gas wells pleaded with the Trump administration Wednesday not to roll back rules for methane pollution, while industry representatives said the changes should go further. The Environmental Protection Agency held a hearing in Denver on the administration's plans to loosen regulations imposed by the Obama administration in 2016. The rules require energy companies to step up the detection and elimination of methane leaks at well sites and other oil and gas facilities. Methane is the primary component of natural gas and also is a greenhouse g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump Says He'll Nominate Andrew Wheeler As Permanent EPA Administrator - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andrew-wheeler-administrator-epa_us_5bef223be4b0b84243e24db0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAGNxG6LgvdXIUPPLmD2KQ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 20:12:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andrew-wheeler-administrator-epa_us_5bef223be4b0b84243e24db0" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Says He'll Nominate Andrew Wheeler As Permanent EPA Administrator&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump said Friday he plans to nominate Andrew Wheeler to be the administrator of the Environmental Protection Agency, installing the former coal lobbyist permanently in a position he’s filled in an acting role since July. Speaking at a Presidential Medal of Freedom ceremony at the White House, Trump said: “Acting administrator, who I tell you is going to be made permanent, he’s done a fantastic job and I want to congratulate him.” Wheeler, who took over four months ago when scandal-plagued former Administrator Scott Pruitt resigned in disgrace, told The New York Times he “w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Acting EPA administrator says administration deserves credit for decline in carbon emissions in wake of climate report - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/politics/epa-administrator-climate-report/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChINm-FVt1aHNsbeEkAlb0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:59:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/politics/epa-administrator-climate-report/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Acting EPA administrator says administration deserves credit for decline in carbon emissions in wake of climate report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Environmental Protection Agency chief Andrew Wheeler did not voice alarm Wednesday about the dire predictions in the government's recent climate report, and instead said the Trump administration deserves credit for a decline in carbon emissions in his first remarks since the government released a devastating report Friday on the growing impacts of climate change. "In the first year of the Trump administration, we've seen a 2.7% reduction in CO2 from 2016 to 2017," Wheeler told an audience at a Washington Post event. The Fourth National Climate Assessment, released by the administration the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>California recommends restrictions for popular pesticide - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/5685ee8ac21644959425f3080dbe4617</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJY_HvaDyiwNbf0Xs4DF35YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 23:04:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/5685ee8ac21644959425f3080dbe4617" target="_blank"&gt;California recommends restrictions for popular pesticide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — California regulators recommended new restrictions Thursday on a widely used pesticide blamed for harming the brains of babies. The Department of Pesticide Regulation issued temporary guidelines for chlorpyrifos that include banning it from crop dusting, discontinuing its use on most crops and increasing perimeters around where it's applied. The DowDuPont pesticide currently used on about 60 different crops — including grapes, almonds and oranges — has increasingly come under fire from regulators, lawmakers and courts. A federal appeals court in August ordered the U.S. En...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump’s EPA Moves To Toughen Rules On Big-Rig Truck Pollution, Surprising Critics - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-epa-trucking-pollution-regulation_us_5beb25b6e4b0caeec2bec981</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENuAiQybqgmVyhk9iXH5X-sqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 20:01:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-epa-trucking-pollution-regulation_us_5beb25b6e4b0caeec2bec981" target="_blank"&gt;Trump’s EPA Moves To Toughen Rules On Big-Rig Truck Pollution, Surprising Critics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Environmental Protection Agency announced a new effort to slash pollution from heavy-duty trucks, surprising critics who say the move is the Trump administration’s first to increase regulations on emitters. Flanked by the heads of trucking industry associations, Acting EPA Administrator Andrew Wheeler said the push, dubbed the “Clean Trucks Initiative,” will include a rule to toughen standards on nitrogen oxides, the emissions that cause asthma-triggering smog. “We are under no regulatory or court-ordered requirements to launch this initiative,” Wheeler said on an embargoed call with re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Draft EPA study finds newer nonstick compound may be harmful - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/fd5a769eb0324980a94580814581a373</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGOlMMYWpupzlup6bjJ-jAgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 23:31:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/fd5a769eb0324980a94580814581a373" target="_blank"&gt;Draft EPA study finds newer nonstick compound may be harmful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Long-term exposure to a chemical compound currently used for making nonstick coatings appears to be dangerous, even in minute amounts, according to draft findings released Wednesday by the Environmental Protection Agency. It was the first time EPA weighed in on newer, supposedly safer versions of an increasingly scrutinized family of stick- and stain-resistant compounds. Older versions of the compound are turning up in dangerous levels in drinking water supplies around the country. Drinking water contamination has been the main concern cited by public health officials and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>EPA seeks new truck pollution rules; says air won't suffer - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f41e49c0c5e24ba183bfc477c9cc64c2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAlQErVE7Thivmr6qwZDiugqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 20:02:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f41e49c0c5e24ba183bfc477c9cc64c2" target="_blank"&gt;EPA seeks new truck pollution rules; says air won't suffer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DETROIT (AP) — The Trump administration's Environmental Protection Agency is proposing to rewrite rules that limit pollution from heavy trucks but that the EPA says slow the economy. Acting EPA Administrator Andrew Wheeler argues that new technology can help improve air quality, noting that the regulation of harmful nitrogen oxide emissions hasn't been revamped since 2000. EPA officials were to announce the plans Tuesday but offered few details and said they were just beginning a regulatory process that can take years. "We are doing it because it's good for the environment," said Wheeler, w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Inside the Shady PR Firm That Attacked George Soros to Help Facebook - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-shady-pr-firm-that-attacked-george-soros-to-help-facebook</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQo5Y9XwlBMsA33DpborlwqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMI6imAI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 03:56:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-shady-pr-firm-that-attacked-george-soros-to-help-facebook" target="_blank"&gt;Inside the Shady PR Firm That Attacked George Soros to Help Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast Definers Public Affairs, the Washington, D.C., opposition research agency that Facebook used against its critics, isn’t exactly a household name. But you might well have already seen the firm’s work without knowing it. You may have encountered a Facebook ad from Power the Future, a self-described “group of patriotic, fed-up Americans” brought together by a shared love of fossil fuels and mutual disdain for “the un-american environmental movement.” If you live in Oregon, you may have seen the TV ad from a mysterious nonprofit called Pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Smoke And Ash Endanger Western Residents Far From Camp And Woolsey Fires - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiegold/2018/11/12/smoke-and-ash-endanger-western-residents-far-from-camp-and-woolsey-fires/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjWwUh62oDnnGN0z5DfyIgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 21:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiegold/2018/11/12/smoke-and-ash-endanger-western-residents-far-from-camp-and-woolsey-fires/" target="_blank"&gt;Smoke And Ash Endanger Western Residents Far From Camp And Woolsey Fires&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wildfires burning in California right now are taking a tremendous toll on locals’ lives, homes, business and communities. They are also creating issues for people who live outside the evacuation zones. Residents hundreds of miles away are seeing their air quality deteriorate with smoke and ash from the distant blazes. The Environmental Protection Agency’s current Air Quality Index (at 1:30 PM on Monday afternoon, November 12, 2018) shows 21 California cities with unhealthy AQI levels and two Arizona counties already listed on the five unhealthiest areas list. The Woolsey and Camp fires ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Trump climate plan will break law by worsening pollution, states say - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/oct/31/epa-trump-pollution-clean-power-plan-states</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKcGxbeNdsLnwSHPQLzT48AqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 22:01:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/oct/31/epa-trump-pollution-clean-power-plan-states" target="_blank"&gt;Trump climate plan will break law by worsening pollution, states say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Environmentally minded US states say the Trump administration’s biggest climate change rollback could increase pollution, violating federal law, according to a preview of how they will fight the federal government. The Environmental Protection Agency is moving to replace Barack Obama’s clean power plan, a rule that would have hastened the US shift away from electricity produced from burning coal. Related: Climate change: local efforts won't be enough to undo Trump's inaction, study says Not only does burning coal warm the planet, it is also causes a range of health problems, from asthma to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Families take step toward suing EPA for toxic paint stripper - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/50b89452b6d148f5b18715777d2bedc6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEALCRR3P5h72OCgkhTiGN5wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 21:00:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/50b89452b6d148f5b18715777d2bedc6" target="_blank"&gt;Families take step toward suing EPA for toxic paint stripper&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The mothers of two men killed by a toxic paint stripper took a step toward suing the Environmental Protection Agency on Wednesday for failing to take quick action to remove the product from the market. The EPA had pledged in May, after then-Administrator Scott Pruitt met with families of two victims, to wrap up action "shortly" on proposed Obama-era regulations that would eliminate most allowable uses of the paint-stripping solvent methylene chloride. The agency disclosed earlier this month that it is now weighing rules that would allow a particular use of the solvent, in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>EPA quietly telling states they can pollute more - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/31/politics/epa-air-pollution/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGianSztRxDZU8hlk1rte28qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 19:39:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/31/politics/epa-air-pollution/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;EPA quietly telling states they can pollute more&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Environmental Protection Agency has quietly signaled it may allow states to release more ozone air pollution, commonly known as smog, dirtying the air in those states and neighboring ones, but the agency did not review the health impact of such a move. The Trump administration's position is outlined in a highly technical guidance memo about plans states must create and submit for EPA approval under the Clean Air Act's good neighbor requirements. It was sent in August to EPA regional offices and posted on the agency's website, but not announced to the public. The memo introduces the idea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump Carbon Plan Attacked by Coastal States, Lauded by Coal Interests - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-carbon-plan-attacked-by-coastal-states-lauded-by-coal-interests-/4637508.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELbOTIHqZbX2DfrN69_6qP0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 22:47:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-carbon-plan-attacked-by-coastal-states-lauded-by-coal-interests-/4637508.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Carbon Plan Attacked by Coastal States, Lauded by Coal Interests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump's proposal to replace an Obama-era policy to fight climate change with a weaker plan allowing states to write their own rules on emissions from coal-fired power plants was criticized by coastal states, but applauded by coal interests on Wednesday. Under the proposed Affordable Clean Energy plan that acting Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) chief Andrew Wheeler issued in August, the federal government would set carbon emission guidelines, but states would have the leeway to set less stringent standards on coal plants, taking into account the age and upgrade costs o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Owner of massive Victorian tyre dump ordered to pay $4.5m cleaning bill - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-30/supreme-court-fines-stawell-tyre-stockpile-owner-millions/10447610</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOdlY3izVFB1SwMcEHBnOtwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 07:12:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-30/supreme-court-fines-stawell-tyre-stockpile-owner-millions/10447610" target="_blank"&gt;Owner of massive Victorian tyre dump ordered to pay $4.5m cleaning bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jessica Black and Bridget Rollason The owners of a tyre dump in western Victoria have been ordered to pay more than $4.5 million to the state's environment watchdog. The Supreme Court ordered the Internet Marketing Solutions Corp (IMSC) to foot the bill of the mammoth clean up undertaken by the Environment Protect Authority (EPA), which removed about 1 million tyres from the Stawell stockpile. The Court has also put an injunction on the Panama-based company selling the site. The EPA took over the site in August last year after the owners failed to comply with multiple orders from the wat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>To protect our health -- and the planet's -- vote green - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/30/opinions/midterm-election-vote-green-mikulka/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA1IT2zEPVNULD_sgWesEZgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 18:52:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/30/opinions/midterm-election-vote-green-mikulka/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;To protect our health -- and the planet's -- vote green&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Mikulka is president of the American Federation of Government Employees Local 704, representing workers in the Environmental Protection Agency's Region 5, and spokesman for the Save the US EPA Campaign, an effort to have a fully staffed and fully funded EPA protect public health and environment. The views expressed in this commentary are his own. View more opinion on CNN. With one week until the 2018 midterms, will voters hold candidates who ignore protecting public health and the planet accountable? They certainly should since the risks could not be greater. Several weeks ago, an a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Justice Kavanaugh, the Federalists and a patient approach to reform - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/643447c4-7df1-33c4-a775-add07e6c73a4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMxCMxCUm45t6MNIebCBquEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/643447c4-7df1-33c4-a775-add07e6c73a4" target="_blank"&gt;Justice Kavanaugh, the Federalists and a patient approach to reform&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of what Donald Trump has done can be undone by the next US president or by the courts. His lifetime appointments for federal judges, however, are nearly impossible to revoke. As Mr Trump said last year: “The judge story is an untold story. Nobody wants to talk about it. But when you think about it . . . that has consequences 40 years out, depending on the age of the judge.” Actually, a lot of people do want to talk about judicial appointments, as we saw in the circus around the confirmation hearing for Brett Kavanaugh, the new Supreme Court judge. Mr Trump’s observation was right, thou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Department Of Transportation's Deregulatory Actions Begin To Bear Fruit - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ikebrannon/2018/10/31/department-of-transportations-deregulatory-actions-begin-to-bear-fruit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIJhULhof3-gqAVDJvaQUN8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 19:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ikebrannon/2018/10/31/department-of-transportations-deregulatory-actions-begin-to-bear-fruit/" target="_blank"&gt;Department Of Transportation's Deregulatory Actions Begin To Bear Fruit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the signature facets of the Trump Administration’s deregulatory agenda is its edict that an agency must abolish two existing rules in order to enact one new rule. That provision has allowed the Office of Information and Regulatory Affairs–the office within the Office of Management and Budget tasked with reviewing the agencies’ regulatory actions–to push back on questionable agency rulemaking in a way that was impossible during the previous administration, when the White House encouraged agencies to pursue an expansive rulemaking agenda, and felt no compunction to rein them in. The ag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How Deep Is Oil And Gas Industry Commitment To Cut Methane Leaks? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andystone/2018/10/31/how-deep-is-oil-and-gas-industry-commitment-to-cut-methane-leaks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHxn32NBnCstQRyv1JtVQl0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andystone/2018/10/31/how-deep-is-oil-and-gas-industry-commitment-to-cut-methane-leaks/" target="_blank"&gt;How Deep Is Oil And Gas Industry Commitment To Cut Methane Leaks?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vent valve in a natural gas storage facility. (Source: Getty Royalty Free) Social cost of carbon is one of the most challenging concepts to wrap one’s head around when talking about climate change. SCC, for short, is inherently nebulous, an effort to assign a current dollar value to the damage that a warming climate will bring to everything from coastal infrastructure to agricultural land and, ultimately, to human wellbeing. Most damages will occur well into the future, which makes their precise value impossible to pinpoint. And, while we know that there will be victims of climate change, w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sources: Justice Department investigating Interior Secretary Ryan Zinke - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/30/politics/zinke-justice-department/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGUHMt5OJyLX4Js3L8WZ9KYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 05:09:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/30/politics/zinke-justice-department/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sources: Justice Department investigating Interior Secretary Ryan Zinke&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Justice Department is investigating Interior Secretary Ryan Zinke for possibly using his office for personal gain, following a referral from Interior's inspector general, two sources familiar with the investigation say. The full extent of the inquiry is unclear. Zinke has faced multiple ethics questions during his time at Interior, and the inspector general's office has multiple public inquiries into the secretary including the department's handling of a Connecticut casino project, whether the boundaries for Grand Staircase Escalante National Monument were redrawn to benefit a state law...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Tricks or Treats? Here Are Washington's 174 Biggest Rules And Regulations In The Pipeline - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/waynecrews/2018/10/30/tricks-or-treats-here-are-washingtons-174-biggest-rules-and-regulations-in-the-pipeline/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJfMhXgwnkN3OxoN5vo6jMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 19:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/waynecrews/2018/10/30/tricks-or-treats-here-are-washingtons-174-biggest-rules-and-regulations-in-the-pipeline/" target="_blank"&gt;Tricks or Treats? Here Are Washington's 174 Biggest Rules And Regulations In The Pipeline&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The White House Office of Management and Budget (OMB) recently reported on which “significant regulatory actions” were added and subtracted in fulfillment of President Trump’s one-in, two-out requirement. President Trump held a session at the White House marking the occasion. U.S. President Donald Trump, right, speaks while meeting with workers in the Oval Office of the White House during a “Cutting the Red Tape, Unleashing Economic Freedom” event in Washington, D.C, U.S., on Wednesday, Oct. 17, 2018. Photographer: Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg The administration got rid of four significant regul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>EPA's Return To Rigorous Cost-Benefit Analysis Continues With Impending Methane-Rule Revision - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/wlf/2018/10/25/epas-return-to-rigorous-cost-benefit-analysis-continues-with-impending-methane-rule-revision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECkP_muy9bdRzavUmy2n1toqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/wlf/2018/10/25/epas-return-to-rigorous-cost-benefit-analysis-continues-with-impending-methane-rule-revision/" target="_blank"&gt;EPA's Return To Rigorous Cost-Benefit Analysis Continues With Impending Methane-Rule Revision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Office of Management and Budget Director Mick Mulvaney testifies before a House Appropriations Committee hearing on Capitol Hill in Washington, Wednesday, April 18, 2018. (AP Photo/Manuel Balce Ceneta) The Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) is set to propose changes to the regulation of mercury emissions that can recalibrate the balance between the costs of such controls and the benefits they confer. This action would be consistent with other administrative agency moves, which we have discussed recently here, to elevate the level and quality of economic analysis that past and future regu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Emails Show ‘Cozy’ Ties Between EPA’s Air Office And Its Chief's Former Firm - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bill-wehrum-epa-lobbying-hunton_us_5bcdeb2ee4b055bc9483285f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC46O2ze578AYa5XsYinJmAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 09:45:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bill-wehrum-epa-lobbying-hunton_us_5bcdeb2ee4b055bc9483285f" target="_blank"&gt;Emails Show ‘Cozy’ Ties Between EPA’s Air Office And Its Chief's Former Firm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A trove of emails obtained by HuffPost sheds light on the ongoing relationship between the Environmental Protection Agency’s air quality chief, Bill Wehrum, and people at his former law and lobbying firm. This latest instance of Trump appointees communicating with previous employers highlights the extent to which corporate interests have gained access to crucial government decision-makers and raises questions about the usefulness of President Donald Trump’s ethics rules. Since he became assistant administrator of the EPA’s Office of Air and Radiation last November, Wehrum has been criticize...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>States Shift Focus To Pollution Victims As Trump Nears 2 Major Climate Rollbacks - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pollution-victims-trump-climate-change_us_5bd09940e4b0d38b587f08b7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAW5QPqGq1PlF61T73ekfJgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 21:23:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pollution-victims-trump-climate-change_us_5bd09940e4b0d38b587f08b7" target="_blank"&gt;States Shift Focus To Pollution Victims As Trump Nears 2 Major Climate Rollbacks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bloc of states opposed to the Trump administration’s rollback of two major federal rules designed to cut climate-changing emissions are ramping up their ongoing challenge to the deregulatory effort ― and spotlighting the victims of increased pollution. On a call with reporters Wednesday afternoon, California Attorney General Xavier Becerra and Illinois Attorney General Lisa Madigan said the group of 19 states would file a joint comment opposed to the White House’s proposed rule to weaken fuel economy standards. The Trump administration’s plan would clear the way for vehicles to spew an ad...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Senator pressures EPA over official's industry ties, meetings - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/politics/senator-pressures-epa-over-officials-industry-ties-meetings/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB38icijV8ziHFq2m_4X8dwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 15:59:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/politics/senator-pressures-epa-over-officials-industry-ties-meetings/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senator pressures EPA over official's industry ties, meetings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key Democrat on the Senate environment committee has fired off two letters over concerns of a violation of President Donald Trump's ethics agreement and conflict of interest at the Environmental Protection Agency. Sen. Sheldon Whitehouse, D-Rhode Island, is raising concerns about the EPA's assistant administrator for the Office of Air and Radiation, Bill Wehrum, who before joining the agency worked as an attorney representing the oil, gas and coal industries. He was confirmed by the Senate in November 2017 and oversees the EPA office responsible for developing policies and regulations for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>GM proposes nationwide zero-emissions vehicle sales mandate - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/58779f0bd6da485ea1a67675c05782d8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGNCz_r5XHIbUlUFDRU8QmEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 01:25:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/58779f0bd6da485ea1a67675c05782d8" target="_blank"&gt;GM proposes nationwide zero-emissions vehicle sales mandate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DETROIT (AP) — General Motors says it will ask the federal government for one national gas mileage standard, including a requirement that a percentage of auto companies' sales be zero-emissions vehicles. Mark Reuss, GM's executive vice president of product development, said the company will propose that a certain percentage of nationwide sales be made up of vehicles that run on electricity or hydrogen fuel cells. "A national zero emissions program will drive the scale and infrastructure investments needed to allow the U.S. to lead the way to a zero emissions future," Reuss said. GM, the nat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>EPA ices plan to limit how many health-related studies can be considered in forming regulations - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/17/politics/epa-scientific-transparency/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbOJDhhUuQaFAB-YI6Yu_QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 23:23:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/17/politics/epa-scientific-transparency/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;EPA ices plan to limit how many health-related studies can be considered in forming regulations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Environmental Protection Agency has put on ice a proposal that would limit the number of health-related studies the agency can consider when drafting regulations -- a rule critics worried would loosen health protections in agency policies. The proposal was championed by then-Administrator Scott Pruitt, who lost his job amid a lengthy list of ethics investigations. The current acting administrator, Scott Wheeler, has sounded less enthusiastic about it. The Strengthening Transparency in Regulatory Science rule would block the agency from considering scientific studies where the underlying...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>U.S. environmental agency says in talks with Volvo over emissions issue - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-volvo-emissions-regulator/u-s-environmental-agency-says-in-talks-with-volvo-over-emissions-issue-idUSKCN1MR2ED</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB01qRzrV2QMamSbsQPN5dMqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 20:48:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-volvo-emissions-regulator/u-s-environmental-agency-says-in-talks-with-volvo-over-emissions-issue-idUSKCN1MR2ED" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. environmental agency says in talks with Volvo over emissions issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency said on Wednesday it has been in talks with Volvo over the last few weeks about an issue with catalytic converters causing some of its vehicles to exceed nitrogen oxide emission limits. Volvo warned a day earlier that some of its truck and bus engines could be exceeding limits for nitrogen oxide emissions due to an emissions control component it uses degrading more quickly than expected. The Swedish truckmaker said it could face material costs to deal with the issue largely affecting trucks and buses sold in North America and Europe, its two largest ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>EPA Signals Andrew Wheeler Could Stay In Place Until 2020 Without Senate Confirmation - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andrew-wheeler-epa-acting-administrator_us_5bc76f92e4b0a8f17ee8b2a9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOVWUfbPdD4S6gn2ZCkghhIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 18:36:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/andrew-wheeler-epa-acting-administrator_us_5bc76f92e4b0a8f17ee8b2a9" target="_blank"&gt;EPA Signals Andrew Wheeler Could Stay In Place Until 2020 Without Senate Confirmation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Andrew Wheeler hit his 100th day at the top of the Environmental Protection Agency this week, the press office put out what seemed to be two humdrum updates on the trip “Administrator Wheeler” took to Louisiana. But the press releases’ subject lines contained a small, almost unnoticeable tweak with significant implications: He still hasn’t been nominated or confirmed to serve as the agency’s permanent chief. He’s not the EPA administrator; he’s the acting EPA administrator. The agency had been noting the distinction ― until this week. The change could easily be chalked up to a mistake ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Dozens more breakfast foods test positive for trace amounts of weed killer, report says - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/health/breakfast-cereal-food-weed-killer-roundup/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDROTmZ98Wx6w1ee02_KMlYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 17:05:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/health/breakfast-cereal-food-weed-killer-roundup/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dozens more breakfast foods test positive for trace amounts of weed killer, report says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dozens of common breakfast cereals and snack bars have trace amounts of a controversial herbicide found in the weed killer Roundup, according to a report released today by an environmental advocacy group. The Environmental Working Group (EWG) found that 26 of the 28 products it tested had levels of Roundup's main ingredient, glyphosate, that were "higher than what EWG scientists consider protective of children's health." An earlier report found similar results in over thirty oat-based foods. Manufacturers say their products are safe, but the EWG report argues that the vast majority of foods...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>EPA puts off final say on science transparency rule - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/2c12602deb6c4beab3d84b024c96ac7d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDzoWldeO8VUZG-I4qd0wVUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgw3utQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 17:16:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/2c12602deb6c4beab3d84b024c96ac7d" target="_blank"&gt;EPA puts off final say on science transparency rule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Environmental Protection Agency said Wednesday it is putting off for at least a year any final announcement on a controversial proposal overhauling how the agency evaluates science. The agency's so-called transparency in regulatory science rule was one of the most contentious proposed by former EPA Administrator Scott Pruitt, who stepped down last summer amid ethics scandals. Trump replaced Pruitt with current acting administrator Andrew Wheeler, who like Pruitt describes himself as a champion of rolling back what they see as unnecessary and burdensome regulations. Sup...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item></channel></rss>