<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Oleg Deripaska - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRFJvYWpCakVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-ZA&amp;gl=ZA&amp;ceid=ZA:en</link><language>en-ZA</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:50:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Roman Abramovich on list of six Russian oligarchs targeted by UK intelligence over links to Putin - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/07/romanabramovich-list-six-russian-oligarchs-targeted-uk-intelligence/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcXZygrb7VUFLKSLoFDjcIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/07/romanabramovich-list-six-russian-oligarchs-targeted-uk-intelligence/" target="_blank"&gt;Roman Abramovich on list of six Russian oligarchs targeted by UK intelligence over links to Putin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roman Abramovich is among a group of Russian oligarchs to be targeted by British intelligence as part of a sustained campaign to disrupt Vladimir Putin, The Telegraph understands. A list of six wealthy high-profile Russians has been drawn up by intelligence agencies and submitted to Theresa May. The Prime Minister has approved the list and the names of the oligarchs will be circulated across Whitehall departments and shared with the UK’s allies in Europe and in North America in an attempt to disrupt their ability to travel and to maintain their business empires. It signals a ratcheting up o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Mueller: Paul Manafort lied about contacts with Trump administration this year - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/paul-manafort-robert-mueller-donald-trump/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAVKkIUW5OFYxOrKIpSCSREqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:53:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/paul-manafort-robert-mueller-donald-trump/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller: Paul Manafort lied about contacts with Trump administration this year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller said Friday that former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort lied about five major issues after agreeing to cooperate with prosecutors, including his "contact with administration officials." In a heavily redacted document, Mueller also said Manafort lied about his interactions with Konstantin Kilimnik. Mueller has said Kilimnik has ties to the Russian military intelligence unit accused of hacking the Democrats, and they've previously outlined how the two men may have worked together to tamper with witnesses following Manafort's arrest last year. The accusatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Menendez says U.S. sanctions on Russia's Deripaska should remain - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions/menendez-says-sanctions-on-russias-deripaska-should-remain-idUSKBN1O42DU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDB0mXiUN0IJ9X3EqLI2joUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:36:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions/menendez-says-sanctions-on-russias-deripaska-should-remain-idUSKBN1O42DU" target="_blank"&gt;Menendez says U.S. sanctions on Russia's Deripaska should remain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top Democrat on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee on Wednesday urged the Trump administration not to waive or remove sanctions on Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska or two companies he controls. In a letter to U.S. Treasury Secretary Steve Mnuchin, Senator Bob Menendez cited unspecified reports that Treasury was considering such a move and noted the department's own analysis says the oligarch is accused of crimes from blackmail to murder. "I see no reason to remove sanctions against Mr. Deripaska, and until he divests from and relinquishes control of Rusal and EN+, there is no justifi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Top Senate Democrat Warns Trump Not to Lift Sanctions Against Russian Billionaire - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/top-senate-democrat-warns-trump-not-to-lift-sanctions-against-russian-billionaire-/4688948.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAQDyn5dFE6mS-q77F0xwFMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:45:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/top-senate-democrat-warns-trump-not-to-lift-sanctions-against-russian-billionaire-/4688948.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top Senate Democrat Warns Trump Not to Lift Sanctions Against Russian Billionaire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key Democratic senator is warning the Trump administration not to lift sanctions against a Russian oligarch or the companies he controls. Oleg Deripaska holds large stakes in the Russian aluminum giant Rusal and the automobile conglomerate GAZ Group. FILE - Oleg Deripaska attends an agreement signing ceremony with the Krasnoyarsk region's government in Moscow, Russia, Dec. 12, 2017. New Jersey's Bob Menendez, the top Democrat on the Foreign Relations Committee, wrote in a letter to the Treasury Department that it would face strong opposition in Congress if it waives sanctions against Deri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Senator Rips Mnuchin for Backpedaling on Manafort-Linked Russia Sanctions - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/senator-rips-mnuchin-for-backpedaling-on-manafort-linked-russia-sanctions</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDNSiMa79kKPJizvrfDjS6AqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/senator-rips-mnuchin-for-backpedaling-on-manafort-linked-russia-sanctions" target="_blank"&gt;Senator Rips Mnuchin for Backpedaling on Manafort-Linked Russia Sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alex Wong/Getty The top Democrat on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee is blasting Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin for entertaining the idea of lifting sanctions on a Russian aluminum company with ties to former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort. In a letter sent Wednesday, Sen. Bob Menendez (D-NJ) urged Mnuchin to maintain the sanctions that were slapped on Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska in April, arguing that they are a necessary aspect of U.S. efforts to punish Russian President Vladimir Putin and his inner circle for Moscow’s interference in the 2016 election. “I welcomed thes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Menendez warns Treasury against lifting sanctions on Russian firms - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/menendez-treasury-russia-sanctions/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELzh9q3lUw4YgEMhZ-8hdqwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:38:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/menendez-treasury-russia-sanctions/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Menendez warns Treasury against lifting sanctions on Russian firms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A top Democratic senator on Wednesday urged the Trump administration not to lift sanctions on two Russian firms, including the world's second-largest aluminum maker, until Russian billionaire Oleg Deripaska fully divests his stake in both companies. "I see no reason to remove sanctions against Mr. Deripaska, and until he divests from and relinquishes control of RUSAL and EN+, there is no justification to remove the sanctions on those companies," New Jersey Sen. Bob Menendez, ranking member of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, wrote in a letter to Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin. In ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>British companies owned by Russian oligarchs to be investigated by US congress to examine links to intelligence agencies - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/british-companies-owned-russian-oligarchs-investigated-us-congress/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBJf13fneqj5Unl-9h6DHoAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:08:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/british-companies-owned-russian-oligarchs-investigated-us-congress/" target="_blank"&gt;British companies owned by Russian oligarchs to be investigated by US congress to examine links to intelligence agencies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US congressional investigators have launched an inquiry into possible links between British-based companies owned by Russian oligarchs and their relationship with Russia’s intelligence agencies. The move follows increasing concerns by U.S. congressmen over the extent of Russian meddling in both the U.S. and Europe, with a number of oligarchs with close ties to Russian President Vladimir Putin forming the main focus of the inquiry. Among the UK-based companies that have aroused the interest of congressional investigators is EN+, the energy company owned by Oleg Deripaska and chaired by Tory ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Chaos at conservative think tank after donor revealed as Russian ‘oligarch’ - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/chaos-at-conservative-think-tank-after-donor-revealed-as-russian-oligarch-2018-12-05</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOH7X4iGcrtdGJXaD9C5vjMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/chaos-at-conservative-think-tank-after-donor-revealed-as-russian-oligarch-2018-12-05" target="_blank"&gt;Chaos at conservative think tank after donor revealed as Russian ‘oligarch’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE NEW YORK POST By Jennifer Gould Keil Charles Davidson — the founder of the Hudson Institute’s Kleptocracy Initiative, a group dedicated to exposing threats by authoritarian regimes to U.S. democracy — has quit Warner Music Group owner Len Blavatnik and Emily Appelson attend the 60th Annual GRAMMY Awards at Madison Square Garden in January. Getty Images/FilmMagic Chaos has erupted at a conservative think tank after it was revealed that one of its new donors is Len Blavatnik, the Ukrainian-born billionaire who owns the Warner Music record label. Charles Davidson — the founder of the Hudso...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Sanctions-hit En+ proposes moving registered office to Kaliningrad - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-en-group-strategy/sanctions-hit-en-proposes-moving-registered-office-to-kaliningrad-idUSKCN1NZ1FJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPgtjoKtc5TA_u-RIoVC2nwqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:18:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-en-group-strategy/sanctions-hit-en-proposes-moving-registered-office-to-kaliningrad-idUSKCN1NZ1FJ" target="_blank"&gt;Sanctions-hit En+ proposes moving registered office to Kaliningrad&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia's En+ Group (ENPLq.L: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), hit by U.S. sanctions in April, has proposed to shareholders that it move its registered office to Russia's Kaliningrad region from Britain's Jersey. London-listed EN+, which is in talks with the United States to have sanctions against it eased, put forward the plan in a document prepared for a shareholder meeting on Dec. 20. The firm controlled by sanctioned billionaire Oleg Deripaska said the move could lead to a suspension or cancellation of the listing and trading of the company's global depository receipts (GDRs). "Whi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Russia's Potanin to appeal UK court decision in battle of billionaires - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-nornickel-rusal-court/russias-potanin-to-appeal-uk-court-decision-in-battle-of-billionaires-idUSKCN1NW1VQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDidhGKoBkKc9X_rBAOH7wAqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 17:06:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-nornickel-rusal-court/russias-potanin-to-appeal-uk-court-decision-in-battle-of-billionaires-idUSKCN1NW1VQ" target="_blank"&gt;Russia's Potanin to appeal UK court decision in battle of billionaires&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian businessman Vladimir Potanin plans to appeal a London court decision to block him from buying shares in mining company Norilsk Nickel (GMKN.MM: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) from fellow investor Roman Abramovich, representatives at Potanin's investment firm said on Tuesday. The ruling, taken in June, was considered to be advantageous for Russian tycoon Oleg Deripaska, who controls aluminum giant Rusal (0486.HK: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), and has long been at loggerheads with Potanin over control of Norilsk Nickel. He wanted to stop Abramovich, owner of England's ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Boycotting World Economic Forum in Davos no great loss for Russia – Putin - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/business/444066-russia-wef-davos-boycott/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFe6dWrjvhnutTfQKP-f0JUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwroQo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 13:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/business/444066-russia-wef-davos-boycott/" target="_blank"&gt;Boycotting World Economic Forum in Davos no great loss for Russia – Putin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin said Thursday that the refusal by Russian businesses to participate in next year’s World Economic Forum in Davos is not going to have any negative impact on the country’s reputation. “Reputation of any country that is a part of the global economy basically depends on its economic power, structure of its economy, as well as on the results it demonstrates from the point of view of GDP, technologies, macro-economic parameters,” said Putin, speaking at the Russia-ASEAN Summit in Singapore. Putin stressed that Russian businessmen are free to decide whether or not...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Medvedev: Russia Will Boycott Davos if Oligarchs Kept Out - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/medvedev-says-russia-will-boycott-davos-if-oligarchs-kept-out/4656431.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPkp1E_0b77-6nFcKo5WW4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 15:16:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/medvedev-says-russia-will-boycott-davos-if-oligarchs-kept-out/4656431.html" target="_blank"&gt;Medvedev: Russia Will Boycott Davos if Oligarchs Kept Out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian Prime Minister Dmitry Medvedev said on Tuesday that no delegation would go to the Davos World Economic Forum in January if top tycoons including Oleg Deripaska were kept out of the prestigious gathering. Several Russian oligarchs and allies of President Vladimir Putin have reportedly been asked to stay away from the World Economic Forum meet. "If all these decisions that have been taken in relation to Russian business representatives are not changed, then we will have to take a decision regarding the cancellation of participation in the Davos forum of state employees and Russian com...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>U.S. postpones sanctions deadline on Russian tycoon's firms - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions/u-s-extends-deadline-for-sanctioned-russian-firms-to-january-idUSKCN1NE2BO</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENkJg7TLfcp0o1KeJ5_h83IqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 22:23:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions/u-s-extends-deadline-for-sanctioned-russian-firms-to-january-idUSKCN1NE2BO" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. postpones sanctions deadline on Russian tycoon's firms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States on Friday said it was postponing the enforcement of sanctions on Russian companies EN+ , Rusal and Gaz PAO for nearly four weeks as their top shareholder works on a plan to cut his stakes. The U.S. Treasury Department had given Russian tycoon Oleg Deripaska until Dec. 12 to reduce his holdings in the three companies but said in a statement that the deadline had been moved to Jan. 7, 2019. “EN+, RUSAL, and GAZ are proposing substantial corporate governance changes that could potentially result in significant changes in control of these sanctioned entities," Treasury said in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Konstantin Kilimnik: elusive Russian with ties to Manafort faces fresh Mueller scrutiny - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/09/konstantin-kilimnik-russia-trump-manafort-mueller</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPHVnedB2POabdmdzC0d2MUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 06:00:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/09/konstantin-kilimnik-russia-trump-manafort-mueller" target="_blank"&gt;Konstantin Kilimnik: elusive Russian with ties to Manafort faces fresh Mueller scrutiny&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Russian man who is said to have ties to Moscow’s intelligence services will be receiving renewed scrutiny from special counsel Robert Mueller’s inquiry into Russian 2016 election interference, according to former federal prosecutors. Mueller is investigating Konstantin Kilimnik with assistance from three Kilimnik associates, including Donald Trump’s former campaign chairman Paul Manafort, who mentored Kilimnik as a political operative for pro-Kremlin figures in Ukraine. Related: What's next for the Trump-Russia inquiry now Sessions has been fired? Kilimnik, an elusive 48-year-old, has alr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Mueller Hones in on ‘Elusive’ Russian Mentored by Manafort, Says Report - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mueller-hones-in-on-elusive-russian-mentored-by-manafort-says-report</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsuLtC4wGa6-JnboFfJFPwqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 10:34:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/mueller-hones-in-on-elusive-russian-mentored-by-manafort-says-report" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller Hones in on ‘Elusive’ Russian Mentored by Manafort, Says Report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reuters / Rick Wilking, A Russian man mentored as a political operative by Paul Manafort is coming under renewed scrutiny from Special Counsel Robert Mueller's investigation into interference in the 2016 election, according to The Guardian. Konstantin Kilimnik, 48, is said to have ties to Moscow’s intelligence services and has already been charged by Mueller with witness tampering. But Mueller is reportedly digging deeper into Kilimnik's actions before the election with assistance from three Kilimnik associates forced to assist him as part of their plea deals: Manafort, his former deputy Ri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Kremlin says Davos undermines itself with Russian blacklisting - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e7ce4104-e273-11e8-a6e5-792428919cee</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBzlAeKNEDEsimrLsfjobBYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 10:08:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e7ce4104-e273-11e8-a6e5-792428919cee" target="_blank"&gt;Kremlin says Davos undermines itself with Russian blacklisting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Economic Forum’s decision to ban three sanctioned Russian businessmen from next January’s Davos conference undermines the entire event, the Kremlin has said, adding that such steps would likely see Russia reduce its delegation to the elite forum. As the FT reported on Tuesday, Russian aluminium magnate Oleg Deripaska, industrial tycoon Viktor Vekselberg and VTB Bank head Andrei Kostin have been informed by WEF that they will not be welcome at Davos despite there being no legal impediment to them travelling to Switzerland. “Mr Deripaska, Mr Kostin and Mr Vekselberg have achieved th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Cyprus Is The Real Loser In The US-Russian Economic War - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/antonisantoniou/2018/10/26/cyprus-is-the-real-loser-in-the-us-russian-economic-war/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECRmT_qI73qqnrHfX1BrLn4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/antonisantoniou/2018/10/26/cyprus-is-the-real-loser-in-the-us-russian-economic-war/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyprus Is The Real Loser In The US-Russian Economic War&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the economic war between the US and Russia is likely to intensify even further in the coming weeks, third parties with economic dependence on these two countries are engaging in a (death-defying) balancing act on a particularly thin tightrope. If their balancing act proves unsustainable, they might need to choose sides, but at what cost? Cyprus is an example of a third party that just might need to make that choice: collateral damage in a wider economic war to which it doesn’t directly belong. From Russia with love Traditionally, Cyprus – an EU member – has been heavily dependent on Russ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>U.S. extends deadline for investors to divest holdings in Russia's Gaz - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions/u-s-extends-deadline-for-investors-to-divest-holdings-in-russias-gaz-idUSKCN1MT2LZ?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=businessNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHW7TX-149D088JK0jcNPKsqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 18:18:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions/u-s-extends-deadline-for-investors-to-divest-holdings-in-russias-gaz-idUSKCN1MT2LZ?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=businessNews" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. extends deadline for investors to divest holdings in Russia's Gaz&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Treasury said on Friday it was extending a deadline for investors to divest certain operations, debt and equity of sanctioned Russian company Gaz Group (GAZA.MM: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) until Dec. 12. The U.S. Treasury Department imposed sanctions in April against billionaire Oleg Deripaska and eight companies in which he is a large shareholder, including automaker Gaz, citing "malign activities" by Russia. The deadline for investors to divest holdings in Gaz had been Oct. 23. Russian Deputy Prime Minister Dmitry Kozak said on Friday he had met with U.S. Ambassador to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Billionaire Roman Abramovich Still Aims To Build The Largest Single Family Home In Manhattan - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/amydobson/2018/10/17/billionaire-roman-abramovich-still-aims-to-build-the-largest-single-family-home-in-manhattan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAp7ymUx9Mn698ELgY93O2cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 13:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/amydobson/2018/10/17/billionaire-roman-abramovich-still-aims-to-build-the-largest-single-family-home-in-manhattan/" target="_blank"&gt;Billionaire Roman Abramovich Still Aims To Build The Largest Single Family Home In Manhattan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Renderings of the front and back of Abramovich’s plans. Click to expand. Roman Abramovich doesn’t let visa troubles or federal agents seizing assets of his associates deter him from investing in opulent real estate. The lavish plans for his six-story house that will consolidate three separate townhouses into a 31,500 square foot single-family home were obtained by the New York Post and revealed earlier this week. The combined size will make this the largest single residence in Manhattan. Starting as early as 2014 Abramovich, whose wealth is estimated at over $11 billion, started accumulati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>FBI 'freezes US assets' of Putin ally Oleg Deripaska - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/08/fbi-freezes-us-assets-putin-ally-oleg-deripaska/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN53-9SXyqSV_lLzkvmDcS8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 19:40:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/08/fbi-freezes-us-assets-putin-ally-oleg-deripaska/" target="_blank"&gt;FBI 'freezes US assets' of Putin ally Oleg Deripaska&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The FBI has reportedly frozen the US assets of Russian oligarch Oleg Desipaska in what is seen as a further tightening of the noose around the necks of President Vladimir Putin’s allies. Mr Deripaska, an industrialist worth an estimated $3.3 billion (£2.5bn) according to Forbes, was placed on a list of individuals sanctioned by the US treasury in April. Now Washington has frozen Mr Deripaska’s US-based assets, the New York Post reported, including massive mansions in Manhattan and Washington, DC. The paper claimed that officials are also negotiating with him to give up some of his European-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Oleg Deripaska: Russian Oligarch's U.S. Assets Frozen, Including NYC Mansion - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/oleg-deripaska-russian-oligarchs-us-assets-frozen-including-nyc-mansion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKqn5_IPfZgjabOCO2CSu4wqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 11:14:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/oleg-deripaska-russian-oligarchs-us-assets-frozen-including-nyc-mansion" target="_blank"&gt;Oleg Deripaska: Russian Oligarch's U.S. Assets Frozen, Including NYC Mansion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;REUTERS, The New York City mansion of Oleg Deripaska—the Russian oligarch very closely linked to Paul Manafort—has been frozen alongside all of his U.S. assets, according to the New York Post. U.S. officials say Deripaska, who made his billions in aluminum, is close with Vladimir Putin and is allegedly involved in murder, money-laundering, bribery and racketeering. His assets include a mansion at 11 East 64th St. but he has reportedly arranged to have the children and ex-wife of business partner and fellow oligarch Roman Abramovich live there in his place. Deripaska bought the East Side pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Corporate Russia feels insulated from sanctions - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/174ca9ac-cc5d-11e8-b276-b9069bde0956</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ65-uU3_cbDeFX2BxVu1kEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 03:00:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/174ca9ac-cc5d-11e8-b276-b9069bde0956" target="_blank"&gt;Corporate Russia feels insulated from sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who’s afraid of the big bad sanctions wolf? Not too many in Moscow, it seems. Six months after the imposition of the harshest-ever US sanctions against a group of Russian businessmen, potential targets of new penalties are exuding quiet confidence that the next set of curbs will not be crippling, and that much of their businesses are well defended from potential attack. Reshoring of assets, restructuring of holding companies and a pivot away from western finance and supply chains over the past few years mean Russian tycoons and major businesses believe they are better prepared for potential...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Putin backs ‘dedollarization’ plan - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/02c3ecc2-c62f-11e8-ba8f-ee390057b8c9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECE3OWJW2CSHN8KcpZa-MjgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 10:38:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/02c3ecc2-c62f-11e8-ba8f-ee390057b8c9" target="_blank"&gt;Putin backs ‘dedollarization’ plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian president Vladimir Putin has backed a tentative “dedollarization” plan to insulate the country from future US sanctions. Andrei Kostin, chief executive of Kremlin-owned bank VTB, told state newswire RIA Novosti on Tuesday that Mr Putin “generally” supported a plan he announced last month that would wean Russia off the dollar. The plan, which also has support from the finance ministry and central bank, is a response to sanctions the US Senate is weighing that would blacklist Russia’s state-owned lenders, including barring them from using dollars. Though the central bank said last mon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>US delays imposition of sanctions on Deripaska’s Rusal - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/71ca3200-be1b-11e8-8274-55b72926558f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBaNS0mhQ_eHaRPdS4O1d_0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 04:48:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/71ca3200-be1b-11e8-8274-55b72926558f" target="_blank"&gt;US delays imposition of sanctions on Deripaska’s Rusal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Treasury has extended a deadline for the full imposition of crippling sanctions against the aluminium empire of Oleg Deripaska, giving the Russian oligarch another three weeks to find a way to win a full reprieve. Washington in April announced it would impose sanctions on Mr Deripaska and his business empire, to prevent him and his companies from using the dollar and doing business with US citizens. Those measures threatened the future of Rusal, the world’s second largest aluminium producer. Late on Friday, the Treasury said it would delay to November 12 a deadline forcing investors ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Steven Mnuchin Accidentally Sanctioned Putin Oligarch Oleg Deripaska - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/steven-mnuchin-accidentally-sanctioned-putin-oligarch-oleg-deripaska</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEImWFVT6RqTEl9-YK-U8KtcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 08:51:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/steven-mnuchin-accidentally-sanctioned-putin-oligarch-oleg-deripaska" target="_blank"&gt;Steven Mnuchin Accidentally Sanctioned Putin Oligarch Oleg Deripaska&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast At a Capitol Hill hearing in January, as lawmakers were hounding him about the Trump administration’s slow implementation of mandatory sanctions against Russia, Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin was backed into a corner. And he blurted out something he would come to regret—by accident, The Daily Beast has learned. “There will be sanctions that come out of this report,” Mnuchin said—a surprise statement, because while Congress had ordered the department to create a report on Russian oligarchs, it didn’t require that any sanctions be im...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Paul Manafort's ties to Russia mean he may have been blackmailed by the Kremlin - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/paul-manafort-trial-guilty-plea-deal-blackmail-money-laundering-russia-us-election-kremlin-a8544396.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMOr-LCaNQyFGV-yQnQHvf0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/paul-manafort-trial-guilty-plea-deal-blackmail-money-laundering-russia-us-election-kremlin-a8544396.html" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Manafort's ties to Russia mean he may have been blackmailed by the Kremlin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump‘s defenders responded to the news of Paul Manafort‘s plea deal on Friday with the usual refrain: his case has nothing to do with the Trump campaign or allegations that it colluded with Russia in 2016. They are wrong. Why? Because they are overlooking the blackmail factor. Special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation has painstakingly documented evidence of Manafort’s role in a 10-year scheme involving money laundering, tax evasion and illicit lobbying – crimes that could lead to decades in a prison cell. Given Manafort’s extensive ties to Russian and Ukrainian oliga...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Rusal share price jumps after US sanctions concession - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4058829e-ba51-11e8-94b2-17176fbf93f5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKSnXqw02sqGLN80K2gGp4sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 16:59:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4058829e-ba51-11e8-94b2-17176fbf93f5" target="_blank"&gt;Rusal share price jumps after US sanctions concession&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Russian aluminium producer Rusal jumped as much as 17 per cent on Monday after the US Treasury said it would allow the company to negotiate some new contracts, easing fears over its future output and raising hopes for a longer-term reprieve from sanctions. Rusal, the world’s largest aluminium producer outside China and a critical supplier to the aerospace and automotive industries, was hit by sanctions in April. The embargo was part of sweeping restrictions imposed on its controlling shareholder, oligarch Oleg Deripaska, banning it from dealing with US citizens or using dollars. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Here's how Paul Manafort might be helpful to the Russia investigation - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/15/politics/paul-manafort-russia-investigation-mueller-probe-help-know/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIjTLZPpfSTHSiPu2cf8OwEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 17:21:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/15/politics/paul-manafort-russia-investigation-mueller-probe-help-know/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Here's how Paul Manafort might be helpful to the Russia investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Manafort has worn many hats: an international political operative, President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman, Trump confidant Roger Stone's business partner and now government witness. In a deal with the special counsel's office, Manafort pleaded guilty Friday to conspiring against the US for his undisclosed foreign lobbying work and agreed to cooperate with authorities. As part of the deal he will have to admit to any crimes he has knowledge of or has committed beyond the tax, financial and undisclosed foreign lobbying matters covered in his deal and he will be required to coo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Customers to shun Rusal at Berlin 'mating season' for 2019 aluminum deals - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-aluminium-contracts-exclusive/exclusive-customers-to-shun-rusal-at-berlin-mating-season-for-2019-aluminum-deals-idUSKCN1LM22U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKq3Q2v9YWMn95yZkP5B80QqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 15:00:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-aluminium-contracts-exclusive/exclusive-customers-to-shun-rusal-at-berlin-mating-season-for-2019-aluminum-deals-idUSKCN1LM22U" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Customers to shun Rusal at Berlin 'mating season' for 2019 aluminum deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;European customers will avoid deals with Russia's United Company Rusal, under U.S. sanctions, when the industry meets in Berlin next week to seal 2019 metal supply agreements, three sources familiar with the discussions said. Known in the industry as the "mating season" and taking place alongside a conference run by industry publication Metal Bulletin, negotiations typically agree quantities and premiums paid above the London Metal Exchange benchmark aluminum price. The aluminum market has so far been sanguine about the fallout from Rusal being placed under sanctions on expectations they wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Former British intelligence officer 'helped effort to flip Russian oligarch against Trump campaign' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/02/former-british-intelligence-officer-helped-effort-flip-russian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4u2NkHquOguHJfETbF28sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 15:16:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/02/former-british-intelligence-officer-helped-effort-flip-russian/" target="_blank"&gt;Former British intelligence officer 'helped effort to flip Russian oligarch against Trump campaign'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christopher Steele, the former MI6 officer who attracted Donald Trump’s fury for drafting a dossier of allegations about collusion with Moscow, was involved in efforts to flip a high-profile Russian oligarch, according to newly released emails. They reportedly reveal that the British agent helped American officials target Oleg Deripaska, a Kremlin-linked billionaire, as part of an effort to persuade influential figures to pass on information about any assistance given to Mr Trump’s election campaign. The details were revealed in emails obtained by The New York Times, which said they had bee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Moscow has noticed US attempts to meddle in Russian election process – foreign ministry - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/437575-us-meddling-russian-elections/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF6Pj0sH1iVXFAU2A4m3eR8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/437575-us-meddling-russian-elections/" target="_blank"&gt;Moscow has noticed US attempts to meddle in Russian election process – foreign ministry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moscow has seen attempts to meddle in the Russian elections coming from the US, a senior Russian diplomat said. It comes as Google is suspected of possibly violating the law by selling political ads for unsanctioned rally. Andrey Nesterenko, a senior Russian diplomat, said the US “certainly does” attempt to meddle in the Russian electoral processes, Interfax reported. He was speaking after a briefing on the issue. “Our collective opinion is that electoral sovereignty is a principle that all civilized nations should respect,” the diplomat said, adding that Moscow will notify “our American pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>NYT: FBI Tried to Turn Kremlin-Linked Russian Oligarch Into Informant - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nyt-fbi-tried-to-turn-kremlin-linked-russian-oligarch-into-informant</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHZgFfDvpBdjogH-JDW0qjYqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 19:38:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/nyt-fbi-tried-to-turn-kremlin-linked-russian-oligarch-into-informant" target="_blank"&gt;NYT: FBI Tried to Turn Kremlin-Linked Russian Oligarch Into Informant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sergei Karpukhin/Reuters, The FBI and Justice Department attempted unsuccessfully to turn Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska into an informant between 2014 and 2016, The New York Times reports. Sources cited by the Times said the failed mission was part of a larger effort to gauge the feasibility of flipping several of Russia’s richest men, most of whom have close ties to Vladimir Putin. In the case of Deripaska, sources told the Times, the FBI and Justice Department were initially hoping to get information on Russian organized crime, and later, on any possible Russian assistance to President ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>NYT: DOJ's Bruce Ohr, dossier author Christopher Steele involved in efforts to flip Russian oligarch - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/01/politics/bruce-ohr-christopher-steele-efforts-flip-russian-oligarch/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMZOIPlo1DQ_rViI9qcyYKwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/01/politics/bruce-ohr-christopher-steele-efforts-flip-russian-oligarch/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;NYT: DOJ's Bruce Ohr, dossier author Christopher Steele involved in efforts to flip Russian oligarch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Department official Bruce Ohr and former British spy Christopher Steele -- frequent targets of President Donald Trump's ire related to the Russia investigation -- were involved in US efforts to flip a Russian oligarch with ties to the Kremlin, The New York Times reports. Between 2014 and 2016, the FBI and the Justice Department sought and attempted to turn Russian businessman Oleg Deripaska into an informant for the United States, the Times reported Saturday. Citing current and former officials and associates of Deripaska, the Times reported that investigators were hoping for inform...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US meddles in Russian affairs by trying to turn our citizens into informants – Kremlin - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/437489-us-recruiting-russians-spies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAO1e-gewqOiQc68E7QbKB0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/437489-us-recruiting-russians-spies/" target="_blank"&gt;US meddles in Russian affairs by trying to turn our citizens into informants – Kremlin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent years, the US has been meddling in Russian affairs by “very crudely” trying to recruit Russians as informants, while exerting moral and other types of pressure on them, Vladimir Putin’s spokesperson said on Monday. Kremlin spokesperson Dmitry Peskov was commenting on a recent story published in the New York Times, stating that in 2014-2016, the FBI and the US Department of Justice tried to recruit Russian business tycoon Oleg Deripaska as an informant. According to the paper, US officials wanted to make the businessman share information on Russian organized crime and the alleged R...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Desperate for collusion proof, FBI ‘tried &amp; failed to recruit Russian oligarchs’ – report - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/437449-trump-fbi-dossier-russian-oligarchs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIzaqmIQyGG_nfUImYFywjsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/437449-trump-fbi-dossier-russian-oligarchs/" target="_blank"&gt;Desperate for collusion proof, FBI ‘tried &amp; failed to recruit Russian oligarchs’ – report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FBI agents tried to turn Russia’s once-richest man into a US mole, according to an explosive NYT report. It claims that Oleg Deripaska was one of six oligarchs targeted for information in a Russiagate-related intelligence flop. According to reports by the New York Times, the US government pushed oligarchs with perceived links to President Vladimir Putin for information. Deripaska was allegedly nudged to give up information on Russian organized crime and “possible Russian aid to President Trump’s 2016 campaign.” Determined to get something on the Kremlin’s unproven involvement in the 2016 el...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>FBI tried to turn Russian oligarch close to Putin into informer on Trump collusion and organised crime - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/oleg-deripaska-donald-trump-putin-russia-collusion-oligarch-informer-manafort-fbi-a8519496.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRsvejs0dxWEN7OqWsy8MQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 17:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/oleg-deripaska-donald-trump-putin-russia-collusion-oligarch-informer-manafort-fbi-a8519496.html" target="_blank"&gt;FBI tried to turn Russian oligarch close to Putin into informer on Trump collusion and organised crime&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the estimation of US officials, Oleg Deripaska, a Russian oligarch with close ties to the Kremlin, has faced credible accusations of extortion, bribery and even murder. They also thought he might make a good source, so between 2014 and 2016, the FBI and the Justice Department unsuccessfully tried to turn him into an informant. They signalled that they might provide help with his trouble in getting visas for the United States or even explore other steps to address his legal problems. In exchange, they were hoping for information on Russian organised crime and, later, on possible Russian a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Republicans 'cherry-picked' Russia probe documents to quiz U.S. official: Democrats - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-ohr/republicans-cherry-picked-russia-probe-documents-to-quiz-us-official-democrats-idUSKCN1LG2NP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDF4np-OUpWGB-fNhqntsrsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 19:56:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-ohr/republicans-cherry-picked-russia-probe-documents-to-quiz-us-official-democrats-idUSKCN1LG2NP" target="_blank"&gt;Republicans 'cherry-picked' Russia probe documents to quiz U.S. official: Democrats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democrats on Friday accused Republicans of "cherry-picking" and leaking portions of text messages and emails between a U.S. law enforcement official and a former British spy who investigated then-businessman Donald Trump's ties to the Russian government. Two lawmakers made the charge in a letter to the Republican chairmen of the U.S. House of Representatives judiciary and government oversight panels, which on Tuesday questioned Associate Deputy Attorney General Bruce Ohr about his ties with former MI6 officer Christopher Steele. The letter was the latest salvo in a fight between the politic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Paul Manafort went to Kyrgyzstan to 'strengthen Russia's position' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/22/paul-manafort-went-to-kyrgyzstan-to-strengthen-russias-position</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBKbF19DIsAzs2a5DFdlfpsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 10:47:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/22/paul-manafort-went-to-kyrgyzstan-to-strengthen-russias-position" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Manafort went to Kyrgyzstan to 'strengthen Russia's position'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Manafort, whose work as a political consultant in Russia and Ukraine led to his conviction in a Virginia courtroom on Wednesday, worked more extensively in the former Soviet Union than was previously reported, a new investigation has claimed. Related: Trump turmoil: aftermath of Cohen and Manafort verdicts - live According to a report published on Wednesday by the new investigative media outlet Project, Manafort and his fixer Konstantin Kilimnik were sent in 2005 to the central Asian republic of Kyrgyzstan, where the two promoted Russian interests, including the closure of the US milit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Escort who claimed to have information linking Russia interference to Trump election says she no longer has evidence - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/russia-trump-election-meddling-interference-escort-tapes-anastasia-vashukevich-a8499281.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM50ADzL9vUKnUxohNnrOkcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 11:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/russia-trump-election-meddling-interference-escort-tapes-anastasia-vashukevich-a8499281.html" target="_blank"&gt;Escort who claimed to have information linking Russia interference to Trump election says she no longer has evidence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Belarusian model and escort who previously claimed she had vital information about Russian meddling in the election of Donald Trump in 2016 says she no longer has the evidence. Anastasia Vashukevich, who appeared at a Thai court hearing on Monday, revealed that she has handed over the audio recordings in question to a Russian oligarch. The escort told an AP reporter present at the court that she had given tapes to Oleg Deripaska, whose conversations about alleged election interference she claims to have recorded. Read more - Giuliani says 'truth isn't truth' over risks of Mueller intervie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Rusal says board backs change of domicile to Russia - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions-rusal/rusal-says-board-backs-change-of-domicile-to-russia-idUSKBN1L20IW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAkh5G-uGssinmjWgqDPxmMqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 06:32:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions-rusal/rusal-says-board-backs-change-of-domicile-to-russia-idUSKBN1L20IW" target="_blank"&gt;Rusal says board backs change of domicile to Russia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia's sanctions-hit aluminum giant Rusal (0486.HK: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) said on Friday its board had discussed and approved a change of domicile from Britain's Jersey to Russia in order to take advantage of new special tax regulations. Rusal, which was hit with U.S. sanctions in April that seriously disrupted aluminum supplies, said the relocation was still subject to shareholder approval. The announcement comes a day after En+ Group (ENPLq.L: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), which is also subject to U.S. sanctions on the two companies' tycoon co-owner Oleg Deripas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Trump-Russia Facts Lead To Only One Reasonable Conclusion - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-patterson-trump-russia-collusion_us_5b72400be4b0bdd0620c350f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHIWGkX4fRfwVeKXWxu-saUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 09:47:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-patterson-trump-russia-collusion_us_5b72400be4b0bdd0620c350f" target="_blank"&gt;The Trump-Russia Facts Lead To Only One Reasonable Conclusion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This fact is incontrovertible: By word and deed, on the world stage Donald Trump has become an invaluable asset to Russia. The question is whether America’s president is also a Russian asset — specifically, whether Trump’s bewildering affinity for President Vladimir Putin is simply a matter of ego and admiration or whether Putin possesses information that empowers him to influence Trump’s conduct. This question has the gravest implications for our foreign policy, national security, electoral integrity and rule of law. If the answer is damning, Trump must quash special counsel Robert Mueller...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Blacklisted Russian firm wins, and then loses a break from Trump's aluminium tariffs - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/rusal-blacklist-russia-us-trump-aluminum-tariff-sanctions-a8485791.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFmfn0d8U7TVynggEirnj0wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 07:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/rusal-blacklist-russia-us-trump-aluminum-tariff-sanctions-a8485791.html" target="_blank"&gt;Blacklisted Russian firm wins, and then loses a break from Trump's aluminium tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of companies have asked the Trump administration for a special break from its sweeping aluminium tariffs. Few have succeeded. One that managed to get an exemption is a Russian firm currently subject to Treasury Department sanctions. How Rusal America – a branch of a Russian metals giant controlled by an oligarch with close ties to president Vladimir Putin – managed to win an exclusion highlights the chaotic and unwieldy process surrounding president Donald Trump’s tariffs. While Rusal and its controlling stakeholder, Oleg V Deripaska, are restricted by US sanctions, one of the comp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Rick Gates testifies he committed crimes with Trump's former campaign manager Paul Manafort - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/06/rick-gates-testifies-committed-crimes-trumps-former-campaign/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDW-uuYx7Ap5bhM3kDIycksqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 22:50:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/06/rick-gates-testifies-committed-crimes-trumps-former-campaign/" target="_blank"&gt;Rick Gates testifies he committed crimes with Trump's former campaign manager Paul Manafort&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rick Gates, a longtime business associate of US President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort, on Monday testified at trial that he helped Manafort file false tax returns and hide his foreign bank accounts. Gates is expected to be the government's star witness in its case against Manafort. Gates, who also served on Trump's campaign, pleaded guilty in February and agreed to cooperate with prosecutors under a deal that could lead to a reduced sentence. Taking the stand on the trial's fifth day, Gates admitted to helping Manafort doctor financial statements, hide sources of f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Rusal defies US sanctions to post rise in profit - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/08/06/rusal-defies-us-sanctions-post-rise-profit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELGlCW_zdP0bH7UPIqcDRO4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 15:31:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/08/06/rusal-defies-us-sanctions-post-rise-profit/" target="_blank"&gt;Rusal defies US sanctions to post rise in profit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian aluminium producer Rusal has defied the imposition of swingeing US sanctions to post a rise in profits in the first half of the year. The company, 48pc owned by billionaire Oleg Deripaska’s EN+ group, reported a doubling in pre-tax profits to $1bn (£777m) in the six months to June, while revenues edged up 4.7pc to $5bn. Earlier this year Rusal’s shares in Hong Kong plunged by half after it became one of a number of entities targeted by the US to punish Russia for its “malign activity”. The company warned the sanctions would be “materially adverse” to its business, as it would restri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Manafort's longtime business partner testifies the pair committed crimes - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-08-07/rick-gates-testifies-he-committed-crimes-with-paul-manafort/10081462</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKCFPBrhob7g4FoFAQTOdXgqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 22:12:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-08-07/rick-gates-testifies-he-committed-crimes-with-paul-manafort/10081462" target="_blank"&gt;Manafort's longtime business partner testifies the pair committed crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rick Gates has testified that he and US President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman, Paul Manafort, committed crimes. Mr Gates, whose testimony in the federal court trial of Mr Manafort — his longtime business partner — in Alexandria, Virginia, was continuing, was expected to be a star witness in the Government's case, having pleaded guilty in February and agreed to cooperate with prosecutors under a deal that could lead to a reduced sentence. Mr Manafort's attorneys signalled they would seek to blame Mr Gates and had accused him of embezzling millions of dollars from Mr Manafort. But...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Who is Rick Gates? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/06/politics/rick-gates-manafort-trial-witness/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbNilSr__lnKX1Z2CNOkg4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 22:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/06/politics/rick-gates-manafort-trial-witness/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Who is Rick Gates?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Manafort's longtime deputy Rick Gates took the stand at Manafort's trial in Virginia Monday afternoon. Gates, who also served on Donald Trump's presidential campaign alongside Manafort, pleaded guilty in February to charges in connection related to special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation into the 2016 election, striking a deal to cooperate with the FBI. Gates and Manafort, who are longtime business associates, were indicted last October in connection with Justice Department special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation on 12 counts that included conspiracy against the United St...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Manafort's right-hand man testifies against him in tax fraud case - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/accountant-of-ex-trump-aide-manafort-faces-cross-exam-after-possibly-damaging-testimony-idUSKBN1KR113</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOj7Am5fcB9M1u20836jShkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:34:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/accountant-of-ex-trump-aide-manafort-faces-cross-exam-after-possibly-damaging-testimony-idUSKBN1KR113" target="_blank"&gt;Manafort's right-hand man testifies against him in tax fraud case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rick Gates, a longtime business associate of U.S. President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort, on Monday testified that he helped Manafort file false tax returns and hide his foreign bank accounts. Gates is the government's star witness in its case against Manafort, who is accused of bank and tax fraud. Gates, who also served on Trump's campaign, pleaded guilty in February and agreed to cooperate with prosecutors under a deal that could lead to a reduced sentence. Taking the stand on the trial's fifth day, Gates admitted to helping Manafort doctor financial statements, h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Paul Manafort's work for Ukraine fit neatly with Putin's agenda - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/06/opinions/manafort-ukraine-russia-agenda-bociurkiw/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKKuIaSkW0FJ4s4HUKN9Ii8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 18:37:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/06/opinions/manafort-ukraine-russia-agenda-bociurkiw/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Manafort's work for Ukraine fit neatly with Putin's agenda&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Bociurkiw is a global affairs analyst and a former spokesperson for the Organization for Security and Cooperation in Europe. The opinions expressed in this commentary are his; view more opinions on CNN. The one searing image out of the first week of the Paul Manafort financial fraud trial in Virginia is the mug shot of the defendant's $15,000 ostrich skin jacket, described by some as a monument to the excess of the Washington swamp. The star exhibit generated plenty of ridicule. But it's very likely that the free-spending political consultant and former Trump campaign manager may ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Paul Manafort Trial: A Who's Who Of Key Names - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/people-manafort-trial_us_5b609aabe4b0de86f49b6af7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDmRkWbrK2e_g8s7XKZ3cK0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 17:20:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/people-manafort-trial_us_5b609aabe4b0de86f49b6af7" target="_blank"&gt;The Paul Manafort Trial: A Who's Who Of Key Names&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before Paul Manafort ran President Donald Trump’s campaign, he spent years working with Russians and Ukrainians with ties to the Kremlin, cashing out millions of dollars in the process. He is now on trial for bank fraud and tax evasion charges in Virginia while he awaits another in D.C. This trial is one of the most closely watched events to date to come out of special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation into the Trump campaign’s possible collusion with Russia. Here are some of the key witnesses who will appear at trial, as well as the Ukrainians and Russians we’ll be hearing about. Paul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>US extends sanctions deadline a third time for EN+, Rusal and Gaz Group - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0c11840e-9503-11e8-b67b-b8205561c3fe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOKmv9JH4H-x5ixyRdYiApEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 20:59:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0c11840e-9503-11e8-b67b-b8205561c3fe" target="_blank"&gt;US extends sanctions deadline a third time for EN+, Rusal and Gaz Group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Treasury has extended a deadline for trading in three sanctioned companies owned by Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska, the third time it has given Rusal, EN+ and Gaz Group more time to develop a business plan than could see sanctions lifted. Mr Deripaska’s aluminium and power empire was hit with sweeping sanctions in April that cut it off from global financial and trading markets. On Tuesday the Office for Foreign Assets Control (Ofac), which oversees US sanction policy, gave the companies until October 23 to find a solution. The third extension, allowing trading of debt and equity in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Manafort accountant asked at trial about loan from Russian oligarch - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort-accountant/manafort-accountant-asked-at-trial-about-loan-from-russian-oligarch-idUSKBN1KR25X</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECxTknjDa4T3pFvapYSfo_UqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 20:05:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort-accountant/manafort-accountant-asked-at-trial-about-loan-from-russian-oligarch-idUSKBN1KR25X" target="_blank"&gt;Manafort accountant asked at trial about loan from Russian oligarch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An accountant for Paul Manafort, U.S. President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman, was asked by a prosecutor on Monday at Manafort's trial on tax and bank fraud charges about a $10 million loan from Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska. The accountant, Cindy Laporta, testified she was unaware if the loan, which the prosecutor said was "supposedly made in 2006," was recognized as income. (Reporting by Nathan Layne; Writing by Eric Beech; Editing by Mohammad Zargham)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Is the Manafort trial the first step towards Trump’s impeachment? - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/paul-manafort-trial-latest-trump-russia-mueller-impeachment-a8471131.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA1AlZwEMXRU2RETAzccCTYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 11:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/paul-manafort-trial-latest-trump-russia-mueller-impeachment-a8471131.html" target="_blank"&gt;Is the Manafort trial the first step towards Trump’s impeachment?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There must be no pictures shown of “a cocktail party with scantily clad women” at the trial of Paul Manafort starting this week: that is the firm direction of the judge in the case. In response prosecutor Greg Andrews has reassured that “there will be no pictures of scantily clad women, period.” The stipulation by US District Judge TS Ellis III about the salacious photographs, if they exist, was an attempt to avoid the jury from forming a pejorative opinion about the billionaire political fixer from tales of his alleged lifestyle. But it is the next sentence by Andrews: “I don’t anticipate ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>US Treasury Extends Time to Divest From EN+, GAZ, Rusal - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-treasury-extends-time-to-divest-three-russia-companies/4508591.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGP2jTN2PHsE8Q4IBuciwcEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:48:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-treasury-extends-time-to-divest-three-russia-companies/4508591.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Treasury Extends Time to Divest From EN+, GAZ, Rusal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Treasury Department said on Tuesday that it had extended the deadline for investors to divest holdings in sanctioned Russian companies EN+, GAZ Group and Rusal to Oct. 23 from Aug. 5. The U.S. Treasury in April imposed sanctions against billionaire Oleg Deripaska and eight companies in which he is a large shareholder, including aluminum exporter Rusal, in response to what it termed "malign activities" by Russia. Deripaska has held a controlling interest in En+, which in turn controls Rusal, the world's largest aluminum producer outside of China. Automaker GAZ is also part of his bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Russian state lender VTB demands CEFC’s Singapore subsidiary repay loan - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/196256bc-9402-11e8-b67b-b8205561c3fe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA4xaPrxvs8F9nEQu6ZQe5IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 14:31:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/196256bc-9402-11e8-b67b-b8205561c3fe" target="_blank"&gt;Russian state lender VTB demands CEFC’s Singapore subsidiary repay loan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AnAn Group, a Singapore subsidiary of troubled Chinese commodity trader CEFC, has received a $170m statutory demand from Russian state bank VTB, the company said on Monday. VTB is demanding that AnAn repay a loan the bank gave it last year to buy a 6.25 per cent stake in the initial public offering of Russian energy company En+ within 21 days, the company said in a statement. AnAn added that it was seeking legal advice and attempting to settle the matter with VTB. AnAn’s $500m cornerstone investment in the En+ IPO last November, partly secured with the VTB loan, was a key boosting for the l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Why is Paul Manafort risking it all to face Mueller charges in court? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jul/29/paul-manafort-mueller-charges-court-trial-trump</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECNFl3Cm8-vwblLMFLMFmC8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 05:00:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jul/29/paul-manafort-mueller-charges-court-trial-trump" target="_blank"&gt;Why is Paul Manafort risking it all to face Mueller charges in court?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump’s former presidential campaign chairman will this week risk spending the rest of his life in prison, rather than help Robert Mueller’s investigation into possible collusion with Russia. Paul Manafort is due to stand trial in Virginia from Wednesday on charges of bank fraud, tax evasion and conspiracy. Manafort, 69, faces prison sentences totalling up to 305 years if convicted on all counts. On Tuesday morning jury selection is scheduled to get underway. Then he is due to stand trial on separate charges in Washington. Sign up to receive the top US stories every morning Manafort ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Robert Mueller Targeted Two Lobbying Firms. One Is Thriving in Trump’s D.C. - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/robert-mueller-targeted-two-lobbying-firms-one-is-thriving-in-trumps-dc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDob0jVopHWa_iV82CC5POQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 08:46:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/robert-mueller-targeted-two-lobbying-firms-one-is-thriving-in-trumps-dc" target="_blank"&gt;Robert Mueller Targeted Two Lobbying Firms. One Is Thriving in Trump’s D.C.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast When Special Counsel Robert Mueller indicted Donald Trump’s former campaign chairman Paul Manafort in the fall of 2017, he implicated two prominent Washington D.C. lobbying powerhouses as being complicit in a scheme to essentially hide foreign influence peddling. Mercury Public Affairs and the Podesta Group appeared, in that moment, were directly embroiled in the biggest scandal to hit K Street since the days of Jack Abramoff. But in the year that has followed, the two lobbying shops have gone on remarkably different directions. Mercury, dubbed “Company...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Manafort is first ex-Trump aide to go on trial in Russia probe - Reuters</title><link>https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/manafort-is-first-ex-trump-aide-to-go-on-trial-in-russia-probe-idUSKBN1KK12L?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=topNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB-mkJeiHCCg7PAMYmFOf7QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 10:07:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/manafort-is-first-ex-trump-aide-to-go-on-trial-in-russia-probe-idUSKBN1KK12L?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=topNews" target="_blank"&gt;Manafort is first ex-Trump aide to go on trial in Russia probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Manafort on Tuesday will become the first of President Donald Trump's former aides to go on trial, accused of bank and tax fraud by federal investigators probing Russian meddling in the 2016 U.S. presidential election. Despite a focus on financial crimes, the trial could yield politically damaging headlines about a man who ran Trump's campaign for three months and attended a June 2016 meeting with Russians offering damaging information on Trump's Democratic rival Hillary Clinton that is now a focal point of Special Counsel Robert Mueller's 14-month-old investigation. "My guess is you w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://internal.www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>En+ may consider sale to China or nationalisation without reprieve from US sanctions - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2b795120-9038-11e8-b639-7680cedcc421</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELI-L6f-Q5DTdf6-wK2kdzIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 18:40:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2b795120-9038-11e8-b639-7680cedcc421" target="_blank"&gt;En+ may consider sale to China or nationalisation without reprieve from US sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EN+ has warned it might consider a sale to China or nationalisation by Russia if it cannot secure a temporary reprieve from US sanctions to push through the final phase of a plan for oligarch Oleg Deripaska to cede control of the energy-to-aluminium business. The plan, which has been filed with the Office of Foreign Assets Control (Ofac) by US-based lobbyist Mercury, would see Mr Deripaska and his family members transfer their assets to an “approved organisation or trustees”. An escrow account “that satisfies Ofac requirement to ensure that Mr Deripaska does not derive any financial benefit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: U.S. open to lifting sanctions off aluminum giant Rusal - Mnuchin - Reuters</title><link>https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-g20-argentina-mnuchin-rusal-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-open-to-lifting-sanctions-off-aluminum-giant-rusal-mnuchin-idUSKBN1KA2VS?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=topNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHlRzmHtS27QEASy0HmDQNQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 13:38:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-g20-argentina-mnuchin-rusal-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-open-to-lifting-sanctions-off-aluminum-giant-rusal-mnuchin-idUSKBN1KA2VS?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=topNews" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: U.S. open to lifting sanctions off aluminum giant Rusal - Mnuchin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Treasury is open to removing Russian aluminum producer Rusal from a U.S. sanctions list, Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin said on Friday, adding the objective was "not to put Rusal out of business." Mnuchin's comment was the latest indication the Trump administration was trying to aid sanctions-hit Rusal, which has taken a series of steps to try to appease the U.S. government and get the restrictions lifted. The U.S. Treasury in April imposed sanctions against billionaire Oleg Deripaska and the eight companies in which he is a large shareholder, including Rusal, in response to wha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://internal.www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>US firm tried to enlist ambassadors to help Russian company - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/9a99c52284a245d5b73eda93494393b9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO7d5r3fJL_98uWVBCVQ3XwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 04:28:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/9a99c52284a245d5b73eda93494393b9" target="_blank"&gt;US firm tried to enlist ambassadors to help Russian company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A U.S. lobbying firm sought to recruit the ambassadors of France, Germany and several other countries to demonstrate international support for severing Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska's control of Rusal, the aluminum manufacturing giant sanctioned by Washington. Documents made public by the Justice Department show that Mercury LLC drafted messages for at least six envoys to send to senior U.S. government officials that expressed support for a plan to eliminate Deripaska's majority stake in the EN+ Group, the holding company that owns nearly 50 percent of Rusal. The records...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Russian court rules in favor of oligarch in disclosure case - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/395dee9e4e2e4c398d45e159df4dba68</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF43ts5NyK6ZpZnQYOzQzy8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 14:54:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/395dee9e4e2e4c398d45e159df4dba68" target="_blank"&gt;Russian court rules in favor of oligarch in disclosure case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — A Russian court has ruled in favor of a billionaire linked to President Donald Trump's former campaign manager Paul Manafort in an unauthorized disclosure of information case. Oleg Deripaska had filed a suit against Anastasia Vashukevich, a woman who posted several videos in 2016 showing the tycoon hosting a top Russian official on a yacht discussing U.S.-Russian relations. Deripaska argued that Vashukevich, who goes by the name Nastya Rybka, had illegally divulged personal information about him. A court in the southern Russian province of Krasnodar on Monday fined Vashukevich...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Paul Manafort Received $10 Million Loan From Russian Magnate - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/manafort-received-dollar10-million-loan-from-russian-magnate</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENxjVJ6-OT4mFvsqGywhgTcqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 21:30:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/manafort-received-dollar10-million-loan-from-russian-magnate" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Manafort Received $10 Million Loan From Russian Magnate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jonathan Ernst/Reuters, Former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort obtained a $10 million loan from Russian aluminum magnate Oleg Deripaska, according to an unsealed search warrant application that was part of special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation. Reuters reports that tax returns for a company owned by Manafort and his wife showed the $10 million loan. The search warrant was granted for Manafort’s Virginia apartment. An affidavit attached to the warrant application also revealed that Deripaska “financially backed Manafort’s consulting work in Ukraine” in the mid-2000s. Deripaska ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Rusal elects new board of directors in bid to escape U.S. sanctions - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions-rusal-board/rusal-elects-new-board-of-directors-in-bid-to-escape-u-s-sanctions-idUSKBN1JO2LN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWkFN2OnMDIEu60qnqAISIqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 16:57:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-sanctions-rusal-board/rusal-elects-new-board-of-directors-in-bid-to-escape-u-s-sanctions-idUSKBN1JO2LN" target="_blank"&gt;Rusal elects new board of directors in bid to escape U.S. sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOSCOW (Reuters) - Shareholders at sanctions-hit Russian aluminum producer Rusal elected a new board of directors on Thursday in an effort to appease the U.S. and get the restrictions lifted. The new board, dominated by independent directors and operational managers, is part of a series of steps which Rusal and its co-owner Oleg Deripaska hope will persuade the U.S. government to remove the company from sanctions that have damaged its business since April. Rusal has felt the impact of the U.S. sanctions because of its entanglement with Deripaska, but the U.S. government is not targeting the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Brexit will strengthen Ireland-US relations, says Irish ambassador - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/30/brexit-will-strengthen-ireland-us-relations-irish-ambassador-daniel-mulhall</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZdfF8kqq0yAfNvHqEo_cMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/30/brexit-will-strengthen-ireland-us-relations-irish-ambassador-daniel-mulhall" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit will strengthen Ireland-US relations, says Irish ambassador&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brexit is likely to lead to a strengthening of the US-Irish bond and the emergence of Ireland as the main bridge between the US and Europe, Dublin’s ambassador to Washington DC has predicted. The UK’s departure would leave Ireland as the only predominantly English-speaking EU member, and a natural destination for US investors looking for a European base because of Ireland’s longstanding “special relationship” with Washington, Daniel Mulhall said. Mulhall, a former Irish ambassador to the UK, said he found anxiety over Brexit had accompanied him from London to Washington. “Since I arrived he...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Investigators detail Manafort money from Ukrainian corruption, Russian oligarch - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/28/politics/mueller-search-warrants-manafort/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGAHX6SAGc3ZlF_xhsu7A9EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 17:14:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/28/politics/mueller-search-warrants-manafort/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Investigators detail Manafort money from Ukrainian corruption, Russian oligarch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New court documents in Paul Manafort's criminal case give the fullest picture yet of what prosecutors say was the former Trump campaign chairman's financial reliance on Ukrainians suspected of corruption and a Russian oligarch, while he allegedly schemed to defraud banks and the US government. A Virginia federal court unveiled several new details on Tuesday in two search warrants and accompanying affidavits used to search Paul Manafort's properties. The search warrant documents, which have been available in court records for months but previously had dozens of pages redacted, reveal for the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Here's what's on the docket for Paul Manafort's pretrial hearing - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/29/politics/manafort-hearing-russia-ukraine-trump-mueller/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFbkCkPuzoAmJrQgNgOW6B0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 10:10:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/29/politics/manafort-hearing-russia-ukraine-trump-mueller/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Here's what's on the docket for Paul Manafort's pretrial hearing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most consequential hearings before former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort goes to trial is unlikely to have him there to witness it. On Friday morning, Judge TS Ellis will review several requests from defense attorneys and federal prosecutors -- including new details on why investigators swept Manafort's apartment and a storage unit for documents related to powerful Ukrainians and Russians he worked for -- as they set the terms of his bank fraud and financial crimes trial in Virginia. The trial, the first of two criminal proceedings for Manafort, is set to begin July 25 and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Deripaska wins London court battle over Norilsk shares - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/5113ec3e-7a20-11e8-bc55-50daf11b720d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBEAV14BZY3Ewd09YwsEHTsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 16:07:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5113ec3e-7a20-11e8-bc55-50daf11b720d" target="_blank"&gt;Deripaska wins London court battle over Norilsk shares&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska has won a legal challenge in London to stop his rival Vladimir Potanin from increasing his stake in major Russian metals producer Norilsk Nickel. Mr Deripaska had sought to block a move by Mr Potanin to buy shares from Roman Abramovich, another Russian oligarch, who had acquired a stake in Norilsk as a means to end a long-running feud between the two men. The decision from the London high court was confirmed by Rusal, Mr Deripaska’s aluminium company, which owns the oligarch’s Norilsk stake. A representative of the company said: “Rusal is pleased with today’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Manafort had $10 million loan from Russian oligarch: court filing - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/manafort-had-10-million-loan-from-russian-oligarch-court-filing-idUSKBN1JN2YF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPxmaHX__qshwEYxOHYbeQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 20:56:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/manafort-had-10-million-loan-from-russian-oligarch-court-filing-idUSKBN1JN2YF" target="_blank"&gt;Manafort had $10 million loan from Russian oligarch: court filing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Reuters) - A search warrant application unsealed on Wednesday revealed closer links than previously known between President Donald Trump’s former campaign manager Paul Manafort and a Russian oligarch with close ties to the Kremlin. In an affidavit attached to the July 2017 application, an FBI agent said he had reviewed tax returns for a company controlled by Manafort and his wife that showed a $10 million loan from a Russian lender identified as Oleg Deripaska. The application to search Manafort's Virginia apartment was granted, providing key evidence for Special Counsel Robert Mueller's i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>US lobbyist for Russian oligarch visited Julian Assange nine times last year - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2018/jun/20/us-lobbyist-for-russian-oligarch-visited-julian-assange-nine-times-last-year</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED6FHHn3n5cJKQOEFIqyNQwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 10:08:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/media/2018/jun/20/us-lobbyist-for-russian-oligarch-visited-julian-assange-nine-times-last-year" target="_blank"&gt;US lobbyist for Russian oligarch visited Julian Assange nine times last year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A longtime US lobbyist for the Russian oligarch Oleg Deripaska visited Julian Assange nine times at the Ecuadorian embassy in London last year, according to visitor logs seen by the Guardian. Adam Waldman, who has worked as a Washington lobbyist for the metals tycoon since 2009, had more meetings with Assange in 2017 than almost anyone else, the records show. It is not clear why Waldman went to the WikiLeaks founder or whether the meetings had any connection to the Russian billionaire, who is now subject to US sanctions. But the disclosure is likely to raise further questions about the exte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Shares in Russia's Sistema drop 9 percent on U.S. sanctions fears - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-usa-sanctions-sistema/shares-in-russias-sistema-drop-9-percent-on-us-sanctions-fears-idUSKBN1JI2LH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChMY0SmzigI6URbJ9Y_jFsqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 18:58:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-usa-sanctions-sistema/shares-in-russias-sistema-drop-9-percent-on-us-sanctions-fears-idUSKBN1JI2LH" target="_blank"&gt;Shares in Russia's Sistema drop 9 percent on U.S. sanctions fears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOSCOW (Reuters) - Shares in Russian business conglomerate Sistema (AFKS.MM: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) (SSAq.L: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) fell 8.7 percent in Moscow trade on Friday, after two U.S. lawmakers called for an investigation into whether the group's owner should be subject to sanctions. In a letter bit.ly/2tj4M14 to U.S. Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin and Secretary of State Mike Pompeo, Congress members Ileana Ros-Lehtinen and Mark Walker called for "immediate action to determine whether Russian national Vladimir Yevtushenkov meets the criteria to be san...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>