<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Stakeknife - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZvT0djMUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:05:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>'Stakeknife' pleads guilty to pornography charges - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/courts/2018/1205/1015252-freddie-scappaticci/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780126892838</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:13:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/courts/2018/1205/1015252-freddie-scappaticci/" target="_blank"&gt;'Stakeknife' pleads guilty to pornography charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.irishmirror.ie/news/irish-news/british-ira-agent-freddie-scappaticci-13691669" target="_blank"&gt;British IRA agent Freddie Scappaticci admits possessing extreme pornography&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Mirror&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/suspected-stakeknife-informer-avoids-jail-over-extreme-pornography-890009.html" target="_blank"&gt;Suspected ‘Stakeknife’ informer avoids jail over extreme pornography&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thesun.ie/news/3478311/british-armys-notorious-ira-agent-stakeknife-freddie-scappaticci-admits-two-counts-of-possessing-extreme-porn/" target="_blank"&gt;British Army’s notorious IRA agent ‘Stakeknife’ Freddie Scappaticci admits two counts of possessing extreme po&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Irish Sun&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/dec/05/stakeknife-informant-freddie-scappaticci-pleads-guilty-to-pornography-charges" target="_blank"&gt;‘Stakeknife informant' pleads guilty to pornography charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWltNXR1bGpZQU1FZnNYUVhMVVNORmhLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Freddie Scappaticci pleads guilty to animal pornography possession - The Irish Times</title><link>https://www.irishtimes.com/news/crime-and-law/freddie-scappaticci-pleads-guilty-to-animal-pornography-possession-1.3720882</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPC8vxnwsMFy_nY8j1dNOz8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqfqFCzD7v4MDMNLDjQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:38:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishtimes.com/news/crime-and-law/freddie-scappaticci-pleads-guilty-to-animal-pornography-possession-1.3720882" target="_blank"&gt;Freddie Scappaticci pleads guilty to animal pornography possession&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Irish Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;West Belfast man widely named as British army's IRA informer 'Stakeknife' gets suspended jail term.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishtimes.com">The Irish Times</source></item><item><title>Friday's headlines: Stakenife, Brexit and scams - BBC News</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-northern-ireland-46396847</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiNWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmJiYy5jb20vbmV3cy91ay1ub3J0aGVybi1pcmVsYW5kLTQ2Mzk2ODQ30gF9aHR0cHM6Ly93d3ctYmJjLWNvbS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy5iYmMuY29tL25ld3MvYW1wL3VrLW5vcnRoZXJuLWlyZWxhbmQtNDYzOTY4NDc_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 08:26:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-northern-ireland-46396847" target="_blank"&gt;Friday's headlines: Stakenife, Brexit and scams&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;BBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We'll start off the papers this morning with the Irish News, which reports "Stakeknife probe set to quiz several high-profile republicans". It says a team of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.bbc.com">BBC News</source></item><item><title>'Stakeknife' admits two counts of possessing extreme porn - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/courts/stakeknife-admits-two-counts-of-possessing-extreme-porn-37600244.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVz_BKFBKo3NCTDCtM6vV4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wmtSiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/courts/stakeknife-admits-two-counts-of-possessing-extreme-porn-37600244.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Stakeknife' admits two counts of possessing extreme porn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man widely named as the British army's notorious IRA agent 'Stakeknife' has avoided prison after admitting two counts of possessing extreme pornography. Freddie Scappaticci (72) appeared briefly before Westminster magistrates in central London to admit the charges, which related to at least 329 images, including those involving animals. Scappaticci wore a blue fleece and green tracksuit bottoms as he entered his pleas to the charges. Chief magistrate Emma Arbuthnot sentenced Scappaticci to three months in custody, suspended for 12 months. The magistrate said: "You have not been before the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Man widely named as 'Stakeknife' the Army's IRA informer guilty of possessing beastiality images - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/man-widely-named-stakeknife-armys-ira-informer-guilty-extreme/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECz-sM-ofYca0LFjp2SqGkwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:40:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/man-widely-named-stakeknife-armys-ira-informer-guilty-extreme/" target="_blank"&gt;Man widely named as 'Stakeknife' the Army's IRA informer guilty of possessing beastiality images&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freddie Scappaticci, the man widely named as the Army’s IRA informer ‘Stakeknife’, has pleaded guilty at Westminster Magistrates’ Court to two charges of possessing extreme pornographic images. The court heard the charges related to at least 329 images, including some involving animals. Magistrate Emma Arbuthnot sentenced Scappaticci, 72, to three months in custody, suspended for 12 months. She said: "You have not been before the court for 50 years - and that's good character in my book." Bedfordshire Police said Scappaticci the two counts under the Criminal Justice and Immigration Act 200...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Stakeknife inquiry will 'go where evidence takes us' - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/ireland/2017/0403/864924-stakeknife-boucher-ira/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAM4HUe09kofBqfgFcLy63sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 18:22:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/ireland/2017/0403/864924-stakeknife-boucher-ira/" target="_blank"&gt;Stakeknife inquiry will 'go where evidence takes us'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The British police officer investigating murders and other crimes linked to the IRA double-agent Stakeknife has promised he will go where the evidence leads him — even if it involves members of the security services and senior figures in the republican movement. Bedfordshire Police Chief Constable Jon Boucher, who was appointed to take charge of the inquiry last year, today made a fresh appeal for information to those who can provide assistance. Stakeknife was the code name given to the individual within the IRA who was in charge of its internal security unit, linked to dozens of murders ov...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Police 'failed to investigate 18 murders in Northern Ireland to protect IRA mole' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/stakeknife-ira-mole-murders-not-investigated-by-northern-ireland-police-a7677361.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPRMObURKvV4ToBr9BRrfskqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 23:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/stakeknife-ira-mole-murders-not-investigated-by-northern-ireland-police-a7677361.html" target="_blank"&gt;Police 'failed to investigate 18 murders in Northern Ireland to protect IRA mole'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police failed to properly investigate the murders of more than a dozen people during the Troubles in Northern Ireland to prevent the identity of a key agent from being revealed, according to a report. Officers covered up a British spy’s alleged links to as many as 18 murders to prevent a mole known as StakeKnife being outed to the IRA, an investigation by the BBC claims to have found. An on-going criminal inquiry named Operation Kenova has been launched to probe whether StakeKnife’s fellow spies were sacrificed so that he could continue as a double agent. However, research by BBC Panorama s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ex-IRA man quizzed over Donaldson killing dies after cancer fight - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/exira-man-quizzed-over-donaldson-killing-dies-after-cancer-fight-35411169.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELZMLVtfnhYShbihxpWW5gEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/exira-man-quizzed-over-donaldson-killing-dies-after-cancer-fight-35411169.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-IRA man quizzed over Donaldson killing dies after cancer fight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former IRA man Victor Notarantonio, who was questioned by gardaí about the murder of British agent Denis Donaldson, has died in his Belfast home. The 67-year-old ex-IRA member had been battling cancer. In the late 1970s, Notarantonio also kneecapped Gerry Adams's paedophile brother, Liam. The shooting was an authorised IRA punishment attack but was unrelated to the child sex abuse charges of which Liam Adams was later convicted. Hundreds of mourners attended Requiem Mass for Notarantonio at St Teresa's Church in west Belfast yesterday, followed by burial in the Blaris Cemetery in Lisburn. A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Informant 'killed by IRA despite warning from British spy' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/10/informant-killed-ira-despite-warning-british-spy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP7hqIYjDTQFx29kme645l4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/10/informant-killed-ira-despite-warning-british-spy/" target="_blank"&gt;Informant 'killed by IRA despite warning from British spy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A police informant working in Northern Ireland may have been "allowed to die" to avoid blowing the cover of another spy, investigators said. Joe Fenton was secretly providing information to the Royal Ulster Constabulary's special branch and was suspected by the armed group of being an informer. Bedfordshire Police Chief Constable Jon Boutcher is investigating the high-ranking Army mole, Stakeknife, who led the republican organisation's "nutting squad" internal security unit which interrogated and murdered suspected spies. His team is probing more than 50 murders and the BBC's Panorama links...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>New evidence uncovered in Stakeknife spy probe - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2016/1014/824076-stakeknife-evidence-probe/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrUlgm8WuQNE8QJWqSQl1sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 16:00:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2016/1014/824076-stakeknife-evidence-probe/" target="_blank"&gt;New evidence uncovered in Stakeknife spy probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Significant new evidence has been uncovered by an English police chief investigating more than 50 murders linked to the British Army's notorious IRA agent Stakeknife. Victims' families have told stories never divulged before at the start of an independent probe by Bedfordshire Police Chief Constable Jon Boutcher into the high-ranking mole who led the IRA's internal security unit, 'nutting squad', while in the employ of the British state. A group of six international policing experts has been appointed to inform the investigation on a voluntary basis. They include senior police officers from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Stakeknife: double agent in IRA 'was given alibi by senior British officials' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/apr/11/stakeknife-double-agent-in-ira-was-given-alibi-by-senior-british-officials</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBn8OKu_Loju_D37G99IVBwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 05:02:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/apr/11/stakeknife-double-agent-in-ira-was-given-alibi-by-senior-british-officials" target="_blank"&gt;Stakeknife: double agent in IRA 'was given alibi by senior British officials'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Britain’s most important agents inside the IRA has been linked to 18 murders and was provided with an alibi by a senior police officer to avoid getting him arrested during the Troubles, it has emerged. Related: Army whistleblower to testify on IRA double agent Stakeknife The Guardian can also reveal that the informer codenamed “Stakeknife” reported directly to the late Martin McGuinness in the 1980s and 90s when the man who would become Northern Ireland’s deputy first minister was the IRA’s northern commander and army council member. Stakeknife, whose real name is believed to be Fred...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Stakeknife could face perjury charges, says senior police officer - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/aug/21/stakeknife-could-face-perjury-charges-says-senior-police-officer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSrXc9knOzmtlgAn65ITyoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 15:19:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/aug/21/stakeknife-could-face-perjury-charges-says-senior-police-officer" target="_blank"&gt;Stakeknife could face perjury charges, says senior police officer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An alleged British secret agent in the IRA who is accused of being linked to at least 20 murders while working for military intelligence could be charged with perjury for denying in court he was a spy, a senior UK police officer has told the Guardian. Stakeknife, whose real name is believed to be Freddie Scappaticci, was the IRA’s chief spy catcher and received £80,000 each year as one of Britain’s most important agents within the terror group. It is alleged that his army and police handlers turned a blind eye to murders in order to promote their agent inside the IRA’s ranks. Police are now...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Man released in Stakeknife probe - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/man-released-in-stakeknife-probe-36561583.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPs5HSYR9tQsyAH0l2FPuYsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 18:49:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/man-released-in-stakeknife-probe-36561583.html" target="_blank"&gt;Man released in Stakeknife probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man widely named as the Army's notorious IRA agent Stakeknife has been released on bail. Detectives have been questioning Freddie Scappaticci from West Belfast about offences including murder and abduction since Tuesday. Mr Scappaticci has always strongly denied claims that he is Stakeknife, a high-ranking military mole who reputedly led the republican organisation's "nutting squad", an internal security unit which interrogated and murdered suspected spies during the Northern Ireland conflict. A team of independent detectives probing claims of murder, kidnap and torture detained the 72-ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Detectives granted more time to question 'Stakeknife' - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/ulster/2018/0131/937430-stakeknife/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEvPdaVoF4WoEG6Kr231ExUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 20:12:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/ulster/2018/0131/937430-stakeknife/" target="_blank"&gt;Detectives granted more time to question 'Stakeknife'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Detectives have been granted additional time to question a man widely named as the British army's notorious IRA agent Stakeknife. A team of independent detectives probing claims of murder, kidnap and torture detained a 72-year-old at an undisclosed location yesterday, a statement from Operation Kenova said. Officers have subsequently been allowed a further 36 hours to question the man. In 2003 Stakeknife was widely named as west Belfast man Freddie Scappaticci but he has always strongly denied the allegation. Bedfordshire Police Chief Constable Jon Boutcher is investigating the high-ranking...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>'Stakeknife' arrested as police probe more than 50 murders - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/stakeknife-arrested-as-police-probe-more-than-50-murders-36549797.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIBuuN3bxYhUL833Cbjp46gqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/stakeknife-arrested-as-police-probe-more-than-50-murders-36549797.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Stakeknife' arrested as police probe more than 50 murders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man widely named as the British army's notorious IRA agent Stakeknife has been arrested by detectives, sources said. Freddie Scappaticci has always strongly denied the allegation. A team of independent detectives probing claims of murder, kidnap and torture detained a 72-year-old at an undisclosed location yesterday, a statement from Operation Kenova said. Bedfordshire Police Chief Constable Jon Boutcher is investigating the high-ranking British army mole who reputedly led the republican organisation's "nutting squad", an internal security unit which brutally interrogated and murdered sus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Detectives arrest 'Stakeknife' in IRA agent investigation, sources say - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/detectives-arrest-stakeknife-in-ira-agent-investigation-sources-say-36548450.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGRKO1Jpa5THekHUD58-hwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 20:01:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/detectives-arrest-stakeknife-in-ira-agent-investigation-sources-say-36548450.html" target="_blank"&gt;Detectives arrest 'Stakeknife' in IRA agent investigation, sources say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man widely named as the Army's notorious IRA agent Stakeknife has been arrested by detectives, sources said. Freddie Scappaticci has always strongly denied the allegation. A team of independent detectives probing claims of murder, kidnap and torture detained a 72-year-old at an undisclosed location on Tuesday, a statement from Operation Kenova said. Bedfordshire Police Chief Constable Jon Boutcher is investigating the high-ranking Army mole who reputedly led the republican organisation's "nutting squad", an internal security unit which brutally interrogated and murdered suspected spies du...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Army spy 'Stakeknife' who was head of IRA's internal security is arrested in investigation over murders - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/01/30/army-spy-stakeknife-head-iras-internal-security-arrested-investigation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARnT0qmXTVjzic0QhkLoWwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 20:37:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/01/30/army-spy-stakeknife-head-iras-internal-security-arrested-investigation/" target="_blank"&gt;Army spy 'Stakeknife' who was head of IRA's internal security is arrested in investigation over murders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man accused of being the high-level Army mole inside the IRA codenamed Stakeknife has been arrested by police investigating dozens of Troubles-era murders. Fred Scappaticci, who has been widely identified as the notorious agent, was reportedly arrested by police “in connection with the investigation into allegations of murder, kidnap and torture”. Stakeknife reputedly led the republican organisation's "nutting squad", an internal security unit which brutally interrogated and murdered suspected spies during the Troubles. Scappaticci was outed as Stakeknife in 2003, following an investigati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>IRA informer ‘Stakeknife’ arrested in murder investigation - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/jan/30/ira-informer-stakeknife-arrested-in-investigation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQbKEPuQ1HHOhE53ARZ1RsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 17:12:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/jan/30/ira-informer-stakeknife-arrested-in-investigation" target="_blank"&gt;IRA informer ‘Stakeknife’ arrested in murder investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Britain’s most important agents inside the IRA, “Stakeknife”, has been arrested by detectives investigating 18 murders during the Northern Ireland Troubles. Republican and security sources in Belfast confirmed on Tuesday that a 72-year-old man detained by police officers working on Operation Kenova was Freddie Scappaticci. Accused of being the IRA’s chief spycatcher, the Belfast man is accused of being a double agent who was working for the security forces while overseeing the murder of informers within the republican movement. A spokesperson for Operation Kenova said the 72-year-old...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Police question IRA informer 'Stakeknife' over UVF murder - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/jan/31/police-question-ira-informer-stakeknife-over-uvf</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELMpMVcpT5s1_3rbiMyGt74qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 14:35:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/jan/31/police-question-ira-informer-stakeknife-over-uvf" target="_blank"&gt;Police question IRA informer 'Stakeknife' over UVF murder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Belfast man accused of being Britain’s most important agent inside the IRA is being questioned about the murder of a prominent Ulster loyalist terrorist, it has emerged. Detectives were questioning Freddie Scappaticci, 72, who is alleged to have been the British spy known as “Stakeknife” who operated within the IRA for 25 years. He was arrested on Tuesday by officers working on Operation Kenova – a multimillion-pound inquiry into the activities of “Stakeknife” – on suspicion of a number of offences. It is also investigating claims that his British handlers allowed the informer to be invol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>StakeKnife: 'IRA informer' Fred Scappaticci arrested over dozens of murders - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/stakeknife-ira-murder-arrest-troubles-northern-ireland-police-informer-a8186041.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENt_YLF1ZtIgUHxCWRc9J9sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/stakeknife-ira-murder-arrest-troubles-northern-ireland-police-informer-a8186041.html" target="_blank"&gt;StakeKnife: 'IRA informer' Fred Scappaticci arrested over dozens of murders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man who is said to have been the most successful British spy inside the IRA for more than a quarter of a century is believed to have been arrested over his alleged involvement in dozens of killings. Fred Scappaticci, codenamed Stakeknife, from Belfast, was detained in England following an investigation which has been going on for the last 18 months. Mr Scappaticci, 72, whose grandfather went to Ulster from Italy, is said to have infiltrated the highest echelons of the Provisionals and ended up running its feared internal security unit, known as the “Nutting Squad”. He was such a valuabl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Gardaí probe role 'Stakeknife' played in murders here - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/garda-probe-role-stakeknife-played-in-murders-here-36487887.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM8w07qzoMGiDOT510VBka0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/garda-probe-role-stakeknife-played-in-murders-here-36487887.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gardaí probe role 'Stakeknife' played in murders here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officers from the Garda Special Branch are investigating the activities on this side of the Border of the British agent and former head of the Provisional IRA internal security unit Freddie Scappaticci. Gardaí are gathering information on a number of incidents in which Scappaticci was allegedly involved, including the murder of Co Louth farmer Tom Oliver in July 1991. The officers are working in tandem with detectives from Operation Kenova, which was set up in Northern Ireland with a budget of £35m (€39m) to probe Scappaticci and, in particular, whether any lives were sacrificed by the secu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Murdoch's UK paper arm admits computer hacking, fuelling criticism of Sky takeover - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sky-m-a-fox-hack/murdochs-uk-paper-arm-admits-computer-hacking-fuelling-criticism-of-sky-takeover-idUSKBN1CB25F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYan5d1SIFpEykm_F7Q-fIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sky-m-a-fox-hack/murdochs-uk-paper-arm-admits-computer-hacking-fuelling-criticism-of-sky-takeover-idUSKBN1CB25F" target="_blank"&gt;Murdoch's UK paper arm admits computer hacking, fuelling criticism of Sky takeover&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON (Reuters) - Rupert Murdoch's British newspaper group said on Friday one of its titles had hacked the computer of a former intelligence officer, an admission which critics said showed why his takeover of European broadcaster Sky should be blocked. In a hearing at London's High Court, Murdoch's News Group Newspapers admitted "vicarious liability" for the hacking of computers belonging to Ian Hurst, who worked for British military intelligence. The case comes a month after Britain's media minister said regulators should scrutinize Murdoch's planned $15 billion takeover of Sky over conce...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>