<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Alok Verma - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZqYlhsalptcDBNUklDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:29:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>India removes investigative agency head amid probe of deputy - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/65110dec5634479b8b89db6143b3d05a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMMw1WQccJQS4rPzOkPb1MYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:32:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/65110dec5634479b8b89db6143b3d05a" target="_blank"&gt;India removes investigative agency head amid probe of deputy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — The government of India placed the director of the federal investigative agency and his deputy on leave on Wednesday days after the agency filed a case against the deputy alleging that he took bribes to settle a money laundering case. A government appointment committee headed by Prime Minister Narendra Modi put out an order around 2 a.m. Wednesday sending the Central Bureau of Investigation's top two officials on leave and appointing a joint director as the interim head. India's Central Vigilance Commission, an autonomous anti-corruption body, had recommended the removal of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>India's FBI-style police agency hit by infighting, government orders probe - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-police/indias-fbi-style-police-agency-hit-by-infighting-government-orders-probe-idUSKCN1MY1LI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIDkrMqFcxREeoUHmLAn_vAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 12:01:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-police/indias-fbi-style-police-agency-hit-by-infighting-government-orders-probe-idUSKCN1MY1LI" target="_blank"&gt;India's FBI-style police agency hit by infighting, government orders probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's government on Wednesday ordered a probe at the country's top crime fighting bureau after its two senior officers accused each other of bribery and interference in police investigations. The weeks-long public spat between Alok Verma, director of the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI), and his second-in-command, Rakesh Asthana, has embarrassed an agency that serves a similar role as the U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation. The CBI is leading several high profile investigations such as the $2 billion fraud at Punjab National Bank involving fugitive diamond billionaire Nirav Modi, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India's CBI chief removed, critics say 'misuse of power' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/india-cbi-chief-removed-critics-misuse-power-181024085438865.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYg_XZaBL5Kdy2vezpULfsqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 14:58:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/india-cbi-chief-removed-critics-misuse-power-181024085438865.html" target="_blank"&gt;India's CBI chief removed, critics say 'misuse of power'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's government removed the head of the country's top investigating agency and his deputy in a pre-dawn raid on Wednesday - a move the opposition parties and constitutional experts said amounted to "misuse of power". Director of the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI), Alok Verma, and Special Director Rakesh Asthana were asked to go on leave after the premier agency filed a corruption case against Asthana. A feud between the two men has been simmering since before Asthana, who is allegedly close to Prime Minister Narendra Modi, was promoted to the agency's second-highest post last year...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item></channel></rss>