<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Dara Calleary - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNREp5WTJadVloSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:59:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Dara Calleary to replace Ó Cuív as Fianna Fail rural affairs spokesperson - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/dara-calleary-to-replace-cuv-as-fianna-fail-rural-affairs-spokesperson-37602381.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK5t0RFaazn6T0g4KCeutJoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:04:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/dara-calleary-to-replace-cuv-as-fianna-fail-rural-affairs-spokesperson-37602381.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dara Calleary to replace Ó Cuív as Fianna Fail rural affairs spokesperson&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil's deputy leader Dara Calleary is to become the party's rural affairs spokesman, replacing Éamon Ó Cuív.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin makes changes to Fianna Fáil frontbench - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/micheal-martin-makes-changes-to-fianna-fail-frontbench-890374.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENpN6cUpckoZLrott2AZIIgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/micheal-martin-makes-changes-to-fianna-fail-frontbench-890374.html" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin makes changes to Fianna Fáil frontbench&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin has made a number of changes to his party's frontbench. Deputy Leader Dara Calleary will become the party's spokesperson on Regional Development, Rural Affairs and the Gaeltacht, TD John Curran will join the frontbench as Spokesperson for National Drug Policy and Urban Affairs. A statement on the changes was been made by Mr Martin this evening. Deputy Martin says urban regeneration and drugs policy has been entirely neglected by this Government. He also says the appointment of the Deputy Leader to the rural affairs portfolio, demonstrates Fianna Fáil's dete...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>'It's our job to question everyone': PAC says probe into president's spending was 'legitimate' - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/pac-presidents-spending-4377724-Dec2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtJ-LAOq2zzHoUofKWs2FoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:33:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/pac-presidents-spending-4377724-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'It's our job to question everyone': PAC says probe into president's spending was 'legitimate'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MEMBERS OF THE Oireachtas Public Accounts Committee have said they are very concerned about the Taoiseach and other political leaders questioning who and what they investigate. The committee got into hot water before the presidential election when it decided to review the spending of the Office of the President of Ireland. At the time, Taoiseach Leo Varadkar said he was concerned about the scrutinising of presidential spending in the midst of an election campaign, stating that it was “not advisable”. The hearing resulted in confusion surrounding an annual payment of €317,000 that’s been pai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Kevin Doyle: 'TDs have one eye on Brexit and the other on Christmas' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/kevin-doyle-tds-have-one-eye-on-brexit-and-the-other-on-christmas-37587725.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOiZ4A9ljhH_JwzcdlQ9TgAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/kevin-doyle-tds-have-one-eye-on-brexit-and-the-other-on-christmas-37587725.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kevin Doyle: 'TDs have one eye on Brexit and the other on Christmas'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leinster House is in total wind down ahead of the Christmas break, which is still more than a fortnight away. The Dáil spent most of last week being filibustered on abortion while over in the Seanad there's a filibuster trying to prevent the Judicial Appointment Bill from progressing. Brexit is the burning issue, but we're in a holding pattern until at least December 11, when the House of Commons votes on the deal. To fill time and look busy, the Government has been going around launching 'funds' for rural folk, urbanites and even climate change. And in the background, the talks on a new co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>TDs reject ‘means-test’ for access to abortion - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/tds-reject-means-test-for-access-to-abortion-888370.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBJ2N7d5zBAXOA0FQpJvgWoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:47:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/tds-reject-means-test-for-access-to-abortion-888370.html" target="_blank"&gt;TDs reject ‘means-test’ for access to abortion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attempts to ban public funding for abortions could lead to means testing for those seeking terminations and discrimination against impoverished women, TDs have warned. The comments came as the Dáil continued to debate the passage of legislation to enact the Yes vote to grant women access to abortions. Independent TD Carol Nolan had moved a motion in report stage to stop public funds being used for terminations. Carol Nolan Several TDs said the move went against the outcome of the referendum and would lead to a two-tier health system for women in Ireland. Fianna Fáil’s Billy Kelleher said th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Dail hears enquiries into Scouting Ireland abuse allegations extended abroad - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/dail-hears-enquiries-on-scouting-ireland-abuse-probe-extended-abroad-887126.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN4oNV2KFxq2UxKbUwYE97AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 13:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/dail-hears-enquiries-on-scouting-ireland-abuse-probe-extended-abroad-887126.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dail hears enquiries into Scouting Ireland abuse allegations extended abroad&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gardai have reached out to police forces overseas about alleged child sexual abusers who had been involved with Scouting Ireland, the Dáil has been told. Speaking during Leaders' Questions, Minister for Justice Charlie Flanagan said that reports had been made to “police forces in jurisdictions where many of the alleged abusers may be living”. He was responding to questions from Fianna Fail's deputy leader Dara Calleary after revelations on Wednesday that 108 sexual abuse cases involving 71 alleged abusers mainly from the 1960s and 1980s were found within Scouting Ireland. During exchanges, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Calls for helpline to be established for victims of Scouting Ireland - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/news/calls-for-helpline-to-be-established-for-victims-of-scouting-ireland-37555835.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGVRJTHW6WKf-202Jj6wnPcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 15:07:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/news/calls-for-helpline-to-be-established-for-victims-of-scouting-ireland-37555835.html" target="_blank"&gt;Calls for helpline to be established for victims of Scouting Ireland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A special helpline should be set up for victims of sexual abuse during their time in the scouts, Fianna Fáil has said. The party has called for proper supports to be put in place after a review found evidence of 71 suspected abusers and 108 victims mostly dating from the 1960s to the 1980s. There are fears the number of historical abuse cases involving scouting organisations could grow substantially. Fianna Fáil’s deputy leader Dara Calleary said a “huge number of people are affected”. “They were much younger when they suffered the initial abuse, but may not have come forward with their sto...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>'Apart from tweeting' Shane Ross has been 'remarkably mute' on public transport crisis - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/apart-from-tweeting-shane-ross-has-been-remarkably-mute-on-public-transport-crisis-774828.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGbm9uoe142m9NaTrbBjVm4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 12:12:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/apart-from-tweeting-shane-ross-has-been-remarkably-mute-on-public-transport-crisis-774828.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Apart from tweeting' Shane Ross has been 'remarkably mute' on public transport crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil says it will not put forward a motion of no confidence in the Transport Minister, but says Shane Ross can not continue to ignore the crisis in public transport. The Dáil will debate a motion tonight on the future of Bus Éireann, with calls for negotiations on restructuring rather than cost-cutting being imposed on workers. Party members say Minister Ross needs to step in. "He has taken a backseat", says Longford TD Robert Troy (pictured). "He has been remarkably mute in relation to the whole issue. "In fact, I think with exception of the topical issue that both myself and Deputy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Union boss wants members' 'stolen' salaries restored - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/union-boss-wants-members-stolen-salaries-restored-35641113.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHLO6xsOR-c3g9wcy6d3bbMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/union-boss-wants-members-stolen-salaries-restored-35641113.html" target="_blank"&gt;Union boss wants members' 'stolen' salaries restored&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A union chief has condemned "beggar my neighbour" calls to cut public service pensions and warned that unions will not agree to a deal that reduces their entitlements. President of the Public Service Executive Union (PSEU) Maria Ryan said unions may have to build protections for pensions into any agreement at talks due to begin next month. She also warned that State workers face a "big challenge" - due to economic uncertainties including Brexit and the Donald Trump presidency - to get back pay cuts that were "stolen" from them. Ms Ryan said the purported value of public service pensions had...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Union threatens boycott of Labour Court if Leo Varadkar restricts right to strike - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/union-threatens-boycott-of-labour-court-if-leo-varadkar-restricts-right-to-strike-35747812.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAHAdqwpjH211vvrtcajpA0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 17:06:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/union-threatens-boycott-of-labour-court-if-leo-varadkar-restricts-right-to-strike-35747812.html" target="_blank"&gt;Union threatens boycott of Labour Court if Leo Varadkar restricts right to strike&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A union has threatened to boycott the state's chief industrial relations troubleshooting body if aspiring Fine Gael leader Leo Varadkar restricts the right to strike. UNITE Regional Coordinating Officer Richie Browne warned that members would refuse to attend the Labour Court to resolve disputes if the proposal got the go ahead. Mr Varadkar wants to make the court's recommendations binding on workers including air traffic controllers so they cannot reject them and take industrial action. Mr Browne condemned Mr Varadkar's plan as an anti-worker "effort to appeal to his grassroots" at a union...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Finance Minister had 'no hand, act or part' in Nama decision on controversial Project Eagle portfolio - Bruton - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/finance-minister-had-no-hand-act-or-part-in-nama-decision-on-controversial-project-eagle-portfolio-bruton-35456865.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBmtWoyAnyEYjidFVCeVNNcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 13:53:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/finance-minister-had-no-hand-act-or-part-in-nama-decision-on-controversial-project-eagle-portfolio-bruton-35456865.html" target="_blank"&gt;Finance Minister had 'no hand, act or part' in Nama decision on controversial Project Eagle portfolio - Bruton&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finance minister Michael Noonan had "no hand, act, or part" in Nama's decisions regarding the sale of it's controversial Project Eagle portfolio. Education minister Richard Bruton made the remarks as he leapt to the defence of Mr Noonan at leader's questions in the Dáil. He was responding to questions from Fianna Fáil Dara Calleary who raised claims that it was "inappropriate" for the Finance Department to meet representatives of Cerberus - the ultimate buyer of Nama's Northern Ireland loan book prior to the sale. And he put it to Mr Bruton that if Mr Noonan was completely cut off from the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Threat to Budget as O'Dea revolts - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/business/budget/threat-to-budget-as-odea-revolts-36185082.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMgd80WoECm89moTYQ34_gMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wr8qiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 20:16:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/business/budget/threat-to-budget-as-odea-revolts-36185082.html" target="_blank"&gt;Threat to Budget as O'Dea revolts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fail social protection spokesman Willie O'Dea has dramatically intervened in Budget negotiations to demand across-the-board social welfare increases for the elderly, disabled and carers. In a statement aimed more at his own party leadership than Fine Gael, Mr O'Dea spoke of Fianna Fail's "fundamentals", lashed out at plans to give tax cuts to €100,000-a-year earners and warned against a "return to regressive Budgets". His intervention leaves him out on a limb and the prospect now exists that he may not be able to support the Budget should his demands not be met, or alternatively that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Tusla to appear before Dáil committee next week as McCabe controversy rumbles on - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/maurice-mccabe-main-players-3236906-Feb2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJZCjISzqNtCSctuDNMqHr0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 14:50:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/maurice-mccabe-main-players-3236906-Feb2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Tusla to appear before Dáil committee next week as McCabe controversy rumbles on&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Updated 2.50pm TUSLA HAS AGREED to appear before the Oireachtas Committee on Children and Youth Affairs this month, as the row over the scandal related to former garda whistleblower Maurice McCabe continued today. The agency had earlier apologised to McCabe, as part of the ongoing fallout from “a clerical error” from the Child and Family Agency that led to the circulation of a false sex abuse allegation against McCabe. On Friday, the chair of the Children’s Committee, Fine Gael TD Jim Daly tweeted that he had asked the CEO of Tusla to address the “procedures and controls” at the agency. To...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Where will Leo Varadkar find cash to refund water charges this year? - Fianna Fail asks - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/where-will-leo-varadkar-find-cash-to-refund-water-charges-this-year-fianna-fail-asks-35746840.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFx6FH6YFizCdKbIgmZgfGYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 12:54:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/where-will-leo-varadkar-find-cash-to-refund-water-charges-this-year-fianna-fail-asks-35746840.html" target="_blank"&gt;Where will Leo Varadkar find cash to refund water charges this year? - Fianna Fail asks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIANNA Fáil has cast doubt on Leo Varadkar's intention for water charge refunds to be issued this year, questioning where the cash would be found. Mr Varadkar has said that water charges should be refunded to those who paid "as soon as possible" and said he wants to see it happen "this year". His Fine Gael leadership rival Simon Coveney has already warned that this can only happen "if the money is there to pay for it". Now Fianna Fáil has said that the funding isn't in place this year and suggested it's an issue that may take up to two years to resolve. The party's public expenditure spokes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Budget to see cut to USC and change in tax bands - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/budget-to-see-cut-to-usc-and-change-in-tax-bands-808578.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECXgeqj2Y171soXdlDmlb2IqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 05:45:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/budget-to-see-cut-to-usc-and-change-in-tax-bands-808578.html" target="_blank"&gt;Budget to see cut to USC and change in tax bands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a cut to the Universal Social Charge in next week's budget. The Irish Independent reports there will also be a change to income tax bands as Finance Minister Paschal Donohue negotiates a deal with Fianna Fáil. The USC cut will help the so-called "squeezed middle" earning up to €70,000 a year, while the tax band tweak will benefit those on over €33,800. But the overall increase in workers' pay slips is likely to be less than €20 a month. Meanwhile, Fianna Fáil’s finance spokesman Micheal McGrath and public expenditure spokesman Dara Calleary are meeting with Mr Donohoe this wee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Industrial relations unrest could have been avoided, says Fianna Fáil - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/industrial-relations-unrest-could-have-been-avoided-says-fianna-fail-763696.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJF9IV_mJMCMwMsdaamRnysqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:04:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/industrial-relations-unrest-could-have-been-avoided-says-fianna-fail-763696.html" target="_blank"&gt;Industrial relations unrest could have been avoided, says Fianna Fáil&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil has said that the current industrial relations unrest in the public sector could have been avoided if the Government took action. Party spokesperson on Public Expenditure and Reform Dara Calleary said that if a commission on public pay - due to begin its work in the New Year - had been established earlier, it would have calmed unions concerns. His comments come after Gardaí cancelled their strike, teachers downed tools and 10,000 community-sector workers are threatening to ballot on industrial action. Deputy Calleary said that procrastination on the issue has lead to a creation ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Once again, Fianna Fáil is where egos dare - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/once-again-fianna-fil-is-where-egos-dare-35422776.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAWRQxVxI6RrelLoavMIr7cqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/once-again-fianna-fil-is-where-egos-dare-35422776.html" target="_blank"&gt;Once again, Fianna Fáil is where egos dare&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latest rumour is that they will issue sunglasses to Fianna Fáil ard fheis delegates sitting in the first three rows to protect their eyes from the bright light shining from new star signing Stephen Donnelly. And that is not the only health and safety issue, of a political nature, arising from Micheál Martin's move to recruit the Wicklow Independent TD - who looked in briefly on the foundation of the Social Democrats in 2015, and had made slagging off Fianna Fáil one of his specialist subjects for several years. Let's acknowledge that the move is a very good one for Mr Martin and Fianna Fáil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>FF not convinced Whelan appointment was lawful - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2017/0622/884642-dail-politics/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0tULDT495WT75LfTBLZksqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 13:24:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2017/0622/884642-dail-politics/" target="_blank"&gt;FF not convinced Whelan appointment was lawful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin will not be withdrawing remarks made in the Dáil about the appointment of Máire Whelan, according to the party's Spokesperson on Public Expenditure and Reform. Dara Calleary said focusing on Mr Martin's remarks was just a distraction from the core element of this issue, which was the process by which the former attorney general was appointed to the Court of Appeal. Speaking on RTÉ’s Morning Ireland, he said the appointment process had been flawed and arrogant and that Fianna Fáil is unconvinced that the appointment was lawful. Mr Calleary said a phone call ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Government pressing ahead with Whelan appointment - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/ireland/2017/0618/883626-politics/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELWZ85oC8dSUp0grJu3VGo4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 21:49:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/ireland/2017/0618/883626-politics/" target="_blank"&gt;Government pressing ahead with Whelan appointment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Government is pressing ahead with the appointment of former Attorney General Maire Whelan to the Court of Appeal. Despite controversy surrounding the move, Ms Whelan's appointment will be formalised by the President tomorrow morning. Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin warned that the Irish judicial system is at risk of being undermined by the appointment of Ms Whelan to the Court of Appeal. Speaking last night, Mr Martin said: "This row has the potential to undermine the stature of the judiciary" and added that "Ms Whelan should consider her position". However, the Government continues t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>'Thanks for calling Katherine' - Frances Fitzgerald has torrid time of it explaining her role in Tusla saga - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/frances-fitzgerald-the-week-in-politics-3235988-Feb2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAB8xFAPyyKQQIoZLMZrvEEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 12:57:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/frances-fitzgerald-the-week-in-politics-3235988-Feb2017/" target="_blank"&gt;'Thanks for calling Katherine' - Frances Fitzgerald has torrid time of it explaining her role in Tusla saga&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FRANCES FITZGERALD INSISTS that the first she knew of the ongoing Tusla scandal regarding Sergeant Maurice McCabe was when the story was broadcast on RTÉ’s Prime Time last Thursday. A clearly flustered Fitzgerald has undergone a torrid interrogation session on RTÉ’s The Week in Politics, but has stuck to her guns and insisted that her story “is the truth”. “Katherine Zappone telephoned me on the day she was meeting Maurice McCabe, 25 January, I remember distinctly taking the call,” she said. I said ‘thanks for calling Katherine’, and that was it. Obviously I wasn’t going to say yes or no, i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>FF to demand renegotiation if new FG leader attempts to introduce new policies - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ff-to-demand-renegotiation-if-new-fg-leader-attempts-to-introduce-new-policies-790841.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdWxdikFEDX1Xf_nsjkPIwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 12:00:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ff-to-demand-renegotiation-if-new-fg-leader-attempts-to-introduce-new-policies-790841.html" target="_blank"&gt;FF to demand renegotiation if new FG leader attempts to introduce new policies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil will demand a renegotiation of the Confidence and Supply Agreement if the new Fine Gael leader attempts to introduce new policies into the Programme for Government, writes Political reporter Elaine Loughlin. It comes after both Simon Coveney and Leo Varadkar published policy documents outlining the changes they would make if elected leader. Speaking outside Leinster House this morning, Fianna Fáil's public expenditure spokesman Dara Calleary said: "At this stage we are maintaining the Confidence and Supply Agreement, the internal Fine Gael decision is a matter for Fine Gael we h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Former Labour Court boss to head up pay body - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/former-labour-court-boss-to-head-up-pay-body-35138835.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELUdRQfMdxzCFZJdK7_ZNMEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/former-labour-court-boss-to-head-up-pay-body-35138835.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Labour Court boss to head up pay body&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The former chairman of the Labour Court Kevin Duffy has been appointed chairman of the new body tasked with examining public sector pay. Public Expenditure Minister Paschal Donohoe is to bring a memo to Cabinet which will formally establish the new public sector pay commission. The commission will examine all issues surrounding public sector pay as the country braces itself for a winter of industrial action. Mr Duffy also heads up the water commission. He and his team are due to report back to the Government in the Spring on the shape of any new pay deal beyond the Lansdowne Road Agreement,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Latest: NBRU claims Bus Éireann dispute could develop into something they cannot control - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/dara-calleary-transport-minister-can-follow-precedent-and-intervene-in-bus-dispute-783993.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcFUttm5bclLNR3qwAWtHIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 06:46:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/dara-calleary-transport-minister-can-follow-precedent-and-intervene-in-bus-dispute-783993.html" target="_blank"&gt;Latest: NBRU claims Bus Éireann dispute could develop into something they cannot control&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Update 2pm: The National Bus and Rail Union is warning that unofficial 'wildcat' strikes by Bus Éireann workers could happen again. The NBRU has insisted they were not involved in yesterday morning's action, which shut down virtually all Irish Rail and Dublin Bus services for several hours. The union also says that, despite reports, they have not received notice of legal action from those companies looking to recoup lost profits. General Secretary of the NBRU Dermot O'Leary says until a resolution is reached, he cannot guarantee there will not be more wildcat strikes. He said: "My union was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Shane Ross: Bus Éireann's €6m losses unsustainable - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/shane-ross-bus-eireanns-6m-losses-unsustainable-773215.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIbP8J8BFUDHp85DaAIh8lMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 18:34:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/shane-ross-bus-eireanns-6m-losses-unsustainable-773215.html" target="_blank"&gt;Shane Ross: Bus Éireann's €6m losses unsustainable&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Transport Minister Shane Ross has said the losses in Bus Éireann, of €6m a year, are unsustainable. Details of this report were leaked to the media last week. It is understood to recommend the closure of the loss-making Expressway service. However, Shane Ross said an internal report commissioned by the bus operator, suggesting the Expressway service could be closed, was only a draft version. The Minister has been under fire after failing to ask Bus Éireann for a copy of the review carried out by consultants Grant Thornton. Fianna Fáil TD Dara Calleary said that when he was briefed by th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Fianna Fáil 'ready' for snap election and won't support Varadkar's 'flimsy' proposal banning strikes - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/fianna-fail-ready-for-snap-election-and-wont-support-varadkars-flimsy-proposal-banning-strikes-790878.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGgWwpiQkJ2YANrPk5HfVskqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 15:08:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/fianna-fail-ready-for-snap-election-and-wont-support-varadkars-flimsy-proposal-banning-strikes-790878.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fianna Fáil 'ready' for snap election and won't support Varadkar's 'flimsy' proposal banning strikes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil has said it is ready for a snap election at any time and could have candidates selected in a matter of days. The party says it is committed to the confidence and supply agreement so long as the new Fine Gael leader and Taoiseach lives up to it too. They have also rounded on Leo Varadkar's proposals to ban workers in essential sectors from striking. Public expenditure spokesperson, Dara Calleary says they would not support it. "In the context of public service pay talks getting underway the timing of the proposals are unhelpful, and I would ask that both candidates would give the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Ross criticised for handling of Bus Éireann issues - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0119/846283-bus-eireann/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC7rnD6_BR0p1GQwJwjQAAAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 21:13:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0119/846283-bus-eireann/" target="_blank"&gt;Ross criticised for handling of Bus Éireann issues&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minister for Transport Shane Ross has been criticised for his handling of concerns over the future of Bus Éireann. In the Dáil this afternoon, Fianna Fáil TD Dara Calleary said the minister "needs to step up to the mark and deal with the issue. Mr Calleary's party colleague Robert Troy also questioned whether the minister had read a report into the company which was carried out by Grant Thornton. Details of this report - including the recommended closure of the loss-making Expressway service, which handles intercity routes - were leaked to the media last week. Mr Ross responded that he has ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Answers to one political poll that really matters - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/answers-to-one-political-poll-that-really-matters-35333052.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJtJkf2lHBKGvT0TLrPW_BwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/answers-to-one-political-poll-that-really-matters-35333052.html" target="_blank"&gt;Answers to one political poll that really matters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. The Marker 2. The O'Donovan Rossa Cumann 3. He will become the longest serving Fine Gael Taoiseach ever, taking over from John A Costello. WT Cosgrave served longer but he was leader of Cumann na nGaedheal and never held the title of Taoiseach - he was president of the executive council. 4. Two - James Reilly and Alex White 5. Shane Ross. 6. Katherine Zappone. 7. Eleven - Fine Gael, Fianna Fail, Sinn Fein, Labour, AAA-PBP, Independent Alliance, Independents 4 Change, Rural Alliance, Social Democrats, Green Party, Workers &amp; Unemployed Action Group. 8. Four. 9. 59 votes in favour of Kenny,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Taxpayers are kept in the dark on mandarins' mystery pay increases - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/taxpayers-are-kept-in-the-dark-on-mandarins-mystery-pay-increases-35406251.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMjfytimHzwfKcJwjY_8ZEAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/taxpayers-are-kept-in-the-dark-on-mandarins-mystery-pay-increases-35406251.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taxpayers are kept in the dark on mandarins' mystery pay increases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like it or not, the cold reality is high-ranking civil servants run the country. Politicians come and go. Some stay longer than others. Some leave a lasting legacy, while others are little more than a footnote in the history books. When an election is called, those who have been successful enough to become ministers gather up their belongings from their desks before saying goodbye to their departmental staff. The secretary general of the department will be standing at the door waving them off as the politician packs their personal effects into the boot of their car. Then they close the door...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Unions scramble for pay deals with €2bn on State table - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/unions-scramble-for-pay-deals-with-2bn-on-state-table-35481233.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJqFWH2tUfa_PmtMjlCEE6gqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/unions-scramble-for-pay-deals-with-2bn-on-state-table-35481233.html" target="_blank"&gt;Unions scramble for pay deals with €2bn on State table&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unions are clamouring for extras worth more than €2bn as a pay rush takes hold ahead of government talks on a new public sector wage deal this summer. Workers are vying to get in first for wage hikes and big changes to their terms and conditions as a new body advising the Government on its pay policy has begun meeting staff representative groups. But Fianna Fáil spokesperson on Public Expenditure and Reform Dara Calleary warned there is no scope for further pay rises before the Lansdowne Road Agreement runs out in September next year. He said unions' demands for the full restoration of cuts...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Varadkar’s big ideas on transport and tax will cost €5bn - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/varadkars-big-ideas-on-transport-and-tax-will-cost-5bn-35749474.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFn4F86RJn0Tip0_-aRAI6AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/varadkars-big-ideas-on-transport-and-tax-will-cost-5bn-35749474.html" target="_blank"&gt;Varadkar’s big ideas on transport and tax will cost €5bn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leo Varadkar's initial plans to cut taxes and improve the country's transport network will cost €5bn, the Irish Independent can reveal. The Social Protection Minister has set out a series of "big projects" which he would prioritise as taoiseach, including a metro for Dublin and a motorway to the north-west. He also wants to reduce the marginal tax rate on workers earning over €70,000 from 52pc, down to 50pc. This move alone will cost €300m in a full year. The figures were revealed as Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin suggested that Mr Varadkar was being fed information from colleagues who s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Donohoe backed by FF in bid to slash income tax - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/donohoe-backed-by-ff-in-bid-to-slash-income-tax-35524420.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEu0G9uRih5Wjl1FkEj7vz8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/donohoe-backed-by-ff-in-bid-to-slash-income-tax-35524420.html" target="_blank"&gt;Donohoe backed by FF in bid to slash income tax&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil's most influential TDs have rowed in behind Public Expenditure Minister Paschal Donohoe's plans to slash tax as part of Ireland's response to Brexit. Mr Donohoe's call for a reduced tax burden for workers has kicked off the negotiations ahead of Budget 2018. As British Prime Minister Theresa May prepares to trigger the Brexit negotiations as early as this week, Mr Donohoe insisted our marginal tax rate of 49.5pc is putting Irish jobs in jeopardy. Fianna Fáil last night expressed its support for tax cuts in a move that will come as a boost to Fine Gael. However, a potentially sig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>HSE campaign cost €250,000 - but lured just 88 nurses home - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/hse-campaign-cost-250000-but-lured-just-88-nurses-home-36056056.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENK3MxGPgDBlPs8beJX0_tcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/hse-campaign-cost-250000-but-lured-just-88-nurses-home-36056056.html" target="_blank"&gt;HSE campaign cost €250,000 - but lured just 88 nurses home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A HSE recruitment campaign, which only succeeded in wooing 88 Irish nurses home from the UK, cost €250,000, it emerged yesterday. The 'Bring Them Home' campaign was aimed at attracting 500 of the 7,500 nurses who emigrated to the UK in recent years back to Irish hospitals. However, the full expense has only now emerged. It included paying €198,000 to recruitment agencies but failed to deliver a substantial number of candidates to hospitals which are desperate to fill nursing vacancies. Audrey Doyle, a HSE official in the human resources division, said advertising, as well as the design and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Dara Calleary: Dept must have 'one very big sofa' to be able to afford public sector pay rise - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/dara-calleary-dept-must-have-one-very-big-sofa-to-be-able-to-afford-public-sector-pay-rise-772931.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOKL-VsqUWIvdRXzP9vHijIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 11:43:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/dara-calleary-dept-must-have-one-very-big-sofa-to-be-able-to-afford-public-sector-pay-rise-772931.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dara Calleary: Dept must have 'one very big sofa' to be able to afford public sector pay rise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil's warning the Public Expenditure Minister they will be keeping a close eye on him to ensure there is no reduction in services to fund the public servants pay deal. Yesterday Paschal Donohoe announced he is bringing forward a pay rise for tens of thousands of public servants at a cost of €120m. Fianna Fáil's Dara Calleary says he is not satisfied at how the minister is able to find money repeatedly that is not in the budget. Mr Calleary said: "The hour before the Budget on the morning of the Budget, they found €100m, then they found €50m for the guards, found €120m yesterday. "I ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>'My stomach churned' - the nation reacts to the Tusla controversy - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/my-stomach-churned-the-nation-reacts-to-the-tusla-controversy-35440075.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHZMneRRD-ZBJ2cEw2g_H98qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 12:49:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/my-stomach-churned-the-nation-reacts-to-the-tusla-controversy-35440075.html" target="_blank"&gt;'My stomach churned' - the nation reacts to the Tusla controversy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Political reaction to revelations on RTE's Prime Time that a mistaken allegation of digital rape of a child was linked to garda whistleblower Maurice McCabe due to a clerical error. Health Minister Simon Harris has said the child and family agency should apologise immediately and did not need to wait for the commission of investigation into an alleged smear campaign against Mr McCabe concludes. "I think they should explain why an apology hasn't issued to Sergeant McCabe, when it was clearly their intention to do so," he added. "I think they should issue that apology forthwith," he told News...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Donohoe plans to fight cases over consultants' pay - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/health/2017/0126/847942-consultants-pay/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENC_hysCeqQJcQ8-L36jUeYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 23:51:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/health/2017/0126/847942-consultants-pay/" target="_blank"&gt;Donohoe plans to fight cases over consultants' pay&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minister for Public Expenditure and Reform Paschal Donohoe has told the Dáil that the Government would "vigorously defend" future cases in relation to consultants' contracts. He was speaking after it emerged that the Health Service Executive formally withdrew an appeal against compensation awards for two consultants over the failure by the State to pay them agreed levels of salary eight years ago. Speaking in the Dáil this afternoon, Mr Donohoe said he would not comment on the details of the two individual cases agreed overnight. However, he said there were a number of other cases which wer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>If Donnelly pulls this off he could end up as party leader - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/business/if-donnelly-pulls-this-off-he-could-end-up-as-party-leader-35443590.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ9IJU2pIbBTNdbPvhHu9ykqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wr8qiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/business/if-donnelly-pulls-this-off-he-could-end-up-as-party-leader-35443590.html" target="_blank"&gt;If Donnelly pulls this off he could end up as party leader&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stephen Donnelly's decision to "apply to join the Fianna Fail parliamentary party" recently met a few reactions. Among politicos it was, "I told you so" or "That was obvious from last September". Nothing is truly obvious until it happens, because there are usually lots of little things that can get in the way. A year ago, Donnelly almost certainly couldn't have seen himself in Fianna Fail, and would have honestly said so. But things change. Nothing is written in the stars. The reaction among the liberal-left elite for whom he was something of a darling was more interesting. There was horror...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>GRA demands to know why it was excluded from pay talks - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/gra-demands-to-know-why-it-was-excluded-from-pay-talks-35376604.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3fKlfE3Xi2yeIzhJflHCsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/gra-demands-to-know-why-it-was-excluded-from-pay-talks-35376604.html" target="_blank"&gt;GRA demands to know why it was excluded from pay talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Garda Representative Association (GRA) has demanded to know why it was excluded from the recent round of pay negotiations with Minister Paschal Donohoe. It comes after the Public Expenditure Minister announced he is bringing forward a €1,000 pay increase for other public sector workers by five months. He took the action to appease the demands of the Irish Congress of Trade Unions (ICTU) after gardaí received a €50m pay deal following the Labour Court ruling that averted a strike late last year. Despite this, the GRA was not included in the talks that led to the acceleration of pay hikes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>False sex abuse allegations against McCabe circulated due to Tusla 'clerical error' - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/maurice-mccabe-allegations-3232271-Feb2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAbst4U7ZWYE8Oeg05QaIEkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 07:39:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/maurice-mccabe-allegations-3232271-Feb2017/" target="_blank"&gt;False sex abuse allegations against McCabe circulated due to Tusla 'clerical error'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE LATEST twist in the whistleblower saga, it was revealed yesterday that the country’s child and family agency Tusla sent gardaí a file that contained false allegations of sexual abuse against Sergeant Maurice McCabe. It has emerged an allegation of sexual abuse on a young woman was included in a report to Tusla by a counsellor in April 2014. One month later the counsellor contacted the agency to say she made “an administrative error” – she had accidentally pasted the line into her report. The revelation was first reported by the Irish Examiner yesterday and then outlined last night in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Pressure builds on Government over teachers’ dispute - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/pressure-builds-on-government-over-teachers-dispute-35166647.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHmf2Cz3ECr8HlA8SF-CkwgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 11:40:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/pressure-builds-on-government-over-teachers-dispute-35166647.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pressure builds on Government over teachers’ dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A total of 23 unions, representing 300,000 public sector workers, have made good deals on pay restoration, Tánaiste Frances Fitzgerald has told the Dáil. As secondary schools remained closed across the country, opposition TDs increased pressure on the Government about this and the upcoming garda dispute. Fianna Fáil’s Dara Calleary said 250,000 secondary school students were at home today while 17,500 secondary teachers in the ASTI union were on strike over pay equality for new teachers. Sinn Féin’s Mary Lou McDonald said pay equality for young teachers recruited after 2011 had to be Govern...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>'I am not scaremongering': Bus Eireann boss warns all jobs could be lost if drastic action not taken - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/bus-eireann-3-3204151-Jan2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN-ssLW9Ggql_ikRk_HG4jgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/bus-eireann-3-3204151-Jan2017/" target="_blank"&gt;'I am not scaremongering': Bus Eireann boss warns all jobs could be lost if drastic action not taken&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACTING CEO of Bus Eireann has warned an Oireachtas committee that the entire company will be insolvent by the end of the year if drastic action is not taken. Ray Hernan told the Transport Committee he wrote to all staff last week to inform them that organisation’s finances were in a “critical state”. He said if something is not done now, the entire company will go bust. That is why I am saying there is such an urgency to implement an emergency plan. All the company, not just Expressway will go out of business… all jobs will be lost… This is not scaremongering. Hernan said he is determined t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>FF: Minister 'seems to be some sort of magician' when it comes to public sector pay rise - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/ff-minister-seems-to-be-some-sort-of-magician-when-it-comes-to-public-sector-pay-rise-772819.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN23Ztaw8WG5VTd6-QF8OYIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 16:17:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/ff-minister-seems-to-be-some-sort-of-magician-when-it-comes-to-public-sector-pay-rise-772819.html" target="_blank"&gt;FF: Minister 'seems to be some sort of magician' when it comes to public sector pay rise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Government is refusing to spell out how it is going to fund a pay rise for public servants. Cabinet has approved a €20 a week pay rise for tens of thousands of workers from April, five months sooner than expected. The Public Expenditure Minister says "efficiencies and savings" will deliver the extra €120m. Public servants earning less than €65,000 were due a €1,000 pay rise under Lansdowne Road from next September. However, after the special Garda deal from the Labour Court the Government now says it will bring forward that €20 a week pay rise to April 1, 2017, for all other public serv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>No houses have been built with €400 million from Bord Gáis sale - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/bord-gais-sale-social-housing-3313108-Mar2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGK9r_EdqjKKZokCidfIhacqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 05:10:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/bord-gais-sale-social-housing-3313108-Mar2017/" target="_blank"&gt;No houses have been built with €400 million from Bord Gáis sale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE GOVERNMENT HASN’T built one social housing unit with the money they got from selling Bord Gáis Energy, despite promising that’s how it would be used. In Budget 2015 the government announced that €400 million of the proceeds of the sale of Bord Gáis Energy was to be used to build additional housing units in support of the government’s Social Housing Strategy. In response to questions posed by Dara Calleary of Fianna Fáil, housing minister Simon Coveney said that there was no evidence any social housing had been built with the funds. “Work on this activity was carried out by my Department...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Fianna Fáil confirm it will abstain from no confidence motion in Government - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/fianna-fail-confirm-it-will-abstain-from-no-confidence-motion-in-government-776792.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBnK10GZAmCjTtKKck6i5e8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 18:08:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/fianna-fail-confirm-it-will-abstain-from-no-confidence-motion-in-government-776792.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fianna Fáil confirm it will abstain from no confidence motion in Government&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil has confirmed that it will abstain on a motion of no confidence in the Government, this week. The party says there are questions to answer and it will be seeking further clarification from the Taoiseach on the handling of the Garda whistleblower controversy. But Fianna Fail's Expenditure and Reform Spokesperson, Dara Calleary (pictured) says Sinn Fein's motion is not what the country needs: "The motion of confidence that Sinn Fein is putting down is entirely opportunitistic at this point. "All it is is political game playing, we want answers as to what happened to this situation...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>FF 'not holding its breath' on plan for 50:50 gender split in the civil service - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/ff-not-holding-its-breath-on-plan-for-5050-gender-split-in-the-civil-service-35370053.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEICMLplB_VR8mwdjC2-reaIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/ff-not-holding-its-breath-on-plan-for-5050-gender-split-in-the-civil-service-35370053.html" target="_blank"&gt;FF 'not holding its breath' on plan for 50:50 gender split in the civil service&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil TD Dara Calleary says he is sceptical that Public Expenditure Minister Paschal Donohoe will achieve a 50:50 gender split in job appointments at the top of the civil service. While welcoming the minister's plan for improving gender balance, Mr Calleary is not confident it will succeed given the failure to meet existing quotas on State boards. Mr Donohoe last night announced a range of initiatives aimed at increasing the number of women being appointed to senior civil service roles. At present, just two of the secretary generals of Government departments are women. Mr Donohoe said...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>State is not an ATM, Donohoe warns ahead of talks on new deal - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/state-is-not-an-atm-donohoe-warns-ahead-of-talks-on-new-deal-35698885.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDae697mB_PavB5sO3wJP84qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/state-is-not-an-atm-donohoe-warns-ahead-of-talks-on-new-deal-35698885.html" target="_blank"&gt;State is not an ATM, Donohoe warns ahead of talks on new deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public Expenditure Minister Paschal Donohoe said the public sector pay report will not lead to the opening of an "ATM". Mr Donohoe said the report makes clear that any pay increases in the future must be linked to the delivery of reform and improvements in productivity. The new pay talks are due to begin by the end of the month, however, Mr Donohoe said he would not he putting a deadline on their completion. "There is not the prospect of an ATM being created in relation to this for the simple reason that the demands in relation to resources available are just hugely significant," he said. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>More than half of Government's State boards fail to meet gender quota - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/more-than-half-of-governments-state-boards-fail-to-meet-gender-quota-35336950.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKutoif_YRicnuPIWkscfYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/more-than-half-of-governments-state-boards-fail-to-meet-gender-quota-35336950.html" target="_blank"&gt;More than half of Government's State boards fail to meet gender quota&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than half of the country's State boards are falling short of the gender quotas set down in law. Some 97 boards have less than 40pc female or male membership, with those under the remit of Agriculture Minister Michael Creed, Housing Minister Simon Coveney and Transport Minister Shane Ross among the worst. An analysis of 180 boards by the Irish Independent shows gender quotas are being largely ignored by ministers. This comes despite recent proposals from Mr Ross's department to withhold funding from sporting organisations unless they fulfil a gender quota on their boards. Under laws int...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>FF insists pay hikes for nurses and doctors must be priority - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/ff-insists-pay-hikes-for-nurses-and-doctors-must-be-priority-35666674.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJSEuBZYnVJuGFu5fxTKRxYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/ff-insists-pay-hikes-for-nurses-and-doctors-must-be-priority-35666674.html" target="_blank"&gt;FF insists pay hikes for nurses and doctors must be priority&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fail is set to put huge pressure on the Government to prioritise wage hikes for doctors and nurses working in under-pressure public hospitals when pay talks begin next month. The party will insist Public Expenditure and Reform Minister Paschal Donohoe urgently addresses the critical number of vacancies in the health service due an ongoing brain drain crisis in the sector. Last night, a source close to Donohoe said the next public sector pay deal would be "collective". "There will be no sectoral specific wage deals," he added. However, it is understood there could be some focus on ind...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Proposed Brexit deal will be put to Dáil vote - Taoiseach - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/proposed-brexit-deal-will-be-put-to-dil-vote-taoiseach-37527804.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFnVrXgFZpbGqFsyIjp-Op8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wr8qiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/proposed-brexit-deal-will-be-put-to-dil-vote-taoiseach-37527804.html" target="_blank"&gt;Proposed Brexit deal will be put to Dáil vote - Taoiseach&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE proposed Brexit deal will be put to a vote in Dáil Éireann, Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has announced. Ministers met this morning to be briefed on the 500-page document which it is hoped will break the deadlock in the talks. All eyes will shift to London this afternoon to see if Prime Minister Theresa May can get the backing of her Cabinet to sign-up to the deal. It includes a UK-wide customs arrangement that will ensure there is no hard border on the island of Ireland. Speaking in the Dáil this afternoon, Mr Varadkar said that meeting would be “very important and sensitive”. The Taoiseach t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin to decide Eamon Ó Cuív's fate today for launching candidate without permission - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/eamon-cuiv-fianna-fail-4329018-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVL_YsitSH4qHly7l-WF-EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 10:16:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/eamon-cuiv-fianna-fail-4329018-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin to decide Eamon Ó Cuív's fate today for launching candidate without permission&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIANNA FÁÍL LEADER Micheál Martin has said he will consider Eamon Ó Cuív’s frontbench position after he went rogue and announced a local election candidate in Tyrone without Martin’s permission. At an event late last month, councillor Sorcha McAnespy, who is already a member of the party’s national executive, was announced as Fianna Fáíl’s candidate in the local elections – the party’s first steps across the border. Standing next to TD Éamon Ó Cuív, the spokesperson on Regional Development, Rural Affairs and the Gaeltacht, as well as Senator Mark Daly, McAnespy is holding a photo of herself...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Public need to know there are no more 'dangerous doctors' in health system - FF - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/public-need-to-know-there-are-no-more-dangerous-doctors-in-health-system-ff-37507494.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJU7VIhh58m2h3GwIvlLuC8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 16:56:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/public-need-to-know-there-are-no-more-dangerous-doctors-in-health-system-ff-37507494.html" target="_blank"&gt;Public need to know there are no more 'dangerous doctors' in health system - FF&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who are sick badly need to be reassured that there are no more “dangerous doctors” working in the health services. Fianna Fáil TD Dara Calleary said the comments by the High Court President about big flaws in doctor recruitment procedures raised very serious concerns among people who are ill and their families. Mr Calleary said Mr Justice Kelly’s “scathing comments” about Health Service Executive’s deficient recruitment procedures raised the most serious questions about patient safety. The Fianna Fáil deputy leader said just two years ago very serious questions were raised about the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin disciplines senator for launching Fianna Fáil candidate in the North - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/fianna-fail-mark-daly-north-candidate-4327419-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHkBzrr_QaFsHl2lNer0N34qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 12:37:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/fianna-fail-mark-daly-north-candidate-4327419-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin disciplines senator for launching Fianna Fáil candidate in the North&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIANNA FÁIL LEADER Micheál Martin has disciplined a senator who took part in what appeared to be the launch of a candidate in Northern Ireland. Martin has sacked Senator Mark Daly as the party’s deputy leader in the Seanad and has taken away his portfolio as Seanad spokesperson for Foreign Affairs, Diaspora and Brexit. Galway West TD Éamon Ó Cuív also took part in the launch, but there is no word yet as to whether he will face similar sanctions. Ó Cuív is the party’s frontbench spokesman on rural affairs. In a statement, using perhaps more delicate language, the party said Martin has “reass...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Hiring of ‘rogue’ doctors to be addressed urgently, says Coveney - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/hiring-of-rogue-doctors-to-be-addressed-urgently-says-coveney-884193.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELogVXlAMODz1cVKFLwxucQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 05:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/hiring-of-rogue-doctors-to-be-addressed-urgently-says-coveney-884193.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hiring of ‘rogue’ doctors to be addressed urgently, says Coveney&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concerns over the hiring of “rogue” doctors will be examined as part of a review of recruitment by the health service and will be urgently addressed by the HSE, according to Tánaiste Simon Coveney. His assurances came after the suspension of a maternity hospital doctor who did not meet basic standards. The President of the High Court, Mr Justice Peter Kelly, this week referred concerns about recruitment of doctors, following the case, to the Health Minister Simon Harris and the HSE. In the Dáil yesterday during leaders’ questions, Fianna Fáil deputy leader Dara Calleary sought a Government ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Dangerous doctors being hired by HSE, judge warns - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/courts/dangerous-doctors-being-hired-by-hse-judge-warns-37505034.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIFZ52Q-3a0H5OOlsEseyVEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/courts/dangerous-doctors-being-hired-by-hse-judge-warns-37505034.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dangerous doctors being hired by HSE, judge warns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with “little knowledge of the basics of medicine” are being allowed to work in hospitals here due to “defective” recruitment in the HSE, a leading judge warned. High Court President Mr Justice Peter Kelly warned starkly of the “obvious danger to patients” as doctors lacking basic skills are being employed. The judge will now contact Health Minister Simon Harris and the head of the HSE over the alarming concerns about recruitment of medical staff. He made the startling comments in the case of a junior doctor in a maternity unit who was suspended from practising by the High Court. Othe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>‘Fianna Fáil needs somebody like Peter Casey to shake it up,’ election runner-up insists - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fianna-fail-needs-somebody-like-peter-casey-to-shake-it-up-election-runner-up-insists-881943.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMqJdiyV0CyWIQ9r1iaZyucqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 03:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fianna-fail-needs-somebody-like-peter-casey-to-shake-it-up-election-runner-up-insists-881943.html" target="_blank"&gt;‘Fianna Fáil needs somebody like Peter Casey to shake it up,’ election runner-up insists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil TDs have outright rejected Peter Casey’s calls to allow him to join and make him party leader, saying he would be “eaten alive” in real politics and will never be welcomed because he is “scapegoating” minority groups. Presidential candidate Peter Casey with his wife Helen at their home in Greencastle in North Donegal. (North West Newspix) A dozen Fianna Fáil TDs backed the party hierarchy’s decision to ignore Mr Casey’s takeover overtures, despite one TD privately saying the businessman’s controversial remarks about Travellers are “the one thing most of us think”. Mr Casey finis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>FF's deputy leader says it was 'premature' for McAnespy to be told she would be a candidate in NI elections - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/fianna-fail-northern-ireland-candidate-sorcha-mcanespy-4307047-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJez0tt2Q_8UR1J_KwxHPd0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/fianna-fail-northern-ireland-candidate-sorcha-mcanespy-4307047-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;FF's deputy leader says it was 'premature' for McAnespy to be told she would be a candidate in NI elections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEPUTY LEADER OF Fianna Fáil Dara Calleary has said it was “premature” for Councillor Sorcha McAnespy to be told she would be a Fianna Fáil candidate at the next local elections in the north. The Tyrone councillor was announced as a candidate at an event last night without the full backing of the party. However, she states she was told by Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin that “she would be the candidate” in the next elections. Utter confusion has reigned since yesterday’s event in Tyrone when McAnespy, who is an independent councillor, and a member of the Fianna Fáil’s national executive, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Peter Casey says he wants Micheál Martin's job because the FF leader is 'too nice' to take on Leo Varadkar - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/peter-casey-fianna-fail-2-4311478-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHvqHbb2ZkvQ6jQJeDPWJr0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 13:57:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/peter-casey-fianna-fail-2-4311478-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Peter Casey says he wants Micheál Martin's job because the FF leader is 'too nice' to take on Leo Varadkar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETER CASEY HAS said that he wants to replace Micheál Martin as Fianna Fáil leader, claiming that Martin is “too nice” to challenge Taoiseach Leo Varadkar. The runner-up in the presidential election spoke yesterday about his desire to run for the Dáil in Donegal, despite Fianna Fáil already having chosen their two candidates for the next general election. Casey’s courting of Fianna Fáil was rejected by party deputies Timmy Dooley and Niall Collins but speaking on RTÉ’s Today with Sean O’Rourke, Casey said that he has yet to speak to the either of them or to Martin. “I can certainly understa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Confidence and supply talks begin this afternoon - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/confidence-and-supply-talks-begin-this-afternoon-881027.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO11xyW62dGFDleCMk1ENvsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 06:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/confidence-and-supply-talks-begin-this-afternoon-881027.html" target="_blank"&gt;Confidence and supply talks begin this afternoon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Confidence and supply talks between Fine Gael and Fianna Fáil will begin this afternoon. The two parties will meet to discuss the deal that's keeping the government in place. Negotiating teams for Fine Gael and Fianna Fáil will sit down this afternoon to begin reviewing the deal that keeps the government in place. Simon Coveney, Paschal Donohoe, Regina Doherty and Martin Heydon will represent Fine Gael. While the Fianna Fáil team will be led by Dara Calleary, Michael McGrath, Lisa Chambers and Charlie McConalouge. [readmore]881029[/readmore] Fine Gael are seeking a two-year extension to the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Fine Gael and Fianna Fáil find neutral ground to sit down and chat about extending their deal - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/fine-gael-fianna-fail-confidence-supply-4305598-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM7peiLbEeg7T9T-v2n01KQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/fine-gael-fianna-fail-confidence-supply-4305598-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Fine Gael and Fianna Fáil find neutral ground to sit down and chat about extending their deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TEAMS FROM FINE Gael and Fianna Fáil sat down together for chats in a small room based between Leinster House and Government Buildings this afternoon. What was discussed? The confidence and supply agreement between the two parties. For the everyday punter concerned with some of life’s real problems like housing, rent, homelessness, school closures and hospital waiting lists, these words might not mean much – but essentially, it is the deal Fianna Fáil signed up to facilitate Fine Gael setting up a minority government. It’s been a long road to get these discussions off the ground – in the ru...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Varadkar rebuffs FF's 'ill-conceived offer' for a Brexit truce - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/varadkar-rebuffs-ffs-illconceived-offer-for-a-brexit-truce-37460335.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhvJY4YaPHK8e2kC5xJznQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/varadkar-rebuffs-ffs-illconceived-offer-for-a-brexit-truce-37460335.html" target="_blank"&gt;Varadkar rebuffs FF's 'ill-conceived offer' for a Brexit truce&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has refused the offer of a Brexit truce from Fianna Fáil on the grounds it would hand Brexiteers control over the timing of the next election. Representatives from the two main parties met for the first time yesterday to see if they could agree an extension to the confidence and supply arrangement. In advance of the talks, Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin was warned by some TDs that he should stop propping up Fine Gael and contest a general election. At a Fianna Fáil parliamentary party meeting in Leinster House, Mr Martin was told the minority Government was a "fail...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Ministers fear 'FF trap' as talks to begin on confidence and supply - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/ministers-fear-ff-trap-as-talks-to-begin-on-confidence-and-supply-37452542.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSlHyQGvPaP98oZo26A0aMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/ministers-fear-ff-trap-as-talks-to-begin-on-confidence-and-supply-37452542.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ministers fear 'FF trap' as talks to begin on confidence and supply&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A row over the rules of engagement for the confidence-and-supply talks erupted even before Fine Gael and Fianna Fáil met for the first time. Amid deep suspicions on both sides over the sincerity with which the other is entering the negotiations, Taoiseach Leo Varadkar is set to insist Fianna Fáil provides costings for any demands being made. Fine Gael ministers met yesterday to discuss its approach to the talks, which could extend the Government lifespan by at least one more budget. Sources indicated there is a "strong belief" Micheál Martin is trying to lure them into "a trap" that will re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin: Confidence and Supply review must be substantive - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/micheal-martin-confidence-and-supply-review-must-be-substantive-877138.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHHsFjDGHaC0gVGwOhQxHBwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 12:12:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/micheal-martin-confidence-and-supply-review-must-be-substantive-877138.html" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin: Confidence and Supply review must be substantive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Update - 1pm: Talks on underpinning the Government must be “substantive”, Micheal Micheál has said. The Fianna Fáil leader highlighted what he termed a “critical delivery deficit” on housing, health, broadband and Brexit preparations. [quote]It must be substantive. It must push aside the increasingly empty PR of government claims and deliver a serious review of the critical policies which are of most concern to the public[/quote] Mr Martin said: “We are setting no new conditions and we will agree to no new conditions or deadlines. “The review must be as we have anticipated from when it was ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Structural issues could affect 40 schools as Taoiseach says it will be difficult to find alternative classrooms - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/school-closures-4302440-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDvCBDAFOTbabkW3QXirKWIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 12:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/school-closures-4302440-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Structural issues could affect 40 schools as Taoiseach says it will be difficult to find alternative classrooms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TAOISEACH LEO VARADKAR has said it will be difficult to find alternative classroom accommodation for students affected by the closure of schools with fire safety and structural defects. He also confirmed that approximately 40 schools will be inspected amidst concerns about structural issues at a number of facilities. Two schools and a building at a third, all in Dublin, have been closed so far this week following inspections by the Department of Education. They are Tyrrelstown Educate Together, St Luke’s National School also in Tyrrelstown and Ardgillan Community College in Balbriggan. Spe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Confidence and Supply talks must be 'substantive', Micheal Martin says - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/confidence-and-supply-talks-must-be-substantive-micheal-martin-says-37442625.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMQ9k5JpLRiKYXZyNxMRbi4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 12:28:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/confidence-and-supply-talks-must-be-substantive-micheal-martin-says-37442625.html" target="_blank"&gt;Confidence and Supply talks must be 'substantive', Micheal Martin says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talks on underpinning the Government must be "substantive", Micheal Martin has said. The Fianna Fail leader highlighted what he termed a "critical delivery deficit" on housing, health, broadband and Brexit preparations. He named a four-strong team to conduct talks on the supply and confidence arrangement which has enabled the minority Government to pass budgets and survive no confidence motions since the 2016 general election. It comprises deputy leader Dara Calleary, spokesman for finance Michael McGrath, Brexit spokeswoman Lisa Chambers and agriculture spokesman Charlie McConalogue and di...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Martin: FF not agreeing to new conditions in Govt talks - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1021/1005664-fianna-fail-talks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENO14PViegj3yWH8YuQvfWIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 14:22:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1021/1005664-fianna-fail-talks/" target="_blank"&gt;Martin: FF not agreeing to new conditions in Govt talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin has said his party will not agree to new conditions or deadlines as part of the Confidence and Supply Agreement talks. Mr Martin also said his party will not be setting any preconditions for the negotiations, which will begin with Fine Gael next week. He was speaking at the annual Wolfe Tone Commemoration in Bodenstown in Co Kildare. The comments come after Tánaiste and Minister for Foreign Affairs Simon Coveney said he would like to see the talks completed within a month. Mr Martin said his party wants a review of the deal that is "substantive" and must pu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Confidence and Supply talks to begin next week - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/ireland/2018/1019/1005407-confidence-suppy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAqYtWTkbJO0SZlWeALji3cqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 16:12:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/ireland/2018/1019/1005407-confidence-suppy/" target="_blank"&gt;Confidence and Supply talks to begin next week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Taoiseach has said that he wants to begin talks about renewing the Confidence and Supply Agreement sooner rather than later. Discussions between Fianna Fáil and Fine Gael, to first review the agreement, will get under way next week. This evening, two of the four TDs who will represent Fianna Fáil at the talks have been confirmed. They are deputy party leader Dara Calleary and Finance Spokesperson Michael McGrath. It has been confirmed too that the Fine Gael team will be comprised of Minister for Finance Paschal Donohoe and Tánaiste Simon Coveney as well as Minister for Social Protection...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Second stage of abortion legislation passed by Dáil - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1023/1006170-abortion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcmQdKdFfwmbNnJlRyfbZcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 18:35:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1023/1006170-abortion/" target="_blank"&gt;Second stage of abortion legislation passed by Dáil&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second stage of the Regulation of Termination of Pregnancy Bill has passed by a large majority in the Dáil. The bill now moves to committee stage where amendments to the bill will be considered and discussed. Introduced to the Dáil the week before the Budget, the second stage of the legislation passed by 102 votes to 12. Seven TDs abstained. Many of those abstentions came from the Fianna Fáil party, whose TDs are free to vote with their conscious. Sinn Féin on the other hand are subject to a party whip on this issue, which means Meath West TD Peadar Tóibín now faces suspension from the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Fine Gael wants Micheál Martin to cost any changes to agreement - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fine-gael-wants-micheal-martin-to-cost-any-changes-to-agreement-878706.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGXLa4kRhJOYQ5PzSexU3fgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fine-gael-wants-micheal-martin-to-cost-any-changes-to-agreement-878706.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fine Gael wants Micheál Martin to cost any changes to agreement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Fiachra Ó Cionnaith and Juno McEnroe Fine Gael has insisted any changes to the confidence and supply deal with and Fianna Fáil must be fully costed. The call comes just hours before the high-profile negotiations are set to begin. A Government spokesperson confirmed that Taoiseach Leo Varadkar wants Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin to agree to the plan, saying any changes must have “rigorous financial planning” in place before they can be discussed. At a post-Cabinet press briefing, the spokesperson said while the Government will approach the negotiations “without pre-conditions”, no “ra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>'Disciplinary proceedings' to be initiated against Tóibín for breaking ranks on abortion legislation - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/abortion-legislation-3-4301107-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAdM-PAF7hn1aVsPA8XfAF0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 17:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/abortion-legislation-3-4301107-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'Disciplinary proceedings' to be initiated against Tóibín for breaking ranks on abortion legislation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DISCIPLINARY PROCEEDINGS ARE to be initiated against Sinn Féin’s Peadar Tóibín, who broke ranks with his party’s policy by voting against the abortion legislation in the Dáil today. As indicated by Sinn Féin party leader Mary Lou McDonald in April, Tóibín could face suspension from the party. However, Tóibín told TheJournal.ie this evening that “this issue is far more important than my job or any job in Leinster house”. The first vote on the Termination of Pregnancy Bill was held today with the Dáil voting by 102-12 to pass it to Second Stage. The Dáil also approved that the Bill be sent to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Poll: Should the confidence and supply agreement be renewed or would you rather an election? - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/confidence-and-supply-4-4297665-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBxKQXpbA7h7XpZsJ-Y-L74qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 08:44:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/confidence-and-supply-4-4297665-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Poll: Should the confidence and supply agreement be renewed or would you rather an election?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AFTER SUCCESSFULLY MAKING it through three Budgets, Fine Gael and Fianna Fáil are set to sit down in the coming days and weeks to discuss the renewal of the confidence and supply agreement. Fianna Fáil has propped up the Fine Gael government for some time, after agreeing a deal following the 2016 election to back them on key issues. Micheál Martin wrote to Taoiseach Leo Varadkar last week urging him not to call an election, given the risk of “creating a dangerous instability” during a crucial time in the Brexit negotiations. Both sides have announced their negotiating teams in the past 24 h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Government calls on UK to honour backstop commitments - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/government-calls-on-uk-to-honour-backstop-commitments-876532.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENjXtuydyDtB8ZkWNRZ-jq8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/government-calls-on-uk-to-honour-backstop-commitments-876532.html" target="_blank"&gt;Government calls on UK to honour backstop commitments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Government has called on the British cabinet to honour in full the commitments given on the Irish border backstop in Brexit negotiations. Justice Minister Charlie Flanagan, taking Leaders’ Questions in place of Taoiseach Leo Varadkar, said he agreed with comments by Ireland’s ambassador to the UK, which accused the British of “backsliding” away from promises already made. Under questions from Fianna Fáil deputy leader Dara Calleary, Mr Flanagan said: “I agree with the Irish ambassador [Adrian} O’Neill that every effort must be made at this stage to ensure obligations on the parts of gov...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item></channel></rss>