<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Glenroe - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRFZvZVhRekVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:04:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Glenroe star Dónall Farmer has died - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2018/1206/1015498-glenroe-star-donall-farmer-has-died/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGR7uUD_-mrtthHR90zVfeMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wmpqhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:31:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2018/1206/1015498-glenroe-star-donall-farmer-has-died/" target="_blank"&gt;Glenroe star Dónall Farmer has died&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Irish actor and director Dónall Farmer - best known for his role in RTÉ soap Glenroe as priest Fr Tim Devereux - has died aged 81.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpFdTYtbWpZQU1FUnFIZURybjVYWjhLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Much-loved: Former 'Glenroe' star Farmer dies aged 81 - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/news/muchloved-former-glenroe-star-farmer-dies-aged-81-37603272.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOFGDXmRErM5DpGpu695F6cqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/news/muchloved-former-glenroe-star-farmer-dies-aged-81-37603272.html" target="_blank"&gt;Much-loved: Former 'Glenroe' star Farmer dies aged 81&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actor and impersonator Mario Rosenstock has led tributes to Dónall Farmer, who has died aged 81.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Glenroe star Dónall Farmer dies aged 81 - The Irish Times</title><link>https://www.irishtimes.com/news/ireland/irish-news/glenroe-star-d%C3%B3nall-farmer-dies-aged-81-1.3722520</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELAnb4tIWDhHiTDipwqWOhcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqfqFCzD7v4MDMIO9jQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:54:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishtimes.com/news/ireland/irish-news/glenroe-star-d%C3%B3nall-farmer-dies-aged-81-1.3722520" target="_blank"&gt;Glenroe star Dónall Farmer dies aged 81&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Irish Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actor and director played role of Fr Tim Devereux in soap.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishtimes.com">The Irish Times</source></item><item><title>Former Glenroe star and RTE Head of Drama Dónall Farmer has died - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/entertainment/television/tv-news/former-glenroe-star-and-rte-head-of-drama-dnall-farmer-has-died-37601009.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgQyu7mDmWe1E_PKKBUEqMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w29KiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:40:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/entertainment/television/tv-news/former-glenroe-star-and-rte-head-of-drama-dnall-farmer-has-died-37601009.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Glenroe star and RTE Head of Drama Dónall Farmer has died&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dónall Farmer, the former Head of Drama at RTE, has died. The Irish actor and director was best known for his role as Fr Tim Devereux in RTE's hugely popular long running soap Glenroe. After graduating from UCC in English and Irish he joined RTE in 1964 and was sent to the BBC for training as a producer/director and went on to direct 50 episodes of The Riordan's before being appoointed Head of Drama at RTE in 1971. As an actor he starred in many plays and TV roles including Ballykissangel and Remington Steele and he twice won a Jacobs Radio and Television Award. Mr Farmer , who was original...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Glenroe star Dónall Farmer dies - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/movies-tv/glenroe-star-donall-farmer-dies-650711</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDU6fuog74MsOWlY-22pVVAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8woL6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:18:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/movies-tv/glenroe-star-donall-farmer-dies-650711" target="_blank"&gt;Glenroe star Dónall Farmer dies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rest in peace. RT has reported the death of actor Dnall Farmer. The Irish actor, originally from County Cork, was best known for his role asFather Tim Devereux in the iconic RT soap opera Glenroe. He also featured in other high profile programmes, such as Ballykissangel, and Remington Steele. Farmer began working at RT 54 years ago,and was sent to the BBC for training as a producer/director. He eventually went on to become Head of Drama at Ireland's national broadcaster. He also directed 50 episodes of The Riordans, another Irish soap opera which ran from 1965 to 1979. Farmeris survived by ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Cork-born Glenroe actor Dónall Farmer has died - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/cork-born-glenroe-actor-donall-farmer-has-died-890268.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOKpd8y08JYGROg0_EWSILgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/cork-born-glenroe-actor-donall-farmer-has-died-890268.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cork-born Glenroe actor Dónall Farmer has died&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actor Dónall Farmer, known for his role as Fr Tim Devereux in Glenroe has died. Dónall Farmer The Corkman helped found the Everyman Theatre in his native city. A graduate of UCC, he was also known for his roles in other RTÉ shows Ballykissangel and Remington Steele He joined RTÉ in 1964 before being sent to the BBC for training after which he commenced a career at the State broadcaster which included being their Head of Drama. Update: 12:00 Tributes are pouring in for Dónall Farmer after news of his death broke this morning. - Digital Desk&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Dónall Farmer - who played Fr Tim Devereux on Glenroe - dies aged 81 - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/donall-farmer-4379513-Dec2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENMObkBUSIsAl4zZNno4JnkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:23:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/donall-farmer-4379513-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Dónall Farmer - who played Fr Tim Devereux on Glenroe - dies aged 81&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IRISH ACTOR DÓNALL Farmer has died aged 81. Dónall was widely known for playing the priest Fr Tim Devereux in RTÉ’s long-running drama Glenroe. Originally from Blackpool, Co Cork, Dónall first joined RTÉ Television in 1964. He was sent to the BBC for training as a producer and a director and went on to direct over 50 episodes of 60s and 70s soap opera the Riordans before becoming Head of Drama for RTÉ in 1971. He was most known for playing Fr Tim Devereux on Glenroe, which ran from 1983 to 2001. Dónall also acted in many theatre plays, radio dramas and TV roles in both English and Irish. He...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>'A fine actor and terribly nice man': Tributes paid to Dónall Farmer - BreakingNews.ie</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/showbiz/a-fine-actor-and-terribly-nice-man-tributes-paid-to-donall-farmer-890403.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2buVK2qgDr_Qc88F7IJCEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow2NLTATCa_DUw5pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:53:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/showbiz/a-fine-actor-and-terribly-nice-man-tributes-paid-to-donall-farmer-890403.html" target="_blank"&gt;'A fine actor and terribly nice man': Tributes paid to Dónall Farmer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;BreakingNews.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tributes have been paid to the actor and director Dónall Farmer, who has died aged 81. The Cork native, best known for his role as Glenroe’s parish priest, Fr Tim Devereux, was also a former Head of Drama at RTÉ, and one of the founders of the Everyman Palace Theatre. A UCC graduate, Mr Farmer spent time in Britain before returning to his native Cork to teach at the Presentation Brothers, where he had gone to school. “I went to work as a teacher in Birmingham. I worked as a pork-pie maker, a goat herd. I worked at anything that would postpone doing a long-avoided MA degree,” he told the Cor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">BreakingNews.ie</source></item><item><title>Family searching for missing former Glenroe actor - Her.ie</title><link>http://www.her.ie/news/family-searching-missing-former-glenroe-actor/318766</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAXSYla-Sj23FndiipHFYqUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8wgJehAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:00:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.her.ie/news/family-searching-missing-former-glenroe-actor/318766" target="_blank"&gt;Family searching for missing former Glenroe actor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The family of former Glenroe actor Diarmaid Lawlor is looking for help in their search for the young man. Lawlor, who is 32 years old, has been missing since Friday October 28th when he was last seen at 6pm on Synge Street in Dublin. He has been described by his family as5'7" (170cm) in height, of slim build, with a light beard and sandy brown hair. He was also wearing a black jacket and black jeans when he was last seen. In a statement given to the Irish Times, Lawlor's family described their loved one as softly spoken and of a gentle nature. We are very concerned for his wellbeing and anx...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>Husband of tragic Coast Guard Catríona Lucas to appear on Late Late Show - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/entertainment/television/tv-news/husband-of-tragic-coast-guard-catrona-lucas-to-appear-on-late-late-show-35363076.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG6I6BC3KkX1vfk9b9cvTb4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w29KiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 16:17:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/entertainment/television/tv-news/husband-of-tragic-coast-guard-catrona-lucas-to-appear-on-late-late-show-35363076.html" target="_blank"&gt;Husband of tragic Coast Guard Catríona Lucas to appear on Late Late Show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OLYMPIC diver Tom Daley, soap stars Ryan and Adam Thomas, style guru Brendan Courtney and former Miss Ireland Amanda Brunker will all appear on RTE’s two main chat shows this weekend. The Late Late Show will feature an interview with tragic coast guard Caitríona Lucas’ husband. The mother-of-two was the first member of the Irish Coast Guard to lose their life during a rescue mission. Her husband Bernard, who is also a Coast Guard volunteer, will be in studio to talk to host Ryan Tubridy about the devastating impact of her death and to pay tribute to her. The show will be celebrating the wor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>It's been 7 years since that man fell on the ice and he has still never been identified - Her.ie</title><link>https://www.her.ie/entertainment/7-years-since-man-fell-ice-still-never-identified/327054</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG4IfDrL0fxnxcHm6tL2fnUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8w4ZahAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 16:09:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.her.ie/entertainment/7-years-since-man-fell-ice-still-never-identified/327054" target="_blank"&gt;It's been 7 years since that man fell on the ice and he has still never been identified&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A truly iconic moment in our history. There have been some iconic moments in the history of Irish broadcasting. Our minds instantly wanders back to moments like David O'Leary's penalty against Romania, Teresa Mannion's report from the end of the world,orMiley and Fidelma's kiss on Glenroe - the dirt birds! While these were allmemorable, it's safe to say that a certain weather report that was airedon the Six-One News from January 8th, 2010 will forever be remembered by the Irish public. Today marks seven years since one of the most beloved moments in the history of Irish television - when an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>The Late Late Show will interview the husband of tragic coast guard Caitríona Lucas - Her.ie</title><link>https://www.her.ie/entertainment/late-late-show-will-interview-husband-tragic-coast-guard-caitriona-lucas/327709</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOrgsp0RaXVm-CKzXt0aE80qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8w6a6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:39:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.her.ie/entertainment/late-late-show-will-interview-husband-tragic-coast-guard-caitriona-lucas/327709" target="_blank"&gt;The Late Late Show will interview the husband of tragic coast guard Caitríona Lucas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is going to be heartbreaking. Ryan Tubridy will interview Bernard Lucas, the husband of coast guard volunteer Caitrona Lucas who tragically died during a rescue mission in September last year. The mum-of-two was the first member of the Irish Coast Guard to lose their life during a rescue mission. Her family will be in studio to talk to host Ryan Tubridy about the devastating impact of her death and to pay tribute to her. Also on the show will be fashion designer and TV presenter Brendan Courtney. He will chat to Ryan about his family's toughest decision whether or not to put their fath...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>The most Irish on-screen moments of romance EVER - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2017/0214/852532-the-most-romantic-irish-on-screen-moments-ever/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENRs39KFgkdiiilsjStZ16QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wmpqhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 17:53:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2017/0214/852532-the-most-romantic-irish-on-screen-moments-ever/" target="_blank"&gt;The most Irish on-screen moments of romance EVER&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;To celebrate Valentine's Day we've trawled through the archives to bring you some of the most memorable and (obviously) cringey Irish romantic moments from television and the movies. Grab the smelling salts. Well holy God! Before Sean Spicer's press conferences, nothing had us quite as transfixed as the blossoming relationship between Biddy and Miley on Ireland's favourite soap, Glenroe. When Miley eventually got fed up of "beating round the bush" (steady) and eventually proposed, RTÉ and the national grid braced themselves as about 97% of the entire population of the country tuned in the s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Where in the World back for one night only! - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2017/0201/849288-where-in-the-world-back-for-one-night-only/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL21nmZ4NtoZycV6sqmxntAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wmpqhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 14:10:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2017/0201/849288-where-in-the-world-back-for-one-night-only/" target="_blank"&gt;Where in the World back for one night only!&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember when Sunday nights consisted of Where in the World and Glenroe, then straight to bed or homework (for the 80s kids amongst us) as soon as the credits rolled as there was school in the morning? The quiz show, Where in the World, was a staple of Sunday nights for nine years and featured two families squaring off to compete for a glamorous holiday (well Spain was glamorous back then in pre-Ryanair times). However it's best remembered for the array of shockingly bright pastel-coloured outfits and big hair that host Theresa Lowe brought into living rooms to brighten up recession hit and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Tull McAdoo wins the vote of Fianna Fáil new boy Donnelly - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/entertainment/theatre-arts/tull-mcadoo-wins-the-vote-of-fianna-fil-new-boy-donnelly-35430059.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFDiPJ-t9FXvy_cA9aRWV_kqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w29KiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/entertainment/theatre-arts/tull-mcadoo-wins-the-vote-of-fianna-fil-new-boy-donnelly-35430059.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tull McAdoo wins the vote of Fianna Fáil new boy Donnelly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was plenty of pressing the flesh at the opening night of the latest Gaiety production. Former D'Unbelievables star Jon Kenny and Glenroe's Mary McEvoy in the play based on 'The Letters of A Successful TD' and 'An Irish Minister of State' by John B Keane. A number of politicians turned up for the opening night of 'The Successful TD.' New Fianna Fáil recruit Stephen Donnelly enjoyed the show, along with former Tánaiste and ex-Labour Party leader Joan Burton and former Minister for Communications Pat Rabbitte. Playwright John B Keane's sons Billy and Conor were also there. 'The Successfu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Never mind the Botox on Late Late's schedule filler - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2017/0112/844474-never-mind-the-botox/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFyulXaTS7RQaoof1_EympUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wmpqhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 11:26:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2017/0112/844474-never-mind-the-botox/" target="_blank"&gt;Never mind the Botox on Late Late's schedule filler&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Set your face to stunned. The Late Late Show audience won't be able to keep a straight face this Friday - unlike guest Amanda Brunker who will be getting Botox live on the show. Yes folks, the procedure is on the rise in Ireland as we all want to look the Kardashians (apparently). Whether you are of this ilk or just like to see people squirm, then you can tune in on Friday to watch as the former Miss Ireland is prodded with a needle full of botulinum toxin. Would you go under the needle for beauty? Amanda Brunker will this Friday night Also joining Tubs is fashion designer and TV presenter ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Radio: All aboard for the magical mystery tour of music - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/entertainment/radio/radio-all-aboard-for-the-magical-mystery-tour-of-music-35975037.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8wHVab5_0o7EAbKjEaIdQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w29KiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/entertainment/radio/radio-all-aboard-for-the-magical-mystery-tour-of-music-35975037.html" target="_blank"&gt;Radio: All aboard for the magical mystery tour of music&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Songs in the Key of Life celebrates its first year on Today FM (Sun 9pm), which makes this as good a time as any for a little shout-out to an enjoyable show. It's a music programme with a difference: host Nadine O'Regan hands over the playlist reins to a guest, generally someone in arts or entertainment. They pick out the tunes that have been important to them down the years, or meant something, or stuck in their memory banks for some particular reason. Then they use this as ingress to discussing the guest's life, work, thoughts and perspectives. Like many great ideas, it's a simple one - a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Gardaí issue appeal for missing former Glenroe actor (32) - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/garda-issue-appeal-for-missing-former-glenroe-actor-32-35190954.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM7telhkRhg9KN4HO34VPSMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 16:22:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/garda-issue-appeal-for-missing-former-glenroe-actor-32-35190954.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gardaí issue appeal for missing former Glenroe actor (32)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gardai have issued an appeal for a former Glenroe actor who went missing last week. Diarmaid Lawlor (32) was last seen on October 28 at 6pm at Synge Street in Dublin. He is described as being 5ft7in (170cm) in height, of slim build, with a light beard and sandy brown hair. When last seen he was wearing a black jacket and black jeans. The family Mr Lawlor appealed for assistance in tracing his whereabouts on Facebook. His brother Ciaran wrote: “As many of you know, my brother, Diarmaid Lawlor is missing. We're very grateful for all the offers of help our family has received over night.” Mr L...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>TUBRIDY v NORTON: The line-ups for the Late Late Show and Graham Norton are here - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/movies-tv/tubridy-v-norton-line-ups-late-late-show-graham-norton-2/573501</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsrn2yRf1bB-s-HWY3NkgIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8woL6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 11:24:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/movies-tv/tubridy-v-norton-line-ups-late-late-show-graham-norton-2/573501" target="_blank"&gt;TUBRIDY v NORTON: The line-ups for the Late Late Show and Graham Norton are here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Graham is very hard to compete with this evening. Staying in tonight? Heres whats on offer on the chat show circuit. The Late Late Show Bernard Lucas Four months on from the tragic death of his wife Catrona last year, Bernard Lucas will talk to Ryan about the devastating impact of the loss of the first member of the Irish Coast Guard to lose their life during a rescue mission. Catronas family will be in studio to pay tribute to her, while there will also be a tribute to the Irish Coast Guard and the RNLI, with Ryan hearing from members hailing from all around the country and some of the peo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Bláthnaid Treacy joins the Xposé team on Virgin Media - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2018/1010/1002267-blathnaid-treacy-joins-the-xpose-team-on-virgin-media/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKTkhbRiHn_F_An-SkTObyMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wmpqhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 20:31:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2018/1010/1002267-blathnaid-treacy-joins-the-xpose-team-on-virgin-media/" target="_blank"&gt;Bláthnaid Treacy joins the Xposé team on Virgin Media&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RTÉ television and 2fm presenter Bláthnaid Treacy has revealed that she has joined the presenting team of Virgin Media One’s fashion and entertainment show Xposé. In an Instagram post on Wednesday, she said: "First day working on Xposé! Gonna be a busy girl for the next while as I'm continuing with all my other gigs at the same time but *so* looking forward to working with the amazing team here for the next few months #xposé" The presenter, who began her showbiz career when she appeared on Glenroe as Biddy and Miley's daughter Denise, will continue hosting the National Chart Show on 2fm on ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Heartfelt house - the home of former Glenroe actress overlooking Blessington Lake - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/style/heartfelt-house-the-home-of-former-glenroe-actress-overlooking-blessington-lake-36857888.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKVJF3rsd1OOSibHfoVMFQkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w4M2iAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/style/heartfelt-house-the-home-of-former-glenroe-actress-overlooking-blessington-lake-36857888.html" target="_blank"&gt;Heartfelt house - the home of former Glenroe actress overlooking Blessington Lake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miriam Brady is an actor turned visual artist; it's not that unusual for people in the seemingly more extrovert arm of the arts to turn to the more solitary, more introspective field. Johnny Depp, Robert De Niro, Lucy Liu and Rosie O'Donnell are all talented artists. Closer to home there are a few artistic thesps too: Catherine Byrne, star of Fair City, The Tudors and Love/Hate, is a sculptor, and Adele King aka Twink is the Frida Kahlo of cakes. All of the above combine their two modes of artistic expression, and put aside their tools when an acting job beckons. Miriam, however, concentrat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>'I won't even tell my family who killed Karen', says Fair City's Detective Yates - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/entertainment/television/tv-news/i-wont-even-tell-my-family-who-killed-karen-says-fair-citys-detective-yates-36796230.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEISz6u_VIlIxWViDVbatKOoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w29KiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 06:31:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/entertainment/television/tv-news/i-wont-even-tell-my-family-who-killed-karen-says-fair-citys-detective-yates-36796230.html" target="_blank"&gt;'I won't even tell my family who killed Karen', says Fair City's Detective Yates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE actor playing the detective investigating Karen's Fair City stabbing murder has said he's been getting grilled by members of the public desperate to found out whodunnit. Actor Nigel Mercier, who plays Detective Yates, has naturally been sworn to secrecy by the producers of the hit RTE programme. However, the former Glenroe star said that doesn't stop viewers from quizzing him on the identity of her killer. "I'm right in the centre of the storyline and I'm getting a very good reaction from it," he said. "One of the first things that people are saying to me is, 'Who did it?' "And then the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Here's What Happened Today: Monday - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/evening-fix-mon-19-mar-2018-3913351-Mar2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHdYri8FdVl4qWGemPHOWd4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 20:53:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/evening-fix-mon-19-mar-2018-3913351-Mar2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's What Happened Today: Monday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEED TO CATCH UP? TheJournal.ie brings you a round-up of today’s news. IRELAND - Mary Lou McDonald says a Sinn Féin senator who retweeted a post calling an IRA victim a ‘sadist’ make a ‘catastrophic error’. Her party also moved forward its Ard Fheis to June in order to sort its policy on the Eighth Amendment. - It’s going to be a chilly -5 degrees in some areas of the country tonight. - A teenager arrested following the fatal stabbing of a man in a Clare nightclub was released without charge. - The UK and the EU agreed on a Brexit ‘backstop’ solution for the Irish border. - A woman in her 8...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Dancing with Stardom: Bláthnaid Treacy on carving out a career niche and her prime-time ambitions - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/entertainment/television/dancing-with-stardom-blthnaid-treacy-on-carving-out-a-career-niche-and-her-primetime-ambitions-36679142.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDuGLl8Kf0rhrlbiClwfj6sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w29KiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/entertainment/television/dancing-with-stardom-blthnaid-treacy-on-carving-out-a-career-niche-and-her-primetime-ambitions-36679142.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dancing with Stardom: Bláthnaid Treacy on carving out a career niche and her prime-time ambitions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two distinct camps of people emerged during Snowmageddon. The first group, the forward thinkers, fetched shovels from their sheds and bought enough bread to last a week. The second group, the pleasure seekers, kept themselves busy sending memes, building igloos and turning laundry baskets into DIY sleighs. It's obvious which group Bláthnaid Treacy falls into... Snow is falling, bread supplies are dwindling and Ireland is about to go into lockdown the day she is scheduled to speak to Weekend magazine. But the 29-year-old TV presenter doesn't take a snowcheck to panic-buy groceries. On the co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Richard Satchwell to join Ray D'Arcy Show on Saturday as the Garda hunt for missing Tina continues - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/news/richard-satchwell-to-join-ray-darcy-show-on-saturday-as-the-garda-hunt-for-missing-tina-continues-36687840.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHNz952mpUetCn5j5FKrbvAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:40:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/news/richard-satchwell-to-join-ray-darcy-show-on-saturday-as-the-garda-hunt-for-missing-tina-continues-36687840.html" target="_blank"&gt;Richard Satchwell to join Ray D'Arcy Show on Saturday as the Garda hunt for missing Tina continues&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richard Satchwell will join the Ray D'Arcy Show this weekend to speak about his wife Tina's disappearance. Richard, husband of missing Tina Satchwell, will discuss how the past year has been for him. It's exactly 12 months since Tina disappeared. This week gardai concentrated their search around Mitchel's Wood outside Castlemartyr in east Cork, in an operation that's set to last for three weeks. Richard will discuss his thoughts about the search and his hope that Tina will still turn up alive. Fresh from partying with Helen Mirren at the Oscars last weekend, Made In Chelsea and I'm A Celeb ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Geraldine Plunkett hoping for Fair City return soon - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2018/0121/934844-rose-hopes-to-return-to-carraigstown-soon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENbNo8SYWQmiQhO7SZXkkWIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wmpqhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 11:48:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/entertainment/2018/0121/934844-rose-hopes-to-return-to-carraigstown-soon/" target="_blank"&gt;Geraldine Plunkett hoping for Fair City return soon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fair City actress Geraldine Plunkett has said she is hoping to return to Carrigstown soon in her role as Rose. Speaking on The Ray D'Arcy Show on RTÉ One at the weekend,the former Glenroe starsaid she had asked to take a break when her husband, the late actor Peadar Lamb, became ill. Geraldine Plunkett as Fair City's Rose "When Peadar got ill I asked to be written out, and they were very considerate and very kind," she said. "I would actually be doing it at the moment, in fact, but I obviously couldn't. "They sort of wrote me out - I hope [just] for the moment anyway!" "Rose has gone down t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item></channel></rss>