<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Aquarius 2 - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJggKIiBDQkFTRWdvTUwyY3ZNV2hvZW1keU1uWm5FZ0psYmlnQVAB?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:48:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>MSF ship Aquarius ends migrant rescues in Mediterranean - BBC News</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46477158</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiLmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmJiYy5jb20vbmV3cy93b3JsZC1ldXJvcGUtNDY0NzcxNTjSAXZodHRwczovL3d3dy1iYmMtY29tLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3Mvd3d3LmJiYy5jb20vbmV3cy9hbXAvd29ybGQtZXVyb3BlLTQ2NDc3MTU4P2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:35:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46477158" target="_blank"&gt;MSF ship Aquarius ends migrant rescues in Mediterranean&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;BBC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors Without Borders (MSF) says it has been forced to end migrant rescue operations in the Mediterranean carried out by the vessel Aquarius. The medical ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.bbc.com">BBC News</source></item><item><title>Aquarius, the last Mediterranean refugee rescue ship, ends operations - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-refugees-shipping-aquarius/aquarius-the-last-mediterranean-refugee-rescue-ship-ends-operations-idUSKBN1O60TL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4mF9SxdiO9NH7y6l_v_JYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:04:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-refugees-shipping-aquarius/aquarius-the-last-mediterranean-refugee-rescue-ship-ends-operations-idUSKBN1O60TL" target="_blank"&gt;Aquarius, the last Mediterranean refugee rescue ship, ends operations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last refugee rescue ship working in the Mediterranean Sea, Aquarius, has ended her operations, French NGO Medecins sans Frontieres said late on Thursday, blaming harassment from Italy and other countries. "This is a somber day," Nelke Mander, Medecins sans Frontieres's general director, said in a statement. "The end of our operations onboard the Aquarius will mean more death in the sea, deaths that are avoidable and without witnesses." The decision to moor the Aquarius is the result of a "constant denigration, smearing and obstruction campaign led" against Medecins sans Frontieres and S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Migrant rescue ship Aquarius forced to cease operations - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/world-news/migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-forced-to-cease-operations-37604412.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOyXkwnE_URR_RWAZmYAbS0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wmtSiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:52:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/world-news/migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-forced-to-cease-operations-37604412.html" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant rescue ship Aquarius forced to cease operations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aid groups Doctors Without Borders and SOS Mediterranee have said they have been forced to end the rescue operations of the Aquarius ship in the Mediterranean Sea. The Aquarius has been docked in Marseille since October after Panama revoked its flag. Last month, Italian prosecutors ordered the seizure of the ship and accused Doctors Without Borders, known by its French acronym MSF, of illegally disposing 24 metric tons of medical and contaminated waste accumulated during rescues. 📅 TODAY 10h30 ⏰ PRESS CONFERENCE in Paris by @SOSMedIntl ⚡️End of #Aquarius charter, for prompt resumption of s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Last Migrant Rescue Ship to End Operations in Mediterranean - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/last-migrant-rescue-ship-to-end-operations-in-mediterranean/4690566.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDUI8S-CXPc5as6HeRCn47EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:14:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/last-migrant-rescue-ship-to-end-operations-in-mediterranean/4690566.html" target="_blank"&gt;Last Migrant Rescue Ship to End Operations in Mediterranean&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The search-and-rescue ship Aquarius, which has helped about 30,000 migrants avoid death in the Mediterranean Sea, is suspending its operations. The humanitarian groups Doctors Without Borders (MSF) and SOS Mediterranee said European governments were forcing them to end the rescue runs. The Aquarius has been docked in Marseille, France, since early October after Panama revoked its registration at the behest of the right-wing, anti-immigration Italian government. The ship has been rescuing migrants who were trying to make the dangerous crossing from Libya to Europe in inadequate rafts and din...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Medecins Sans Frontieres forced to pull rescue boat from Mediterranean after being stuck in port for months - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/msf-rescue-boat-aquarius-mediterranean-sea-migrants-refugees-italy-salvini-libya-a8671571.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPfcoCHUJt9GX1cQt3AZIRoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/msf-rescue-boat-aquarius-mediterranean-sea-migrants-refugees-italy-salvini-libya-a8671571.html" target="_blank"&gt;Medecins Sans Frontieres forced to pull rescue boat from Mediterranean after being stuck in port for months&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An aid organisation has been forced to end its rescue missions of migrants in the Mediterranean Sea. Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF) and its partner SOS Mediterranee said the rescue ship Aquarius would no longer be used to save migrants travelling by boat from North Africa to Italy - one of the deadliest migration routes in the world. The vessel had remained in port for the past two months, MSF said, due to a “sustained smear campaign” headed by the Italian government. Last month, regional prosecutors in Italy baselessly claimed the Aquarius could bring infectious diseases such as HIV, menin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Migrant rescue vessel Aquarius ends operations in Mediterranean - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/migrant-rescue-vessel-aquarius-ends-operations-mediterranean/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAsrfzagb_oOXOurwFerfN4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:31:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/migrant-rescue-vessel-aquarius-ends-operations-mediterranean/" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant rescue vessel Aquarius ends operations in Mediterranean&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Aquarius migrant rescue ship is to end its operations in the Mediterranean, the humanitarian groups that chartered the boat said on Thursday. The vessel has been stranded in Marseille since early October after Panama revoked the right to fly its flag following a request from Italy's far-Right, anti-establishment government. Last month Rome also ordered the seizure of the Aquarius, which had been conducting rescue operations off Libya since 2016, for allegedly dumping toxic waste. "This is the result of a sustained campaign, spearheaded by the Italian government and backed by other Europ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Migrant rescue ship that saved thousands 'forced' to end operations - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/migrant-search-and-rescue-ship-aquarius-ends-operations/10595438</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN2AsRHr_jxDATx58TpoXy4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:33:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/migrant-search-and-rescue-ship-aquarius-ends-operations/10595438" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant rescue ship that saved thousands 'forced' to end operations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A search-and-rescue ship that saved tens of thousands of migrants from drowning in the Mediterranean has ended its operations, the charity that runs the ship has said. Key points: - Up to 5,000 migrants died in 2016 while trying to cross the route the Aquarius monitored - The ship had already lost its registration in France and faced calls to be impounded in Italy - Doctors Without Borders denies wrongdoing Doctors Without Borders (MSF) and its partner SOS Mediterranee said they were forced to terminate the Aquarius' operations due to a "smear campaign" by European governments. The ship has...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Refugee ship Aquarius to stop rescue mission in the Mediterranean - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/refugee-ship-aquarius-stop-rescue-mission-mediterranean-181207062845983.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKud7Uw8DzlQO-Rxrilh3tgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:24:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/refugee-ship-aquarius-stop-rescue-mission-mediterranean-181207062845983.html" target="_blank"&gt;Refugee ship Aquarius to stop rescue mission in the Mediterranean&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rescue and relief organisations SOS Mediterranee and Doctors Without Borders (MSF) have announced they are ending the Aquarius refugee rescue mission in the Mediterranean Sea after what they call "a relentless ongoing political, judicial and administrative campaign backed by several European states". Thursday's decision came after the Aquarius, which has been operating since February 2016, was forced to wait in a port in Marseille for two months, following the revocation of its registration. "Repeated and targeted attacks against life-saving aid organisations, coupled with the EU states' cr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>MSF says Aquarius forced to shut down operations - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/12/07/msf-says-aquarius-forced-to-shut-down-operations_47ea2193-b0bf-49ba-b948-256fd52dd633.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHORM6khqiYxIDva7y4Syv8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:42:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/12/07/msf-says-aquarius-forced-to-shut-down-operations_47ea2193-b0bf-49ba-b948-256fd52dd633.html" target="_blank"&gt;MSF says Aquarius forced to shut down operations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROME - MSF and SOS Méditerranée said they have been forced to terminate activities carried out by the ship Aquarius, after "two months in the port of Marseille without managing to get a flag, and while men, women, and children continue to die at sea". They called it "a difficult choice, but unfortunately obligatory, which will leave more needless deaths in the Mediterranean that will go unwitnessed". In the past two months, "with desperate people who continue to flee at sea on the deadliest migratory route in the world, the Aquarius was stuck in port, unable to carry out its lifesaving huma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>'Dark day': migrant rescue ship Aquarius ends operations - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/07/dark-day-migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-ends-operations-mediterranean</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECfoOfx3pTmPkqJOpGXV3wAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:04:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/07/dark-day-migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-ends-operations-mediterranean" target="_blank"&gt;'Dark day': migrant rescue ship Aquarius ends operations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Search and rescue ship Aquarius, which has saved tens of thousands of migrants from drowning in the Mediterranean, has ended its operations, said Médecins Sans Frontières, the charity that runs the ship. MSF and its partner SOS Mediterranee said they were forced to terminate its operations due to a “smear campaign” by European governments. Related: 'Race against time': flag revoked for Aquarius migrant rescue ship The ship has been blocked at the French port of Marseilles since it lost its Panamanian registration at the end of September. The Aquarius was the last charity rescue ship operati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Italy orders seizure of migrant rescue ship - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/world-news/europe/italy-orders-seizure-of-migrant-rescue-ship-37550537.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENXjJdfIFnOuaLivkpCrsSwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wmtSiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/world-news/europe/italy-orders-seizure-of-migrant-rescue-ship-37550537.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy orders seizure of migrant rescue ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italy has ordered the seizure of the migrant rescue ship Aquarius for alleged illegal waste treatment, Médecins Sans Frontières (MSF) said yesterday. Investigators suspect the vessel, chartered by MSF and the SOS Mediterranee charity and currently stuck in the French port of Marseille, passed off 24 tonnes of potentially toxic waste as ordinary waste, Italian media reported. MSF bank accounts in Italy have been blocked by the authorities, the international charity said. Prosecutors in the Sicilian city of Catania are running the inquiry into migrant clothing, food leftovers and sanitary was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Italy orders seizure of migrant rescue ship on spurious health grounds - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/italy-migrant-rescue-ships-aquarius-sos-mediterranean-health-hiv-matteo-salvini-a8643096.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIGUH1b2z8VmaIXLPX6BzP0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/italy-migrant-rescue-ships-aquarius-sos-mediterranean-health-hiv-matteo-salvini-a8643096.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy orders seizure of migrant rescue ship on spurious health grounds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italian authorities have upped the ante in their war against ships rescuing migrants drowning in the Mediterranean by ordering the seizure of one of the vessels on spurious health grounds. Italy’s government, fronted by far-right interior minister Matteo Salvini, has waged a campaign against ships like the Aquarius, closing ports to the rescue boats and otherwise frustrating charities’ efforts. On Tuesday regional prosecutors baselessly claimed that the ship could bring infectious diseases such as HIV, meningitis and tuberculosis into the country on the clothing of migrants. - Read more Ita...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Aid groups condemn Italy's order to seize Aquarius rescue ship - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/italy-orders-seizure-migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-msf-181120082930731.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENe6_gvPTz4JS7WCd3xMqG4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:54:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/italy-orders-seizure-migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-msf-181120082930731.html" target="_blank"&gt;Aid groups condemn Italy's order to seize Aquarius rescue ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two aid groups operating a rescue ship in the Mediterranean have strongly condemned a decision by Italy to order its seizure, rejecting an accusation that the vessel was being used to illegally dump toxic waste at ports in southern Italy. Italian magistrates on Tuesday ordered the Aquarius, which is chartered by Doctors Without Borders (MSF) and the SOS Mediterranee groups, to be impounded. The vessel, which has saved thousands of migrants since 2016, is currently docked in the French port of Marseille. According to Italian media, Aquarius was suspected of passing off 24 tonnes of potential...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Italy orders seizure of migrant rescue ship Aquarius for 'illegal waste treatment' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/20/italy-orders-seizure-migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-illegal-waste/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECidnyP8_5BCosrNR_aYlHIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 08:49:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/20/italy-orders-seizure-migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-illegal-waste/" target="_blank"&gt;Italy orders seizure of migrant rescue ship Aquarius for 'illegal waste treatment'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italian authorities have ordered the seizure of the migrant rescue ship “Aquarius” in the French port of Marseille, alleging it has illegally disposed of infectious waste in 11 ports in the southern Italy. Médecins Sans Frontières, the French NGO which operates the ship, called the move to seize assets and freeze bank accounts an “unfounded and disproportionate” measure aimed at further criminalising rescue efforts that have saved 80,000 people at sea over the last three years. More than 2000 migrants have perished this year alone trying to cross the Mediterranean. "After two years of defa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Italy orders seizure of migrant rescue ship over 'HIV-contaminated' clothes - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/20/italy-orders-seizure-aquarius-migrant-rescue-ship-hiv-clothes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENchhFApv6RkV1zZW7eKBjgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 12:59:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/20/italy-orders-seizure-aquarius-migrant-rescue-ship-hiv-clothes" target="_blank"&gt;Italy orders seizure of migrant rescue ship over 'HIV-contaminated' clothes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italian authorities have ordered the seizure of the migrant rescue ship Aquarius after claiming that discarded clothes worn by the migrants on their voyage from Libya to Italy could have been contaminated by HIV, meningitis and tuberculosis. Prosecutors from Catania, eastern Sicily, alleged that the waste was illegally labelled by the ship’s crew as “special waste” rather than “toxic waste”. Related: Italy's Salvini forced into U-turn over school lunches for immigrant children The Aquarius is currently docked in Marseilles, France, where so far it is beyond the reach of the Italian authorit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Italy accuses NGO migrant ship of dumping toxic waste - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-italy-aquarius/italy-accuses-ngo-migrant-ship-of-dumping-toxic-waste-idUSKCN1NP1E4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGXOUAVuV2-XJiZBYA5xJogqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:16:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-italy-aquarius/italy-accuses-ngo-migrant-ship-of-dumping-toxic-waste-idUSKCN1NP1E4" target="_blank"&gt;Italy accuses NGO migrant ship of dumping toxic waste&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italian magistrates on Tuesday accused the Doctors without Borders (MSF) charity of illegally dumping toxic waste at ports in southern Italy in what MSF said was an attempt to undermine migrant rescue efforts. Magistrates ordered the MSF-operated ship Aquarius, which has saved thousands of migrants since 2016, to be impounded but the charity denied any wrongdoing and accused Italy of seeking to criminalize humanitarian search and rescue missions. The Aquarius has been blocked at the French port of Marseilles since September, after failing to find a country willing to register its trips to t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Italian officials: Migrant rescuers mishandled medical waste - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/cc3137a01e024c7bb6b90bffcaad4c68</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEZGI_9cLHE8oWFZQv-jbjoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:10:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/cc3137a01e024c7bb6b90bffcaad4c68" target="_blank"&gt;Italian officials: Migrant rescuers mishandled medical waste&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROME (AP) — Italian prosecutors have ordered the seizure of a migrant rescue ship and accused the aid group Doctors Without Borders of illegally disposing of 24 metric tons (26.5 tons) of medical and contaminated waste accumulated during nearly 50 rescues. Prosecutors in Catania, Sicily said Tuesday that 24 people were under investigation, including the aid group's Italy personnel and the crew of the Aquarius. Prosecutors accused them of working with a Sicily-based shipping company to mix medical and "contaminated" waste, like migrants' clothing, with other garbage to save money. Prosecutor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Italy Orders Seizure of Migrant Rescue Ship - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/world/europe/italy-aquarius-seizure-order.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOw_IiZ7wpm5BB9SaaeKze4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 14:55:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/world/europe/italy-aquarius-seizure-order.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy Orders Seizure of Migrant Rescue Ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROME — Italy has ordered the seizure of the Aquarius, the rescue ship at the center of international criticism over its government’s hard line against migration, saying the vessel had illegally disposed of potentially infectious waste. Prosecutors in the Sicilian city of Catania announced on Tuesday that they had accused 24 people of having “systematically shared, planned and executed an illegal waste-disposal project of an enormous quantity” in southern Italian ports between January 2017 and May 2018. They said the waste included contaminated garments, leftover food, and medical supplies a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Italian Officials: Migrant Rescuers Mishandled Medical Waste - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/italian-officials-migrant-rescuers-mishandled-medical-waste/4666498.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4fzm1hJ2GCNRzymNg3btoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 17:27:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/italian-officials-migrant-rescuers-mishandled-medical-waste/4666498.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italian Officials: Migrant Rescuers Mishandled Medical Waste&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italian prosecutors have ordered the seizure of a migrant rescue ship and accused the aid group Doctors Without Borders of illegally disposing of 24 metric tons (26.5 tons) of medical and contaminated waste accumulated during nearly 50 rescues. Prosecutors in Catania, Sicily said Tuesday that 24 people were under investigation, including the aid group's Italy personnel and the crew of the Aquarius. Prosecutors accused them of working with a Sicily-based shipping company to mix medical and “contaminated” waste, like migrants' clothing, with other garbage to save money. Prosecutors ordered th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>'Race against time': flag revoked for Aquarius migrant rescue ship - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/nov/02/race-against-time-flag-revoked-for-aquarius-migrant-rescue-ship</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHERh80s_DwFABrrEo5ZyTEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 15:14:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/nov/02/race-against-time-flag-revoked-for-aquarius-migrant-rescue-ship" target="_blank"&gt;'Race against time': flag revoked for Aquarius migrant rescue ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A desperate search is under way for a country willing to issue a flag to the Aquarius, the last civilian migrant rescue ship operational in the Mediterranean, after its Panamanian flag officially expired this week. The Aquarius is unable to sail without a flag and is now grounded in Marseilles, starting an effective blackout across the Mediterranean, with no vessels aside from the Libyan coastguard conducting search and rescue operations. “We are in a race against time to find another state willing to issue a flag to the Aquarius,” said Sophie Beau, co-founder of SOS Méditerranée, the organ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Migrants - and a dog - disembark in Malta after long wait at sea - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-aquarius/migrants-and-a-dog-disembark-in-malta-after-long-wait-at-sea-idUSKCN1MA0QD</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOCA_6MdiZJetMTEayVqA4QqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 15:37:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-aquarius/migrants-and-a-dog-disembark-in-malta-after-long-wait-at-sea-idUSKCN1MA0QD" target="_blank"&gt;Migrants - and a dog - disembark in Malta after long wait at sea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A military ship brought 58 migrants - and a dog - to Malta on Sunday, where they disembarked after spending several days waiting for seas to calm so they could be transferred from the charity rescue ship Aquarius. The migrants were rescued from two small boats off the coast of Libya at least a week ago. They include Libyans, Syrians, Palestinians, Somalis and Pakistanis. Among them are seven families and three children under five years of age. The Aquarius spent five days off the coast of Malta waiting for the weather to improve so it could transfer the migrants to a Maltese cutter. Panama ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Closing ports against humanity - Paris - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/09/25/closing-ports-against-humanity-paris_815e7633-9c90-4691-8fc0-182714a507a3.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEOicAVamrEWLLWLuHVTB20qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 10:16:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/09/25/closing-ports-against-humanity-paris_815e7633-9c90-4691-8fc0-182714a507a3.html" target="_blank"&gt;Closing ports against humanity - Paris&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Paris, September 25 - A senior member of the French government said Tuesday that Italy should not close its ports to ships carrying migrants rescued at sea. "Europe's level of solidarity is 10 times what it was before," European Affairs Minister Nathalie Loiseau told Sud radio when asked about the case of the Aquarius NGO-run migrant-rescue ship. "That is why we say again to Italy that the idea of closing its ports to people in danger is against the law, it is against humanity". Interior Minister and Deputy Premier Matteo Salvini has denied migrant-rescue vessels access to Itali...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>5 EU Countries Reach Deal to End Limbo of Rescued Migrants - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/eu-countries-reach-deal-to-end-limbo-of-rescued-migrants/4587070.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMwkkVy-gHIBqmrSNQeU7gAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 21:49:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/eu-countries-reach-deal-to-end-limbo-of-rescued-migrants/4587070.html" target="_blank"&gt;5 EU Countries Reach Deal to End Limbo of Rescued Migrants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five European Union countries struck a deal Tuesday to distribute between them 58 migrants rescued in the Mediterranean Sea and left stranded by continuing disagreements in the bloc over how to cope with the influx of people trying to enter illegally from North Africa. A Spanish official who wasn't authorized to be named in media reports said Spain, France, Portugal, Germany and Malta agreed to take the migrants, who were rescued by charities off Libya last week but then stuck on a private rescue ship because it couldn't find a country which would let it dock. The breakthrough came after da...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Italy denies leaning on Panama - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/09/24/italy-denies-leaning-on-panama_3ee13cc8-be6c-4a5f-909d-2d4ed6119973.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOt9wAhNITc11PuCtaUQcA4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 15:12:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/09/24/italy-denies-leaning-on-panama_3ee13cc8-be6c-4a5f-909d-2d4ed6119973.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy denies leaning on Panama&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, September 24 - Italian Interior Minister Matteo Salvini has denied two migrant-rescue NGOs' claim he leant on Panama to strip their ship Aquarius2 of its flag and thus become a 'pirate' ship. "It's clear that no country wants to take the responsibility of being identified with a ship that hampers sea rescue operations, refuses coordination with the Libyan coast guard, attacks democratic governments like the Italian one, and expects to distribute clandestine migrants in Europe," he said Sunday night. SOS Méditerranée and Doctors Without Borders (MSF) said earlier they we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Panama stops Aquarius. Salvini: 'It won't arrive in Italy' - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/09/24/panama-stops-aquarius.-salvini-it-wont-arrive-in-italy_0aa77560-9f9f-4f54-87d3-81c215f15b99.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK1TEsDROQYWqZBppkdPUM0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 16:13:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/09/24/panama-stops-aquarius.-salvini-it-wont-arrive-in-italy_0aa77560-9f9f-4f54-87d3-81c215f15b99.html" target="_blank"&gt;Panama stops Aquarius. Salvini: 'It won't arrive in Italy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROME - The migrant-rescue vessel Aquarius "will never arrive in Italy", Interior Minister Matteo Salvini said. "We are working with all required lawyers but I can assure all Italians that this ship will never arrive in Italy. I do not want to be an accomplice of human trafficking", he said. Salvini spoke after a new controversy on immigration, with the Aquarius vessel that saw its Panama flag revoked. Doctors without Borders, which operates the ship together with Sos Mediterranée, has accused Italy of putting pressure on Panama, an allegation denied by the interior ministry. Salvini warned ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Italy denies Aquarius2 claim - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/09/24/italy-denies-aquarius2-claim_f4b49d35-cf6f-4d07-aeae-5fdf364bd39e.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEObeTXJh1SBGdxktuiYgCu4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/09/24/italy-denies-aquarius2-claim_f4b49d35-cf6f-4d07-aeae-5fdf364bd39e.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy denies Aquarius2 claim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, September 24 - Italian Interior Minister Matteo Salvini has denied two migrant-rescue NGOs' claim he leant on Panama to strip their ship Aquarius2 of its flag and thus become a 'pirate' ship. "It's clear that no country wants to take the responsibility of being identified with a ship that hampers sea rescue operations, refuses coordination with the Libyan coast guard, attacks democratic governments like the Italian one, and expects to distribute clandestine migrants in Europe," he said Sunday night. SOS Méditerranée and Doctors Without Borders (MSF) said earlier they we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Aquarius migrant ship calls on Europe for help, sails to Marseille - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-aquarius/aquarius-migrant-ship-calls-on-europe-for-help-sails-to-marseille-idUSKCN1M420P</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAXkACkMRgThgBM9mEiQ-CoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 16:26:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-aquarius/aquarius-migrant-ship-calls-on-europe-for-help-sails-to-marseille-idUSKCN1M420P" target="_blank"&gt;Aquarius migrant ship calls on Europe for help, sails to Marseille&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Charities operating the Mediterranean rescue ship Aquarius on Monday urged European governments to help the vessel find a new flag to sail under after Panama revoked its registration, and they asked France to let its passengers disembark in Marseille. Panama's move to cancel the registration of the Aquarius, now sailing toward the southern French port with 58 migrants on board, means there will be no charity rescue ships operating off the Libyan coast in the near future. "This a call to European countries," Francis Vallat, head of the SOS Mediterranee charity, told reporters in Paris. "The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Panama revokes registration of last migrant rescue ship in central Mediterranean - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-migration-aquarius-panama/panama-revokes-registration-of-last-migrant-rescue-ship-in-central-mediterranean-idUSKCN1M30S9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELfYVGvhZCwvGM46Ls_hfM8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 19:53:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-migration-aquarius-panama/panama-revokes-registration-of-last-migrant-rescue-ship-in-central-mediterranean-idUSKCN1M30S9" target="_blank"&gt;Panama revokes registration of last migrant rescue ship in central Mediterranean&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Panama Maritime Authority has revoked the registration of search and rescue ship Aquarius 2 in a move that means there will be no charity rescue ships off the Libyan coast in the near future unless the vessel can find a new flag to sail under. Aquarius 2, the one remaining charity rescue vessel still operating in the Central Mediterranean area, is currently at sea with 58 survivors on board. The decision by the Panama Authority (PMA) means that once the ship comes into port it will be deflagged and will not be allowed to operate again unless it can find a new flag. SOS Mediterranee, one...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Portugal, Spain, France, Germany agree to take in Aquarius ship migrants - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-aquarius/portugal-spain-france-germany-agree-to-take-in-aquarius-ship-migrants-idUSKCN1M50QI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECEXrNZxUrLTTkRlNnVoJe4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 17:15:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-aquarius/portugal-spain-france-germany-agree-to-take-in-aquarius-ship-migrants-idUSKCN1M50QI" target="_blank"&gt;Portugal, Spain, France, Germany agree to take in Aquarius ship migrants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France, Portugal, Spain and Germany struck a deal on Tuesday to take in migrants from the Mediterranean rescue ship Aquarius sailing off the coast of Malta, the French government said, after Italy refused to let the vessel dock. The agreement marks the second such co-operation between European countries since Italy's new anti-establishment coalition started turning away from Italian ports ships carrying migrants rescued in the Mediterranean earlier this year. Portugal said it had agreed to take 10 of the 58 migrants on board as part of a "response of solidarity to the flow of migrants seeki...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Italy used EU cash to send migrant boat to Spain in propaganda coup - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/22/italy-used-eu-cash-send-migrant-boat-spain-propaganda-coup/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENylDn-9blAacRFVlnTwzdUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 16:26:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/22/italy-used-eu-cash-send-migrant-boat-spain-propaganda-coup/" target="_blank"&gt;Italy used EU cash to send migrant boat to Spain in propaganda coup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italy spent hundreds of thousands of euros in European Union funds to escort the Aquarius migrant boat to Spain after refusing it permission to land at Italian ports. The new populist coalition government in Rome used the turning away of the Aquarius to signal a new tougher anti-migrant stance shortly after the far-right League and anti-establishment Five Star Movement came to power just days earlier. More than 600 refugees and migrants were left stranded at sea in a four-day standoff until Spain agreed to take in the charity boat at Valencia. At least €200,000 euros (about £180,000), 90 pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>5 EU countries to take Aquarius migrants - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/08/14/5-eu-countries-to-take-aquarius-migrants_be6cc64d-95f4-40b4-87d7-e3653867d360.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMwvcikOybw74vbp3VH9wwcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 15:27:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/08/14/5-eu-countries-to-take-aquarius-migrants_be6cc64d-95f4-40b4-87d7-e3653867d360.html" target="_blank"&gt;5 EU countries to take Aquarius migrants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(supersedes previous) (ANSA) - Rome, August 14 - Five EU countries have reached an agreement to receive the 141 migrants recently saved by the Aquarius NGO-run search-and-rescue ship in the Mediterranean, European Home Affairs Commissioner Dimitris Avramopoulos told ANSA on Tuesday. The countries are Spain, France, Portugal, Germany and Luxembourg. The Aquarius will dock in Malta. Malta and Italy had both refused to allow the ship access to their ports. Read the full article on ANSA English&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Italy refuses to take in migrants from Aquarius ship - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/world/2018/0813/984865-italy-aquarius-migrants/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEACrxql9mAXDOPwfJRyEGH8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 18:11:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/world/2018/0813/984865-italy-aquarius-migrants/" target="_blank"&gt;Italy refuses to take in migrants from Aquarius ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italy has denied safe harbour to the 141 people rescued by the humanitarian ship Aquarius off the coast of Libya last week, setting up another stand-off with European Union allies over who will take them in. The Aquarius, run by Franco-German charity SOS Mediterranee and Doctors without Borders (MSF), picked up the people in two separate operations and is now in international waters between Italy and Malta. Malta said it had no legal obligation to berth the ship while Spain said its ports were not the safest destination for the vessel. More than 650,000 migrants have come to Italy's shores ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>#Aquarius appeals for port of safety - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/general_news/2018/08/13/aquarius-appeals-for-port-of-safety_5fc7af3b-36a3-4f5f-a6c6-06c6f78e7bfe.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIr6NsgMwXOmUn3gr1d9g70qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 11:40:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/general_news/2018/08/13/aquarius-appeals-for-port-of-safety_5fc7af3b-36a3-4f5f-a6c6-06c6f78e7bfe.html" target="_blank"&gt;#Aquarius appeals for port of safety&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, August 13 - The SOS MEDITERRANEE and Médecins Sans Frontières (MSF) NGOs on Monday appealed to European governments to assign the migrant-rescue ship Aquarius a port of safety "without delay" after it saved 141 people in the Mediterranean. "Maritime authorities from #Malta and #Italy inform #Aquarius that they will not grant 141 people onboard a place of safety to disembark," MSF said via Twitter. "#Aquarius has now reached a standby position exactly between Malta and Italy and is awaiting further guidance". The NGOs said more than 70% of those rescued originate from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Aquarius can't come to Italy - Salvini - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/08/13/aquarius-cant-come-to-italy-salvini_ce2fc7fc-1bd2-42d1-a640-97f57f7f5e6f.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPdVf53r_yFNNgsfvspqJMIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 10:44:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/08/13/aquarius-cant-come-to-italy-salvini_ce2fc7fc-1bd2-42d1-a640-97f57f7f5e6f.html" target="_blank"&gt;Aquarius can't come to Italy - Salvini&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, August 13 - Interior Minister and Deputy Premier Matteo Salvini said Monday that the NGO-run migrant search-and-rescue ship Aquarius will not be allowed access to Italy's ports. "Aquarius NGO ship with another 141 immigrants on board: German owned, rented by French NGO, foreign crew, in Maltese waters, flying the flag of Gibraltar," Salvini said via Twitter. "It can go where it wants, (but) not to Italy! Stop human being traffickers and accomplices, #portsclosed and #openhearts". Read the full article on ANSA English&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Migrant rescue ship arrives in Malta, ending standoff - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants/migrant-rescue-ship-arrives-in-malta-following-standoff-idUSKBN1L01AE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2zwHYE09aVqZJpQ8TSEvYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 20:21:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants/migrant-rescue-ship-arrives-in-malta-following-standoff-idUSKBN1L01AE" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant rescue ship arrives in Malta, ending standoff&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mediterranean rescue ship Aquarius arrived at Valletta harbor in Malta on Wednesday to allow 141 migrants to get off, ending a five-day tug-of-war among European Union countries which had seen the vessel banned from docking in several ports. The ship, run by the Franco-German charity SOS Mediterranee and Doctors without Borders (MSF), was allowed in after France, Germany, Luxembourg, Portugal and Spain agreed on Tuesday to take in the migrants, who were rescued off the coast of Libya. Aid groups said there were more than 70 children on board. The EU countries will also take some of a gr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Italy calls on UK to take responsibility for 141 people rescued by ship sailing under Gibraltar flag - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/13/italy-calls-uk-take-responsibility-141-people-rescued-ship-sailing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKCHjn4zzoixMvtF6_N0nqgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 15:30:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/13/italy-calls-uk-take-responsibility-141-people-rescued-ship-sailing/" target="_blank"&gt;Italy calls on UK to take responsibility for 141 people rescued by ship sailing under Gibraltar flag&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italy’s transport minister has called on the UK to take responsibility for 141 people rescued by a ship sailing under the flag of the British territory of Gibraltar. Danilo Toninelli, the transport and infrastructure minister and a senior member of the anti-establishment 5-Star Movement (M5S), said via Twitter on Monday that the rescue was co-ordinated by the Libyan coast guard and the rescue ship was in Maltese waters, sailing under the flag of Gibraltar. “At this point the United Kingdom assumes its responsibility for the safeguarding of the shipwrecks," he said. A European Commission spo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Malta to allow Aquarius migrant ship to dock, as five EU countries agree to share responsibility for 141 on board - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/14/malta-allow-aquarius-migrant-ship-dock-five-eu-countries-agree/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPQe9dwLV_qwidiPeFosY8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 14:14:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/14/malta-allow-aquarius-migrant-ship-dock-five-eu-countries-agree/" target="_blank"&gt;Malta to allow Aquarius migrant ship to dock, as five EU countries agree to share responsibility for 141 on board&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spain will take in 60 of the 141 migrants on board the Aquarius rescue ship as part of an agreement with other European nations, Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez said Tuesday. "Spain has coordinated a pioneering agreement with six countries to distribute the reception of the people of the Aquarius.. Spain will receive 60 people," he wrote on Twitter. At the same time, his Maltese counterpart Joseph Muscat said Valetta would allow the boat to dock and that those on board would be sent to France, Germany, Luxembourg, Portugal and Spain in a posting on Twitter. Malta had at the end of June agreed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>6 EU countries to take Aquarius migrants - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/08/14/6-eu-countries-to-take-aquarius-migrants_d5d6b9b9-3eec-4f35-b1d0-51bf24315507.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECqLhFaV_-zCwY8pp0NbwM8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 13:34:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/08/14/6-eu-countries-to-take-aquarius-migrants_d5d6b9b9-3eec-4f35-b1d0-51bf24315507.html" target="_blank"&gt;6 EU countries to take Aquarius migrants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, August 14 - Six EU countries have reached an agreement to receive the 141 migrants recently saved by the Aquarius NGO-run search-and-rescue ship in the Mediterranean, El Pais reported on Tuesday, citing Spanish government sources. Spain will take 60 asylum seekers, the daily said. France and Lisbon will also receive some of the migrants, with the latter taking 30, according to the report. It did not say which other countries were involved in the agreement. According to Portuguese media, the Aquarius will dock in Malta. Malta and Italy had both refused to allow the ship ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Malta lets rescue ship dock after EU states agree to take migrants - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants/malta-lets-rescue-ship-dock-after-eu-states-agree-to-take-migrants-idUSKBN1KZ1JV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK1e6UfxOn5FrzPCxkADvYwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 18:46:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants/malta-lets-rescue-ship-dock-after-eu-states-agree-to-take-migrants-idUSKBN1KZ1JV" target="_blank"&gt;Malta lets rescue ship dock after EU states agree to take migrants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malta said on Tuesday it would allow the Mediterranean rescue ship Aquarius, which has been barred for four days from several coastal states, to dock after five European Union countries agreed to take in the 141 migrants on board. The boat, run by the Franco-German charity SOS Mediterranee and Doctors without Borders (MSF), had been at the center of the latest continent-wide tug-of-war over how to cope with the arrival of seaborne migrants. The migrants rescued off the coast of Libya together with some others who arrived in Malta separately will be distributed among France, Germany, Luxembo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Humanitarian ship seeks European port for rescued migrants - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-ngo/humanitarian-ship-seeks-european-port-for-rescued-migrants-idUSKBN1KX0O8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEJtwLlV-IhvrRHkB2dBwowqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 10:19:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-ngo/humanitarian-ship-seeks-european-port-for-rescued-migrants-idUSKBN1KX0O8" target="_blank"&gt;Humanitarian ship seeks European port for rescued migrants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human rights groups called on European governments on Sunday to tell a charity ship where it can dock and let more than 140 migrants rescued in the Mediterranean disembark in safety. The Aquarius, run by Franco-German charity SOS Mediterranee and Doctors without Borders (MSF), rescued 141 people in two separate operations off the Libyan coast last week. The boat had just started heading north on Sunday toward Europe when Libyan coastguards called it back to pick up 10 migrants spotted aboard a small fiberglass boat. As that rescue was underway, SOS Mediterranee and MSF asked for guidance on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Italy tells UK to take in 141 refugees on rescue boat in Mediterranean: 'It can go where it wants, but not in Italy' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/aquarius-charity-rescue-boat-italy-uk-libya-m-decins-sans-fronti-res-gibraltar-a8489671.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHebz1b76R1foyhNPcfappgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 14:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/aquarius-charity-rescue-boat-italy-uk-libya-m-decins-sans-fronti-res-gibraltar-a8489671.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy tells UK to take in 141 refugees on rescue boat in Mediterranean: 'It can go where it wants, but not in Italy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italy has demanded that the UK takes in 141 refugees rescued by a humanitarian ship in the Mediterranean Sea. Officials in Italy and Malta have refused to let the Aquarius dock after it picked up the people from overcrowded wooden boats adrift off the coast of Libya on Friday. The charities SOS Mediterranee and Médecins Sans Frontières (MSF), which operate the rescue ship, have appealed for European governments to offer refuge to those on board. - Read more Refugee drownings ‘skyrocket’ as Italy’s right-wingers block ships Sixty-seven unaccompanied children are among the migrants, who are m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Libya's coastguard says it has intercepted more than 570 refugees bound for Europe - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/libya-refugee-crisis-europe-coastguard-migrants-a8474006.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJl4J2B__3e_Zi0wnE_iyeAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 09:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/libya-refugee-crisis-europe-coastguard-migrants-a8474006.html" target="_blank"&gt;Libya's coastguard says it has intercepted more than 570 refugees bound for Europe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libya’s coast guard intercepted 574 refugees bound for Europe from the Mediterranean Sea in a single day, a spokesperson has said. The three groups included 388 men, 66 women and 19 children, a coast guard spokesman, Ayoub Gassim, said in a statement. He said one group of 292 refugees, including 42 women and 10 children, embarked on the perilous trip for Europe on three rubber boats, but the coast guard stopped them off the coast of the western town of Zawiya. The three groups included 388 men, 66 women and 19 children (MAHMUD TURKIA/AFP/Getty Images) Another group of 101 refugees on a rubb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Migrant rescue ship Aquarius returns to sea after Italy-Malta dispute - Reuters</title><link>https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-ngo/migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-returns-to-sea-after-italy-malta-dispute-idUSKBN1KM51V?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcVil0RIMCENrG1TQgsHzIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 13:19:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-ngo/migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-returns-to-sea-after-italy-malta-dispute-idUSKBN1KM51V?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant rescue ship Aquarius returns to sea after Italy-Malta dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The migrant rescue ship Aquarius, source of a dispute between Italy and Malta in June after both refused to accept more than 600 people it had picked up, will begin a new mission in the southern Mediterranean on Wednesday, organizers said. The 77-metre vessel, operated by Franco-German charity SOS Mediterranee, will set sail from Marseille on its tenth operation of the year, having already rescued about 3,000 people during 2018, many fleeing from the shores of Libya. "(The ship) goes back to sea this afternoon," Francis Vallat, president of SOS Mediterranee, told reporters. "If only one rea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://internal.www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Migrant rescue ship Aquarius won't take people back to Libya - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-ngo/migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-wont-take-people-back-to-libya-idUSKBN1KQ0N4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECflYyU1Yo-FdL8e2l5X8ssqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 18:38:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-europe-migrants-ngo/migrant-rescue-ship-aquarius-wont-take-people-back-to-libya-idUSKBN1KQ0N4" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant rescue ship Aquarius won't take people back to Libya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rescue ship Aquarius, which has picked up almost 3,000 migrants from the Mediterranean this year, will carry out rescue missions without waiting for orders from coastguards and will not return people to Libya, its search and rescue head said. "When we see there is a vessel in distress, with a high likelihood of people dying, we will go and rescue them immediately as per international maritime law," Nick Romaniuk told Reuters on board the Aquarius. Over the last year coordination centers asking rescue vessels to go on standby or wait for clarification on certain things had added to the dange...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Lifeline offloads migrants in Malta - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/28/lifeline-offloads-migrants-in-malta_77ba233b-1c7e-4e20-94e8-c9f5e083b12d.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIGNd-Pt3Q78fnrCvTY5xacqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 08:43:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/28/lifeline-offloads-migrants-in-malta_77ba233b-1c7e-4e20-94e8-c9f5e083b12d.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lifeline offloads migrants in Malta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Valletta, June 28 - Migrant rescue ship Lifeline on Wednesday night offloaded its human cargo of 234 migrants at Maltese capital Valletta. The German NGO ship, which had been at the centre of a week-long international wrangle, has been impounded and its captain is being questioned. The migrants will be shared out among eight European Union countries. Italian Interior Minister Matteo Salvini, who has imposed a new policy of turning away NGO ships, rejoiced at the Lifeline case and the previous one of another ship, the Aquarius, which docked in Valencia after a stand-off bet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Conte set to wield veto at EU summit - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/28/conte-set-to-wield-veto-at-eu-summit_5c029d3c-c0ea-42f6-b0af-e04a20d4172c.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEXL7XrMwSE2bac8jx4NdpIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 08:01:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/28/conte-set-to-wield-veto-at-eu-summit_5c029d3c-c0ea-42f6-b0af-e04a20d4172c.html" target="_blank"&gt;Conte set to wield veto at EU summit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, June 28 - Italian Premier Giuseppe Conte is set to wield a veto at the European Union summit today and tomorrow unless the conclusions lay down the principle of shared responsibility for migrant sea rescues, Italian government sources have said. Sharing the task of rescuing migrants in the Mediterranean is a "red line" which Rome has set for the gathering of EU leaders, the sources said. Meanwhile the 234 migrants aboard the Lifeline NGO ship have landed at Malta after a week-long international wrangle and will be divvied up among eight EU countries - barring Germany which...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Lifeline to dock in Malta - Conte - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/26/lifeline-to-dock-in-malta-conte_4523e32f-377b-4e82-80ae-48e2dccfd4ac.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDD5j3ly2PS3xzCdFyjGqPYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 17:30:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/26/lifeline-to-dock-in-malta-conte_4523e32f-377b-4e82-80ae-48e2dccfd4ac.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lifeline to dock in Malta - Conte&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, June 26 - Premier Giuseppe Conte said Tuesday after a secret meeting with French President Emmanuel Macron in Rome on Monday night that Malta has agreed to let the Lifeline dock there while Italy is set to receive some of the migrants that it has on board. "I have just spoken on the telephone to (Maltese) Premier (Joseph) Muscat," Conte said. "The Lifeline NGO ship will dock in Malta. "Consistent with the cardinal principle of our proposal on immigration - according to which, those who land on the Italian, Spanish, Greek or Maltese coast, land in Europe - Italy will do its...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Migrant 'invasion' stopping - Salvini - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/26/migrant-invasion-stopping-salvini_3b9b9960-9411-4e06-825f-72fa3b4757a4.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGxZ5Ogi6okoV8i9EtTFjdcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 12:41:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/26/migrant-invasion-stopping-salvini_3b9b9960-9411-4e06-825f-72fa3b4757a4.html" target="_blank"&gt;Migrant 'invasion' stopping - Salvini&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, June 26 - Interior Minister and Deputy Premier Matteo Salvini said Tuesday that the "invasion" of asylum seekers was ending after the cases of the Aquarius and Lifeline migrant-rescue ships, which were denied access to Italian ports. "That makes two!," Salvini said via Twitter. "After the NGO (ship) Aquarius was sent to Spain, now it's the turn of the Lifeline NGO, which will go to Malta and this outlaw ship that will finally be impounded. "The doors are open for women and children truly fleeing war, but not to all the others! #stopinvasion (#stopinvasione)". Read the f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Will the Migrant Issue Tear Europe Apart? - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/will-the-migrant-issue-tear-europe-apart</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFRy5j7g2zExjrTFVb_vd-MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 08:53:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/will-the-migrant-issue-tear-europe-apart" target="_blank"&gt;Will the Migrant Issue Tear Europe Apart?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast ROME—Matteo Salvini is a man on a mission that will either make the European Union work together on the migrant issue or drive it further apart. His now well known hardline policy on migration, which surely would make Donald Trump proud, will be tested this week when European leaders meet to discuss the burgeoning migration crisis. Salvini didn’t cause it, but he single-handedly forced it onto the top of the European Union’s agenda by imposing what amounts to a naval blockade to stop African migrants from entering Italy. By preventing all foreign-flagge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Aid group says Malta hasn't cleared rescue ship - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/e6d4f6206d1c46fe89042b092b0fb23c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKgVzpQzo4U6G75-gptZskqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 19:25:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/e6d4f6206d1c46fe89042b092b0fb23c" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Aid group says Malta hasn't cleared rescue ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The Latest on Europe's migrant crisis (all times local) 8:45 p.m. A German aid group with an overloaded rescue boat that has been waiting in the Mediterranean Sea for five days is contradicting the leaders of Italy and France, saying Malta won't let the Lifeline enter its territorial waters. A tweet sent Tuesday evening from Mission Lifeline's account said the group could not confirm media reports that quoted French President Emmanuel Macron and Italian Premier Giuseppe Conte saying Malta had agreed to authorize the ship. Macron also said several European countries were workin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Lifeline will get OK to dock - Malta (3) - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/27/lifeline-will-get-ok-to-dock-malta-3_150cac43-a4ee-4336-a284-ba619d3bd707.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPLh6cHlGeHFaB08elwHxMwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 12:36:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/27/lifeline-will-get-ok-to-dock-malta-3_150cac43-a4ee-4336-a284-ba619d3bd707.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lifeline will get OK to dock - Malta (3)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, June 27 - Maltese Premier Joseph Muscat said Wednesday that the Lifeline will be given permission to dock in Malta later in the day, adding that the migrant-rescue ship is set to be impounded. The ship, which is at the centre of an international wrangle, was given permission to enter Maltese waters to shelter from bad weather conditions earlier on Wednesday but did not get the green light to dock. "The Lifeline will be sequestered for the launch of an investigation," Muscat told a news conference. "The captain of the vessel ignored international laws". The NGO ship h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Malta Will Take in Migrant Rescue Ship, Italy Says - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/malta-migrant-rescue-ship-italy/4455795.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOFMq-nY5zMthcrI4y1FbmAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 20:39:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/malta-migrant-rescue-ship-italy/4455795.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malta Will Take in Migrant Rescue Ship, Italy Says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malta will let the rescue ship Lifeline dock after Italy refused it entry, ending the vessel's near-weeklong wait in the Mediterranean with more than 230 migrants on board, Italy's prime minister said Tuesday. Lifeline said one person had been evacuated for medical reasons and that general conditions onboard were worsening. Malta's offer resolved a standoff with Rome, where a new government, co-led by the anti-immigrant League party, has announced it will no longer let in charity ships that rescue migrants. The ships cover the sea route to Italy, where thousands of refugees have died in rec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Hundreds rescued from busy shipping lane - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/world/hundreds-rescued-from-busy-shipping-lane-850724.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECQqsDThlSo02XbK_hOJn6UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwzaShAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 14:56:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/world/hundreds-rescued-from-busy-shipping-lane-850724.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hundreds rescued from busy shipping lane&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spanish authorities have rescued 569 refugees crossing the Mediterranean from North Africa to Europe by boat. They include over 260 people in 16 vessels in the Strait of Gibraltar, a busy shipping lane with treacherous currents. A week ago, Spain took in 630 refugees after Malta and Italy, which were closer, refused to grant the ship they were in access to their ports. Rescued refugees arrive on the NGO "SOS Mediterranee" Aquarius at the eastern port of Valencia, Spain, Sunday, Jun. 17.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>European leaders urged to guarantee safe ports for migrants - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/24/european-leaders-urged-to-guarantee-safe-ports-for-migrants</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECdnribvpESPkR4aHLgl_VcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 11:20:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/24/european-leaders-urged-to-guarantee-safe-ports-for-migrants" target="_blank"&gt;European leaders urged to guarantee safe ports for migrants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Charities operating search-and-rescue missions in the Mediterranean have called on European leaders to urgently guarantee safe ports for migrants and refugees, warning the political standoff is already costing lives. As EU leaders met on Sunday for an emergency summit on migration, a week after 630 people rescued by the Aquarius ship arrived in Spain having been turned away by Italy and Malta, the fate of another vessel remained in limbo. The German NGO Mission Lifeline said its ship, carrying 234 people, was adrift in international waters after Italy refused it entry and Maltese authoritie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Italy refuses port to migrant rescue ship - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/world/italy-refuses-port-to-migrant-rescue-ship-850481.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK8QUWpmokdyFDXCOCyciBYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwzaShAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 08:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/world/italy-refuses-port-to-migrant-rescue-ship-850481.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy refuses port to migrant rescue ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italy’s hard-line interior minister has refused port to a Dutch-flagged rescue boat with 224 migrants on board, a week after turning away another foreign ship, the Aquarius, carrying 630 migrants. Matteo Salvini said the ship operated by the German aid group Mission Lifeline had loaded the migrants in Libyan waters after the Italian coast guard told it to leave the rescues to the Libyan coast guard. Salvini said he had contacted the Dutch ambassador about the ship’s activities, adding that the migrants “will only see Italy on a postcard”. La NAVE FUORILEGGE #Lifeline è ora in acque di Malta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Sold as a 'slave', fleeing FGM, orphaned at 11: Lives of Aquarius - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/sold-slave-fleeing-fgm-orphaned-11-lives-aquarius-180618181015563.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6UgMCCc3chae_X1SBPKVYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 20:14:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/sold-slave-fleeing-fgm-orphaned-11-lives-aquarius-180618181015563.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sold as a 'slave', fleeing FGM, orphaned at 11: Lives of Aquarius&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Valencia, Spain - Ibrahim, a 20-year-old, had travelled to Libya to look for work, but after he arrived he was abducted and sold for 1,000 dinars ($738). "[My owner] was drunk," he said. "He came and took some other black men to his truck and shot them. A friend and I had to pick up the bodies and bury them." A year later, in the country's southwest, he was tortured by another group of men. "I was beaten with an iron bar while the men filmed and laughed at me. They were filming to force my family back home for money, for my freedom. They kept sending videos and images of them beating me dai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Aquarius rescue ship arrives at Spanish port - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/world/2018/0617/971078-aquarius-migrants/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHHI_rn7dq9qmRJiaapQrUoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 21:36:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/world/2018/0617/971078-aquarius-migrants/" target="_blank"&gt;Aquarius rescue ship arrives at Spanish port&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Aquarius migrant rescue boat which was turned away by Italy and Malta arrived at the Spanish port of Valencia this morning, ending a gruelling voyage which has made it a symbol of Europe's failure to agree on immigration. Spain offered to help 629 mainly sub-Saharan Africans on board the Aquarius last week after Italy's new government, asserting its anti-immigrant credentials, refused to let it dock. Spain's Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez, who took office two weeks ago, took the opportunity to show a more liberal stance. But the plight of the Aquarius, run by Doctors Without Borders (MSF)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Aquarius migrant ship arrives in Spain after rough week at sea - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-06-18/aquarius-migrant-ship-arrives-in-spain-after-rough-week-at-sea/9879018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBV9w1LbjW1GkZQC0QFwV6UqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 19:57:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-06-18/aquarius-migrant-ship-arrives-in-spain-after-rough-week-at-sea/9879018" target="_blank"&gt;Aquarius migrant ship arrives in Spain after rough week at sea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A migrant rescue boat turned away by Italy and Malta has arrived at the Spanish port of Valencia, ending a gruelling voyage which has made it a symbol of Europe's failure to agree on immigration. Key points: - Migrants will get special 45-day humanitarian permits to stay, and asylum requests will be assessed - Anti-migrant feeling is high in Italy, with more than 600,000 sea arrivals in past five years - But in Spain, there is a push to welcome more migrants Spain swooped to help 629 mainly sub-Saharan Africans on board the Aquarius last week after Italy's new government, asserting its anti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>2 migrant rescue vessels suspend operations after Italian intervention - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/22/europe/migrant-rescue-boats/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEPTuTflZjIihlruhX2mP6wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 10:12:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/22/europe/migrant-rescue-boats/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;2 migrant rescue vessels suspend operations after Italian intervention&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid the ongoing controversy over immigration, the owners of two rescue boats say Italy has forced them to stop operating. One of the boats, the Lifeline, has 234 people on board whom it rescued off the coast of Libya and 17 crew members. Italy says it will seize the Lifeline for violating international law. The other, the Seefuchs, or Sea Fox, docked in Malta after Italy questioned its registration. The boats are operated by German nongovernmental organizations. Operators insist they are registered in the Netherlands, which has denied responsibility for them. Danilo Toninelli, the Italian ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Italy interior minister refuses port to migrant rescue ship - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/c6685496f0ee4b4fa4b75eba1eab3842</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEES6aD51-LFK84cIWE6idMYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 18:59:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/c6685496f0ee4b4fa4b75eba1eab3842" target="_blank"&gt;Italy interior minister refuses port to migrant rescue ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MILAN (AP) — Italy's hard-line interior minister on Thursday refused port to a Dutch-flagged rescue boat with 224 migrants on board, a week after turning away another foreign ship, the Aquarius, carrying 630 migrants. Matteo Salvini said the ship operated by the German aid group Mission Lifeline had loaded the migrants in Libyan waters after the Italian coast guard told it to leave the rescues to the Libyan coast guard. Salvini said he had contacted the Dutch ambassador about the ship's activities, adding that the migrants "will only see Italy on a postcard." Mission Lifeline said it conduc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>“Politics has been put before the lives of people" EU governments slammed as Aquarius docks - Newstalk Newsfeed</title><link>https://www.newstalk.com/Politics-has-been-put-before-the-lives-of-people-EU-governments-slammed-as-Aquarius-docks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdtJJyQocbdCP3r4tvGkFIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowmeSfCTCcwW8wmpuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 14:42:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newstalk.com/Politics-has-been-put-before-the-lives-of-people-EU-governments-slammed-as-Aquarius-docks" target="_blank"&gt;“Politics has been put before the lives of people" EU governments slammed as Aquarius docks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newstalk Newsfeed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;International humanitarian organisation Médecins Sans Frontières has accused European governments of choosing political point-scoring over saving lives at sea as the Aquarius convoy carrying more than 600 migrants arrived in Spain. They were rescued a week ago off the coast of Libya and have been at sea ever since - as the Italian government refused to allow them dock in Italy. They were rescued in several different operations last weekend after Italian coastguard vessels reported a group of small rubber dinghies off the coast of Libya. The Government of Malta also refused to allow the ship...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newstalk.com">Newstalk Newsfeed</source></item><item><title>1,000 migrants stranded in the Mediterranean as Italian ports 'remain closed' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/24/1000-migrants-stranded-mediterranean-italian-ports-remain-closed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMZzp2ygtZo-2gusfsfHP80qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 17:44:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/24/1000-migrants-stranded-mediterranean-italian-ports-remain-closed/" target="_blank"&gt;1,000 migrants stranded in the Mediterranean as Italian ports 'remain closed'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italy’s hardline interior minister said 1,000 migrants hoping for rescue off the coast of Libya should be picked up by the Libyan coast guard rather than European NGOs, as the standoff in the Mediterranean intensified. Matteo Salvini said the asylum seekers should be sent straight back to Libya, despite humanitarian organisations saying they face rape, torture, beatings and forced labour. “Another 1,000 migrants in rubber dinghies? It’s right that the Libyan authorities intervene, without having NGO boats interrupt and bother them,” he wrote on Twitter, which has become one of his favoured ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Aquarius convoy carrying over 600 migrants arrives in Spain - Newstalk Newsfeed</title><link>https://www.newstalk.com/Aquarius-convoy-carrying-over-600-migrants-arriving-in-Spain--</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFNeHGd6pwzI3nn6Dkst_hEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowmeSfCTCcwW8wmpuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 14:38:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newstalk.com/Aquarius-convoy-carrying-over-600-migrants-arriving-in-Spain--" target="_blank"&gt;Aquarius convoy carrying over 600 migrants arrives in Spain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newstalk Newsfeed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ships carrying more than 600 migrants have arrived in Spain - after Italy and Malta refused to let them dock in their ports. The Aquarius convoy docked in Valencia across the morning. The Italian coast guard vessel Dattilo arrived in the Spanish port just before 7am local time on Sunday, followed later by charity rescue vessel Aquarius and an Italian navy ship, the Orione. The total number of people being transported was 630. The migrants were rescued a week ago off the coast of Libya and have been at sea ever since, as the Italian government refused to allow them dock in Italy. The ship's ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newstalk.com">Newstalk Newsfeed</source></item><item><title>Govt blasts 'illegal' NGO migrant rescue (5) - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/21/govt-blasts-illegal-ngo-migrant-rescue-5_eae175e2-0a0c-4e0f-a7fa-98ddcd316774.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAesfJitGYAHcegAG6EKZ4kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 16:08:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/21/govt-blasts-illegal-ngo-migrant-rescue-5_eae175e2-0a0c-4e0f-a7fa-98ddcd316774.html" target="_blank"&gt;Govt blasts 'illegal' NGO migrant rescue (5)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, June 21 - Interior Minister Matteo Salvini and Transport Minister Danilo Toninelli both launched high-voltage attacks on German NGO Mission Lifeline on Thursday after its ship rescued over 200 migrants off the coast of Libya. "The Lifeline NGO ship is operating in Libyan waters outside all rules, outside international law," Toninelli, whose brief includes control of Italy's ports, said on Facebook. "They have taken on 250 boat-wreck victims even though they don't have the technical means to guarantee their safety or the safety of the crew," he added, saying he had asked th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Govt blasts 'illegal' NGO migrant rescue (3) - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/21/govt-blasts-illegal-ngo-migrant-rescue-3_4324d4b2-11c7-4351-9d57-e628fbf3d8ab.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHVUmR_0tfgkesGz8BPS6i8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 11:42:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/21/govt-blasts-illegal-ngo-migrant-rescue-3_4324d4b2-11c7-4351-9d57-e628fbf3d8ab.html" target="_blank"&gt;Govt blasts 'illegal' NGO migrant rescue (3)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, June 21 - Interior Minister Matteo Salvini and Transport Minister Danilo Toninelli both launched high-voltage attacks on German NGO Mission Lifeline on Thursday after its Dutch-flagged ship rescued hundreds of migrants off the coast of Libya. "The Lifeline NGO ship is operating in Libyan waters outside all rules, outside international law," Toninelli, whose brief includes control of Italy's ports, said on Facebook. "They have taken on 250 boat-wreck victims even though they don't have the technical means to guarantee their safety or the safety of the crew," he added, sayin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Govt blasts 'illegal' NGO migrant rescue (4) - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/21/govt-blasts-illegal-ngo-migrant-rescue-4_38e1cc8f-d913-4fa6-b737-1f85e905c15f.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGXFcb7uofE0o1NNbAwAwS4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 15:12:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/21/govt-blasts-illegal-ngo-migrant-rescue-4_38e1cc8f-d913-4fa6-b737-1f85e905c15f.html" target="_blank"&gt;Govt blasts 'illegal' NGO migrant rescue (4)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, June 21 - Interior Minister Matteo Salvini and Transport Minister Danilo Toninelli both launched high-voltage attacks on German NGO Mission Lifeline on Thursday after its ship rescued hundreds of migrants off the coast of Libya. "The Lifeline NGO ship is operating in Libyan waters outside all rules, outside international law," Toninelli, whose brief includes control of Italy's ports, said on Facebook. "They have taken on 250 boat-wreck victims even though they don't have the technical means to guarantee their safety or the safety of the crew," he added, saying he had asked...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Italy requests Malta take Lifeline (4) - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/22/italy-requests-malta-take-lifeline-4_a49a8c9a-6ff9-4c60-a28b-1fa22b8f19b2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGKR--2-lweAnIiyDfPpjRIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 15:09:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/06/22/italy-requests-malta-take-lifeline-4_a49a8c9a-6ff9-4c60-a28b-1fa22b8f19b2.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy requests Malta take Lifeline (4)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, June 22 - The Italian port authority on Friday made a formal request for Malta to allow the NGO-run migrant-rescue ship Lifeline to dock at a port on the Mediterranean island, government sources said. The Dutch-flagged ship, run by German NGO Mission Lifeline, may be set to be at the centre of an international wrangle like that which involved another NGO-run migrant-rescue vessel, the Aquarius, which ended up docking in Valencia last week after Italy and Malta refused it access to ports. Italian Transport Minister Danilo Toninelli on Thursday accused the Lifeline of "opera...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Malta says not responsible for Lifeline boat denied by Italy - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/europe/2018/06/malta-responsible-lifeline-boat-denied-italy-180622154705983.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEASz80EiL_v3GKSLhybs-yYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 20:25:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/europe/2018/06/malta-responsible-lifeline-boat-denied-italy-180622154705983.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malta says not responsible for Lifeline boat denied by Italy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A ship with more than 200 migrants and refugees on board is being blocked from entering Italian waters, the second time in two weeks that a new anti-immigrant government in Rome has turned away a vessel carrying people rescued from drowning in the Mediterranean. The ship - named Lifeline and operated by the German aid group Mission Lifeline - had 234 people on board whom its crew pulled from the Mediterranean. Matteo Salvini, the Italian interior minister and one of the country\s two deputy prime ministers, had previously indicated that the ship may not dock in Italy and that Malta should t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>What next for refugees after the Aquarius fallout? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/180619163302062.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEObILTozKZ_fs2Qwh-4E5rcqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 16:33:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/180619163302062.html" target="_blank"&gt;What next for refugees after the Aquarius fallout?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Valencia, Spain - When Gima Ayele moved from Ethiopia to Valencia, he found the port city so hospitable that it remains his home 10 years later. So when the 49-year-old industrial engineer heard that the MV Aquarius would arrive on Sunday, he went to the harbour to welcome the refugees and migrants on board. The search and rescue boat, run by charities SOS Mediteranee and Doctors Without Borders (MSF), had held the world's attention as it was stranded in the water for 36 hours between Italy and Malta, carrying 630 weak and tired refugees and migrants. The ship - which has saved 30,000 peopl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Migrant ship passengers represent 31 countries - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/687c2e2d319d4c4987299cfeadbe2b08</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHmQZOFVLGf7AHO0eTQpkyAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 21:03:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/687c2e2d319d4c4987299cfeadbe2b08" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Migrant ship passengers represent 31 countries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VALENCIA, Spain (AP) — The Latest on the influx of migrants into Europe (all times local): 4:00 p.m. The United Nations refugee agency is warning against a repeat of the standoff that left a private rescue ship carrying 629 migrants at sea for a week. A convoy consisting of the aid ship Aquarius and two Italian military ships disembarked the passengers in Valencia, Spain on Sunday, a week after Italy and Malta had refused to give the Aquarius permission to dock. The U.N. high commissioner for refugees, Filippo Grandi, said in a statement from Geneva: "We're grateful this ordeal is over for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item></channel></rss>