<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Damien Delaney - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNR1IyTW00NUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:35:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>'A big box ticked for me' - Delaney leaves Cork City - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/soccer/2018/1206/1015635-a-big-box-ticked-for-me-delaney-leaves-cork-city/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBNRo3Z3sSPh9O3LpVLaoPoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:15:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/soccer/2018/1206/1015635-a-big-box-ticked-for-me-delaney-leaves-cork-city/" target="_blank"&gt;'A big box ticked for me' - Delaney leaves Cork City&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damien Delaney has left Cork City after reaching a mutual agreement with the Leesiders to cancel his contract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWl5a3NhbWpZQU1FYTV6X1k2ZHhmUWtLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Damien Delaney leaves Cork City by mutual consent - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/damien-delaney-leaves-cork-city-by-mutual-consent-890360.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHxoR6AVpyOxry0pCxO-JkcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/damien-delaney-leaves-cork-city-by-mutual-consent-890360.html" target="_blank"&gt;Damien Delaney leaves Cork City by mutual consent&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damien Delaney has left Cork City by mutual consent. The former Republic of Ireland international returned to the club in July after nearly 20 years in the English leagues, with his final six seasons being spent with Crystal Palace. Speaking to CorkCityFC.ie, Delaney said: “I would like to thank everyone associated with Cork City for helping me to fulfil my long-held ambition to come back and play for the club again. John Caulfield gave me that opportunity, and I am eternally grateful to him, his staff and my team mates. The chance to play European football at Turner’s Cross was a big box t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>'I am eternally grateful': Ireland defender Delaney exits Cork City after six months - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/damien-delaney-departure-cork-city-league-of-ireland-sse-airtricity-league-4380315-Dec2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGqfky9tY3DTWmUv4fEXgPQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:13:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/damien-delaney-departure-cork-city-league-of-ireland-sse-airtricity-league-4380315-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'I am eternally grateful': Ireland defender Delaney exits Cork City after six months&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CORK CITY HAVE parted ways with Ireland international Damien Delaney after six months at the club where the 36-year-old just nine starts since arriving in June. Delaney spent the majority of his career in England having moved to Leicester City in 2000, most recently making 170 appearances for Premier League side Crystal Palace — also making nine appearances for Ireland. He arrived back at Turners Cross as John Caulfield’s men prepared for Champions League qualifiers against Legia Warsaw, while also attempting to defend their Premier Division and FAI Cup titles. A poor performance against Bo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Seagulls soar into top half with win over Eagles despite first-half red card - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/seagulls-soar-into-top-half-with-win-over-eagles-despite-firsthalf-red-card-37595909.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO42xjCqSQKALQtF2xdExgAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:07:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/seagulls-soar-into-top-half-with-win-over-eagles-despite-firsthalf-red-card-37595909.html" target="_blank"&gt;Seagulls soar into top half with win over Eagles despite first-half red card&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brighton shrugged off the dismissal of Shane Duffy to ease to a 3-1 home victory over rivals Crystal Palace. The defender was given a straight red card for thrusting his head into Patrick van Aanholt’s, with Brighton 1-0 up through Glenn Murray’s penalty – but Leon Balogun and Florin Andone then found the target to secure all three points by half-time. Although Luka Milivojevic pulled one back from the penalty spot, it did not stop Chris Hughton’s team moving into the Premier League’s top 10. However, Roy Hodgson’s side remain only three points above the bottom three. ⏰ One of those special...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Ten-man Brighton take ‘M23 derby’ spoils after first-half thriller - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/04/first-half-thriller-sets-brighton-way-m23-derby-bragging-rights/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMRbUBLNkrJZmtcCitC4u5wqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDKzbcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:52:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/04/first-half-thriller-sets-brighton-way-m23-derby-bragging-rights/" target="_blank"&gt;Ten-man Brighton take ‘M23 derby’ spoils after first-half thriller&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the strangest but most ­entertaining rivalries in English football produced one of the ­strangest but most entertaining 20 minutes of this and many a season on a night that left Brighton fans wondering if what they had seen had really just happened. The “M23 derby” has a whole new tale that will be passed down the generations. For Brighton fans, it will be the memory of a three-goal surge of footballing delight, and for Palace and Roy Hodgson it will be a story forever remembered for a refereeing decision that triggered a defensive meltdown for the ages. In less than half an hour of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Wilfried Zaha is inhibited by his position change but Crystal Palace's lack of creativity is their real problem - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/05/wilfried-zaha-inhibited-position-change-crystal-palaces-lack/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF6M1Z4AVEz3uXKBpF1u7U0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:10:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/05/wilfried-zaha-inhibited-position-change-crystal-palaces-lack/" target="_blank"&gt;Wilfried Zaha is inhibited by his position change but Crystal Palace's lack of creativity is their real problem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest cheers on a night of jubilation for Brighton fans at the Amex Stadium on Tuesday was triggered not by one of their three goals, but by a relatively inconsequential tackle near the halfway line. Wilfried Zaha had taken the ball down for Crystal Palace, but he barely had time to look up before he had been barrelled out of the way by Brighton’s Martin Montoya. As Montoya sped down the touchline, the Brighton fans rose to their feet as one. For them this was a moment, as much as any of their three goals in a dramatic first half, that displayed their dominance over their great...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Brighton vs Crystal Palace: Ten-man Seagulls out-bully rivals in bitter encounter - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/brighton-vs-crystal-palace-live-score-goals-result-premier-league-epl-a8667606.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJgFg3MUysVmIjeu5UjLZuUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/brighton-vs-crystal-palace-live-score-goals-result-premier-league-epl-a8667606.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brighton vs Crystal Palace: Ten-man Seagulls out-bully rivals in bitter encounter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brighton fans have waited a long time – since 2013 – for a home league win over their great rivals from the other end of the A23 and there will have been extra satisfaction in the manner of this one. They went down to ten men after 31 minutes when Ireland defender Shane Duffy was sent off for headbutting Patrick van Aanholt shortly after Glenn Murray had put the Seagulls ahead against his old club from a highly controversial penalty, his seventh goal in seven home games this season. Substitute Leon Balogun then scored with his first touch to make it 2-0 and another substitute, Florin Andone...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Our morale is still good, insists Palace boss Hodgson - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/our-morale-is-still-good-insists-palace-boss-hodgson-37582313.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBxCLYIGdKJ39Nr129suUoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/our-morale-is-still-good-insists-palace-boss-hodgson-37582313.html" target="_blank"&gt;Our morale is still good, insists Palace boss Hodgson&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roy Hodgson is adamant morale at Crystal Palace is good despite an eight-match winless run in the Premier League, five matches without a goal and just two goals at Selhurst Park all season. Palace’s recent run can be explained by the high calibre of the opposition. Both home goals, in six matches, were penalties for Luka Milivojevic in the October 28 2-2 draw with Arsenal. Losses to Chelsea and Tottenham followed, before last week’s goalless draw at Manchester United. Burnley, who are a place behind Palace in 17th, visit Selhurst Park on Saturday, with Hodgson accentuating the positives and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Townsend brilliance helps Palace clinch overdue win to increase Burnley’s worries - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/townsend-brilliance-helps-palace-clinch-overdue-win-to-increase-burnleys-worries-37584907.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGQ80NfZF8Z-RaDac4OdsnEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 17:01:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/townsend-brilliance-helps-palace-clinch-overdue-win-to-increase-burnleys-worries-37584907.html" target="_blank"&gt;Townsend brilliance helps Palace clinch overdue win to increase Burnley’s worries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Palace ended their eight-match winless streak with a dominant 2-0 victory at Selhurst Park on Saturday as Burnley’s torrid campaign took another turn for the worse. James McArthur scored Palace’s first goal from open play at home this season before Andros Townsend secured the win with a fine goal 12 minutes from time. Sean Dyche’s side, now with just a single point from their last six outings, may have finished seventh last season, but the Clarets are a team devoid of confidence and, on the evidence of their display here, relegation would appear a distinct possibility. Their woes sh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Sam Allardyce's Sunderland reunion a forgettable one as Crystal Palace get hammered - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/sam-allardyces-sunderland-reunion-a-forgettable-one-as-crystal-palace-get-hammered-a7563096.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFHnPOwM6-JjyfnNwwQnbOoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/sam-allardyces-sunderland-reunion-a-forgettable-one-as-crystal-palace-get-hammered-a7563096.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sam Allardyce's Sunderland reunion a forgettable one as Crystal Palace get hammered&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Allardyce expected this reunion with his former club to mark a staging point in Crystal Palace's bid to secure their Premier League status. Instead, the manager was left humiliated as his current side were overwhelmed and embarrassed by a devastating first half performance from Sunderland that was capped by three goals in the final six minutes. With Lamina Kone having put Sunderland ahead in the tenth minute, Didier Ndong’s goal followed by two from Jermain Defoe settled the outcome before the interval had been reached. In a game between two sides rooted in the bottom three, only one lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Crystal Palace 0 Sunderland 4: Boos ring round Selhurst Park as Sam Allardyce's side are humiliated in six-pointer - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/02/04/crystal-palace-0-sunderland-4-boos-ring-roundselhurst-park-sam/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH6_3DT5pQOx8wXYsAcgxeYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDKzbcF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 17:16:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/02/04/crystal-palace-0-sunderland-4-boos-ring-roundselhurst-park-sam/" target="_blank"&gt;Crystal Palace 0 Sunderland 4: Boos ring round Selhurst Park as Sam Allardyce's side are humiliated in six-pointer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Allardyce had summed up this game as “the ultimate six-pointer” last week. The Crystal Palace manager never imagined that ‘ultimate humiliation’ may prove a more apt description. A devastating spell that brought three goals in six minutes at the end of the second half ensured it was Sunderland who emerged from this meeting between two of the bottom three teams with their spirit and survival hopes strengthened. David Moyes’ side move level on points with Allardyce’s side but the full impact of this result may become clearer in the coming weeks. Everything went right for Sunderland from t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Damien Delaney comes in for special mention as Alan Pardew reveals how Palace upped their game - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/sport/soccer/damien-delaney-comes-in-for-special-mention-as-alan-pardew-reveals-how-palace-upped-their-game-766990.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJuj44bsSL_00u0BjP_FrhkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 18:52:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/sport/soccer/damien-delaney-comes-in-for-special-mention-as-alan-pardew-reveals-how-palace-upped-their-game-766990.html" target="_blank"&gt;Damien Delaney comes in for special mention as Alan Pardew reveals how Palace upped their game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alan Pardew has revealed Crystal Palace's vastly-improved performance in their 3-0 defeat of Southampton owed much to a punishing training session on Thursday. The manager's team ended a run of six successive defeats that had put intense pressure on his position while earning their first clean sheet since August after two goals from Christian Benteke and another from James Tomkins. Victory took them away from the relegation zone while Southampton slid to 11th after a flat performance - and came after a week in which Pardew drilled his defence at Selhurst Park instead of their Beckenham trai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Frustration for Sam Allardyce as Christian Benteke's embarrassing penalty miss denies him first Palace victory - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/frustration-for-sam-allardyce-as-christian-bentekes-embarrassing-penalty-miss-denies-him-first-palace-victory-35321138.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECLgSle7hqgj0KB83FWEZEkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 14:49:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/frustration-for-sam-allardyce-as-christian-bentekes-embarrassing-penalty-miss-denies-him-first-palace-victory-35321138.html" target="_blank"&gt;Frustration for Sam Allardyce as Christian Benteke's embarrassing penalty miss denies him first Palace victory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Allardyce was denied victory in his first match as Crystal Palace manager after Troy Deeney's penalty earned Watford a 1-1 draw. The former England manager succeeded in coaxing an improved performance from some of the players whose poor form had contributed to predecessor Alan Pardew being sacked, and they were on course to win as he resumed his Premier League career at the same ground he oversaw his last match with Sunderland. Yohan Cabaye's first-half finish had given Palace the lead as they pursued only a fifth league win of the season, but the penalty that ended substitute Troy Deen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Watford vs Crystal Palace live - Troy Deeney penalty draws hosts level in Sam Allardyce's first game in charge - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2016/12/26/watford-vs-crystal-palace-live-sam-allardyce-takes-charge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIG2QTZdNfMeQgDBGJcRt24qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDKzbcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 14:25:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2016/12/26/watford-vs-crystal-palace-live-sam-allardyce-takes-charge/" target="_blank"&gt;Watford vs Crystal Palace live - Troy Deeney penalty draws hosts level in Sam Allardyce's first game in charge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;2:25PMFULL TIME Watford 1 Crystal Palace 1 Troy Deeney's penalty earns Watford a point after Christian Benteke misses from the spot. 2:23PM90 minutes+3 The ball is staying in midfield almost exclusively. A winning goal looks unlikely. 2:21PM90 minutes (1-1) Nice technique for Guedioura who swivels and gets a volley on target. Four minutes of stoppage time to play. 2:20PM89 minutes (1-1) Palace look reasonably content with a point. Watford having the better of the closing stages, but have lacked accuracy in their final pass especially from wide areas. 2:17PM87 minutes (1-1) Big Palace penalt...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Walking Dead: what is going wrong at the Premier League clubs with no points? - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/09/08/walking-dead-going-wrong-premier-league-clubs-no-points/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZMW8utHVRWztr9usnTT5wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/09/08/walking-dead-going-wrong-premier-league-clubs-no-points/" target="_blank"&gt;The Walking Dead: what is going wrong at the Premier League clubs with no points?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bournemouth Position:18th Results: West Brom (A, L 0-1), Watford (H, L 0-2), Man City (H, L 1-2) What's behind their slow start? Bournemouth have stuttered amid two different challenges: managing heightened expectations and ongoing changes to the squad. In their first two Premier League seasons, Bournemouth were very much regarded like Huddersfield as the club who had achieved something akin to a football miracle just by being there. Having finished in the top half of the table last season, the margins for further improvement are narrowing fast and that has created a different environment. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Benteke helps Big Sam break his Palace duck - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/benteke-helps-big-sam-break-his-palace-duck-35413963.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO8yZ5piw1o-Rbo_2YiSQBwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/benteke-helps-big-sam-break-his-palace-duck-35413963.html" target="_blank"&gt;Benteke helps Big Sam break his Palace duck&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Palace secured their first Premier League win under Sam Allardyce at the sixth time of asking as Bournemouth completed January without a win. Eagles winger Wilfried Zaha was excellent on his first appearance since returning from the African Nations Cup, but it was Scott Dann who gave the visitors the lead less than a minute into the second half. The defender capitalised on Damien Delaney's clever flick to score his first goal since September. There was further good news for Palace last night when a loan move was confirmed for Liverpool centre-back Mamadou Sakho with Palace paying a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>WATCH: Damien Delaney was confronted by an angry fan on the pitch at half-time - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/football/watch-damien-delaney-confronted-angry-fan-pitch-half-time/111997</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJViHTK1P5dUitKpvE0DAkgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wsq6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 17:06:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/football/watch-damien-delaney-confronted-angry-fan-pitch-half-time/111997" target="_blank"&gt;WATCH: Damien Delaney was confronted by an angry fan on the pitch at half-time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Palace lost 4-0 to Sunderland today. Four-nil. At home. To Sunderland, their relegation rivals. David Moyes' Sunderland. To make matters even worse for the home fans at Selhurst Park, Palace were losing 4-0 at half-time. Bottom of the table Sunderland would have been happy to beat any team. But to hammer the team managed by their former manager must have been very sweet. And Sam Allardyce must really wish he was still England manager. One Palace supporter was so angered by what he saw from Allardyce's side, he took his frustrations out on Damien Delaney. The supporter invaded the pi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Steve Parish gives Crystal Palace players dressing down after humiliating Sunderland defeat - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/02/06/steve-parish-gives-crystal-palace-players-dressing-humiliating/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBggHnkp4FgutSQ9wfrhm4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 09:30:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/02/06/steve-parish-gives-crystal-palace-players-dressing-humiliating/" target="_blank"&gt;Steve Parish gives Crystal Palace players dressing down after humiliating Sunderland defeat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Palace chairman Steve Parish laid it on the line to the club’s players after the humiliating 4-0 home defeat to Sunderland that leaves them in the Premier League relegation zone. Parish is understood to have taken the unusual step of going into the dressing room after Saturday’s match to tell the players how much a dire performance like that hurts the club’s supporters. His dramatic intervention occurred with the backing of Palace manager Sam Allardyce who also called the first-team squad into the club’s training ground at 7am on Sunday morning to go over the humiliating loss. Alla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Seamus Coleman scores late Everton winner to prove Crystal palace's stay in the relegation zone may be a long one - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/crystal-palace-vs-tottenham-match-report-seamus-coleman-goal-premier-league-epl-table-results-latest-a7539526.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjfaDTxmb_StuPNS97yYNAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 16:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/crystal-palace-vs-tottenham-match-report-seamus-coleman-goal-premier-league-epl-table-results-latest-a7539526.html" target="_blank"&gt;Seamus Coleman scores late Everton winner to prove Crystal palace's stay in the relegation zone may be a long one&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Allardyce’s search for a first Premier League win with Crystal Palace will stretch to its sixth game after Seamus Coleman’s late strike consigned the south Londoners to the fourth defeat of his short tenure so far. Upon taking the job at Selhurst Park, Allardyce may have been confident that even if this costly squad of floundering players continued to underperform, three others elsewhere would still do worse. Then came Swansea’s lunchtime win at Anfield, which dropped Palace into the bottom three and suggested there are few certainties in this season’s relegation scrap. Allardyce made t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Crystal Palace 0 Burnley 2: Sean Dyche's side finally end away-day woes to near Premier League safety - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/04/29/crystal-palace-vs-burnley-live-scores-plus-roboblogger-goals2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPnf3Q6PF9fdpzdZhkduHt8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 18:42:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/04/29/crystal-palace-vs-burnley-live-scores-plus-roboblogger-goals2/" target="_blank"&gt;Crystal Palace 0 Burnley 2: Sean Dyche's side finally end away-day woes to near Premier League safety&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burnley took a huge stride towards retaining their Premier League existence with their first away win of the season, as goals from Ashley Barnes and Andre Gray moved them above Palace and into 14th place. Neither side are certain of safety yet, and Palace may face sanctions after James Tarkowski, the Burnley defender, was hit on the head by a cigarette lighter thrown from the crowd as he celebrated the opening goal with his team-mates in the seventh minute. Tarkowski went down clutching his head after being hit by the lighter, which appeared to come out of the corner of the Holmesdale End, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Burnley take vital points as they seal first away win of the season - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/burnley-crystal-palace-report-3366310-Apr2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMpivcPoHncWQcBMw-CJ3FoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 19:01:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/burnley-crystal-palace-report-3366310-Apr2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Burnley take vital points as they seal first away win of the season&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BURNLEY WON AWAY in the Premier League for the first time this season, at the 18th time of asking, with Ashley Barnes and Andre Gray scoring in a 2-0 success at Crystal Palace on Saturday. Sean Dyche’s side had lost on 13 of their 15 Premier League visits to London and had won just one of their last 11 league matches to slip precariously close to the relegation zone. But a vital three points sees Burnley move away from danger – the Clarets are eight points clear of third-bottom Swansea City – and they now look well set to survive in the Premier League for the first time in the club’s histor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Watford vs Crystal Palace match report: Troy Deeney gets Hornets out of jail as Sam Allardyce sees enough to work with - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/watford-vs-crystal-palace-match-report-troy-deeney-jail-sam-allardyce-a7496301.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHs5W-4AUaZOGBaO6xlLuUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/watford-vs-crystal-palace-match-report-troy-deeney-jail-sam-allardyce-a7496301.html" target="_blank"&gt;Watford vs Crystal Palace match report: Troy Deeney gets Hornets out of jail as Sam Allardyce sees enough to work with&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Allardyce knew the chants were coming but what he did learn is that his Crystal Palace players are up for the fight. Allardyce, having never been relegated from the Premier League, would have seen enough at Vicarage Road to remain confident that his CV will remain unblemished. A hard-fought point at Watford could have been much more. It took a needless shove from Damien Delaney for Troy Deeney's penalty to cancel out Yohan Cabaye's opener. - Read more Allardyce says critics 'can't take away England job from him' Allardyce, aka the survival specialist, is back and doing what he does best...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Sam Allardyce has made Crystal Palace more resilient, says Damien Delaney - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2016/dec/27/sam-allardyce-crystal-palace-damien-delaney</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENSNlGI8JS4jmtiVX_f4VywqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 22:30:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2016/dec/27/sam-allardyce-crystal-palace-damien-delaney" target="_blank"&gt;Sam Allardyce has made Crystal Palace more resilient, says Damien Delaney&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damien Delaney expects the Sam Allardyce effect to ensure Crystal Palace remain in the Premier League but admitted there is still plenty of work to be done after allowing Watford to rescue a point at Vicarage Road on Boxing Day. Yohan Cabaye’s first‑half goal had given Palace a 1-0 lead but Delaney’s tug on Sebastian Prödl cost them dear when Troy Deeney converted from the penalty spot for his 100th Watford goal. It was a disappointing ending to what had been a much-improved performance from Palace, who sacked Alan Pardew and replaced him with the former England manager last week. The resul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Fan arrested after confrontation with Ireland international Damien Delaney - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/sport/soccer/fan-arrested-after-confrontation-with-ireland-international-damien-delaney-775590.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIFrrpjc6-UIM25PdyLiDTMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 19:30:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/sport/soccer/fan-arrested-after-confrontation-with-ireland-international-damien-delaney-775590.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fan arrested after confrontation with Ireland international Damien Delaney&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Crystal Palace supporter has been arrested after he invaded the Selhurst Park pitch to confront Damien Delaney at half-time of their 4-0 home defeat by Sunderland. The result - in a crucial fixture they needed to win against a relegation rival - has left them at significant risk of returning to the Championship and represented a new low in their season, while Sunderland's was revived. Palace conceded three goals in the six minutes leading up to half-time, leading to widespread booing among their fans and chants of "you're not fit to wear the shirt". Fan tries to 'Punch' Delaney pic.twitte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Sam Allardyce: Palace must win Selhurst showdown with Swansea - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/sam-allardyce-palace-must-win-selhurst-showdown-with-swansea-35335429.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENFEd7IUM-AIO5iEP4duJh0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 11:01:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/sam-allardyce-palace-must-win-selhurst-showdown-with-swansea-35335429.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sam Allardyce: Palace must win Selhurst showdown with Swansea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Allardyce has identified Tuesday's home showdown with Swansea as being crucial to Crystal Palace's hopes of surviving in the Premier League. Sunday's 2-0 defeat at Arsenal left Allardyce's new club in 17th place and with a total of only 16 points from 19 games. Swansea are widely expected to appoint a new manager of their own by Tuesday evening, but Allardyce is wary of the need to win if Palace are to climb clear of the bottom three. He has already complained that Swansea have had an additional day's preparation for this fixture, and to that end made second-half changes at Arsenal to p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Crystal Palace 1 Huddersfield Town 0: Bakary Sako bags rare goal at Selhurst Park in League Cup tie - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/09/19/crystal-palace-1-huddersfield-town-0bakary-sako-bags-rare-goal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJqffjBnArDi67IaKck17MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 20:49:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/09/19/crystal-palace-1-huddersfield-town-0bakary-sako-bags-rare-goal/" target="_blank"&gt;Crystal Palace 1 Huddersfield Town 0: Bakary Sako bags rare goal at Selhurst Park in League Cup tie&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has been a long time coming – since May 14, to be precise – but Crystal Palace finally scored against another Premier League club last night at the seventh attempt. Bakary Sako became the first Palace player since Patrick van Aanholt wrapped up a 4-0 victory over Hull City in the penultimate match of last season to put the ball past a top-flight goalkeeper when he headed home after 13 minutes. The caveat, of course, is that he beat Huddersfield Town’s reserve goalkeeper in a match in which both sides made nine changes from their most recent Premier League match. Manchester City, Palace’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Sam Allardyce gets first league win as Crystal Palace ease past Bournemouth - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/sam-allardyce-gets-first-league-win-as-crystal-palace-ease-past-bournemouth-a7556046.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEArDuaghydXkMiAVUmoD5FcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/sam-allardyce-gets-first-league-win-as-crystal-palace-ease-past-bournemouth-a7556046.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sam Allardyce gets first league win as Crystal Palace ease past Bournemouth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Dann and Christian Benteke's second half goals gave Sam Allardyce the deadline day outcome the Crystal Palace manager wanted most. Six league games on since he took charge at Selhurst Park – and with just a solitary point earned from the previous five – the manager was finally able to celebrate winning three points. A clean sheet came as a welcome bonus and while Palace’s plight means it will take more performances like this to ensure they succeed in their battle to avoid relegation, Allardyce will undoubtedly view this as a potential turning point. The manager had voiced his frustrat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Burnley record their first away win of the season to leave Crystal Palace staring nervously over their shoulder - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/crystal-palace-0-burnley-2-premier-league-match-report-andre-barnes-andre-gray-goals-a7709816.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGnMesf4DAnfX1dWsrQTkGgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/crystal-palace-0-burnley-2-premier-league-match-report-andre-barnes-andre-gray-goals-a7709816.html" target="_blank"&gt;Burnley record their first away win of the season to leave Crystal Palace staring nervously over their shoulder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last time Burnley won a Premier League match away from home, Great Britain was still in the European Union, David Cameron was still the Prime Minister, and the chances of relegation-threatened Leicester City winning the Premier League appeared as remote as those of reality television star Donald Trump being elected to the White House. How times change. But at Selhurst Park on Saturday, Burnley finally ended a run of 17 away matches that had seem them accrue just four points, Ashley Barnes and Andre Gray scoring in a win that could well have just secured their Premier League status for a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Daniel McDonnell: Long and Wilson calls highlight shortage of Premier options - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/international-soccer/daniel-mcdonnell-long-and-wilson-calls-highlight-shortage-of-premier-options-35719338.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK_EBXg7zF0_vfIzLWA-hu4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/international-soccer/daniel-mcdonnell-long-and-wilson-calls-highlight-shortage-of-premier-options-35719338.html" target="_blank"&gt;Daniel McDonnell: Long and Wilson calls highlight shortage of Premier options&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of Irishmen to have lined out at Premier League action this season stands at 18. Two of those, Damien Delaney and Shay Given, are no longer available to Martin O'Neill. So the maths are simple enough when the Irish boss has a penchant for naming squads that run close to 40 names. Any player capable of a spin at top-flight level automatically comes into the equation. The meeting of Burnley and West Brom last Saturday week was significant because six Irish options figured in proceedings. By making their first league appearances of the season, Kevin Long and Marc Wilson put themselv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Crystal Palace defender Damien Delaney says it's time to stand up and be counted - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/crystal-palace-defender-damien-delaney-says-its-time-to-stand-up-and-be-counted-35341201.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIK_M4blJOWXTLaix-LPbnIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 12:26:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/crystal-palace-defender-damien-delaney-says-its-time-to-stand-up-and-be-counted-35341201.html" target="_blank"&gt;Crystal Palace defender Damien Delaney says it's time to stand up and be counted&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Palace's Damien Delaney believes their 2-1 defeat by Swansea on Tuesday has demonstrated how much they are at risk of relegation. It was widely felt that the recent appointment of Sam Allardyce, a manager who has never been relegated from the Premier League, combined with the several quality players Palace possess would ensure they would climb clear of the bottom three. On Tuesday, however, in a match Allardyce insisted was crucial to their hopes of survival, they were poor and were booed off at half-time. Delaney believes the time has passed for 17th-placed Palace to think their co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Brian Kerr: Long way to go - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/brian-kerr-long-way-to-go-35481521.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOniwrmRAz_-1_v-FVJioSEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 17:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/brian-kerr-long-way-to-go-35481521.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brian Kerr: Long way to go&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you wanted to, you could look at the world of Irish football right now and trick yourself into believing everything was perfect. After all, 2016 ended with Martin O'Neill's team top of their World Cup qualification group following on from three credible performances at the European Championships when Irish people began to feel good about their national team again. More immediately, you could point to the presence of Shane Long at Wembley tomorrow and point out that he is just the latest Irish international to visit the home of English football within the last three years, following on fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Crystal Palace fan arrested by police after attempting to 'punch' Damien Delaney - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/crystal-palace-fan-arrested-by-police-after-attempting-to-punch-damien-delaney-35423693.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA_7X2PAQyoadLo8t0A9r_QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 17:48:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/crystal-palace-fan-arrested-by-police-after-attempting-to-punch-damien-delaney-35423693.html" target="_blank"&gt;Crystal Palace fan arrested by police after attempting to 'punch' Damien Delaney&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A furious Crystal Palace supporter had to be restrained by Selhurst Park security after invading the pitch to confront Eagles defender, Damien Delaney. In a must-win match for Sam Allardyce's Premier League strugglers, Crystal Palace were left stunned as they found themselves 4-0 down to Sunderland at half time. Lamine Kone had given the away side an early lead before three quick-fire goals led to chants of "you're not fit to wear the shirt" from irate Palace supporters. The humiliating scoreline was too much for one fan to bare as he forced his way onto the Selhurst Park pitch to confront ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Crystal Palace v Burnley - the story of the match - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/crystal-palace-v-burnley-the-story-of-the-match-35666172.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMaYTQk1HzdTeyyXzhrkopIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 18:36:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/crystal-palace-v-burnley-the-story-of-the-match-35666172.html" target="_blank"&gt;Crystal Palace v Burnley - the story of the match&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burnley broke their away-day duck and eased their relegation fears as goals from Ashley Barnes and Andre Gray secured a 2-0 win at Crystal Palace. Barnes struck after just eight minutes and goalkeeper Tom Heaton kept Palace at bay before substitute Gray hit a late second, to ensure the Clarets finally registered their first success on the road this season. It was also Burnley's first ever Premier League victory in London - at the 16th attempt - which lifted them above Palace and, crucially, eight points clear of the drop zone. TWEET OF THE MATCH "The Clarets secure a crucial first #PL away ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Seamus Coleman hits late Everton winner with Sam Allardyce still waiting for his first league win with Palace - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/seamus-coleman-hits-late-everton-winner-with-sam-allardyce-still-waiting-for-his-first-league-win-with-palace-35386940.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFUbJzg7FCuaWnlXt5sFr1QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 17:30:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/seamus-coleman-hits-late-everton-winner-with-sam-allardyce-still-waiting-for-his-first-league-win-with-palace-35386940.html" target="_blank"&gt;Seamus Coleman hits late Everton winner with Sam Allardyce still waiting for his first league win with Palace&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everton earned a third win in four when Seamus Coleman's 87th-minute goal gave them a deserved 1-0 Premier League victory at Crystal Palace and ensured their season continued to gain momentum. They had last week unexpectedly defeated Manchester City 4-0, but despite that free-scoring performance appeared at risk of dropping two points amid Palace resiliently defending their consistent and convincing attacks. Victory strengthens Everton's grip on seventh place, and leaves relegation-threatened Palace in the bottom three, but the hosts may yet take some consolation in knowing new manager Sam ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Damien Delaney is better than Paul Pogba. Not our words but the words of this excited bunch - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/football/damien-delaney-is-better-than-paul-pogba-not-our-words-but-the-words-of-this-excited-bunch/106299</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELc3IE1BQjb8UhLqi7U996cqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wsq6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 22:17:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/football/damien-delaney-is-better-than-paul-pogba-not-our-words-but-the-words-of-this-excited-bunch/106299" target="_blank"&gt;Damien Delaney is better than Paul Pogba. Not our words but the words of this excited bunch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We wouldn't hold our breaths waiting for Damien Delaney's 100 million move but, still, this was a gorgeous little flick. The Corkman came up with a sublime piece of skill at the start of the second half to set up the equaliser for James McArthur when Crystal Palace hosted Manchester United on Wednesday night. United claimed all three points but it was the performance of the Irish defender that stole the headlines. Well, not so much the performance as this one touch. Not what you would call the flashiest player on any pitch, Delaney provided a no-look, first time flick that played in McArthu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>The Dozen: the weekend's best Premier League photos - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/gallery/2016/oct/24/the-dozen-the-weekends-best-premier-league-photos</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJBfZcchBPuobAB8u8vqcJoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 23:05:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/gallery/2016/oct/24/the-dozen-the-weekends-best-premier-league-photos" target="_blank"&gt;The Dozen: the weekend's best Premier League photos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A scenic view of Turf Moor as Burnley seal the points with a 2-1 win over Everton. Sam Vokes opened the scoring, before Yannick Bolasie equalised, but Scott Arfield’s 90th-minute winner gave Burnley their third victory of the season Photograph: Anthony Devlin/Reuters Burnley’s Michael Keane wraps up Everton’s Kevin Mirallas. Sean Dyche’s side haven’t conceded more than once in any of their past 19 league games at Turf Moor, since a 2-0 defeat to Preston in December 2015 Photograph: Anthony Devlin/Reuters Winston Reid scores the only goal of the game against Sunderland at the Londo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Sunderland’s Jermain Defoe heaps misery on broken Crystal Palace - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2017/feb/04/crystal-palace-sunderland-premier-league-match-report</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJThlAW4t4E2PJdTP11e4VgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 17:09:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2017/feb/04/crystal-palace-sunderland-premier-league-match-report" target="_blank"&gt;Sunderland’s Jermain Defoe heaps misery on broken Crystal Palace&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fine performance was not enough to lift Sunderland off the bottom of the table but four first-half goals did bring them level on points with Crystal Palace. What’s more, at the 38th time of asking they finally won a Premier League match which their midfielder Jack Rodwell started. Substituted in the second half with a hamstring injury, the midfielder will have enjoyed getting this giant chest-beating gorilla off his back. Sam Allardyce, by contrast, was left visibly appalled and apoplectic by a first half in which Palace charitably allowed Sunderland to score more goals than they had mana...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Fan arrested after confrontation with Delaney - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/soccer/2017/0204/850235-fan-confrontation-delaney/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ-4jBexhwfDWrJrk84dw0EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 23:47:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/soccer/2017/0204/850235-fan-confrontation-delaney/" target="_blank"&gt;Fan arrested after confrontation with Delaney&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Crystal Palace supporter has been arrested after he invaded the Selhurst Park pitch to confront former Ireland international Damien Delaney at half-time of their 4-0 home defeat by Sunderland. This was crucial game for struggling Palace and defeat to the bottom team sees them slump to second last in the table, ahead of Sunderland only on goal difference. Palace conceded three goals in the six minutes leading up to half-time, leading to widespread booing among their fans and chants of "you're not fit to wear the shirt". It was as they were walking off at half-time that the fan broke onto t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Premier League club captains: name the 20 for the 2017-18 season - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2017/aug/08/premier-league-club-captains-name-the-20-for-the-2017-18-season</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH4nT4T7TptXaHK6sPL1hbAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 11:00:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2017/aug/08/premier-league-club-captains-name-the-20-for-the-2017-18-season" target="_blank"&gt;Premier League club captains: name the 20 for the 2017-18 season&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Arsenal - Laurent Koscielny - Per Mertesacker - Aaron Ramsey - Theo Walcott - Bournemouth - Simon Francis - Artur Boruc - Steve Cook - Harry Arter - Brighton - Liam Rosenior - Glenn Murray - Dale Stephens - Bruno - Burnley - Phil Bardsley - Sam Vokes - Tom Heaton - Robbie Brady - Chelsea - David Luiz - Gary Cahill - Eden Hazard - Cesc Fàbregas - Crystal Palace - Martin Kelly - James Tomkins - Damien Delaney - Jason Puncheon - Everton - Wayne Rooney - Phil Jagielka - Leighton Baines - Ashley Williams - Huddersfield Town - Dean Whitehead - Aaron Mooy - Mark Hudson - Tom Ince - Leicester Cit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Tracing the marginalisation of Irish players in the Premier League - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/tracing-the-marginalisation-of-irish-players-in-the-premier-league-3541394-Aug2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFaIxi3OvLm68R234LNmzuUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 06:15:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/tracing-the-marginalisation-of-irish-players-in-the-premier-league-3541394-Aug2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Tracing the marginalisation of Irish players in the Premier League&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE IS A widely held perception that there has been a significant decrease in the prevalence of Irish players in England’s top flight in the last 25 years. While this assumption is true to a degree, it needs to be placed in a wider context. The figures below prove illuminating, but firstly a number of factors as to how they were compiled must be taken into consideration. It should be noted that in order to be eligible for the list below, the Irish player in question needs to have started at least one Premier League game in the relevant season. So Declan Rice, who appeared as a substitute ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Patrick van Aanholt's winner against Middlesbrough moves Sam Allardyce's Eagles in the right direction - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/crystal-palace-middlesbrough-relegation-fight-patrick-van-aanholt-goal-relegation-a7599616.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPpNuioJBcIaOuoktnUhsgAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 16:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/crystal-palace-middlesbrough-relegation-fight-patrick-van-aanholt-goal-relegation-a7599616.html" target="_blank"&gt;Patrick van Aanholt's winner against Middlesbrough moves Sam Allardyce's Eagles in the right direction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Allardyce can, on occasion, look somewhat pleased with himself, like the cat that got the cream. But, on a drizzly afternoon in south London, 25,416 people witnessed a Crystal Palace victory that felt almost entirely of his own making. The Eagles did not overcome the most testing of foes in Middlesbrough, but they did get back to winning ways and rise out of the relegation zone with a performance that was unrecognisable from what had come before. Palace had gone from a team treading water at the end of Alan Pardew’s reign to one that was simply drowning when Sunderland came to Selhurst ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Sunderland stun Crystal Palace to go level on points with relegation rivals - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/sunderland-stun-crystal-palace-to-go-level-on-points-with-relegation-rivals-35423639.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECxG1fG1Rz6RU4M-1aqpIYcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 17:06:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/sunderland-stun-crystal-palace-to-go-level-on-points-with-relegation-rivals-35423639.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sunderland stun Crystal Palace to go level on points with relegation rivals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunderland began their latest attempt to secure another great escape from relegation with a convincing 4-0 victory at troubled Crystal Palace. Strengthened by their recruitment throughout January and the returns of those playing at the African Nations Cup, they left their hosts at their greatest risk of relegation since they returned to the Premier League in 2013. Even after Jermain Defoe's two goals doubled the advantage built by earlier finishes from Lamine Kone and Didier N'Dong, Sunderland's latest three points only brought their total to 19 - level with 19th-placed Palace - and did not...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>In Tray facing the new Crystal Palace manager - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/in-tray-facing-the-new-crystal-palace-manager-35315399.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJUtLMUiy4LtBmgxctWH-BUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 16:26:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/in-tray-facing-the-new-crystal-palace-manager-35315399.html" target="_blank"&gt;In Tray facing the new Crystal Palace manager&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Palace are on the lookout for a new manager after sacking Alan Pardew on Thursday. The Eagles are currently just a point and a place above the Premier League relegation zone after one win in 11 games. Here, Press Association Sport takes a look at what the pressing issues will be for Pardew's replacement at Selhurst Park. ORGANISE THE DEFENCE Oddly, given the experienced Scott Dann, Damien Delaney and James Tomkins are Palace's senior central defenders, they have conceded far too many goals since the start of the season. The Eagles have let in 32 in 17 Premier League games, the sort ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Crystal Palace manager Sam Allardyce says fans have every right to boo players following Sunderland thrashing at Selhurst Park - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/02/05/crystal-palace-manager-sam-allardyce-says-fans-have-every-right/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELSM-Jbv8f_NJ1y_gmO_hbsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDKzbcF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/02/05/crystal-palace-manager-sam-allardyce-says-fans-have-every-right/" target="_blank"&gt;Crystal Palace manager Sam Allardyce says fans have every right to boo players following Sunderland thrashing at Selhurst Park&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A week of soul-searching has begun at Crystal Palace, with manager and players in agreement that the Selhurst Park supporters were entitled to vent their fury following Saturday’s collapse against Sunderland. Sam Allardyce condemned the pitch invader who was arrested after confronting Damien Delaney as the centre-back left the pitch at half-time but, having expressed his dismay at his side’s fragility, said he understood the view of the majority that was reflected in the angry reaction to a five-minute spell before the break in which the home side conceded three preventable goals. “It’s an ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>A complete guide to Irish footballers playing in the Premier League this season - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/irish-players-in-the-premier-league-guide-russia-2018-martin-oneill-3541992-Aug2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEELBPduTt5Xf_oCeLosEILEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 07:30:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/irish-players-in-the-premier-league-guide-russia-2018-martin-oneill-3541992-Aug2017/" target="_blank"&gt;A complete guide to Irish footballers playing in the Premier League this season&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Updated at 8.45 THE NUMBER OF Irish players in the Premier League has decreased every season over the last five years. From a high of 33 in 2011-12 the number has dropped to just 16 as the 2017/18 season gets underway this weekend. Here is a complete guide to every Irish player who will be playing in the top tier of English football this season: Harry Arter Club: Bournemouth Age: 27 Appearances/goals last season: 35 (1) What to expect: Arter played 35 times last season as Bournemouth finished in ninth place. The player has been at the club throughout its incredible rise from League One to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Jeff Hendrick and 35 other Irish players who could feature in the FA Cup this weekend - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/irish-players-could-feature-fa-cup-this-weekend-3209015-Jan2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEovjx7u-sVbcZYuPwCtYhkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 15:26:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/irish-players-could-feature-fa-cup-this-weekend-3209015-Jan2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Jeff Hendrick and 35 other Irish players who could feature in the FA Cup this weekend&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;N.B. THIS LIST does not include Irish players who are currently injured. Richard Keogh, Alex Pearce and Cyrus Christie could all feature for Derby, who take on reigning Premier League champions Leicester at the iPro Stadium tonight. Joe Mason, Connor Ronan and Matt Doherty are all available for Wolves’ early Saturday kick-off against Liverpool. Derrick Williams, Darragh Lenihan and Anthony Stokes are in line to play for Blackburn against Blackpool, who have Mark Yeates and Eddie Nolan available. Jeff Hendrick and Stephen Long are in contention to play Bristol City, who have Callum O’Dowda i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Alan Pardew gives unlikely Irish defender the almost impossible task of taming the Premier League's best striker - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/alan-pardew-gives-unlikely-irish-defender-the-almost-impossible-task-of-taming-the-premier-leagues-best-striker-35301574.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDERosHMbIvFgQffDlicdcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 10:51:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/alan-pardew-gives-unlikely-irish-defender-the-almost-impossible-task-of-taming-the-premier-leagues-best-striker-35301574.html" target="_blank"&gt;Alan Pardew gives unlikely Irish defender the almost impossible task of taming the Premier League's best striker&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alan Pardew has given Damien Delaney the task of nullifying the threat posed by Diego Costa when Crystal Palace host Chelsea. The Premier League leaders visit Pardew's team on Saturday hoping to equal a club-record run of 11 straight wins, when the in-form Costa is again expected to be key. Since Antonio Conte's summer appointment as Chelsea manager, Costa has excelled with his work-rate and in scoring 12 goals in 18 games, perhaps establishing himself as even more influential than Eden Hazard. Delaney, meanwhile, has re-emerged as significant to Pardew's team having losing his first-team p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Christian Benteke could lose Crystal Palace penalty duty - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/christian-benteke-could-lose-crystal-palace-penalty-duty-35332278.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED077CNgiZqhyZINF4qughUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 12:06:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/christian-benteke-could-lose-crystal-palace-penalty-duty-35332278.html" target="_blank"&gt;Christian Benteke could lose Crystal Palace penalty duty&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christian Benteke could pay the penalty for his spot-kick blunders this season. The Crystal Palace striker has missed twice in four attempts from 12 yards, the latest a weak effort in the 1-1 Boxing Day draw at Watford. That failure arguably cost Sam Allardyce a winning start to life as Eagles manager, and they head to Arsenal on New Year's Day with Allardyce weighing up his penalty options. "We need to find someone to take penalties. I have no idea who at the moment," Allardyce said. "But first I've got to decide on the team, then when we've done that we'll talk about the penalty situation...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Cazorla, Terry, Touré: the Premier League players with expiring contracts - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2016/dec/29/cazorla-terry-toure-expiring-contracts-premier-league</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL1SEzfnnD0zVkAoCA4-owQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 14:54:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2016/dec/29/cazorla-terry-toure-expiring-contracts-premier-league" target="_blank"&gt;Cazorla, Terry, Touré: the Premier League players with expiring contracts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The traditional January sales may have taken a hit from Black Friday but the football world still loves a good bargain. With less than six months left on their contracts when 2017 is ushered in on Sunday, almost 70 Premier League first-team squad members will be free to discuss terms with clubs from overseas under Fifa’s rules on transfers. That means the likes of Arsenal’s Santi Cazorla, Yaya Touré of Manchester City, Manchester United’s Michael Carrick and Chelsea’s John Terry could all sign pre-contract agreements if they fancy a change of scenery. Related: A 2016 football moment to reme...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Big Sam sees red as Delaney is confronted by angry fan - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/big-sam-sees-red-as-delaney-is-confronted-by-angry-fan-35425816.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAaLHXLUD7oaNrK6vwcCpB0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/big-sam-sees-red-as-delaney-is-confronted-by-angry-fan-35425816.html" target="_blank"&gt;Big Sam sees red as Delaney is confronted by angry fan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A week of soul-searching has begun at Crystal Palace, with manager and players in agreement that the Selhurst Park supporters were entitled to vent their fury following Saturday's 4-0 thrashing by Sunderland. Sam Allardyce condemned the pitch invader who was arrested after confronting Damien Delaney as the centre-back left the pitch at half-time. However, the Palace boss said he understood the angry reaction of the supporters to a five-minute spell before the break in which the home side conceded three preventable goals. "It's an emotional game and fans get very emotional when they see us t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Crystal Palace not looking to sign John Terry, says manager Sam Allardyce - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/crystal-palace-not-looking-to-sign-john-terry-says-manager-sam-allardyce-35639329.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKNUrAdZm2-Esdx0Ry0tJOQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 13:46:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/crystal-palace-not-looking-to-sign-john-terry-says-manager-sam-allardyce-35639329.html" target="_blank"&gt;Crystal Palace not looking to sign John Terry, says manager Sam Allardyce&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Allardyce has dismissed the prospect of John Terry joining Crystal Palace when he leaves Chelsea at the end of the season. The 36-year-old is to leave Stamford Bridge when his contract expires in the summer, and he intends to play on. Offers to remain in London may appeal to Terry should he choose against uprooting his family, but even as Palace edge closer to securing their Premier League status their manager insists Terry has no place in his plans. Palace have no option to retain Mamadou Sakho beyond the end of his loan spell and Damien Delaney's contract is also due to expire around ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>The FA are FINALLY clamping down on the worst part of football - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/football/fa-finally-clamping-worst-part-football/109759</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGb9sJLD3G5GoTrt_3CoUVoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 09:01:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/football/fa-finally-clamping-worst-part-football/109759" target="_blank"&gt;The FA are FINALLY clamping down on the worst part of football&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good. Now let's make sure they follow through. The FA are looking at ways of stamping diving out of football and they're looking at introducing retrospective bans to do so. How many times does a player throw himself over to either try or succeed in winning a penalty or a free? How many times does a player feign injury when there's contact from an opposing player? How many times does a player feign injury when there's no contact from an opposing player? All of it is cheating - the stingiest form of it. It's unsportsmanlike. It's disgusting. No-one likes it. Every time a player gains an advan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Fan arrested after Delaney incident - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/fan-arrested-after-delaney-incident-35424426.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzrVtPz5mjedrisdYjKx0MqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/fan-arrested-after-delaney-incident-35424426.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fan arrested after Delaney incident&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Crystal Palace supporter has been arrested after he invaded the Selhurst Park pitch to confront Damien Delaney at half-time of this defeat. The result has left the troubled Eagles deep in relegation trouble and represented a new low in their season, while Sunderland's was revived. Palace conceded three goals in the six minutes leading up to half-time, leading to widespread booing among their fans and chants of "you're not fit to wear the shirt". It was as they were walking off at half-time that the fan broke onto the pitch to confront Delaney, coming face to face with the defender and app...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Top 50 Irish players of the Premier League era - 40-31 - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/top-50-irish-players-of-the-premier-league-era-4031-36011623.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOX_7nUusQWNBtD1bPtGEPkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 13:43:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/top-50-irish-players-of-the-premier-league-era-4031-36011623.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top 50 Irish players of the Premier League era - 40-31&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the Premier League prepares to enter its 26th season this weekend, we’ve decided to celebrate its first 25 years this week by honouring the top 50 Irish players to ever play in the top flight of English football. The list accounts for a player’s talent, the individual and team success he had in the league, and the impact they had at their respective clubs, hence, why a player like Kevin Moran, who played just two seasons in the Premier League with Blackburn Rovers, is not rated as highly as Kevin Kilbane who played 11 seasons in the Premier League. The list is not necessarily a reflectio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Premier League round up: Wins for Palace and Swans - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/soccer/2017/0131/849130-premier-league-round-up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMihXxGHh78L1VJ8FErsdNEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 22:13:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/soccer/2017/0131/849130-premier-league-round-up/" target="_blank"&gt;Premier League round up: Wins for Palace and Swans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Allardyce finally tasted victory in his sixth league match as Crystal Palace manager as his team took a step towards safety with a 2-0 win at Bournemouth. Scott Dann put Palace in front a minute after halftime after Damien Delaney had flicked on Jason Puncheon's cross. After withstanding intense second-half pressure from Bournemouth, Christian Benteke made sure of all three points when he headed in a cross from substitute Andros Townsend. Palace, who gave a debut to wing back to Patrick van Aanholt, signed on Monday from relegation rivals Sunderland, had gone closest in an uninspiring f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>'It's only a matter of time before he gets into the international team' - QPR boss has high hopes for young Irish star - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/its-only-a-matter-of-time-before-he-gets-into-the-international-team-qpr-boss-has-high-hopes-for-young-irish-star-35518493.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL3RrSEul-Yyxn5Trd_-PEYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 09:56:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/its-only-a-matter-of-time-before-he-gets-into-the-international-team-qpr-boss-has-high-hopes-for-young-irish-star-35518493.html" target="_blank"&gt;'It's only a matter of time before he gets into the international team' - QPR boss has high hopes for young Irish star&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GALWAY lad Ryan Manning will progress to play at Premier League and international level, the player's manager at club level believes. Manning (20) has only 12 first team appearances under his belt at QPR this season, having been given a debut by new boss Ian Holloway in December. A senior international call up will have to wait as the former Galway United man won't be involved for the World Cup qualifier at home to Wales and will instead get his first-ever call up to the U21 squad, for a Euro qualifier against Kosovo. But Holloway feels Manning has the talent to go all the way. "He could ea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Punishing training session led to much-improved Palace display - Alan Pardew - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/punishing-training-session-led-to-muchimproved-palace-display-alan-pardew-35265855.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECOJxW_oBbEbY3qNJs1EQRIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 18:51:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/punishing-training-session-led-to-muchimproved-palace-display-alan-pardew-35265855.html" target="_blank"&gt;Punishing training session led to much-improved Palace display - Alan Pardew&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alan Pardew has revealed Crystal Palace's vastly-improved performance in their 3-0 defeat of Southampton owed much to a punishing training session on Thursday. The manager's team ended a run of six successive defeats that had put intense pressure on his position while earning their first clean sheet since August after two goals from Christian Benteke and another from James Tomkins. Victory took them away from the relegation zone while Southampton slid to 11th after a flat performance - and came after a week in which Pardew drilled his defence at Selhurst Park instead of their Beckenham trai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Spurs youngster Foyth shrugs off nightmare Premier League debut to score winner at Crystal Palace - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/spurs-youngster-foyth-shrugs-off-nightmare-premier-league-debut-to-score-winner-at-crystal-palace-37514659.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI9F7aqBirk16NtPlYeBoqQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 21:14:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/spurs-youngster-foyth-shrugs-off-nightmare-premier-league-debut-to-score-winner-at-crystal-palace-37514659.html" target="_blank"&gt;Spurs youngster Foyth shrugs off nightmare Premier League debut to score winner at Crystal Palace&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juan Foyth shrugged off his nightmare Premier League debut to score his first goal in professional football as Tottenham won 1-0 at Crystal Palace. In last week's fixture at Wolves Foyth conceded two penalties to put Spurs' eventual 3-2 victory and his reputation at risk. But, with his team struggling to convince at Selhurst Park, the 20-year-old Argentinian demonstrated an unrivalled hunger and desire to seize on the loose ball and head home the goal that secured all three points. Anything less and a victory for Arsenal on Sunday, also against Wolves, would have meant Spurs dropping out of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Have a little Foyth! Argentine defender nets decisive goal as Spurs continue winning ways - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/spurs-beat-crystal-palace-4333440-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFKoLqRfZULtCxIk_cQxpsIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 20:45:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/spurs-beat-crystal-palace-4333440-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Have a little Foyth! Argentine defender nets decisive goal as Spurs continue winning ways&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUAN FOYTH REPAID Mauricio Pochettino’s faith by scoring the decisive goal as Tottenham left Crystal Palace with a 1-0 Premier League triumph on Saturday, their fourth in a row across all competitions. The young centre-back had received criticism for a difficult Premier League debut in last week’s 3-2 win over Wolves, but Pochettino refused to drop Foyth and he subsequently secured the spoils for Spurs in a poor match at sodden Selhurst Park. Chances were few and far between during an unremarkable first half that was more notable for the weather than the standard of football on display. The...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Chelsea are refusing to let themselves get carried away as unbeaten Premier League continues - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/chelsea-fc-news-pedro-league-maurizio-sarri-fixtures-results-crystal-palace-a8618411.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL_8uk5Btj6pd7LhltG2focqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 13:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/chelsea-fc-news-pedro-league-maurizio-sarri-fixtures-results-crystal-palace-a8618411.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chelsea are refusing to let themselves get carried away as unbeaten Premier League continues&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pedro says Chelsea are refusing to look too far ahead after their unbeaten start to the Premier League season. The Blues, fifth last term, claimed an eighth win from 11 games with Sunday’s 3-1 victory over Crystal Palace. The win, secured by Alvaro Morata’s double and a Pedro strike, took Maurizio Sarri’s side into second, above Liverpool on goal difference and trailing holders Manchester City by two points. “The most important thing is step by step, game by game,” Pedro told Chelsea TV. “The team knows we’re now in a very good position, but it’s too early to know anything. Chelsea vs Cryst...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Álvaro Morata double helps Chelsea sweep past Crystal Palace - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/nov/04/chelsea-crystal-palace-premier-league-match-report</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKYHNwTz4p5xgkNkWJ5PNDIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 17:56:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/nov/04/chelsea-crystal-palace-premier-league-match-report" target="_blank"&gt;Álvaro Morata double helps Chelsea sweep past Crystal Palace&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea are not dismissing opponents with quite the same mouth-watering panache as Manchester City, or even drawing as much focus in the title race as a resurgent Liverpool. They are not even watertight on home territory these days, always offering opponents a hint of reward. Yet, for all Maurizio Sarri’s public utterances to the contrary, they are a side refusing to believe this is merely a two-team title race. This was an impressive victory not least because Chelsea were challenged for periods, and even pegged back to parity, but they never panicked. It helped they could send on Eden Haza...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Morata double ensures Chelsea continue strong form with win over Palace - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/chelsea-palace-premier-league-report-4322657-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB84uppKvRXdh40kZXFMt_8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 18:06:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/chelsea-palace-premier-league-report-4322657-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Morata double ensures Chelsea continue strong form with win over Palace&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ALVARO MORATA CONTINUED his strong recent form with a brace as Chelsea beat Crystal Palace 3-1 at Stamford Bridge in the Premier League on Sunday. Morata gave Chelsea the lead by finishing well after good work from Pedro, but Palace levelled when a one-two with James McArthur caught David Luiz out of position and Andros Townsend beat Kepa Arrizabalaga with a fine drive. The improving Morata, though, scored his fourth goal in as many Premier League appearances, converting a free-kick from substitute Eden Hazard to set the Blues up a fourth consecutive win in all competitions. And when Pedro ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>'A lot of people who complain about our style of football will be sat at home on Sunday' - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/alan-bennett-interview-2018-fai-cup-final-4317671-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFyEleR8CjNhQHUKI78S0jIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 07:05:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/alan-bennett-interview-2018-fai-cup-final-4317671-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'A lot of people who complain about our style of football will be sat at home on Sunday'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT THE CLUB’S media event for the 2018 FAI Cup final at the Cork International Hotel on Monday afternoon, there was universal agreement among the Cork City players in attendance as they assessed a season that will conclude against Dundalk on Sunday. A fourth consecutive trip to the Aviva Stadium, as well as a second-placed finish in the league behind a team that set a record for points earned and goals scored, could hardly be described as disastrous. Nevertheless, the 2017 double winners were simultaneously keen to acknowledge that the standards they set for themselves haven’t been met. For...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Chelsea vs Crystal Palace: Roy Hodgson surprised by Palace's Premier League run without a win - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/roy-hodgson-press-conference-interview-chelsea-vs-crystal-palace-result-score-highlight-epl-premier-a8617331.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgZvzma_8ZUQHF6KSKUjCgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 19:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/roy-hodgson-press-conference-interview-chelsea-vs-crystal-palace-result-score-highlight-epl-premier-a8617331.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chelsea vs Crystal Palace: Roy Hodgson surprised by Palace's Premier League run without a win&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roy Hodgson admits he is surprised by Crystal Palace’s recent run of form following their 3-1 defeat to Chelsea f.c, their sixth consecutive Premier League match without a win. Palace’s latest defeat, their seventh of the season, could have been a different result had the visitors at Stamford Bridge kicked on after Andros Townsend levelled the score following Alavro Morata’s first half goal. Instead, Chelsea restored their lead through Morata’s second strike and Pedro completed the job the make it 3-1. Hodgson became Palace manager last season in the middle of their run of seven consecutive...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Arsenal pay the penalty as Luka Milivojevic strikes to end winning run - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/arsenal-pay-the-penalty-as-luka-milivojevic-strikes-to-end-winning-run-37467532.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGm-nhZOa-3NSxAQAfKQBs4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 15:40:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/premier-league/arsenal-pay-the-penalty-as-luka-milivojevic-strikes-to-end-winning-run-37467532.html" target="_blank"&gt;Arsenal pay the penalty as Luka Milivojevic strikes to end winning run&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luka Milivojevic achieved redemption by scoring a brace of penalties as Crystal Palace ended Arsenal's winning run with a deserved draw at Selhurst Park. Arsenal had looked on course to record a 12th consecutive win in all competitions after a superb Granit Xhaka free-kick and a controversial Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang strike had cancelled out Milivojevic's penalty on the stroke of half-time. But the Palace captain, who missed from 12 yards in the defeat at Everton last weekend, made no mistake in securing a 2-2 draw when referee Martin Atkinson awarded the hosts a second penalty of the afte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Soccer Republic - Top 10 most watched goals for 2018 - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/soccer/2018/1009/1002021-soccer-republic-top-10-most-watched-goals-for-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBxLiCC-b_7vabuaavYdCZ0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 15:30:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/soccer/2018/1009/1002021-soccer-republic-top-10-most-watched-goals-for-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Soccer Republic - Top 10 most watched goals for 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With over 700,000 views on the Soccer Republic Twitter page, Ian Morris’ wonder strike for Bohemians against Cork City was a certainly a goal to savour. But a few other crackers have also adorned the said Twitter page. So let’s countdown the top 10 most watched goals so far in 2018. 10 The 'Tubbercurry Tornado' Rafael Cretaro proves he still has it after this superb finish against Limerick. Rafael Cretaro proves he still has it as @sligorovers bag vital win #RTEsoccer pic.twitter.com/lH7zM8cm6Y — Soccer Republic (@SoccRepublic) August 19, 2018 9 Chris Shields with the only goal at Turner's ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Wolves show their teeth once more with fine win at Palace - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/wolves-show-their-teeth-once-more-with-fine-win-at-palace-37391219.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGyNgFq5LykNH9KUVayma4sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 15:00:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/wolves-show-their-teeth-once-more-with-fine-win-at-palace-37391219.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wolves show their teeth once more with fine win at Palace&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;History-making Wolves continued their fine start to the Premier League season with a deserved 1-0 victory at Crystal Palace. They became the first team in the competition’s existence to name an unchanged starting XI throughout their first eight fixtures, and their manager Nuno Espirito Santo was rewarded when Matt Doherty’s goal secured the three points that took them up to seventh place. Think @Nuno enjoyed that one? 🐺😆 pic.twitter.com/XdHTRtMtNk — Wolves (@Wolves) October 6, 2018 Wolves have already been spoken of as the best team to have been promoted from the Championship, and while s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Andros Townsend bags a brace for Crystal Palace to make it a happy return to West Brom for Roy Hodgson - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/09/25/andros-townsend-bags-brace-make-happy-return-roy-hodgson-hawthorns/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENRSmTAd2n2qXFn5qCjG_v4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 21:38:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/09/25/andros-townsend-bags-brace-make-happy-return-roy-hodgson-hawthorns/" target="_blank"&gt;Andros Townsend bags a brace for Crystal Palace to make it a happy return to West Brom for Roy Hodgson&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two goals by Andros Townsend helped Roy Hodgson to the most routine of victories on his return to The Hawthorns with a second-string Crystal Palace. Hodgson made eight changes yet his side eased comfortably into round four of the Carabao Cup at the expense of his former club with Patrick van Aanholt also on target. Albion made 10 changes from the side pushing for promotion in the Sky Bet Championship yet Darren Moore’s understudies were a clear second best to Hodgson’s, whose progress past round three rarely looked in doubt once Townsend had provided an early lead with the classiest of thre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Angry Newcastle fans turn on owner Mike Ashley in Crystal Palace draw - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/angry-newcastle-fans-turn-on-owner-mike-ashley-in-crystal-palace-draw-37343912.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJxGLGUDqY6qg8bogjCE4LIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 15:08:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/angry-newcastle-fans-turn-on-owner-mike-ashley-in-crystal-palace-draw-37343912.html" target="_blank"&gt;Angry Newcastle fans turn on owner Mike Ashley in Crystal Palace draw&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Newcastle’s bad-tempered protests turned ugly when a bottle thrown onto the Selhurst Park pitch struck Crystal Palace’s Aaron Wan-Bissaka in the two clubs’ goalless Premier League draw. The travelling supporters met owner Mike Ashley’s first appearance at a Newcastle game since May 2017 by launching sustained chanting against his stewardship of the Tyneside club. After repeated chants of “You fat cockney b******, get out of our club” and “We want Ashley out” though, one supporter among the Newcastle enclosure saw fit to throw a bottle at Palace right-back Bissaka. Crystal Palace’s Wilfried ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Caulfield sees red as dominant Dundalk move within touching distance of title - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/league-of-ireland/caulfield-sees-red-as-dominant-dundalk-move-within-touching-distance-of-title-37342856.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDkwHzhVOm-6HaRpKs6pNf0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/league-of-ireland/caulfield-sees-red-as-dominant-dundalk-move-within-touching-distance-of-title-37342856.html" target="_blank"&gt;Caulfield sees red as dominant Dundalk move within touching distance of title&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the night that a power cut affected a good portion of the city, the lights went out on Cork City's title defence. It will take a while for the darkness to lift. Like all four meetings between the fierce rivals this term, this game was decided by a one-goal margin. But that did not do justice to Dundalk's superiority. On the pitch, Cork City failed to land a blow on their guests in their second-half search for an equaliser. They were missing the sideline presence of John Caulfield who was sent to the stands after a half-time tunnel row involving players and staff. Cork City assistant John...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item></channel></rss>