<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNREkzZURZek1CSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:04:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Islamic State re-emerges as guerilla force in Syria and Iraq - The Irish Times</title><link>https://www.irishtimes.com/news/world/middle-east/islamic-state-re-emerges-as-guerilla-force-in-syria-and-iraq-1.3720983</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMHYx4ZsDGFp2XVHF5nEKtwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqfqFCzD7v4MDMIO9jQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishtimes.com/news/world/middle-east/islamic-state-re-emerges-as-guerilla-force-in-syria-and-iraq-1.3720983" target="_blank"&gt;Islamic State re-emerges as guerilla force in Syria and Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Irish Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Terror group still poses threat as it takes advantage of political instability to rebuild.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishtimes.com">The Irish Times</source></item><item><title>Inside ISIS’ weapons factory where terror fanatics built suicide belts and car bombs on an industrial scale - The Irish Sun</title><link>https://www.thesun.ie/news/3489270/inside-isis-weapons-factory-where-terror-fanatics-built-suicide-belts-and-car-bombs-on-an-industrial-scale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMijgFodHRwczovL3d3dy50aGVzdW4uaWUvbmV3cy8zNDg5MjcwL2luc2lkZS1pc2lzLXdlYXBvbnMtZmFjdG9yeS13aGVyZS10ZXJyb3ItZmFuYXRpY3MtYnVpbHQtc3VpY2lkZS1iZWx0cy1hbmQtY2FyLWJvbWJzLW9uLWFuLWluZHVzdHJpYWwtc2NhbGUv0gHYAWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LXRoZXN1bi1pZS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy50aGVzdW4uaWUvbmV3cy8zNDg5MjcwL2luc2lkZS1pc2lzLXdlYXBvbnMtZmFjdG9yeS13aGVyZS10ZXJyb3ItZmFuYXRpY3MtYnVpbHQtc3VpY2lkZS1iZWx0cy1hbmQtY2FyLWJvbWJzLW9uLWFuLWluZHVzdHJpYWwtc2NhbGUvYW1wLz9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:02:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thesun.ie/news/3489270/inside-isis-weapons-factory-where-terror-fanatics-built-suicide-belts-and-car-bombs-on-an-industrial-scale/" target="_blank"&gt;Inside ISIS’ weapons factory where terror fanatics built suicide belts and car bombs on an industrial scale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Irish Sun&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOLDIERS have captured an ISIS weapons factory where terrorist fanatics built car bombs, IEDs and other explosives on an industrial scale. A battle-hardened ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thesun.ie">The Irish Sun</source></item><item><title>Syrians slaughter ‘weak’ ISIS in bloody door-to-door raids as they blitz jihadis’ last hellhole stron - The Irish Sun</title><link>https://www.thesun.ie/news/3475223/syrians-slaughter-weak-isis-in-bloody-door-to-door-raids-as-they-blitz-jihadis-last-hellhole-strongholds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMijAFodHRwczovL3d3dy50aGVzdW4uaWUvbmV3cy8zNDc1MjIzL3N5cmlhbnMtc2xhdWdodGVyLXdlYWstaXNpcy1pbi1ibG9vZHktZG9vci10by1kb29yLXJhaWRzLWFzLXRoZXktYmxpdHotamloYWRpcy1sYXN0LWhlbGxob2xlLXN0cm9uZ2hvbGRzL9IB1gFodHRwczovL3d3dy10aGVzdW4taWUuY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy93d3cudGhlc3VuLmllL25ld3MvMzQ3NTIyMy9zeXJpYW5zLXNsYXVnaHRlci13ZWFrLWlzaXMtaW4tYmxvb2R5LWRvb3ItdG8tZG9vci1yYWlkcy1hcy10aGV5LWJsaXR6LWppaGFkaXMtbGFzdC1oZWxsaG9sZS1zdHJvbmdob2xkcy9hbXAvP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:01:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thesun.ie/news/3475223/syrians-slaughter-weak-isis-in-bloody-door-to-door-raids-as-they-blitz-jihadis-last-hellhole-strongholds/" target="_blank"&gt;Syrians slaughter ‘weak’ ISIS in bloody door-to-door raids as they blitz jihadis’ last hellhole stron&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Irish Sun&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SYRIAN have slaughter a “weak” ISIS in bloody door-to-door raids as they blitz the jihadis' last hellhole strongholds. Tribesmen, who once suffered atrocities at ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thesun.ie">The Irish Sun</source></item><item><title>The strange tale of the US soldier who wanted to teach mixed martial arts to Isis - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-soldier-isis-syria-iraq-mixed-martial-arts-mma-fbi-agent-sting-ikaika-erik-kang-a8672791.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDkog-SGm0O9qSwMIWr6kkcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-soldier-isis-syria-iraq-mixed-martial-arts-mma-fbi-agent-sting-ikaika-erik-kang-a8672791.html" target="_blank"&gt;The strange tale of the US soldier who wanted to teach mixed martial arts to Isis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ikaika Erik Kang stood in front of a Go-Pro camera alongside his Isis assistant, donned a mask, and pressed record. Then, he started grappling. The US citizen and mixed martial artist hoped his combat training video would be useful to Isis members fighting in the battlefields of Iraq and Syria. What he didn’t know that the man he was rolling around on the ground with was an FBI agent. Kang, a 35-year-old native of Hawaii, was sentenced to 25 years in jail this week for attempting to provide material support to Isis. He was caught following a year-long undercover operation. But what concerne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Attacks Continue as Iraq Marks One Year Since Islamic State Victory - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/attacks-continue-as-iraq-marks-one-year-since-islamic-state-victory/4690659.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIjO2frYP4_z5DsUp6oqgUoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:12:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/attacks-continue-as-iraq-marks-one-year-since-islamic-state-victory/4690659.html" target="_blank"&gt;Attacks Continue as Iraq Marks One Year Since Islamic State Victory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the desert outside Mosul there is a giant sinkhole, once thought a natural wonder, with stories about it going back for generations. There are believed to be as many as 10,000 or more bodies decomposing inside, unceremoniously dumped by Islamic State militants, after or during the killings. And as Iraq marks the first anniversary of its victory over IS, this area is still strewn with so many bombs that authorities do not expect to recover those remains soon, if at all. The sinkhole known as Khafsa is believed to contain the bodies of as many as 10,000 people, killed by Islamic State mili...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Attacks Continue as Iraq Marks One Year Since Islamic State Defeat - VOA News</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eYQv0dYQJcA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECh8jQGvIPw_2T9hscy83ckqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw78Uq</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:04:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eYQv0dYQJcA" target="_blank"&gt;Attacks Continue as Iraq Marks One Year Since Islamic State Defeat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Iraq marks the first anniversary of its victory over Islamic State, tensions are rising in the terrorist group's former strongholds as attacks continue and security forces conduct near-daily operations. Locals fear the militants hiding in the deserts and mountains are emboldened by recent killings, and warn the group's resurgence is likely if sectarian tensions and economic disparity are not addressed. VOA's Heather Murdock has this report from Mosul and the surrounding countryside in Iraq. Originally published at - https://www.voanews.com/a/attacks-continue-as-iraq-marks-one-year-since-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>IS Signals Re-Emergence in Parts of Iraq - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/is-signals-re-emergence-in-parts-of-iraq/4688907.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBXlkU7Kf1kNpsiw4Qmbu44qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:38:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/is-signals-re-emergence-in-parts-of-iraq/4688907.html" target="_blank"&gt;IS Signals Re-Emergence in Parts of Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this month marks the first anniversary of the Iraqi-proclaimed victory over the Islamic State (IS) terror group, U.S.-backed Iraqi forces are still trying to hunt down remaining IS militants as the extremist group returns to its insurgent roots. In a televised address on December 9, 2017, former Iraqi prime minister Haider al-Abadi announced the defeat of IS and the end of Iraqi campaign to recapture its territory. While many considered IS obliterated following the declaration, recent reports show the militant group is still active in parts of the country and increasingly has been ass...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>US needs 35-40k local fighters in Syria, only 20% there now – General Dunford - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445797-dunford-syria-fighters-training/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDYtJcZ4aSOkrXEAYxprkEMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:12:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445797-dunford-syria-fighters-training/" target="_blank"&gt;US needs 35-40k local fighters in Syria, only 20% there now – General Dunford&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;To "provide stability" in Syria, the US needs to train and equip around 40,000 local fighters, but is only 20 percent of the way to that number right now, Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff General Joseph Dunford said. “The presence we have in Syria right now is sustainable and can be adjusted based on conditions,” Dunford added, during the “Transformers:Defense” event hosted by the Washington Post on Thursday. 35,000-40,000 local forces need to be trained/equipped to provide stability in #Syria, per Gen Dunford, but only 20% through the training process — Jeff Seldin (@jseldin) December...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Nadia Murad: ‘I survived the Isis genocide, now I want to rebuild the Yazidi homeland’ - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/f28c4184-f823-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKSk_ohPuVTf4QcY8dUXm9YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f28c4184-f823-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Nadia Murad: ‘I survived the Isis genocide, now I want to rebuild the Yazidi homeland’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Change can happen when one least expects it. I know this to be true because my life changed in an instant. One moment I was a farm girl, going to school in my village in northern Iraq and the next I was an Isis sex slave, “owned” by militants. My peaceful existence was shattered simply because my religious beliefs were deemed sub-human by a group of men who believed they were superior. Isis murdered my family and took me captive, exposing me to horrors which would be impossible to imagine had I not endured every moment and felt each brutal blow. My story is not unique. I am only one Yazidi ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Terrorism deaths down in 2017, but far-right terrorism rising, report says - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/global-terrorism-index-2018/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRtJiKLbZ9aUGlvDCIEkKAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:23:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/global-terrorism-index-2018/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Terrorism deaths down in 2017, but far-right terrorism rising, report says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deaths from terrorism declined in 2017 for the third straight year, but far-right extremism was on the rise, according to a new report released Wednesday. The 2018 Global Terrorism Index found that deaths resulting from terrorism decreased 27% worldwide last year. Ninety-six of the 163 countries tracked by the index saw an improvement; 46 had declines. Sixty-seven countries had at least one death from terrorism in 2017 -- a drop from 2016's record high rate of 79 countries, according to the report. The report was produced by the Institute for Economics &amp; Peace, a nonpartisan think tank that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US-backed fighters enter major IS-held town in east Syria - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/408eb33089264fe09d01f164dd35b78e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJLpOVEulvizR29boukrdAMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:01:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/408eb33089264fe09d01f164dd35b78e" target="_blank"&gt;US-backed fighters enter major IS-held town in east Syria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — An opposition activist and a war monitor say U.S.-backed Syrian fighters have broken through the defenses of the last area controlled by the Islamic State group in the country. Members of the Kurdish-led Syrian Democratic Forces have been trying to take the town of Hajin and nearby villages in the eastern province of Deir el-Zour since Sept. 10 with little luck. The Britain-based Syrian Observatory for Human Rights said Thursday that SDF fighters entered Hajin and now control parts of it. Omar Abou Leila, who monitors the war in Deir el-Zour from Europe, said SDF fighters brok...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The Deadliest Terrorist Groups In The World Today - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/12/05/deadliest-terrorist-groups-in-the-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGNVVi5rCoqA76Eg7gztXykqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/12/05/deadliest-terrorist-groups-in-the-world/" target="_blank"&gt;The Deadliest Terrorist Groups In The World Today&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the 18,814 deaths caused by terrorists around the world last year, well over half were due to the actions of just four groups: Islamic State, the Taliban, Al-Shabaab and Boko Haram. According to Global Terrorism Index 2018, compiled by the Institute for Economics &amp; Peace (IEP), these four organisations were responsible for 10,632 deaths in 2017. Their actions contribute to the instability of what are some of the most dangerous countries in the world, including Afghanistan, Iraq, Nigeria, Somalia and Syria. Over the past decade they have accounted for 44% of all terrorist deaths. Islamic ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>US 'Model Soldier' Gets 25 Years in Prison for IS Support - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-model-soldier-to-be-sentenced-for-islamic-state-support/4686104.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOL5_hkQZZm7mM3VVTZDFr0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:26:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-model-soldier-to-be-sentenced-for-islamic-state-support/4686104.html" target="_blank"&gt;US 'Model Soldier' Gets 25 Years in Prison for IS Support&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A U.S. Army sergeant described by former colleagues as a onetime "model soldier" was sentenced to 25 years in prison at a federal court in Hawaii on Tuesday after pleading guilty of providing material support to the Islamic State militant group. Ikaika Erik Kang, 35, agreed to a plea deal in August on four counts of breaking anti-terrorism laws in which he accepted a proposed 25-year sentence. U.S. District Judge Susan Oki Mollway accepted the terms of the plea deal at Tuesday morning's hearing, court records showed. Kang had begun expressing support for Islamic State, which the United Stat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Number of far-right terror attacks increases as overall deaths from terrorism fall, report finds - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/politics/global-terrorism-index-farright-attacks-increase-overall-deaths-fall-institute-for-economics-peace-a8667031.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEzIL5gTjfyzJF-Gm4d_kHgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/politics/global-terrorism-index-farright-attacks-increase-overall-deaths-fall-institute-for-economics-peace-a8667031.html" target="_blank"&gt;Number of far-right terror attacks increases as overall deaths from terrorism fall, report finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Far-right political terrorism is on the rise in western Europe and north America, a report on global terror has cautioned. Right-wing groups and individuals killed 66 people between 2013 and 2017, with 17 deaths and 47 of those attacks occurring last year, according to the 2018 Global Terrorism Index. “There has been a real and significant increase in far-right terrorist activity, particularly in the last two years,” Tom Morgan, a senior research fellow at the Institute for Economics and Peace, which produced the report, told The Independent. The UK suffered 12 far-right terror attacks last...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>IS Clings to Last Stronghold in Eastern Syria - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/is-clings-to-last-stronghold-in-eastern-syria-/4687300.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPHo5R6UKoDcjPsIpq9lZBMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:55:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/is-clings-to-last-stronghold-in-eastern-syria-/4687300.html" target="_blank"&gt;IS Clings to Last Stronghold in Eastern Syria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite losing most of the territory they once held, Islamic State (IS) fighters are now holding their ground against U.S.-backed forces in their last stronghold in eastern Syria. Fierce clashes have been taking place around Hajin, in the Syrian province of Deir el-Zour, for three weeks, with Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF) trying to close in on the remaining IS militants in the town. But local sources say IS fighters have been putting up a tough fight in Hajin, taking advantage of foul weather. "In the last 24 hours, the SDF has brought additional reinforcements to add more pressure on [IS]...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Soldier who tried to help terrorists gets 25-year sentence - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/6eaa929e6f2742d7b14a0ff54e6af2d5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGm7EIDSI0sd2cks_r1cfXsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:32:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/6eaa929e6f2742d7b14a0ff54e6af2d5" target="_blank"&gt;Soldier who tried to help terrorists gets 25-year sentence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — A soldier based in Hawaii was sentenced Tuesday to 25 years in prison for trying to help the Islamic State group. Sgt. 1st Class Ikaika Kang, 35, pleaded guilty in August to four counts of attempting to provide material support to a foreign terrorist organization. He provided classified military documents, a drone and other help, he said. "Your honor, I know what I did was wrong," Kang said before Senior U.S. District Judge Susan Oki Mollway imposed a sentence that includes 20 years of supervised release. "When I'm released I won't do it again." The sentence is part of a ple...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>In Early 2019, UN Team to Begin Probe of IS Crimes in Iraq - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/in-early-2019-un-team-to-begin-probe-of-is-crimes-in-iraq/4687322.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA1OvVb-azGZIGPHfCN0HcAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:28:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/in-early-2019-un-team-to-begin-probe-of-is-crimes-in-iraq/4687322.html" target="_blank"&gt;In Early 2019, UN Team to Begin Probe of IS Crimes in Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A U.N. team authorized over a year ago to investigate the massacre of the Yazidi minority and other atrocities by jihadists in Iraq will finally begin work early next year, the head of the investigation said Tuesday. The U.N. Security Council adopted a resolution in September 2017 to bring those responsible for Islamic State group war crimes to justice — a cause championed by Nobel Peace Prize winner Nadia Murad and international human rights lawyer Amal Clooney. The team, led by British lawyer Karim Asad Ahmad Khan, was deployed to Baghdad in October, but has since focused on administrativ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Islamic State executing people in Syria's Deir al-Zor: U.N. - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-un/islamic-state-executing-people-in-syrias-deir-al-zor-un-idUSKBN1O418H</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOg4QILpgYdKF0qO9X19_sgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:59:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-un/islamic-state-executing-people-in-syrias-deir-al-zor-un-idUSKBN1O418H" target="_blank"&gt;Islamic State executing people in Syria's Deir al-Zor: U.N.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations has reports of Islamic State (ISIL) executing people perceived as cooperating with rebel fighters in Deir al-Zor governorate in eastern Syria, the U.N. human rights boss said on Wednesday. Michelle Bachelet, speaking to a news conference in Geneva, voiced deep concern for 7,000 civilians who she said were trapped between Islamic State fighters preventing them from leaving Deir al-Zor and air strikes by a U.S.-led coalition. "We also have reports of ISIL executing people perceived as cooperating with SDF (Syrian Democratic Forces) or other parties to the conflict," she sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Isis returns to insurgent roots after battlefield defeats - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c46be2aa-f3cd-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEETIcW9I-nmEa5XVrh_MWrYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:00:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c46be2aa-f3cd-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Isis returns to insurgent roots after battlefield defeats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Isis is carrying out a rising number of kidnappings, killings and bombings in Iraq and fighting fiercely in Syria as the extremist group returns to its insurgent roots having been driven out of almost all the territory it once controlled. A recent US Department of Defense report said an “effective clandestine Isis organisation appears to be taking hold” four years after the group controlled swaths of Syria, as much as a third of Iraq, and declared a caliphate. A suspected Isis roadside bomb in Mosul killed at least three schoolchildren late last month and a car bomb killed at least five peo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Terrorism In Decline: Number Of Deaths By Terrorist Groups Falls For Third Year In A Row - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/12/05/terrorism-in-decline/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOSoKxRaXJ-_mX7vKrqls8gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/12/05/terrorism-in-decline/" target="_blank"&gt;Terrorism In Decline: Number Of Deaths By Terrorist Groups Falls For Third Year In A Row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is the world starting to get to grips with the scourge of terrorism? There are at least some hopeful signs. Last year, the number of deaths caused by terrorist groups was 18,814, 27% less than the year before and the third consecutive year of improvement. At the same time, the number of attacks fell by 23%. These numbers come from the Global Terrorism Index 2018, compiled by the Institute for Economics &amp; Peace (IEP) and published today. According to the index, most countries saw their situation improve last year, with 94 countries showing a decline in the impact of terrorism, compared to 46...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>US can’t stop Iran oil exports, Persian Gulf will shut if they try – Rouhani - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445541-rouhani-us-oil-exports-iran/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOL60MAw0XBSPl0xlBrjncEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445541-rouhani-us-oil-exports-iran/" target="_blank"&gt;US can’t stop Iran oil exports, Persian Gulf will shut if they try – Rouhani&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US is incapable of preventing Iran from exporting its oil and any attempt to stop oil tankers from passing through the Persian Gulf will result in the vital waterway being shut down, Iran’s President Hassan Rouhani has said. In a televised address on Tuesday, Rouhani dismissed Washington’s stated desire to reduce his Tehran’s oil exports to zero, and said that Iran would take retaliatory action against any efforts to do so. via GIPHY “America should know that we are selling our oil and will continue to sell our oil and they are not able to stop our oil exports,” he said. He went on to w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Families of Local IS Members Face Rejection in Iraq - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/families-of-local-is-members-face-rejection-in-iraq-/4685630.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBvlwRGGrH4pAryGb6mEi7EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:45:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/families-of-local-is-members-face-rejection-in-iraq-/4685630.html" target="_blank"&gt;Families of Local IS Members Face Rejection in Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than one year after its liberation from Islamic State terror, the Iraqi city of Mosul still suffers from scars left behind. Families and children of the terror group have returned to their homes in Mosul, facing rejection and shame by the local community. One widow of a former IS fighter in Mosul, who requested anonymity, told VOA she and her two children have been going through a distressing situation for being linked to an IS member. "My husband was an IS member, but what does this have to do with me? If my husband joined the al-Qaida group, what does this have to do with my children...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>US coalition targets IS figure involved in killing American - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/16ecc1a8925a441bb20a29d4987221f3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXShGfyeKBm9XT5rQTT6aIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:08:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/16ecc1a8925a441bb20a29d4987221f3" target="_blank"&gt;US coalition targets IS figure involved in killing American&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — The U.S.-led coalition has targeted a senior member of the Islamic State group involved in the 2014 killing of American aid worker Peter Kassig, a military spokesman said Monday. Col. Sean Ryan, a spokesman for the U.S.-led coalition fighting IS, told The Associated Press that coalition forces conducted precision strikes against Abu al-Umarayn and several other IS members. He said the strikes, which took place on Sunday, occurred in a desert area in southeastern Syria. The area is close to where Syria's state news agency said the U.S.-led coalition fired several missiles at Sy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Isis' shrinking territory forces its leaders into the open, and into the crosshairs - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/isis-leaders-syria-iraq-assassination-caliphate-islamic-state-a8665286.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEASRNXiTIF6q19MQRLKnzDsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 17:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/isis-leaders-syria-iraq-assassination-caliphate-islamic-state-a8665286.html" target="_blank"&gt;Isis' shrinking territory forces its leaders into the open, and into the crosshairs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Isis leaders who for years have found sanctuary in the vast “caliphate” that once stretched across Iraq and Syria are being captured and killed in increasing numbers, as the impending loss of the last of the group’s territory has left them with nowhere to run. At the height of its power, Isis controlled an area roughly the same size as Britain and ruled over some 10 million people, but today it is cornered into a string of towns and villages in eastern Syria along the Euphrates River in Deir Ez-Zor. The area around the town of Hajin, near the border with Iraq, has been a refuge for senior m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>US says airstrike has killed Isil jihadist involved in executions of Western hostages - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/03/us-says-airstrike-has-killed-isil-jihadist-involved-executions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELYsZT4zTidfbg8fMIauFIoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:22:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/03/us-says-airstrike-has-killed-isil-jihadist-involved-executions/" target="_blank"&gt;US says airstrike has killed Isil jihadist involved in executions of Western hostages&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US-led coalition against the Islamic State group said on Monday that it had killed a senior jihadist involved in the executions of an American aid worker and other Western hostages. Abu al-Umarayn was accused of involvement in the November 2014 beheading of Peter Kassig, a former US ranger who was doing volunteer humanitarian work when captured in 2013. "He was killed and more information will be available after a full assessment," Sean Ryan, spokesman for the US-led coalition, said in a statement issued after the Sunday strikes. "Al Umarayn had given indications of posing an imminent t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Conscience of the revolution' Fares spoke for ordinary Syrians - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/world-news/middle-east/conscience-of-the-revolution-fares-spoke-for-ordinary-syrians-37583442.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIsSKQ1DYL-0CF5vtaQkwC8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wmtSiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/world-news/middle-east/conscience-of-the-revolution-fares-spoke-for-ordinary-syrians-37583442.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Conscience of the revolution' Fares spoke for ordinary Syrians&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last Friday in the northern Syria town of Kafranbel began like any other. It ended with the news that Raed Fares, a local opposition activist who had brought Kafranbel to international attention through wit, ingenuity and an unswerving belief in his cause, had been shot dead. Raed Fares was the kind of Syrian Bashar al-Assad did not want the world to know as he sought to cast the uprising against his regime as a jihadist conspiracy. Fares was not a jihadist. In fact, Hayat Tahrir al-Sham (HTS), a group formerly affiliated with al-Qa'ida, is suspected of murdering him. What Fares represented...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>US-led coalition announces senior ISIS leader killed in Syria strike - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/politics/us-isis-leader-killed-syria/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFYX63HIsp-DmcubSy6c5a0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 22:17:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/politics/us-isis-leader-killed-syria/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;US-led coalition announces senior ISIS leader killed in Syria strike&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US-led coalition fighting ISIS in Syria and Iraq announced Sunday that a strike killed an ISIS leader in Syria who was tied to the death of a US citizen. Army Col. Sean Ryan, a spokesman for the coalition, said the strikes on Sunday were against "a senior ISIS member, Abu al Umarayn, and several other ISIS members." "Al Umarayn had given indications of posing an imminent threat to coalition forces, and he was involved in the killing of American citizen and former US Army Ranger Peter Kassig," Ryan said. "He has been linked to and directly involved with executing several other prisoners ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Welcome to Jinwar, a women-only village in Syria that wants to smash the patriarchy - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/jinwar-syria-north-patriarchy-kurdish-women-raqqa-a8661866.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI0ZefX7YVuKuKdbcYH9G08qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/jinwar-syria-north-patriarchy-kurdish-women-raqqa-a8661866.html" target="_blank"&gt;Welcome to Jinwar, a women-only village in Syria that wants to smash the patriarchy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of a long dusty road in the plains of northern Syria, a young woman with a rifle over her shoulder guards the entrance to the isolated village of Jinwar. Thirty brick houses lie beyond the gate, decorated with splashes of purple and blue. They surround a large plot of agricultural land where rows of vegetables are growing. A war zone perhaps isn’t the most obvious setting for a feminist utopia. But here, in a far corner of a country that has been devastated by ongoing conflict, a group of women have created an escape from the chaos around them. Built over the past two years, this...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Senior IS Leader Killed in Strike in Syria - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/senior-islamic-state-leader-killed-strike-syria/4685590.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMHFc8MH2eoIt-Wpcln8GukqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 23:50:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/senior-islamic-state-leader-killed-strike-syria/4685590.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senior IS Leader Killed in Strike in Syria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S.-led coalition fighting Islamic State has targeted and killed a senior leader of the group in Syria who was linked to the murder of an American citizen. Pentagon spokesman U.S. Navy Cmdr. Sean Robertson told VOA on Monday that coalition forces killed Abu al-Umarayn and several other Islamic State members during a precision strike Sunday in the Badiyah Desert. "Al-Umarayn had given indications of posing an imminent threat to Coalition Forces, and he was involved in the killing of American citizen and former U.S. Army Ranger, Peter Kassig," Robertson said in an emailed statement. The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Cars, guns and TV interviews: The militiaman on the UAE payroll - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/cars-guns-tv-interviews-militiaman-uae-payroll-181124115831124.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGFxzm7fTuuYGiMKiejeS6oqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 09:52:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/cars-guns-tv-interviews-militiaman-uae-payroll-181124115831124.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cars, guns and TV interviews: The militiaman on the UAE payroll&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;He's designated a terrorist by the US, shares the same ideology as al-Qaeda, yet for more than three years, Abu al-Abbas, a Yemeni commander who controls most of the flashpoint city of Taiz, has been receiving financial and military support from the United Arab Emirates, sources told Al Jazeera. After purging the Houthis from Taiz's eastern districts and killing dozens of Houthi fighters, al-Abbas' forces now patrol the city's streets with high-tech US weaponry, arresting dissidents, reportedly carrying out extrajudicial killings, and instilling fear in the local population. Sources in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>US coalition 'targets ISIL chief linked to Peter Kassig killing' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/coalition-targets-isil-chief-linked-peter-kassig-killing-181203082400538.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPC64y4hX48Vf-RHpAClgRoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 09:17:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/coalition-targets-isil-chief-linked-peter-kassig-killing-181203082400538.html" target="_blank"&gt;US coalition 'targets ISIL chief linked to Peter Kassig killing'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US-led coalition fighting ISIL (ISIS) says it carried out air raids in Syria targeting a senior leader involved in the execution of American aid worker Peter Kassig and other prisoners. Sean Ryan, spokesperson for the US-led coalition, said on Sunday that coalition forces carried out "precision strikes against a senior ISIS member, Abu al Umarayn, and several other ISIS members in the Badiyah Desert, Syria". Al Umayran has "given indications of posing an imminent threat to coalition forces and he was involved in the killing of American citizen and former US Army Ranger, Peter Kassig", R...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Canada court rules Vice journalist must hand over ISIL notes - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/canada-court-rules-vice-journalist-hand-isil-notes-181201062225748.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELfJHR8_dA6li6Cls47sWsQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 09:12:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/canada-court-rules-vice-journalist-hand-isil-notes-181201062225748.html" target="_blank"&gt;Canada court rules Vice journalist must hand over ISIL notes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court of Canada has ordered a Vice News reporter to give police his communications with Farah Shirdon, a late ISILfighter who was charged with terrorism-related offences. In a unanimous decision released on Friday, the court acknowledged the potential "chilling" effects of such a decision on both journalists and sources, but said in this particular case the "state's interest in the investigation and prosecution of crime outweighed the media's right to privacy in gathering and disseminating the news". Justice Michael Moldaver wrote that the production order for Ben Makuch's recor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>‘Precision strike?' US coalition targets ISIS butcher, as Syria says the missiles hit army positions - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445411-coalition-strikes-isis-syria/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBciyNuDvGZ2QeRM2c9i_ZYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 02:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445411-coalition-strikes-isis-syria/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Precision strike?' US coalition targets ISIS butcher, as Syria says the missiles hit army positions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US-led coalition says it targeted a top Islamic State terrorist commander, who was involved in the beheading of a US officer and posed an “imminent threat.” Local media, however, claim the airstrike hit Syrian army positions. “Coalition forces conducted precision strikes against a senior ISIS (Islamic State, IS) member, Abu al Umarayn, and several other ISIS members on Dec. 2 in the Badiyah Desert,” after determining an “imminent threat” from the cell, a spokesperson for the US-led Operation Inherent Resolve told RT in a written statement, without elaborating on the success of the missi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>US-led coalition denies attack on Syrian govt forces in Homs - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/12/03/us-led-coalition-denies-attack-on-syrian-govt-forces-in-homs_0749b76c-fc4c-43a6-9965-f9ddf05c5882.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFr1uHk8JOT7PoN1coOccYQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:26:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/12/03/us-led-coalition-denies-attack-on-syrian-govt-forces-in-homs_0749b76c-fc4c-43a6-9965-f9ddf05c5882.html" target="_blank"&gt;US-led coalition denies attack on Syrian govt forces in Homs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIRUT - The US-led anti-ISIS coalition on Monday denied that it hit Syrian government military positions in the region of Homs, as the Syrian government had claimed through state news agency SANA. Pan-Arab media on Monday morning reported US-led coalition spokesman Sean Ryan said a senior member of ISIS, Abu al-Umarayn, was killed in a missile attack in the district of Sukhna. The US maintained that the local jihadist leader was responsible for numerous killings, including the 2014 beheading of American aid worker Peter Kassig, who was kidnapped by ISIS in Syria in the months prior to his ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Syria: Hundreds of bodies exhumed from mass grave in Raqqa - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/syria-hundreds-bodies-exhumed-mass-grave-raqqa-181127151642097.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEABP89SQgcKcAspoLDVGqyEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:10:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/syria-hundreds-bodies-exhumed-mass-grave-raqqa-181127151642097.html" target="_blank"&gt;Syria: Hundreds of bodies exhumed from mass grave in Raqqa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A month and a half since digging in one of Raqqa's largest discovered mass graves began, grave diggers continue to exhume bodies, with one official saying that more than 500 bodies have been so far recovered. The operation in the city in northern Syria, once the de facto capital of the Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant (ISIL, also known as ISIS) armed group, is being undertaken by local groups and first responders amid concerns regarding the preservation of bodies and evidence for possible war crimes trials. Raqqa was taken from ISIL in October 2017 after a fierce US-backed campaign, but...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>U.S.-led aircraft hit Islamic State hostage killer in Syria-coalition - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-islamic-state/us-led-aircraft-hit-is-hostage-killer-in-syria-coalition-envoy-idUSKBN1O20LS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELnmDHsSrgQcqIMEiUUn9WMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 11:32:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-islamic-state/us-led-aircraft-hit-is-hostage-killer-in-syria-coalition-envoy-idUSKBN1O20LS" target="_blank"&gt;U.S.-led aircraft hit Islamic State hostage killer in Syria-coalition&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S.-led war planes killed an Islamic State leader on Sunday in Syria responsible for executing hostages including an American, Washington's envoy to the coalition fighting the jihadist group said. "Earlier today, coalition air forces conducted precision strikes against a number of ISIS leaders in southeast Syria. Those targeted included Abu al-Umarayn," Brett McGurk said in a Tweet late on Sunday. Abu al-Umarayn was responsible for killing several prisoners including the U.S. aid worker Peter Kassig, who was captured by the group in Syria and beheaded in 2014, McGurk said. The strike in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Aid workers fear jail for entering conflict zones under new terror laws proposed by government - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/terror-laws-isis-counter-border-security-bill-aid-workers-jail-designated-areas-human-rights-syria-a8661836.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBdhlMsPenkGx-8oufPfYs8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/terror-laws-isis-counter-border-security-bill-aid-workers-jail-designated-areas-human-rights-syria-a8661836.html" target="_blank"&gt;Aid workers fear jail for entering conflict zones under new terror laws proposed by government&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aid workers fear being jailed for entering conflict zones under proposed new terror laws meant to target Isis fighters. The Counter-Terrorism and Border Security Bill would mean anyone entering a “designated area” abroad, could be jailed for up to 10 years, unless they can prove a “reasonable excuse” to be there. Ministers say the proposal was designed to criminalise returning Isis fighters who cannot be prosecuted for other crimes because of a lack of proof. Read more - Proposed terror laws could 'violate human rights', MPs tell government - New terror laws could violate 'fundamental legal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>U.S. strike kills 11 suspected Qaeda militants in Libya: Africom - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security/us-strike-kills-11-suspected-qaeda-militants-in-libya-africom-idUSKCN1NZ238</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0_SNnW35FRRlvakrOeoCgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:23:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-libya-security/us-strike-kills-11-suspected-qaeda-militants-in-libya-africom-idUSKCN1NZ238" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. strike kills 11 suspected Qaeda militants in Libya: Africom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. military said on Friday it killed 11 suspected al Qaeda militants in an air strike in Libya's southwestern desert. U.S. Africa Command (Africom) said Thursday's attack was its third since March on the militant group's North African branch - al Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb (AQIM). The strike near the town of Al Uwaynat, close to the Algerian border, destroyed three vehicles and "at this time, we assess no civilians were injured or killed," Africom added. Jihadists linked to al Qaeda and Islamic State have found a haven in Libya's vast southern desert as the country struggles to rest...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Afghan Hazaras slaughtered and Australian families want action - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/afghan-hazaras-slaughtered-australian-families-action-181130021409272.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPCjo2jWPrIM97YMhOIknYMqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:23:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/afghan-hazaras-slaughtered-australian-families-action-181130021409272.html" target="_blank"&gt;Afghan Hazaras slaughtered and Australian families want action&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melbourne, Australia - Australian members of the ethnic Hazara diaspora are desperately calling upon their government to do more to protect civilians in Afghanistan in the wake of heightened violence in the districts of Malistan and Jaghori. As Australian parliament resumed in Canberra on Monday for its final sitting of 2018, dozens of Hazara Australians sat outside demanding action to prevent the "Talibanisation" of Afghanistan, including their rural highland homelands known as Hazarajat. "The effects of the recent violence on the Hazara families in Australia have been profound," Niamatull...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Influential Syrian activist Raed Fares gunned down in Idlib - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/23/influential-syrian-activist-raed-fares-gunned-down-in-idlib</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOyom3AVXEjcQOmSoqclJAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 14:54:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/23/influential-syrian-activist-raed-fares-gunned-down-in-idlib" target="_blank"&gt;Influential Syrian activist Raed Fares gunned down in Idlib&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Syria’s most prominent activists, known for eye-catching protest banners and influential “Radio Fresh” broadcasts, has been assassinated in the rebel-held northern enclave in Idlib province. Raed Fares took on the regime of Bashar al-Assad and the proliferation of Islamist extremists that grew out of Syria’s civil war with equal energy and commitment. Fellow activist Hamoud Jneed was murdered with him on Friday morning by gunmen who have not been identified. Their killers waited in a van outside an office the two men shared, followed them through the market, attacked their car then s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Germany considers taking Isil suspects - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/world-news/europe/germany-considers-taking-isil-suspects-37576554.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA41GzOTIUxSIj094TIgS6EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wmtSiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/world-news/europe/germany-considers-taking-isil-suspects-37576554.html" target="_blank"&gt;Germany considers taking Isil suspects&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Germany is considering bringing home suspected Isil fighters and their families currently being held by Kurdish forces in Syria, it has emerged. The development will add to international pressure on the UK to repatriate Britons suspected of joining Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant (Isil), who are held under similar circumstances - including two members of the notorious "Beatles" execution cell. "The federal government is examining all options for a possible return of German nationals," the foreign ministry in Berlin said yesterday in a written response to a parliamentary question. At le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>ISIS Official Known for Caging Foes Is Captured by Iraq - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/30/world/middleeast/iraq-isis-prisoner.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ6JfOVH0Jb5PQfOL-0pMvkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 01:03:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/30/world/middleeast/iraq-isis-prisoner.html" target="_blank"&gt;ISIS Official Known for Caging Foes Is Captured by Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BAGHDAD — The Iraqi authorities released a video on Friday with the confession of a recently captured Islamic State operative who was involved in a notorious incident in which captured Kurdish soldiers were put in cages and paraded around a northern Iraqi city by hooded Islamic State fighters. At the time, early 2015, the Islamic State was threatening to burn them to death much as they had done two months earlier to a Jordanian pilot who had been captured, caged and then set on fire in Syria. It is not clear how the Kurdish captives were killed. The captured operative, Jamal al-Mashadani, w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Afghanistan: Women, children among 23 killed in US attack: UN - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/afghanistan-women-children-23-killed-strike-181130095042921.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELErESdtx7OvYLzSeW_ZztwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:16:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/afghanistan-women-children-23-killed-strike-181130095042921.html" target="_blank"&gt;Afghanistan: Women, children among 23 killed in US attack: UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 23 civilians, including women and children, were killed by an air raid carried out by the United States in southern Afghanistan earlier this week, according to a UN investigation. "Initial findings indicate that the vast majority of the victims were women and children," the UN mission in Afghanistan said in a report received by AFP late on Thursday, adding that at least three people were also injured in the attack. The attack occurred during a firefight between Afghan special forces working with US advisers and Taliban fighters late on Tuesday in restive Helmand province. NATO said...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Nigerian Islamists kill scores of soldiers in military base attack - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/23/nigerian-islamists-kill-scores-of-soldiers-in-military-base-attack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMcI-4s6ejUdaBs9tHZFSNMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:52:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/23/nigerian-islamists-kill-scores-of-soldiers-in-military-base-attack" target="_blank"&gt;Nigerian Islamists kill scores of soldiers in military base attack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamic militants in Nigeria may have killed as many as 100 soldiers in an attack on a military base, according to media reports and security officials. The reported death toll is among the highest since President Muhammadu Buhari came to power in 2015 and comes as the country prepares for elections in three months. The worst losses came when militants overran a military base in the village of Metele in the north-eastern state of Borno on Sunday. The area is the centre of an insurgency waged by Boko Haram, which was founded nine years ago to bring strict Islamic law to swaths of Nigeria, an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Raqqa after Isis: The US destroyed the city to liberate it, but who will rebuild? - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/raqqa-after-isis-syria-isis-us-airstrikes-coalition-bombing-rebuild-islamic-state-terror-a8644921.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELaevFPaWt1PKw6YMdeWHm0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/raqqa-after-isis-syria-isis-us-airstrikes-coalition-bombing-rebuild-islamic-state-terror-a8644921.html" target="_blank"&gt;Raqqa after Isis: The US destroyed the city to liberate it, but who will rebuild?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one terrible moment, Muhammad Ahmed Tadfi lost 10 members of his family when an airstrike destroyed their home in the west of Raqqa. His mother, brother, sister-in-law and seven nieces and nephews were all killed as they sheltered in the basement in the final stages of the battle for the city, a little over a year ago. That they had survived the worst of the fighting made their deaths all the more senseless to him. “The area was liberated. There was no Isis there,” he says, sitting in the restaurant where he now works. “They could have avoided this destruction.” Tadfi is one of thousands...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Israeli lawmakers vote against recognizing ISIS’ anti-Yazidi cleansing as genocide - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/444602-irael-yazidi-genocide-not-recognized/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMG5NyVECSclxXBvqsVP6pYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 03:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/444602-irael-yazidi-genocide-not-recognized/" target="_blank"&gt;Israeli lawmakers vote against recognizing ISIS’ anti-Yazidi cleansing as genocide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israeli MPs have refused to recognize the suffering of the Yazidi minority living under Islamic State as a genocide. Up to 5,000 have been killed and over 3,000, mostly women and children, taken captive and enslaved. On Wednesday, the Israeli parliament voted down a draft bill that would have formally recognized the atrocities of Islamic State (IS, formerly ISIS/ISIL) against the Yazidi people as a genocide. The proposed legislation was rejected by 58 parliamentarians, including the members from the ruling right-wing coalition led by Israeli PM Benjamin Netanyahu. Thirty-eight votes in supp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>With little aid, Syria's Raqqa struggles to revive schools - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-raqqa-education-idUSKCN1NV1I7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECK84bkfgPkCFRKvpHhKdxwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 17:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-raqqa-education-idUSKCN1NV1I7" target="_blank"&gt;With little aid, Syria's Raqqa struggles to revive schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Syrian city of Raqqa, children wear hats, scarves and coats to guard against the winter cold as they struggle to catch up on years of lost learning in a classroom with no doors or glazed windows. More than a year since the United States and its allies defeated Islamic State at Raqqa, many of the city's schools still look like battlefields with buildings left lying in rubble and playgrounds dotted with wrecked cars. "When the crisis started, we stopped studying, the schools closed. Now we've come back to study and we need help. Fix the windows, doors, we're dying of cold," said 12-yea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Germany planning to bring home suspected Isil fighters - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/germany-planning-bring-home-suspected-isil-fighters/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGBV4JK7Ua0tptZCirIgg74qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 20:13:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/germany-planning-bring-home-suspected-isil-fighters/" target="_blank"&gt;Germany planning to bring home suspected Isil fighters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angela Merkel’s government is considering plans to bring home German suspected Isil fighters and their families currently being held by Kurdish forces in Syria, it emerged today. The development will add to international pressure on the UK to repatriate British Isil suspects being held under similar circumstances — including two members of the notorious “Beatles” execution cell. “The federal government is examining all options for a possible return of German nationals,” the German foreign ministry said on Wednesday in a written answer to a parliamentary question. Hundreds of European citize...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Meghan cookbook mosque linked to 19 terror suspects including 'Jihadi John' in group's investigation - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/23/meghan-cookbook-mosque-linked-19-terror-suspects-including-jihadi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM5YKNxBAUMivC4URJRkyK8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/23/meghan-cookbook-mosque-linked-19-terror-suspects-including-jihadi/" target="_blank"&gt;Meghan cookbook mosque linked to 19 terror suspects including 'Jihadi John' in group's investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acommunity kitchen supported by the Duchess of Sussex is housed inside a mosque linked by experts to individuals connected to “terrorist acts” and run by an imam who says girls who listen to music risk becoming strippers. Meghan visited the Al Manaar Muslim Cultural Heritage Centre on Wednesday after championing a cookbook to raise funds for the “Hubb Community Kitchen” project there to help victims of the fire at nearby Grenfell Tower. In February it emerged the 37-year-old royal had made secret visits to the mosque in Westbourne Grove, which has also hosted Princes William and Harry, Ther...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>3 US troops killed in Afghanistan blast - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/444968-three-us-troops-killed-afghanistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA5qjnJ__cmeSrNQCESdu78qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 12:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/444968-three-us-troops-killed-afghanistan/" target="_blank"&gt;3 US troops killed in Afghanistan blast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three US service members have been killed and another three wounded in an improvised explosive device blast near the Afghan city of Ghazni, the NATO Resolute Support mission said. A US civilian contractor was also wounded in the blast, and is being treated along with the military personnel. The latest casualties bring to 11 the number of US troops killed in Afghanistan so far this year, per Reuters figures. Bad week in #Afghanistan: Three US troops killed, three more wounded. pic.twitter.com/dYBZ5NTylM — Kristina Wong (@kristina_wong) November 27, 2018 Ghazni, in central Afghanistan, was se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Iraq: Seven killed, thousands displaced in flash flooding - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/iraq-killed-thousands-displaced-flash-flooding-181123121055986.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEllA7sXeV10crHe9taMhYkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:47:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/iraq-killed-thousands-displaced-flash-flooding-181123121055986.html" target="_blank"&gt;Iraq: Seven killed, thousands displaced in flash flooding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least seven people, including children, have been killed and thousands have been forced to flee their homes after heavy rains triggered flash floods in northern Iraq. Officials told the dpa news agency on Friday that the seven people were killed when floods hit the al-Houreya village in Salahuddin province. Ali Dodah, the mayor of Shirqat, a town 260km northwest of Baghdad and around 80km south of Mosul, said rains had flooded houses and farms with "some 3,000 people now homeless". Footage from the state-run Iraqi News Agency showed people in Salahuddin province, where Shirqat is located...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>ISIS to launch false flag chemical attack on Syrian Kurds – and Russian military is watching closely - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445082-isis-falseflag-chemical-attack-deirezzor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP-8ABfa_KsGG356M_mgfV4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 17:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445082-isis-falseflag-chemical-attack-deirezzor/" target="_blank"&gt;ISIS to launch false flag chemical attack on Syrian Kurds – and Russian military is watching closely&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamic State terrorists are plotting to shell Kurdish-led militia with chemical-filled munitions in Deir ez-Zor, Syria, Russian military said. The terrorists want to frame Damascus for the attack to trigger new US-led airstrikes. Islamic State (IS, formerly ISIS) has launched production of toxin-filled mortar shells in the east of the Deir ez-Zor province, Russian military said on Wednesday. The shells are filled with chemicals by a crew of 11 terrorists, who received foreign training and came to Syria specifically to carry out the false-flag attack. FILE PHOTO. Home-made mortar shells, pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Suicide bombing kills more than 50 gathered to celebrate Prophet Mohammed's birth - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-21/kabul-suicide-bombing-kills-more-than-50/10519032</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGqF8FMzreflsUT6Gi-tIiYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 06:02:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-21/kabul-suicide-bombing-kills-more-than-50/10519032" target="_blank"&gt;Suicide bombing kills more than 50 gathered to celebrate Prophet Mohammed's birth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 50 people are dead after a suicide bomber targeted a gathering of hundreds of Islamic scholars in the Afghan capital of Kabul on Tuesday (local time) as Muslims marked the birthday of the Prophet Mohammed. Key points: - The bomber snuck into a wedding hall filled with hundreds of Muslim scholars and clerics - Nobody has claimed the attack, but the Taliban and local IS have targeted Muslim scholars - Afghan President Ashraf Ghani called the suicide bombing "an attack on humanity" Another 83 people were wounded in the attack, with 20 of them in critical condition and the toll likely ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>'Immense loss for Syria': Gunmen kill Idlib activist Raed Fares - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/loss-syria-gunmen-kill-idlib-activist-raed-fares-181123134749540.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDHh5R3Mrupru4VduusZzcwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 07:29:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/loss-syria-gunmen-kill-idlib-activist-raed-fares-181123134749540.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Immense loss for Syria': Gunmen kill Idlib activist Raed Fares&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gunmen in Syria's rebel-held Idlib province have killed Raed Fares, a prominent activist who ran an independent radio station in the country's last opposition stronghold. Fares was shot on Friday along with his colleague Hamoud Juneid in the town of Kafranbel, according to their Radio Fresh station. Fares and Juneid were "shot dead by unknown assailants riding a van in Kafranbel", Fresh FM, which provides independent news and satirises both President Bashar al-Assad and opposition groups, said in a post on Facebook. Salman, a 33-year-old mathematics teacher, who witnessed the attack, told ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Turkey uneasy about U.S. plan for observation posts on Syria border: minister - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-turkey-usa/turkey-uneasy-about-u-s-plan-for-observation-posts-on-syria-border-minister-idUSKCN1NT0D9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPh5281PfSOWjzhILHPfji4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 11:26:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-turkey-usa/turkey-uneasy-about-u-s-plan-for-observation-posts-on-syria-border-minister-idUSKCN1NT0D9" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey uneasy about U.S. plan for observation posts on Syria border: minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey is uneasy about U.S. plans to set up "observation posts" in Syria along parts of its border with Turkey, Turkish Defence Minister Hulusi Akar said on Saturday. Defense Secretary Jim Mattis said on Wednesday the United States was setting up the posts to help keep the focus on clearing the final Islamic State militant strongholds in Syria. The United States has long complained that tension between Turkey and the Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF) - which includes the Syrian Kurdish YPG militia - has at times slowed progress on the fight against Islamic State. Akar said he told U.S. Chief o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Hundreds of bodies exhumed from Isis mass grave in Syria - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/isis-mass-grave-syria-war-death-bodies-raqqa-a8655066.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJUiIe3utPOJKIrWxzYiQBAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/isis-mass-grave-syria-war-death-bodies-raqqa-a8655066.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hundreds of bodies exhumed from Isis mass grave in Syria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of bodies have been exhumed from one of the largest mass graves near the Syrian city of Raqqa - once the capital of Isis‘s self-declared caliphate. Concerns about the preservation of bodies and evidence for possible war crimes trials, have led local groups and first responders to work around the clock to exhume the bodies. “We’re in a race against time,” said Sara Kayyali, of Human Rights Watch. ”These bodies are decomposing at an exponential rate.” Read more - Amnesty asks public to help track civilian casualties in Syria - Raqqa after Isis: Mass grave reveals horror of city’s fin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>How We Can End The Exploitation Of Women By Terrorist Groups - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/nikitamalik/2018/11/28/how-we-can-end-the-exploitation-of-women-by-terrorist-groups/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1I0wgfFObrfzgJtFvg3K4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/nikitamalik/2018/11/28/how-we-can-end-the-exploitation-of-women-by-terrorist-groups/" target="_blank"&gt;How We Can End The Exploitation Of Women By Terrorist Groups&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shayra, Iraq – May 28, 2017: A young Yazidi woman sits with her three children inside a tent in Sharya IDP camp in northern Iraq. They and their families fled the 2014 ISIS advance in which many Yazidis were killed and others, especially women and children, captured and trafficked by ISIS. It is about time we face the horrifying fact that men with a history of sexual violence and domestic abuse are attracted to organisations like Islamic State precisely because of its systemic use of rape and slavery as a form of terrorism. Sexual violence by extremist groups is central to recruiting, retai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Syria war: Amnesty asks public to help track civilian casualties of US-led bombing in Raqqa - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/syria-civil-war-raqqa-us-military-bombing-coalition-strike-tracker-amnesty-a8642656.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIgcKBXqwff0H0KryQJE5UkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/syria-civil-war-raqqa-us-military-bombing-coalition-strike-tracker-amnesty-a8642656.html" target="_blank"&gt;Syria war: Amnesty asks public to help track civilian casualties of US-led bombing in Raqqa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone with access to an internet connection will soon be able to investigate civilian casualties caused by the US-led military coalition bombing of Raqqa during the battle to capture the city from Isis. Amnesty International is launching a new project that it hopes will involve thousands of members of the public in its ongoing investigation into the destruction in the city. “Strike Tracker”, designed in conjunction with independent casualty monitor Airwars, will allow anyone to sift through satellite pictures of Raqqa over the period of the battle and mark when a building was destroyed. Do...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Decorated Navy SEAL Is Accused of War Crimes in Iraq - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/15/us/navy-seal-edward-gallagher-isis.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOYig27yGf3OXSh2okRnagqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 15:23:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/15/us/navy-seal-edward-gallagher-isis.html" target="_blank"&gt;Decorated Navy SEAL Is Accused of War Crimes in Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAVAL BASE SAN DIEGO — Edward Gallagher was something special, even by the punishing standards of the Navy SEALs. Both a lifesaving medic and a crack sniper, he was repeatedly decorated for valor and for coolheaded leadership during 19 years of combat deployments. After his latest tour, fighting Islamic State militants in Iraq, he was named the top platoon leader in SEAL Team 7 and nominated for the Silver Star, the military’s third-highest honor. But now, less than a year later, Special Operations Chief Gallagher, 39, is locked in the brig, facing charges that during that same deployment —...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Amnesty to Expand Probe of US-Led Campaign in Syria's Raqqa - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/amnesty-to-expand-probe-of-us-led-campaign-in-syria-s-raqqa/4668138.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVAixielRzZLZ6rd14FY2UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 17:27:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/amnesty-to-expand-probe-of-us-led-campaign-in-syria-s-raqqa/4668138.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amnesty to Expand Probe of US-Led Campaign in Syria's Raqqa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amnesty International said Wednesday it's enlisting the help of thousands of online activists to speed up its investigation into the U.S.-led campaign that drove Islamic State militants from their self-styled capital of Raqqa but left the Syrian city in ruins. The London-based rights group said the new phase of its investigation enables thousands of online activists, using satellite imagery of the city, to map out the destruction over the four-month campaign, which ended in October 2017. The U.N estimates that more than 10,000 buildings were destroyed — or 80 percent of the city. Amnesty's ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Two Decades After 9/11, Militants Have Only Multiplied - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/us/politics/terrorism-islamic-militants.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDzHmUDvFLJN19vGoGozyvEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloEY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 05:16:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/us/politics/terrorism-islamic-militants.html" target="_blank"&gt;Two Decades After 9/11, Militants Have Only Multiplied&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON — Nearly four times as many Sunni Islamic militants are operating around the world today as on Sept. 11, 2001, despite nearly two decades of American-led campaigns to combat Al Qaeda and the Islamic State, a new independent study concludes. That amounts to as many as 230,000 Salafi jihadist fighters in nearly 70 countries, with the largest numbers in Syria, Afghanistan and Pakistan, according to the study by the Center for Strategic and International Studies, a Washington think tank. The report’s conclusions, drawing on multiple databases dating to 1980 to compile one of the most...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>US Adds IS Leader's Associate to Terror List - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-adds-islamic-state-leader-s-associate-to-terror-list/4667448.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIzXMSnioR06IfzVKts1t_EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:36:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-adds-islamic-state-leader-s-associate-to-terror-list/4667448.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Adds IS Leader's Associate to Terror List&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hajji Abd al-Nasir, an Iraqi national who served as a senior Islamic State military leader in Syria and a close confidant of its leader, Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi, has been named as a specially designated global terrorist by the United States, the U.S. State Department announced Tuesday. Al-Nasir, also known to Interpol as Taha al-Khuwayt, was born between 1965 and 1969 in the Iraqi northern town of Tal Afar. He has held several leadership positions in the Islamic State terror group over the past five years, including working as IS's military “amir” or leader in Syria and as chair of the IS Dele...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Iraqi military says it killed 15 Islamic State militants in the north - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-iraq/iraqi-military-says-it-killed-15-islamic-state-militants-in-the-north-idUSKCN1NQ14S</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE38di5XpDLpXZl9SLRL9zYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:21:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-iraq/iraqi-military-says-it-killed-15-islamic-state-militants-in-the-north-idUSKCN1NQ14S" target="_blank"&gt;Iraqi military says it killed 15 Islamic State militants in the north&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iraqi forces have killed 15 Islamic State militants inside a tunnel during a search operation in the northern Sunni-majority Salahuddin province, the military said on Wednesday. Islamic State, which once occupied a third of Iraq's territory, has been largely defeated in the country but has continued to carry out ambushes, assassinations and bombings there and still poses a threat. Security forces "have completed a search operation which led to the destruction of two hideouts used by the terrorists and the killing of 15 elements inside a large tunnel," a spokesman for the military's Joint Op...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Russia poses greater threat than Isis, new British army chief warns - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/nov/24/russia-poses-greater-threat-than-isis-new-british-army-chief-warns</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMgPyaG8B5n_03xbR8JrTVEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 07:29:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/nov/24/russia-poses-greater-threat-than-isis-new-british-army-chief-warns" target="_blank"&gt;Russia poses greater threat than Isis, new British army chief warns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia “indisputably” poses a far greater threat to national security than Islamic terrorist groups such as al-Qaida and Isis, the new head of the British army has warned. General Mark Carleton-Smith said the UK cannot be complacent about the threat Russia poses “or leave it uncontested”. The former SAS commander said Russia had made plain its preparedness to use force to expand its interests, while it had also been “systematic” in its efforts to exploit cyber space and undersea military arenas. “The Russians seek to exploit vulnerability and weakness wherever they detect it,” he told the D...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Syrian army says Islamic State cleared from southeastern desert - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria/syrian-army-says-islamic-state-cleared-from-southeastern-desert-idUSKCN1NO25N</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEJlT2CV26-G57_mTFsmJA4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 17:26:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria/syrian-army-says-islamic-state-cleared-from-southeastern-desert-idUSKCN1NO25N" target="_blank"&gt;Syrian army says Islamic State cleared from southeastern desert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Syrian army said on Monday Islamic State militants had been cleared from a rugged area in southeastern Syria, where they had been holding out for months against a campaign to defeat them. In a statement, Syria's army high command said it had taken full control of the Tulul al-Safa heights, a volcanic plateau east of Sweida province. The area was Islamic State's last stronghold in southern Syria and the Syrian armed forces recovered a large amount of light and medium weaponry, the statement said. Local sources told Reuters on Sunday hundreds of Islamic State insurgents had withdrawn from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>U.S.-backed Syrian fighters say they hold Islamic State leader's assistant - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-arrest/us-backed-syrian-fighters-say-they-hold-islamic-state-leaders-assistant-idUSKCN1NZ22Y</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOpRvcHWoZpzNaGmOd3t6S8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:19:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-arrest/us-backed-syrian-fighters-say-they-hold-islamic-state-leaders-assistant-idUSKCN1NZ22Y" target="_blank"&gt;U.S.-backed Syrian fighters say they hold Islamic State leader's assistant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S.-backed fighters in Syria have captured a senior Islamic State leader who served as an assistant to the group's self-declared "caliph" Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi, they said on Friday. The Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF), a Kurdish-led militia alliance that holds the quarter of Syria east of the Euphrates, detained Osama al-Awaid last week, it said in a statement. SDF fighters have been attempting to take Islamic State's last Syrian pocket of territory on the banks of the Euphrates near Iraq for weeks, in an offensive backed by U.S.-led air strikes. They captured Awaid in a special operation in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Islamic State says U.S.-led strikes kill 40 in militant pocket in Syria - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-casualties/islamic-state-says-us-led-strikes-kill-40-in-militant-pocket-in-syria-idUSKCN1NM0PY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKm_NG9K_bRqnEdNyZd8y-IqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 22:04:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-casualties/islamic-state-says-us-led-strikes-kill-40-in-militant-pocket-in-syria-idUSKCN1NM0PY" target="_blank"&gt;Islamic State says U.S.-led strikes kill 40 in militant pocket in Syria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least forty people, mostly women and children were killed on Saturday in the latest wave of U.S.-led coalition airstrikes against the last remaining Islamic State-held pocket in Syria near the border with Iraq, the militants and some local residents said. Asked about reports of air strikes in the Buqan area near Hajin on the eastern banks of the Euphrates River on Saturday, the coalitio’s spokesman confirmed that there were strikes but denied there were civilian casualties. Colonel Sean Ryan, the coalition spokesman, said "the coalition takes great measures to identify and strike appropr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Are we the baddies? Al Qaeda team plays on the same side as the US in Yemen (VIDEO) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/444977-us-al-quaeda-ties/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF5nXcYJT94sjTzz7zvbTBoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/444977-us-al-quaeda-ties/" target="_blank"&gt;Are we the baddies? Al Qaeda team plays on the same side as the US in Yemen (VIDEO)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US media obfuscation of the truth about the Yemen war has effectively shielded the American public from learning that their country is in league with Al Qaeda forces there, Rania Khalek reports. Al Qaeda in the Arab Peninsula (AQAP) is supposed to be the branch most dangerous to Americans because it is actively plotting attacks on the US. Yet, the US-backed coalition of Arab nations, led by Saudi Arabia, has cozied up with the group amid the stalled military intervention against the Houthis. AQAP not only fights coalition members, but even serves as a source of recruits for it. The US has a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Iraq launches air strikes against Islamic State in Syria - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-iraq/iraq-launches-air-strikes-against-islamic-state-in-syria-idUSKCN1NP1DC</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMbBLFp1twKCOSNR7WeHVNYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 12:40:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-iraq/iraq-launches-air-strikes-against-islamic-state-in-syria-idUSKCN1NP1DC" target="_blank"&gt;Iraq launches air strikes against Islamic State in Syria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iraq launched an air strike on an Islamic State target inside neighboring Syria on Tuesday, its military said on Monday. F-16 fighter jets destroyed a building where members of the ultra-hardline Sunni militant group were storing weapons, killing 10 of them, the Iraqi military said in a statement. A second air strike destroyed a building housing 30 Islamic State fighters, the statement said. (Reporting by Ahmed Aboulenein in Cairo; Editing by Kevin Liffey)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>US Setting Up 'Observation Posts' Along Turkey-Syria Border - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-setting-up-observation-posts-along-turkey-syria-border/4668586.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIZwHRyKH5Bcj4R_qxJ9lSoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 22:06:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-setting-up-observation-posts-along-turkey-syria-border/4668586.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Setting Up 'Observation Posts' Along Turkey-Syria Border&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States is setting up “observation posts” along parts of the border between Turkey and Syria to help keep the focus on defeating Islamic State militants in Syria, Defense Secretary Jim Mattis said on Wednesday. The observation posts would not require additional U.S. troops being sent to Syria, Mattis told reporters. The Pentagon says it has about 2,000 troops in Syria. The United States has long been complained that tensions between Turkey and the Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF), which includes the Syrian Kurdish YPG militia, have at times slowed down progress on fighting Islamic S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>