<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Jim McGuinness - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR1p3YWw5MGFCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:18:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Donegal All-Ireland winning manager Jim McGuinness signs a 3-year deal with USL Championship side - Donegal Now</title><link>https://www.donegalnow.com/soccer/donegal-ireland-winning-manager-jim-mcguinness-signs-3-year-deal-usl-championship-side/261218</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780129525640</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.donegalnow.com/soccer/donegal-ireland-winning-manager-jim-mcguinness-signs-3-year-deal-usl-championship-side/261218" target="_blank"&gt;Donegal All-Ireland winning manager Jim McGuinness signs a 3-year deal with USL Championship side&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Donegal Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/jim-mcguinness-coach-charlotte-4381250-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;All-Ireland winner Jim McGuinness takes head coach role with US second-tier side Charlotte&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/soccer/2018/1207/1015763-jim-mcguinness-lands-north-carolina-head-coaching-role/" target="_blank"&gt;Jim McGuinness lands North Carolina head coaching role&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/soccer/jim-mcguinness-lands-first-professional-managerial-role-in-america-37603692.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jim McGuinness lands first professional managerial role... in America&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.irishtimes.com/sport/soccer/jim-mcguinness-named-head-coach-of-north-carolina-soccer-team-1.3723552" target="_blank"&gt;Jim McGuinness named head coach of North Carolina soccer team&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWlJdl95bWpZQU1FZXB1N3Juc1ZIOXhLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.donegalnow.com">Donegal Now</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/KC6eAlFcb0PQ0HG2kbbKPmBLBcI7Ub-GJ2BZuQBIjjMv7pXXagXwLOnL6U2OB2S4ePQFWfrgQfLOTHM5wZe_cLNUZ3cqxiOLESHMjUGB9QowZPi5ghaL67c7HPr52w-jNDwxIn8Y2glJaN19p8dRJrtUZPsVWs9RdeMrs5WZU1FY_ns9YsOOFMhV495Vt1R60yBlvMSA35DCGgUkn-hsSozBAvj6vYK1zxJhidtLj2DieRNdSPxCtjZbmOTrQGRYKEmR1M3Mbgb0c7aBtgTZuC6GfaT2QvLfRvBuD90nAEPSX5sMaT_lWvTHMKbWoiHe8Flvtg6Il6ozE0wPZjJ6MpzMCUMLJS_niAcBVOB2m5ymFibktpKDdvi9pKDFAi6ypE-IunKYdkZZ0o06oFwtOa92tKCeLa8vtgTgDCtR2ISiH846DDMcYyvBoXy8NwOHhfdzwcL0ubd85NqI7ZCL8UQOm_Tghsi11gy6rkShw-S-bQIg6wLOm7Am-xWw8qbEvKSuoJIIZAoz-B5KiuCGT7zzJIuEpLfS0QsuMsIpGVTLY5PjKQ9H7QONh4TBFaZ3xQDBNTgA2_YQPxZIlxGj7OYGj_SEFhe4Zd-8AYg6htiKgA37ioCDIyGRj1qoRNREocczMk0o5yUfK2LLODre-Tisjo393696-hms6yQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Latest Sports News From - TodayFM</title><link>https://www.todayfm.com/Sport/Jim-McGuinness-Bound-For-The-US</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiPWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRvZGF5Zm0uY29tL1Nwb3J0L0ppbS1NY0d1aW5uZXNzLUJvdW5kLUZvci1UaGUtVVPSAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:35:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.todayfm.com/Sport/Jim-McGuinness-Bound-For-The-US" target="_blank"&gt;Latest Sports News From&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TodayFM&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Get all the latest Irish &amp; International sports news and keep up to date with all the sporting news that really matters.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.todayfm.com">TodayFM</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/bqp5g8aGK9RjTfELK5NyIty7AKwo00vsTqyUwtTUdmC7WJdsKJio6WUe43HRhLMmcl0bhNBSRvHZ7rQuhDyQ1pCctxy1dPO6QIyhIU3dIjpur-r6mUaSqNMHqUAsyA4hLeZOa_G2DTCMZQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Former Donegal manager Jim McGuinness signs coaching deal with US soccer team - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/former-donegal-manager-jim-mcguinness-signs-coaching-deal-with-us-soccer-team-890539.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAGLiRhhbisvBCA7ko1l4tMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/former-donegal-manager-jim-mcguinness-signs-coaching-deal-with-us-soccer-team-890539.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Donegal manager Jim McGuinness signs coaching deal with US soccer team&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jim McGuinness is to continue his soccer career in the USA. The former Donegal All-Ireland winning boss has been given his first role in management, signing a three-year contract with the Charlotte Independence as their new head coach. Jim McGuinness is the new head coach of the Charlotte Independence The Charlotte Independence play in the United Soccer League, North America's largest professional soccer organisation. McGuinness managed the Donegal team who won the 2012 All-Ireland senior football title and left Gaelic Football management in 2014. He then spent time as a Performance Consult...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Gweedore's Kevin Cassidy: If I’d carried on with Donegal, I’d be in stands now - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/gaa/gweedores-kevin-cassidy-if-id-carried-on-with-donegal-id-be-in-stands-now-889619.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAF3TOXedpu6CajhZwIpDTMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/gaa/gweedores-kevin-cassidy-if-id-carried-on-with-donegal-id-be-in-stands-now-889619.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gweedore's Kevin Cassidy: If I’d carried on with Donegal, I’d be in stands now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kevin Cassidy thinks he has God and Jim McGuinness to thank for the sweetest moment of his career. The premature end to Cassidy’s inter-county career after a fallout with the former Donegal manager in 2011 is well documented, but a new footnote can be written now he’s been crowned an Ulster club winner with Gweedore at the age of 37. Cassidy defied his creaking body to deliver a masterful performance in Healy Park on Sunday, and he believes it wouldn’t have happened if events had taken a different turn. Kevin Cassidy celebrates Gaoth Dobhair’s Ulster club success. Cassidy, 37, retired from ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Composed Ferry has final say as Gaoth Dobhair see off Scotstown - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/composed-ferry-has-final-say-as-gaoth-dobhair-see-off-scotstown-37587826.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAsgMnYNWcAqjazwV7B_HX4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/composed-ferry-has-final-say-as-gaoth-dobhair-see-off-scotstown-37587826.html" target="_blank"&gt;Composed Ferry has final say as Gaoth Dobhair see off Scotstown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the first 15 minutes or so, there was no sign of what was to come. For the large part the football reflected the weather. There was an emphasis on possession and patience and a huge spill of rain before throw-in that continued into the first half, and made conditions on an already wet pitch even more difficult. At one stage in the first half, Scotstown attacker Conor McCarthy tried to hop the ball before taking a free. It simply stuck in the sodden turf. There was plenty of endeavour early on but not much in the way of penetration. Both teams were trying hard but trying to make anythi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Dramatic scenes in Omagh as Gaoth Dobhair outlast Scotstown to win first Ulster club title after extra time - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/dramatic-scenes-in-omagh-as-gaoth-dobhair-outlast-scotstown-to-win-first-ulster-club-title-after-extra-time-37586786.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO43nOgUEFQm9hF6d5f3y9oqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 17:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/dramatic-scenes-in-omagh-as-gaoth-dobhair-outlast-scotstown-to-win-first-ulster-club-title-after-extra-time-37586786.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dramatic scenes in Omagh as Gaoth Dobhair outlast Scotstown to win first Ulster club title after extra time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gaoth Dobhair are Ulster club champions for the first time in their history after seeing off 14-man Scotstown in a thrilling final in Omagh’s Healy Park. The Donegal men needed extra time to see off Kieran Donnelly’s Monaghan champions, who had Shane Carey sent off on a straight red card in the first period of extra time. In the end, Shane Ferry’s point, the only score in the second period of extra time, was enough to see the Donegal men home, who also finished the game with 14 men after Eamonn McGee was shown a second yellow card with almost the last action of the game. The game could have...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Few pubs have witnessed the scenes going on in Micís in Gaoth Dobhair right now - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/pubs-witnessed-scenes-going-micis-gaoth-dobhair-right-now-186747</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHZenygpX0eTOXgn0-76liEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:41:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/pubs-witnessed-scenes-going-micis-gaoth-dobhair-right-now-186747" target="_blank"&gt;Few pubs have witnessed the scenes going on in Micís in Gaoth Dobhair right now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only trouble for Mics this Christmas will be keeping the drink out to them. Teach Mhic in the heart of Gaoth Dobhair was the place to be on Monday morning and it will be the place to be this Christmas too. The club won their first ever Ulster title on Sunday afternoon and despite celebrating the famous victory late into the night, the people of Gaoth Dobhair were ready for action early on Monday morning too in Mics HQ, the pub owned by Kevin Cassidy. For now at least, it's the centre of the world. Cassidy had promised the GAA Hour Show a Skype Call live from Mics if they won Ulster but ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Missing the medal: Best decision I ever made, says Kevin Cassidy - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/gaa/missing-the-medal-best-decision-i-ever-made-says-kevin-cassidy-885980.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAzXk8dk6E46z96rviElcW4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/gaa/missing-the-medal-best-decision-i-ever-made-says-kevin-cassidy-885980.html" target="_blank"&gt;Missing the medal: Best decision I ever made, says Kevin Cassidy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow, at 37, Kevin Cassidy plays for Gaoth Dobhair in the Ulster Club SFC semi-final. Regarded as the unluckiest man in Donegal for missing the 2012 All-Ireland success, he sits down with the man whose book led to his exile from Jim McGuinness’ setup. He doesn’t have any regrets. ‘We’re a special kind of people’ The travelling fans from Naomh Conaill could hardly believe their eyes as they crawled along the narrow lanes of Magheragallon towards the home of Gaoth Dobhair CLG. There for all to see, was an eight by four-foot sign with the message; ‘We’re a special kind of people, we breed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>'It’s harder to get over a defeat like that': The psychology behind Mayo's latest All-Ireland final loss - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/mayo-final-psychology-3611053-Sep2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFxRnR_1HZNIrDvU463bEwQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 10:00:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/mayo-final-psychology-3611053-Sep2017/" target="_blank"&gt;'It’s harder to get over a defeat like that': The psychology behind Mayo's latest All-Ireland final loss&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE MAJORITY OF this Mayo group have had two cracks at an All-Ireland final under both James Horan and Stephen Rochford, and they’ve still failed to land that coveted Celtic Cross. “It’s a long trek to get back here but I have no doubt the lads will look to regroup over the winter and see what that takes them next spring and into the summer,” said Stephen Rochford in the Citywest Hotel on Monday morning. “It’s something that we’ll look to get over during the winter.” The big worry for Rochford and Mayo fans is whether this ageing group of players go one better in 12 months’ time. Andy Moran...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Donegal confirm Banty and Bonner in the running for senior football job - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/donegal-banty-bonner-3576227-Sep2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBUTEgb1kRnPJ0JrGtRx9xgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 11:55:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/donegal-banty-bonner-3576227-Sep2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Donegal confirm Banty and Bonner in the running for senior football job&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE DONEGAL COUNTY Board have released the names of the five candidates in the running to replace Rory Gallagher as manager of the senior football side. Shaun Paul Barrett, Declan Bonner, Cathal Corey, Gary McDaid and Seamus McEnaney are the five candidates in the race. McEnaney recently stepped down from his position in Wexford after just one year in charge, while Bonner has enjoyed success in recent years with the Donegal U21s and minors. A nephew of ex-Donegal boss Brian McIver, Corey was interviewed for the position in 2014, when Gallagher got the job, while he also applied for the role...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Competitive 'Super 8' a must to allay elitist fears - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0807/895828-super/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-FnUHGtH8N5AU2REPj4jgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 08:03:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0807/895828-super/" target="_blank"&gt;Competitive 'Super 8' a must to allay elitist fears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;And so a weekend has concluded of one-sided games in the All-Ireland football championship. The facile victories of Tyrone, Dublin and Mayo brings into sharp focus the gap that now exists between the leading counties and the rest. But we've been down this road before. Between them, Kerry and Dublin dominated the football landscape in the period from 1974 to 1986 - sharing 12 of the 13 All-Ireland titles that were played. Offaly's famous triumph in 1982 broke that sequence. It was also a period in which the standard in Connacht was not strong enough to challenge for September glory. It wasn'...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Dublin a certainty for Sam Maguire? All-Ireland coronations have been crushed in the past - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/dublin-a-certainty-for-sam-maguire-allireland-coronations-have-been-crushed-in-the-past-36124948.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYrAzRDZgmh2NgzW3ugljQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 07:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/dublin-a-certainty-for-sam-maguire-allireland-coronations-have-been-crushed-in-the-past-36124948.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dublin a certainty for Sam Maguire? All-Ireland coronations have been crushed in the past&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FANCY a light? Then may we recommend this priceless keepsake from a quarter-century ago. “Dublin All-Ireland Football Champions 1992,” our lighter (pictured below) proudly boasts. It mightn’t be as notorious as those Kerry five-in-a-row T-shirts but it’s a metaphor worth recalling in this, of all weeks. Especially if you’re a Dub diehard convinced that what happens next is preordained. Examples are littered through the decades, salutary tales of All-Ireland coronations quashed. The years when everyone – fawning media, presumptuous public – had concluded in advance that Sam Maguire was goi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>You really don't know what you're going to get from Mayo but it will probably be a win - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/really-dont-know-youre-going-get-mayo-will-probably-win-132873</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDdKEz-8VB3PbsHo4YUUItcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 09:50:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/really-dont-know-youre-going-get-mayo-will-probably-win-132873" target="_blank"&gt;You really don't know what you're going to get from Mayo but it will probably be a win&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What a bank holiday Monday treat. Say what you want about Mayo, they are very entertaining. We didn't get our Mayo vs. Roscommon matchup in the Connacht Championship so the two sides decided to bring things to a replay to even things out for the fans, how considerate. Stephen Rochford's side have been poor this year, yet they are still in the hunt to win an All-Ireland and that is the most important thing. A victory over Roscommon will mean a seventh consecutive semifinal berth and will again silence doubters that say they are not a top team and despite the lack of form the pundits on the G...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>If Galway star is suspended for All-Ireland final for this, it's an absolute joke - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/galway-star-suspended-ireland-final-absolute-joke-132967</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPacZs3ZBD_EbXZk59wQD54qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 21:38:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/galway-star-suspended-ireland-final-absolute-joke-132967" target="_blank"&gt;If Galway star is suspended for All-Ireland final for this, it's an absolute joke&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Galway fans would be livid if Adrian Touhy got suspended for the All-Ireland final, and you can't blame them for that. The Sunday Game team rose the issue of the Beagh club man's supposed indiscretion during the second half of their All-Ireland semi-final triumph against Tipperary. The faceguard rule, which according to the GAA rulebook includes"behaving in any way which is dangerous to an opponent, including deliberately pulling on or taking hold of a faceguard or any part of an opponents helmet (in hurling)." Tadhg De Brca was cited for this category III infraction for his incident with W...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Let's celebrate a victory for football - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/lets-celebrate-a-victory-for-football-36094437.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3TeZuAO_497ZmyyzJRN9IqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 17:00:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/lets-celebrate-a-victory-for-football-36094437.html" target="_blank"&gt;Let's celebrate a victory for football&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dublin might as well have been playing against traffic cones last Sunday. Like the trainer who had set out the cones for the warm-up, the Tyrone players looked as though they had been set down into their 13 defensive positions. While they rigidly stuck to their one-dimensional plan, Dublin played football. And when the Dubs scored a goal after a few minutes, the game was over. I wrote last week that Tyrone's big problem would be working the ball out of their blanket defence. Normally, they have free men to offload to, but not against the Dubs, who pushed up on them and tackled ferociously t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>The hair-raising pre-match speech that could only apply to Dublin - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/hair-raising-pre-match-speech-apply-dublin-132847</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECuR_YHrqSq715xf6QuLTFsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 21:14:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/hair-raising-pre-match-speech-apply-dublin-132847" target="_blank"&gt;The hair-raising pre-match speech that could only apply to Dublin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone watching that brilliant Netflix documentary, Last Chance U, has probably long since given up on taking much inspiration from it or even finding someone likeable enough there to enjoy. It's just a fascinating insight into the grim desperation in the States where young men will do whatever it takes to advance their American Football careers by even just a year if it comes to that. No long term plans or ideas, no thought that they might not even make it. It's all or nothing and the vast, vast majority of them are headed for nothing and God only knows what their lives have in store for t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Dublin fan finally gives Mayo all the credit and admiration they deserve - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/dublin-fan-finally-gives-mayo-credit-admiration-deserve-137661</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPsH6SWPHEpZMC-_-VGBLGYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 07:43:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/dublin-fan-finally-gives-mayo-credit-admiration-deserve-137661" target="_blank"&gt;Dublin fan finally gives Mayo all the credit and admiration they deserve&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's nearly a week. Nearly a week since Dublin achieved one of the finest achievements in GAA history, the three in a row. Nearly a week since Dean Rock slotted over that free and Lee Keegan threw a GPS tracker in desperation. Nearly a week since Keegan knew the same thing was going to happen to Mayo, they were going to miss out by just a hair, again. The three in a row is a great achievement but this time even many Dublin fans thought 'maybe Mayo deserve just one' but sport is cruel. This time around there was no bitterness towards Mayo, no slagging or banter, just sympathy. How many times...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Galway manager "stole" one of Tipperary panel's most important members this year - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/galway-manager-has-inside-information-on-tipperary-players-that-could-prove-crucial-132709</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOphT8ytVOUvdIfozquw3dwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 11:53:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/galway-manager-has-inside-information-on-tipperary-players-that-could-prove-crucial-132709" target="_blank"&gt;Galway manager "stole" one of Tipperary panel's most important members this year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This one is going to be personal. Tipperary and Galway are neigbhours, they are rivals, and they will meet in Croke Park for an All-Ireland semi-final for the third time in three years - one win apiece, this Sunday will be the decider. Damien Hayes is from Portumna, and he knows all about the ferocity of this rivalry. The east Galway man, club mate of Joe Canning's, was born only a stone's throw away from Lorrha Dorrha, the most northerly club in North Tipperary, and the home of The Premier County's two-time All Star Patrick 'Bonner' Maher. Hayes was speaking on The GAA Hour Hurling Show on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>One of the greats has called time on his intercounty career - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/one-greats-called-time-intercounty-career-135620</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPeKo1ecm-K4d_UociD2cmQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 19:49:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/one-greats-called-time-intercounty-career-135620" target="_blank"&gt;One of the greats has called time on his intercounty career&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Karl Lacey has announced his retirement from intercounty football. 14 seasons, one All-Ireland title, three Ulster titles, four All-Stars and one footballer of the year award later, Karl Lacey has kicked his last ball for the Donegal senior team. Lacey was a key figure in Jim McGuinness's All-Ireland winning side in 2012, the same year he claimed the Footballer of the Year accolade. Coming on as a half-time sub in Donegal's defeat to Galway will be the last time he togged out for the county. Check out his statement in full below. "Having allowed some dust to settle on our season, I now feel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Tyrone's fascinating warm-up drill shows their style of play perfectly - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/tyrones-warm-up-drill-132827</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEADYvrphhoAjqy3o0KFz0P8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 19:21:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/tyrones-warm-up-drill-132827" target="_blank"&gt;Tyrone's fascinating warm-up drill shows their style of play perfectly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's the thing about Mickey Harte, he doesn't really give a f**k how you play. He has his system, they've been perfecting it for a while now and how the opposition set up doesn't affect the Ulster champions. Tyrone's warm-up drill before the All-Ireland quarter-final dismantling of Armagh gave a great insight into what they're working on in Garvaghey and how their training, obviously, suits their style of play. After the Donegal game back in June, the Red Hand manager spoke about giving people a glimpse of what was to come in Gaelic Football. The details were hazy but you get the feeling ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Fermanagh announce Rory Gallagher as their new senior football manager - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/rory-gallagher-fermanagh-senior-football-manager-ratified-3593111-Sep2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH42Q2Kk4AS6tZbYLti8IXIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 20:32:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/rory-gallagher-fermanagh-senior-football-manager-ratified-3593111-Sep2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Fermanagh announce Rory Gallagher as their new senior football manager&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RORY GALLAGHER HAS been named as the new manager of Fermanagh’s senior footballers. The 39-year-old, who represented his native Erne county and Cavan as a player, had been in charge of Donegal since October 2014 but resigned from his post three years into a four-year term back in July. He had previously worked as part of the Jim McGuinness backroom team that helped the Tir Chonaill men win Sam Maguire in 2012. Fermanagh announced tonight that Gallagher has been ratified after a county board meeting. He replaces Pete McGrath, who departed this summer just a week after seemingly committing hi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>WATCH: Marty Morrissey's child-like hysteria was how we all felt during semi-final clash - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/watch-marty-morrisseys-child-like-hysteria-felt-semi-final-clash-132940</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL3enXm9eDHRB7r9YbguYNsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 16:42:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/watch-marty-morrisseys-child-like-hysteria-felt-semi-final-clash-132940" target="_blank"&gt;WATCH: Marty Morrissey's child-like hysteria was how we all felt during semi-final clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What a game that was. Galway edged the best hurling game of the year in their All-Ireland semi-final clash with Tipperary in Croke Park. A 73rd minute Joe Canning effort separated the sides as the Tribesmen emerged victorious on a scoreline of 0-22 to 1-18. The first half of Tipperary and Galway's All-Ireland semi-final meeting didn't live up to the lofty expectations predicted, but by God, the second half was a totally different ball-game. The Premier County went into the break with a one-point cushion over the Micheal Donoghue's Tribesmen but you just knew there was going to be a sting in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>'There seemed no doubt that putting O'Shea on Donaghy was like the time Ed Sheeran was in Game of Thrones' - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/tommy-martin-column-aidan-oshea-kieran-donaghy-debate-3564231-Aug2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEqyzl572cyO0nhbY0CuHW4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/tommy-martin-column-aidan-oshea-kieran-donaghy-debate-3564231-Aug2017/" target="_blank"&gt;'There seemed no doubt that putting O'Shea on Donaghy was like the time Ed Sheeran was in Game of Thrones'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Updated at 12.00 IF HISTORY IS written by the victors, what happens when it’s a draw? The thought came to mind this week after the epic battle between Mayo and Kerry, and in particular the keynote skirmish involving Aidan O’Shea and Kieran Donaghy. In the immediate aftermath there seemed no doubt: Putting O’Shea on Donaghy was one of the great strategic blunders of all time, like Hitler invading Russia, David Cameron’s Brexit referendum, or that time Ed Sheeran was in Game of Thrones. The pundits were unanimous. “Donaghy was the most influential player… Aidan was all over the shop,” said J...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Connolly cameo possibly down to card issue, says Casey - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0913/904457-casey-connolly-black-card-dublin-mayo-rte-gaa-podcast/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF_tGxiCDCufLIatSvIsiWsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 16:46:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0913/904457-casey-connolly-black-card-dublin-mayo-rte-gaa-podcast/" target="_blank"&gt;Connolly cameo possibly down to card issue, says Casey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diarmuid Connolly’s late cameo against Tyrone may have been down to protecting one of Dublin’s star men from an All-Ireland final suspension, according to former Mayo player John Casey. Different theories have been doing the rounds since the semi-final cakewalk about why the St Vincent’s man, who had just finished a 12-week ban for pushing a linesman, was granted so little game-time. Former Kerry player Marc Ó Sé suggested the introduction of the two-time All Star in the 70th minute, with the game long over as a contest, was a "rap across the knuckles" from manager Jim Gavin. Donegal’s 2012...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Ciaran Kilkenny as point-guard: How basketball has transformed Dublin's style of play - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/dublin-footballers-basketball-3600209-Sep2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFVC__IJDrwcVevBZ-hO4hEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 07:00:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/dublin-footballers-basketball-3600209-Sep2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Ciaran Kilkenny as point-guard: How basketball has transformed Dublin's style of play&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHILE THE TYRONE players were on the Croke Park field coming to terms with their defeat to Cork in the 2009 All-Ireland semi-final, which ended their reign as champions, Pat Spillane was in full-flow in the RTÉ studios. “Cork out-Tyroned Tyrone at Tyrone’s own game,” he said, his head shaking with delight. “Can I just conclude by saying, at least this puts to bed one argument. Might I suggest Joe (he nods over to Joe Brolly), the team of the decade has four All-Irelands and two National Leagues. “The second best team of the decade, Tyrone. Don’t give me anymore crap about the team of the de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Declan Bonner looks set to be ratified as new Donegal manager tomorrow - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/declan-bonner-looks-set-to-be-ratified-as-new-donegal-manager-tomorrow-806801.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHS2tmqFY5cLFGdEpwmdLIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 11:47:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/declan-bonner-looks-set-to-be-ratified-as-new-donegal-manager-tomorrow-806801.html" target="_blank"&gt;Declan Bonner looks set to be ratified as new Donegal manager tomorrow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Declan Bonner is set to go before the clubs of Donegal with a view to being ratified for the position of county senior manager tomorrow night, writes Alan Foley. Bonner was part of the 1992 All-Ireland winning panel who were the GAA’s Jubilee team at Croke Park on Sunday and has enjoyed success as manager of the Donegal minors and under-21’s in recent seasons. Donegal won the Ulster U-21 championship this year and with Bonner in charge the county’s minors were provincial champions in 2014 and All-Ireland finalists, losing out to Kerry who have since gone on to win four-in-a-row. Bonner, a c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Niall Sludden was rocking the oldest hairstyle in the book against Armagh - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/niall-sludden-rocking-oldest-hairstyle-book-armagh-132771</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGwKUje7ghbgv7wPjOP1WncqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 15:47:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/niall-sludden-rocking-oldest-hairstyle-book-armagh-132771" target="_blank"&gt;Niall Sludden was rocking the oldest hairstyle in the book against Armagh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reeling in the years. Mickey Harte's Tyrone got out of the blocks in Croke Park in Usain Bolt like fashion. They lead the battle of Ulster against Armagh by 1-5 to 0-0 after fifteen minutes of the game. Niall Sludden was pulling the strings from centre forward, Peter Harte was doing what Peter Harte does and Sean Cavanagh was looking as fresh as ever, marking his brother in law, Charlie Vernon in his 88th appearance for the Red Hand county. Harte buried a penalty with the finesse we have come to expect of him in the 15th minute of the game, and things were looking dull from the on for the o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>WATCH: Joe Canning's post-match comments are just full of integrity and class - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/watch-joe-cannings-post-match-interview-is-just-full-of-integrity-and-class-132958</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELpyV3GXAixPvaEK4uNobzYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 18:38:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/watch-joe-cannings-post-match-interview-is-just-full-of-integrity-and-class-132958" target="_blank"&gt;WATCH: Joe Canning's post-match comments are just full of integrity and class&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was written in the stars, wasn't it? Heroes stand up when the stakes are at their highest. Heroes stand up when they are needed the most. Galway had a tribe of heroes in Croke Park on Sunday, from the guts of Conor Whelan to the bravery and defiance of Gearid McInerney. Joe Canning has been a hero for Galway ever since he burst onto the scene in 2008, and he was a hero again on Sunday. Expectations have always been high for Canning, sometimes too high, but by God did he exceed these expectations against Tipperary. Canning has often been a victim of his own profile, he's had dark days, bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Joe Brolly had a problem with Andy Moran's celebration against Roscommon - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/joe-brolly-problem-andy-morans-celebration-roscommon-132990</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGOkc6t1xpPNixBIx86L3wsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 14:52:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/joe-brolly-problem-andy-morans-celebration-roscommon-132990" target="_blank"&gt;Joe Brolly had a problem with Andy Moran's celebration against Roscommon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andy Moran must have felt pretty damn good about drilling the ball into the net. The Mayo man was booed by a small section of Roscommon supporters every time he touched the ball when both counties couldn't be separated in Croke Park at the end of July. It is believed that Moran being from Ballaghaderreen, Roscommon but opting to play for Mayo was the reasoning behind the hostility. In the replay on the August bank holiday Monday, Moran jogged off the pitch to rapturous applause after putting in one hell of a shift in Mayo's 4-19 to 0-9 annihilation over their provincial rivals. He grabbed t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Jim Gavin has learned the lessons of Donegal in 2014 - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0823/899547-jim-gavin-2014/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQVDxD90bvMNgQ7I8XkCrIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 09:25:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0823/899547-jim-gavin-2014/" target="_blank"&gt;Jim Gavin has learned the lessons of Donegal in 2014&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2013 Jim Gavin’s Dublin won the All-Ireland in swashbuckling style and they set about the defence of Sam Maguire in 2014 in similar fashion. They blasted their way out of Leinster and on into the All-Ireland series, blitzed Monaghan in a quarter-final and set up a last-four meeting with 2012 champions Donegal. It was to be an intriguing clash of styles - the Dubs' traditional approach against Donegal, under forward-thinking manager Jim McGuinness, with their well-drilled defensive system. I think our game-plan continues to change - Jim Gavin At stages in the first half the Boys in Blue l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Jonny Cooper embarrassed himself with dive and reaction after Conor McManus scuffle - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/jonny-cooper-embarrassed-dive-reaction-conor-mcmanus-scuffle-132817</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEix-i_aJdt7gu77mgAFDQQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 17:42:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/jonny-cooper-embarrassed-dive-reaction-conor-mcmanus-scuffle-132817" target="_blank"&gt;Jonny Cooper embarrassed himself with dive and reaction after Conor McManus scuffle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hill 16 may have been lacking it's famous Dublin flag, but that didn't seem to be affecting Jim Gavin's men in the first half. The Dubs got off to a rip roaring start, with Paul Mannion kicking a fine point from play in the first minute of the game, and that was the trend of the half. Con O'Callaghan was pulling the strings around the middle of the field, while Dean Rock was as reliable as ever from placed balls. The Farney Army weren't doing themselves justice, however, and though defensive tactics can be excused against a side of Dublin's calibre, they were leaving Jack McCarron as a lone...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Mayo must beat Dubs to keep us interested - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/mayo-must-beat-dubs-to-keep-us-interested-36074920.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIOx9MfcumeD8a49WWYGSrAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/mayo-must-beat-dubs-to-keep-us-interested-36074920.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mayo must beat Dubs to keep us interested&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dublin are both the best thing in the football championship and the worst thing for it. That's why we need Mayo to beat them in the All-Ireland final and salvage not just this sorry season but the very idea of the championship as a viable competitive entity. The men in green and red have done a bit of rescue work already this year. Take them out of the 2017 championship and highlights would be few and far between. On September 17th they must play the game of their lives not just for their own county's sake but for the sake of Gaelic football as a whole. There were times in yesterday's metro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Naomh Conaill overturn a six-point deficit to narrowly qualify for the Donegal SFC final - The42</title><link>http://the42.ie/football-wrap-3624323-Sep2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEXpInZIk1MPnzxAxWO3GlQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 21:21:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://the42.ie/football-wrap-3624323-Sep2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Naomh Conaill overturn a six-point deficit to narrowly qualify for the Donegal SFC final&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donegal SFC NAOMH CONAILL RALLIED from six points down to book their place in the Donegal SFC final, following a a slender one-point win over Gaoth Dobhair. A goal from substitute Kieran Gallagher was a pivotal moment in the game, as the 2015 Donegal champions brought the game back to a draw in the concluding stages. Donegal’s Odhran Mac Niallais combined with Eamon McGee to give Gaoth Dobhair the early advantage, with Mac Niallais finishing up with a personal tally of 0-04. But despite building up a 1-08 0-05 half-time lead, Naomh Conaill revived in the second half to come away with a 1-13...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>'It's a big shift but in terms of football, it's been fantastic': Life in Beijing with six kids at home - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/jimmy-mcguinness-beijing-guoan-life-in-china-kids-3577904-Sep2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDqvY9gMbqZoiflBhzAsOWkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 14:02:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/jimmy-mcguinness-beijing-guoan-life-in-china-kids-3577904-Sep2017/" target="_blank"&gt;'It's a big shift but in terms of football, it's been fantastic': Life in Beijing with six kids at home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FROM GLENTIES TO Glasgow and now to Beijing, Jim McGuinness has had a crazy few years. He’ll always be best known for guiding Donegal to All-Ireland glory in 2012, but he’s been making a name on the association football scene further afield since. He took up a role with Celtic, and worked in sports psychology with their first team there, before undertaking a coaching position with the U20 side. In June, Chinese Super League club Beijing Sinobo Guoan came knocking and he obliged. He signed a two-and-a-half year contract, and he’s been working alongside ex-Bayer Leverkusen and Red Bull Salzbu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>'Simply the best. One of the greats' - Tributes pour in for retiring Karl Lacey - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/karl-lacey-twitter-tributes-3575749-Sep2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENvAv2GqHb-JgKryRDOcmPsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 09:45:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/karl-lacey-twitter-tributes-3575749-Sep2017/" target="_blank"&gt;'Simply the best. One of the greats' - Tributes pour in for retiring Karl Lacey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THREE YEARS TO the day after Donegal’s All-Ireland semi-final win over Dublin, Karl Lacey announced his retirement from county action. Tributes have been flowing in from former teammates and opponents following Lacey’s decision to call time on his career. He bows out as Donegal’s most decorated footballer, winning four All-Stars, Footballer of the Year and an All-Ireland. Eamon McGee Tomas Ó Sé Pat Shovelin Paddy Bradley Rory Kavanagh Conor Mortimer Charlie Harrison Alan O’Mara Subscribe to The42 podcasts here: Hurling may be the best thing we do as a nation but is something many never get ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Odhrán Mac Niallais shows Donegal what they've been missing with truly scandalous score - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/odhran-mac-niallais-shows-donegal-theyve-missing-truly-scandalous-score-138322</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIA5dxap0Uy41_cV_vEwVO8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 20:30:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/odhran-mac-niallais-shows-donegal-theyve-missing-truly-scandalous-score-138322" target="_blank"&gt;Odhrán Mac Niallais shows Donegal what they've been missing with truly scandalous score&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sweet Jesus. If there's one job that incoming Donegal senior football manager Declan Bonner should prioritise, it's surely luring the mercurial Gaoth Dobhair maestro Odhrn Mac Niallais back into the set-up. Mac Niallais burst onto the Donegal scene as a sprightly 18-year-old under Jim McGuinness in 2011. He served his apprenticeship in the next three years and really began to carve out a name for himself in the year 2014, when he helped himself to three wonder-points in the Ulster final against Monaghan. Donegal fans were struck by his wondrous shooting ability off his left foot, and his la...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>A lot of people are talking about Colm O'Rourke's 'idea of the GAA' - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/lot-people-talking-colm-orourkes-idea-gaa-132993</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVisjKJHvtdueHluTLOraEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 15:51:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/lot-people-talking-colm-orourkes-idea-gaa-132993" target="_blank"&gt;A lot of people are talking about Colm O'Rourke's 'idea of the GAA'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colm O'Rourke has called for revolution in the GAA. Colm O'Rourke is fed up of what he's seeing in the GAA following Mayo's complete annihilation of Roscommon in a let-down of a quarter-final. Speaking on RT following the one-sided affair, the Meath native argued for the GAA to do away with what he sees as a capitalist model and move towards a socialist model for a more even playing field. He spoke out against the controversial Sky deal, the Super 8 format which is set to introduced next year in the incredible rant which you can watch below. "My idea of the GAA is that the GAA should rail a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>David Mulgrew's second goal redefined movement expectations of forwards - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/david-mulgrews-second-goal-redefined-movement-expectations-forwards-132793</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGI2qw4PPND-1ENgQec0UagqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 16:53:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/david-mulgrews-second-goal-redefined-movement-expectations-forwards-132793" target="_blank"&gt;David Mulgrew's second goal redefined movement expectations of forwards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mickey Harte really has this Tyrone side in peak physical condition. They are strong, they are lean and this allows them break at absolute break-neck pace. Armagh simply weren't able to keep up with this blend of physicality and skill and ended up losing out by 18 points. It appears that every single member of this Tyrone team are programmed for this fast-paced, direct running and supporting game - but nobody on their team embodied these characteristics quite like second half substitution David Mulgrew. The Ardboe starlet was willing upon his introduction, he was energetic, and his movement...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>How to write an article like an ex-Kerry player and more in this week's sportswriting - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/weeks-best-sportswriting-15-3555421-Aug2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEvFhJrFt9SBfN6XyVacHGsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 07:30:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/weeks-best-sportswriting-15-3555421-Aug2017/" target="_blank"&gt;How to write an article like an ex-Kerry player and more in this week's sportswriting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. “I’ve seen things I don’t think anyone else has seen in football,” Jermaine Pennant says on a late afternoon streaked with fading sunshine in Essex. We sit together on a small concrete bench behind an empty series of pitches which nurture the football dreams of boys at the West Ham Academy but, today, provides the training ground for Pennant’s unlikely new team. Billericay Town play in the Bostik Premier League, a regional division of semi-professional clubs which occupies the seventh tier of English football.” Donald McRae of The Guardian sits down with Jermaine Pennant to discuss his c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>WATCH: Cormac Costello chucks away David Clarke's tees at vital moment - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/watch-cormac-costello-chucks-away-david-clarkes-tees-vital-moment-137545</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhWsDkU8D9Y3zLSKClt4EgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 15:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/watch-cormac-costello-chucks-away-david-clarkes-tees-vital-moment-137545" target="_blank"&gt;WATCH: Cormac Costello chucks away David Clarke's tees at vital moment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;And all the grief Lee Keegan was getting. The Mayo man was criticised for throwing a GPS device at the ball during Dean Rock's All-Ireland winning free kick but, listen, who wouldn't do it? We can say we don't condone it, we can even pretend to be outraged but most competitive beings would do what it takes if it meant survival and if it was for the good of your county. Cormac Costello is no different. The hero of the 2016 final was a late, late sub on Sunday when he was thrown in after 73 minutes of time had been played. He didn't have much impact in open play but he was one of the Dublin f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Joe Brolly: There is a point when a team with greater desire and that can stifle your attacking system can succeed - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/joe-brolly-there-is-a-point-when-a-team-with-greater-desire-and-that-can-stifle-your-attacking-system-can-succeed-36025775.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBnED8m8vTtpz_aiNA8RTzwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 14:26:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/joe-brolly-there-is-a-point-when-a-team-with-greater-desire-and-that-can-stifle-your-attacking-system-can-succeed-36025775.html" target="_blank"&gt;Joe Brolly: There is a point when a team with greater desire and that can stifle your attacking system can succeed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joe Brolly thinks this Tyrone team can hand Dublin a first championship defeat since 2014 - but only if they attack Jim Gavin's side with a 'ferocity for 70 minutes'. Dublin are strong favourites to advance to another All-Ireland final with their three in-a-row hopes alive, but the clash of styles promises to make for a riveting encounter in two weeks time. Speaking on this week's episode of The Throw-In, Independent.ie's GAA podcast, Brolly explained why he thinks the game will be won or lost on how Dublin deal with Tyrone's defensive set-up. Subscribe and listen to The Throw-In podcast on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>What does benching Diarmuid Connolly say about Jim Gavin? - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/diarmuid-connolly-jim-gavin-136936</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJBOUwULD4wCI6EnPj3-kAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 15:52:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/diarmuid-connolly-jim-gavin-136936" target="_blank"&gt;What does benching Diarmuid Connolly say about Jim Gavin?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all the criticism Jim Gavin receives, nobody can question his managerial ability. The Round Towers Clondalkin man has won three All-Ireland titles in four years and in such a short space of time has already surpassed Kevin Heffernan as the greatest Dublin manager of all time. Hes done this by keeping everyone guessing, creating a system that is difficult to come up with a winning formula against, and keeping his squad motivated despite having achieved everything there is to achieve. For any Rick and Morty fans out there (spoiler alert on the latest episode), Evil Morty returns to the sh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>How to write GAA articles like Jim McGuinness and the week's best sportswriting - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/sportswriting-of-the-week-7-3530923-Aug2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFB5UhpMi9OpbzxZNkpluMwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 07:30:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/sportswriting-of-the-week-7-3530923-Aug2017/" target="_blank"&gt;How to write GAA articles like Jim McGuinness and the week's best sportswriting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Needless to remark, you were in Rome/Geneva/Disneyland Paris to meet some sporting luminary who has noticed you from afar like a lonely sheep farmer at a dance would long after a local maiden, and you spent several hours in their company exchanging stories of how insightful each of you are before you were ferried off to a conference on sports performance where some random (but very inspirational) non-athlete was the lead speaker. (E.g. Bear Grylls, Neil Armstrong or Grover from Sesame Street) Great minds like yours are often sparked into long rambling anecdotes by some small external age...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Ex-Donegal boss Rory Gallagher is back in inter-county management - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/exdonegal-boss-rory-gallagher-is-back-in-intercounty-management-36122627.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMCZjDQI-jCOZJDsymIYOdUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 20:21:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/exdonegal-boss-rory-gallagher-is-back-in-intercounty-management-36122627.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-Donegal boss Rory Gallagher is back in inter-county management&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rory Gallagher has been confirmed as the new manager of the Fermanagh senior footballers. The Fermanagh native has been a leading favourite to replace the ousted Pete McGrath with the Ernesiders since he parted ways with Donegal. Gallagher was a central member of the Jim McGuinness backroom team that masterminded an All-Ireland success in 2012. He took over the top job after McGuinness left to join Celtic. Gallagher had to deal with a number of high profile retirements and squad withdrawals in recent years. Donegal were heavily beaten by Tyrone in Ulster before exiting the championship in t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>New manager Bonner promises to change 'one-dimensional' Donegal - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/new-manager-bonner-promises-to-change-onedimensional-donegal-36160072.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDeozC1hfC2s00suxlH8dAAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/new-manager-bonner-promises-to-change-onedimensional-donegal-36160072.html" target="_blank"&gt;New manager Bonner promises to change 'one-dimensional' Donegal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Declan Bonner says he plans to change a 'one-dimensional' Donegal to stay competitive next year. Bonner was last night installed as the new Donegal manager, the 1992 All-Ireland winner returning to the role for a second time. The Lettermacaward man has been given a three-year term to take him to the end of the 2020 season. Last month, Rory Gallagher - who has since been appointed as Fermanagh manager - stepped down following a meek performance in a 4-17 to 0-14 qualifier defeat by Galway. "We have to expand and we have to change the way we play," Bonner said. "A lot of things will have to c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Donegal GAA confirm 'Banty' and Bonner among five in running for senior football role - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/sport/gaa/donegal-gaa-confirm-banty-and-bonner-among-five-in-running-for-senior-football-role-804202.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPgDH8_USFeDbvJLobcg90UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 12:30:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/sport/gaa/donegal-gaa-confirm-banty-and-bonner-among-five-in-running-for-senior-football-role-804202.html" target="_blank"&gt;Donegal GAA confirm 'Banty' and Bonner among five in running for senior football role&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donegal county board have released the names of the five candidates that are in the running to replace Rory Gallagher as manager of the senior football team, writes Ciara Phelan. Gallagher resigned at the start of August despite having a year remaining in his term as manager. Séamus “Banty” McEnaney and Declan Bonner are in the running for the role. The Fermanagh man had succeeded All-Ireland winning manager Jim McGuinness two years ago but Gallagher had a disappointing 2017 campaign. The five men in the race to become Gallagher's replacement are: Donegal's minor football manager Shaun Paul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Rory Gallagher named new Fermanagh manager - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0911/903952-rory-gallagher-named-new-fermanagh-manager/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN7dKwPGtIvhMptzWiswTvMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 04:28:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0911/903952-rory-gallagher-named-new-fermanagh-manager/" target="_blank"&gt;Rory Gallagher named new Fermanagh manager&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rory Gallagher has been ratified as the new football manager of his native Fermanagh, just over a month after resigning from his post with Donegal. Gallagher handed in his resignation with a year of his term left after Donegal were well beaten 4-17 to 0-14 by Galway in the final stage of the qualifiers. He succeeded All-Ireland-winning boss Jim McGuinness two years ago, but speculation had mounted regarding his future following a disappointing campaign, and he informed the county board of his decision to vacate the role. Now, he takes the reins of the Erne County, who parted ways with Pete ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Vote for your performance of the weekend - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/vote-performance-weekend-2-132963</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBixzjqWWFSUJJMZVyaN9xUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 20:27:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/vote-performance-weekend-2-132963" target="_blank"&gt;Vote for your performance of the weekend&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the weekend's football action may not have been as competitive as we would have hoped, but there were some individual performances of pure and utter class. Up to this weekend, some of the new teams on the block - the Armaghs, the Monaghans were making progress, but they were well and truly cut down to size by a rampant Tyrone, and a typically business-like Dublin. We now know three of our four All-Ireland semi-finalists, and you wouldn't have had too many predicting otherwise at the start of the year. Kerry, Tyrone and Dublin are the big three of the football landscape, and we will find ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Master tacticians to show their hand - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/master-tacticians-to-show-their-hand-36070565.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEASL6DYr2q6FMNiCS75EqkUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/master-tacticians-to-show-their-hand-36070565.html" target="_blank"&gt;Master tacticians to show their hand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Dublin's quarter-final against Monaghan coming up immediately afterwards, Jim Gavin would not have seen Tyrone humiliate Armagh in real time three weeks ago but you can take it that the TV footage was diced, spliced and presented to him by the following day. As Gavin and his acolytes watched it, the challenges facing them for today's game stacked up. For a start, they would have noticed how rarely Armagh were allowed work the ball into the high-probability scoring area around the 'D'. Four or five times? Even then, one of them came when a shot rebounded off a post. The scarcity of acti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Match programme's weight and height measures of players shows up surprising imbalance - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/match-programmes-weight-height-measures-players-shows-surprising-imbalance-132884</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFnL9v5XCB7EY4rSaQRdhiAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 14:38:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/match-programmes-weight-height-measures-players-shows-surprising-imbalance-132884" target="_blank"&gt;Match programme's weight and height measures of players shows up surprising imbalance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Size matters. The match programme for Tipperary and Galway's All-Ireland semi-final clash in Croke Park has told us one thing - these Tipperary lads will be up against it to match Galway's physicality. Tipperary's defensive problems, particularly in the full back line, have been well pronounced so far this year. There has been lots of chopping and changing in Tipperary's last line of defence, with Cathal Barrett being dropped from the panel, James Barry being moved out of full back and then drafted back in - stability has been lacking. For Galway it has been all plain sailing. The Tribesmen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Armagh advised to use bizarre shooting tactic against Tyrone that could be revolutionary - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/armagh-advised-to-use-bizarre-shooting-tactic-that-could-totally-change-the-game-132740</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECmRZhfOTXIdosLH-zvkTm8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 13:03:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/armagh-advised-to-use-bizarre-shooting-tactic-that-could-totally-change-the-game-132740" target="_blank"&gt;Armagh advised to use bizarre shooting tactic against Tyrone that could be revolutionary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Armagh are priced at 4/1 to trump Tyrone on Saturday, so in order to win the battle of Ulster, they'll need to be clever, they'll need to be smart, they'll need to surprise Mickey Harte. Tyrone have swept all before them in Ulster this year - playing with a less defensive style than we are used to seeing from them. Tiernan McCann claimed on The GAA Hour earlier in they year, however, that Tyrone alter their tactics, their use of defensive taggers on players based on their opposition. For example if they are playing Derry, like they were in the first round of Ulster this year, the game plan ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>McEnaney joins the race to be next Donegal manager - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0829/900702-mcenaney-joins-the-race-to-be-next-donegal-manager/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBwmqZFO80doi3EcEUiGevIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 11:49:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0829/900702-mcenaney-joins-the-race-to-be-next-donegal-manager/" target="_blank"&gt;McEnaney joins the race to be next Donegal manager&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seamus McEnaney is understood to have joined the race to be the next Donegal football manager. Rory Gallagher tendered his resignation with a year remaining in his term at the start of the month, following Donegal's 4-17 to 0-14 qualifier loss to Galway. The Fermanagh man took the reins from All-Ireland-winning manager Jim McGuinness two years ago, but speculation had been mounting regarding his future following a disappointing 2017 campaign, and he informed the county board of his decision to vacate the role. Now, the hunt for a new boss begins, and there are five names in the running. Dec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>'Jim Gavin became obsessed with blanket defences after Donegal shock' - Alan Brogan on Dublin-Tyrone - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/jim-gavin-became-obsessed-with-blanket-defences-after-donegal-shock-alan-brogan-on-dublintyrone-36015196.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJjpyVc_sD8nDEYO8dKmWKQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:09:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/jim-gavin-became-obsessed-with-blanket-defences-after-donegal-shock-alan-brogan-on-dublintyrone-36015196.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Jim Gavin became obsessed with blanket defences after Donegal shock' - Alan Brogan on Dublin-Tyrone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jim Gavin's last and only championship defeat as manager left a deep impression on the Dublin boss. Dublin's 3-14 to 0-16 point defeat to Donegal in the 2014 All-Ireland semi-final - Jim McGuinness's managerial masterpiece - left the Dublin supremo obsessed with the challenge of breaking down defensive minded teams. According to Alan Brogan, speaking to the Throw-In podcast on Independent.ie, Gavin is understandably confident on the rare occasions when Dublin face a team naive enough to take them on in a shootout. But it's strong, resourceful teams with a well organised defensive structur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Joe Canning's nephew has lit up Croke Park with the most outrageous score - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/joe-cannings-nephew-has-only-gone-and-lit-up-croke-park-132909</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBRgPO-wuJ8Mr-jZGTgp6OgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 14:18:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/joe-cannings-nephew-has-only-gone-and-lit-up-croke-park-132909" target="_blank"&gt;Joe Canning's nephew has lit up Croke Park with the most outrageous score&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, it's just in the genes. Jack Canning has been making tracks in the underage ranks of Galway hurling for quite some time now. The Portumna youngster, nephew of both Joe and Ollie, was on fire when the Tribesmen defeated Clare in the All-Ireland quarter final, notching 1-3 from open play. The eighteen-year-old was back at it again after just 30 seconds of Galway's All-Ireland minor semi-final against Kilkenny in Croke Park. Canning, who lined out at full forward for Jeffrey Lynskey's side, was sent in an inviting low ball as he made a diagonal run towards the sideline. His first to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>How Dublin's shock defeat to Donegal in 2014 changed Jim Gavin's football philosophy - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/jim-gavin-dublin-tyrone-3563200-Aug2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYNK3wMhbqJRYu8eDOTD8QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 17:31:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/jim-gavin-dublin-tyrone-3563200-Aug2017/" target="_blank"&gt;How Dublin's shock defeat to Donegal in 2014 changed Jim Gavin's football philosophy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DUBLIN’S ONLY CHAMPIONSHIP defeat under Jim Gavin came to Donegal in 2014 and it was a seminal moment in the evolution of the Metropolitans. Prior to that shock loss, Gavin had taken a more purist approach to the game. “We play the game with certain values in the squad and we play the game the way we believe it should be played,” he said after the 2013 final. But Jim McGuinness taught Gavin a lesson the following year, when his deep-lying defence drew Dublin into their web and hit them with devastating effect on the break. “I accept full responsibility for the philosophy and for the way Dub...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>QUIZ: Can you name every 2016 football All Star - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/quiz-can-name-every-2016-football-star-132917</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIupRvwnYgQn_OpKfUO4H1UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 14:13:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/quiz-can-name-every-2016-football-star-132917" target="_blank"&gt;QUIZ: Can you name every 2016 football All Star&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;15/15 is a must really. Ah, the All Star awards. They seem like only yesterday. Not much to this quiz, name all 15 players awarded with an All Star last year. 90 seconds is very generous but hey... If there are any problems playing the quiz you can also try it here. Jim McGuinness' Ulster bias, Stephen Cluxton in the changing room and massive weekend preview on The GAA Hour. Listen below or subscribe here on iTunes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>5 talking points after Tyrone swatted aside Armagh to book Dublin showdown - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/tyrone-armagh-talking-points-3532516-Aug2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFlH1OgvGF5r3VNl_WDzHm0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 19:47:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/tyrone-armagh-talking-points-3532516-Aug2017/" target="_blank"&gt;5 talking points after Tyrone swatted aside Armagh to book Dublin showdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Tyrone blitz their way into semi-finals TYRONE’S MARGIN OF victory was far easier than expected. They’ve blitzed their way through the competition so far in the championship, winning the four games by an average of 11.5 points to get to the last four of the All-Ireland series. It’s probably unfair to class Tyrone as a ‘defensive’ team. The Red Hand drop 14 bodies behind the ball when they don’t have possession, but they attack with real intent when they turn it over. Much of the talk around their All-Ireland credentials surrounds the absence of a marquee forward, but scores of 0-22, 1-21...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Mattie Donnelly's stats should scare the shit out of Dublin - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/mattie-donnelly-stats-132806</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFp7Dsr3-jnlKsR7yajAKQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 17:58:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/mattie-donnelly-stats-132806" target="_blank"&gt;Mattie Donnelly's stats should scare the shit out of Dublin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;70 minutes of all-action. 70 minutes of Mattie Donnelly that should have the champions sitting up and taking notice. Tyrone are more than just a system and far more than just athleticism. They have some of the finest, most effortless footballers in the country and despite everyone labelling them a defensive team, they've racked up 6-77 over four games in the championship so far, winning them by a combined total of 46 points. On Sunday against Armagh - their most comprehensive victory to date - you could've picked out any of them for special attention. You could've looked at Colm Cavanagh an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Race For Sam: The 4 teams bidding for All-Ireland football glory - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/race-for-sam-maguire-3550252-Aug2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENyOqmqgIJQo3s6sCxj1j-sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/race-for-sam-maguire-3550252-Aug2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Race For Sam: The 4 teams bidding for All-Ireland football glory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kerry Their recent semi-final history involves… a great deal of success. You have to go all the way back to Tyrone in 2003 to find the last team outside of Dublin to beat Kerry in an All-Ireland semi-final. The Dubs evicted Kerry in the last four of 2016 and ’13, but they did enjoy victories at this stage over Tyrone in ’15 and Mayo after a replay in ’14. The player they cannot do without is…Paul Geaney. The Dingle poacher didn’t set the world alight against Galway, but Kerry will need him to perform close to his optimum on Sunday against a talented Mayo rearguard. Geaney dispatched 1-5 in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>If Dean Rock wasn't as deadly at frees he'd be getting the praise he damn well deserves - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/if-dean-rock-wasnt-as-deadly-at-frees-hed-be-getting-the-praise-he-damn-well-deserves-132826</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVMMb0qxw8Q0SjUdSCIK8UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 18:54:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/if-dean-rock-wasnt-as-deadly-at-frees-hed-be-getting-the-praise-he-damn-well-deserves-132826" target="_blank"&gt;If Dean Rock wasn't as deadly at frees he'd be getting the praise he damn well deserves&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dean Rock is one of the most consistent performers in the game. The Ballymun Kickhams club man has ice running through his veins standing over a dead ball, and his prowess and unerring accuracy from frees is unrivalled by any other footballer in the GAA. Rock's precision and razor sharp accuracy from the deck is a major facet of his game - but he's often the victim of just how good he is at frees. How often do we hear people saying that Rock wouldn't be on this Dublin team were it not for his frees? Not only is that argument self defeating based on the fact that scoring these frees is so im...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Joe Brolly: Fasten your seatbelts as two superpowers collide in All Ireland semi-final - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/columnists/joe-brolly/joe-brolly-fasten-your-seatbelts-as-two-superpowers-collide-in-all-ireland-semifinal-36072425.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELPppfOQt3omR1neJSTqkD4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 13:00:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/columnists/joe-brolly/joe-brolly-fasten-your-seatbelts-as-two-superpowers-collide-in-all-ireland-semifinal-36072425.html" target="_blank"&gt;Joe Brolly: Fasten your seatbelts as two superpowers collide in All Ireland semi-final&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tyrone are the least-loved, most-feared team in the game and Mickey Harte will be happy with that. "Ruthless man, very ruthless man," said Owen Mulligan during the week, looking back on his own decapitation from the squad. "Mickey never even rung me, which hurt me a lot." The leader must be right, or the team cannot succeed. He may be infuriating, stubborn to the death, self-righteous, blinkered, even suffering from a touch of megalomania. But he is a leader that moulds hard, ruthless teams. The thing I have liked about Tyrone this year (and it's not their style of play), is the way they ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Mac Niallais masterclass puts Gweedore into first Ulster final - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/mac-niallais-masterclass-puts-gweedore-into-first-ulster-final-37541614.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHbsL3OhUqdH57XiykJJTEwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/mac-niallais-masterclass-puts-gweedore-into-first-ulster-final-37541614.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mac Niallais masterclass puts Gweedore into first Ulster final&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Youth and experience are pretty useful commodities in the club championship and Gweedore made the most of both ends of the age spectrum to advance to a first AIB Ulster Club SFC final. Backboned by 10 players who won the Ulster U-21 championship in February, and wily old foxes like Neil and Eamon McGee and Kevin Cassidy, the Donegal champions are on one hell of a journey this year and took out one of the competition's aristocrats in convincing fashion in Healy Park yesterday. A first-half hat-trick by Daire ó Baoill, a great second half from Cassidy and a superb afternoon's work by Odhrán M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Ó Baoill hat-trick steers Gaoth Dobhair past Crossmaglen into first Ulster final - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/gaoth-dobhair-beat-crossmaglen-ulster-sfc-4346333-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKqQ2FNTvJQ69XXG2Tsy_BQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 19:05:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/gaoth-dobhair-beat-crossmaglen-ulster-sfc-4346333-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Ó Baoill hat-trick steers Gaoth Dobhair past Crossmaglen into first Ulster final&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gaoth Dobhair 4-11 Crossmaglen Rangers 0-16 Declan Bogue reports from Healy Park, Omagh FOR THE FIRST time ever, Gaoth Dobhair have made it to an Ulster club final where they will meet Monaghan’s Scotstown. And any questions of their credentials in this first foray into Ulster were met with an emphatic trouncing of Crossmaglen Rangers, who simply had no answer to the Donegal men’s slick passing game and their ability to expose the long-established practice of Cross playing a traditional-type game. Three first-half goals from Dáire Ó Baoill brought them into a nine-point lead after 25 minute...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Former members of Donegal and Mayo set-ups join Sligo backroom team - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/joe-keane-adam-speer-sligo-coaching-staff-4312948-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF5e1SC10M5yqf5G9wcUdU4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 15:23:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/joe-keane-adam-speer-sligo-coaching-staff-4312948-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Former members of Donegal and Mayo set-ups join Sligo backroom team&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW SLIGO MANAGER Paul Taylor has confirmed his backroom team for the 2019 campaign with former members of the Mayo and Donegal set-ups coming on board. Crossmolina native Joe Keane joins Sligo as coach/selector, while Donegal’s Adam Speer will operate as strength and conditioning coach and former Sligo player John MacPartland has been appointed selector. Keane has been involved with the Mayo U21s and seniors in recent years, leaving the county set-up after Stephen Rochford’s departure as manager in August. Speer previously worked under Jim McGuinness in Donegal, while MacPartland was invol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Jim McGuinness ‘definitely’ won’t take Mayo job - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/gaa/jim-mcguinness-definitely-wont-take-mayo-job-865844.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHefQ5vNxcfM5fHNWBcWln4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 07:41:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/gaa/jim-mcguinness-definitely-wont-take-mayo-job-865844.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jim McGuinness ‘definitely’ won’t take Mayo job&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jim McGuinness will not be the next Mayo football manager, with the 2012 All-Ireland winning Donegal boss ruling himself out of the running to succeed Stephen Rochford. When asked at yesterday evening’s Off The Ball All-Ireland preview event at Croke Park if he was interested in returning to inter-county management, McGuinness replied: “Not at the moment, definitely not.” McGuinness, who left his assistant coach role at Chinese club Beijing Sinobo Guoan in January, is committed to soccer for the immediate future. I am on a journey, really. I have come back and finished my badges. I’m ready ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Jim McGuinness not interested in Mayo role - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/0830/990626-jim-mcguinness-not-interested-in-mayo-role/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2x5bQWrUc-V6XLRLXFBOQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 19:58:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/0830/990626-jim-mcguinness-not-interested-in-mayo-role/" target="_blank"&gt;Jim McGuinness not interested in Mayo role&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jim McGuinness has ruled himself out of the running for the vacant Mayo senior football managerial hotseat, insisting that he is not looking for a return to GAA management. On Monday Stephen Rochford announced his resignation from the Mayo job, bringing an end his three-year reign after a stand-off with the county's Executive Committee. McGuinness and James Horan have been among those linked with replacing Rochford, but the former Donegal does not appear to be keen. Speaking at Newstalk's All-Ireland preview at Croke Park, the All-Ireland winning boss was asked if he was interested in the r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Soccer-focused Jim McGuinness says he's not interested in Mayo job - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/jim-mcguinness-james-horan-mayo-football-job-4211202-Aug2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAxJQ6R0s8W3hX79UpduYZoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 20:10:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/jim-mcguinness-james-horan-mayo-football-job-4211202-Aug2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Soccer-focused Jim McGuinness says he's not interested in Mayo job&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JIM MCGUINNESS HAS insisted that he’s not interested in a return to GAA management at the minute, effectively ruling himself out of the running for the vacant Mayo job. Stephen Rochford announced that he was stepping down from his role as Mayo senior football manager on Monday, ending his three-year stint at the helm. And Donegal’s All-Ireland winning manager in 2012 McGuinness was one name immediately linked with the job. But at tonight’s Off The Ball All-Ireland preview at Croke Park, he ruled out the possibility of a return to inter-county management, stating that his immediate future is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Who's in the frame to become the next Mayo senior football boss? - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/mayo-new-manager-contenders-4204815-Aug2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPqrR4Two8X7Y-uO0HoNW8EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 07:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/mayo-new-manager-contenders-4204815-Aug2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Who's in the frame to become the next Mayo senior football boss?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE ALL-IRELAND football final is only days away but Stephen Rochford’s decision to step down as Mayo boss will dominate the news agenda over the next 48 hours as the county begin their search for a replacement. Source: James Crombie/INPHO Few details around his departure have emerged as of yet, but in a statement released this evening Rochford said a lack of support from the county board’s executive committee led to his resignation. Rochford’s appointment in December 2015 arrived on the back of a player heave against joint-managers Pat Holmes and Noel Connelly. He led the county to narrow ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>'It's disappointing for the players' - Lee Keegan has his say on Stephen Rochford's decision to quit Mayo - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/its-disappointing-for-the-players-lee-keegan-has-his-say-on-stephen-rochfords-decision-to-quit-mayo-37266619.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL4FQ5BeyM-RJbqOehcjeCAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 09:23:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/its-disappointing-for-the-players-lee-keegan-has-his-say-on-stephen-rochfords-decision-to-quit-mayo-37266619.html" target="_blank"&gt;'It's disappointing for the players' - Lee Keegan has his say on Stephen Rochford's decision to quit Mayo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Keegan has said the Mayo players were left "shocked" when they heard manager Stephen Rochford had stepped down. Rochford confirmed his departure from the 2017 All Ireland runners up on Monday because he felt he did not have adequate support from the county board. Mayo officials last night confirmed they have set up a committee to lead the hunt for a new manager with former boss James Horan the favourite to take over. Speaking on OffTheBallAM this morning, Keegan insisted Rochford owes the county nothing after his three years in charge when he twice brought the Dubs all the way in the Al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Mayo play waiting game - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/mayo-play-waiting-game-37262118.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDwQVG0YqTyoTVmXQ30ut5sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/gaelic-football/mayo-play-waiting-game-37262118.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mayo play waiting game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The likelihood of Jim McGuinness making a sensational return to inter-county management with Mayo looks slim as last year's All-Ireland finalists are set to play the waiting game with their next senior boss. Stephen Rochford's shock resignation on Monday evening after three years in charge has left a massive void but it is understood that no knee-jerk reactions will be made to fill the high-profile post. McGuinness has been linked to the job - as he was in Cavan and with the Galway United manager's role - having guided Donegal to All-Ireland success in 2012, but it is understood that his at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item></channel></rss>