<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>General practitioner - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyY3ZNVEl3ZG0xNVgyd1NBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:50:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Doctors to hold EGM over abortion service concerns - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/health/2018/1130/1014279-abortion-services/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPy50pKvwJsoAj45G4EeXYwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 08:01:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/health/2018/1130/1014279-abortion-services/" target="_blank"&gt;Doctors to hold EGM over abortion service concerns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concerns over how abortion services will be introduced in Ireland have prompted the Irish College of General Practitioners to convene an Extraordinary General ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>GP out-of-hours surgeries to be 'exempt from abortions' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/gp-outofhours-surgeries-to-be-exempt-from-abortions-37606269.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPfGZ-0emFSo4GQtwF-YKI0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/gp-outofhours-surgeries-to-be-exempt-from-abortions-37606269.html" target="_blank"&gt;GP out-of-hours surgeries to be 'exempt from abortions'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women will not be able to secure a medical abortion from GP out-of-hours surgeries, the Irish Independent has learned. The GP service, which provides medical cover from 6pm to 8am, has become the first port of call for an increasing number of patients due to a shortage of doctors. Dr Ken Egan, chairman of the National Association of GP Co-ops, said a woman seeking an abortion would not be classified as an emergency which is the service out-of-hours doctors provide. However, he said they will treat women who have had an abortion and develop complications. "We wrote to the Irish College of Ge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>One in five patients waits two weeks to see a GP, finds report - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/07/one-in-five-patients-now-waits-at-least-two-weeks-to-see-a-gp-finds-report</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPMOfcmHRPN7Qvf3dVpjkvoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:40:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/07/one-in-five-patients-now-waits-at-least-two-weeks-to-see-a-gp-finds-report" target="_blank"&gt;One in five patients waits two weeks to see a GP, finds report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One in five patients now has to wait at least 15 days to see a GP in England, NHS figures have revealed. Just under 5m of the 27.1m appointments at GPs’ surgeries in October involved waiting anywhere between 15 and 28 or more days to see a doctor or practice nurse. That was almost one in five (18.3%) of the total consultations available, NHS Digital figures showed. The publication of the figures – the first of their kind ever issued by the NHS – have prompted renewed concern about how the rising demand for care and shortage of GPs are forcing patients to wait much longer than before for an ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>One in 10 patients waits 3 weeks to see their GP, new figures show - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/one-10-patients-waits-3-weeks-see-gp-new-figures-show/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFG8BXByao-bWGnou9MjU-kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:33:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/one-10-patients-waits-3-weeks-see-gp-new-figures-show/" target="_blank"&gt;One in 10 patients waits 3 weeks to see their GP, new figures show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One in ten patients is waiting at least three weeks to see their GP, new figures show. The monthly data, published for the first time, shows that in October 2.8 million people secured an appointment more than 21 days after seeking it. They included 1.4 million people who saw a doctor four weeks after trying to arrange a consultation. Every day, around 1 million people see a GP in England, the figures show. The statistics also show that one in twenty patients failed to turn up after making an appointment. Health | Latest newsNhs at 70 people per nurses and doctors The figures, which cover th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Eilish O'Regan: 'Moving the deckchairs on the Titanic' is unlikely to help ease the trolley crisis' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/eilish-oregan-moving-the-deckchairs-on-the-titanic-is-unlikely-to-help-ease-the-trolley-crisis-37603320.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENVb2HITvqbTM-u9CHU_s6IqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/eilish-oregan-moving-the-deckchairs-on-the-titanic-is-unlikely-to-help-ease-the-trolley-crisis-37603320.html" target="_blank"&gt;Eilish O'Regan: 'Moving the deckchairs on the Titanic' is unlikely to help ease the trolley crisis'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moving patients from one hospital struggling with A&amp;E chaos to a bed in another hospital which is under less strain will have undoubted benefits. But this latest addition to the HSE's winter-plan menu will not make up for the lack of beds in overcrowded hospitals, as the worst weeks of the trolley crisis loom. It was likened by one doctor as "moving the deckchairs on Titanic". The HSE is pinning much on this new system of allowing each hospital to access real-time data to help ease overcrowding. Each hospital with the available technology will be able to see another's figures on the numbers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>'Send trolley patients off to less busy hospitals' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/send-trolley-patients-off-to-less-busy-hospitals-37603265.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMo2EMUZyuRtNCRmCNBxSFUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/send-trolley-patients-off-to-less-busy-hospitals-37603265.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Send trolley patients off to less busy hospitals'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients who are suffering long waits on A&amp;E trolleys during the worst weeks of overcrowding may be moved to another hospital which is less busy as part of the HSE's winter plan. The delayed €30m plan, which was finally unveiled yesterday, comes as hospital emergency services are braced for the post-Christmas and new year influx of patients, which caused record trolley gridlock last winter. For the first time, each hospital will have an insider's view of how other hospitals are performing with electronic dashboards giving real-time data on how many patients are on trolleys, waiting times, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>HSE urged not to drag cancer victims to court - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/hse-urged-not-to-drag-cancer-victims-to-court-37603317.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJoY692xiesoFKcHzty7CQAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/hse-urged-not-to-drag-cancer-victims-to-court-37603317.html" target="_blank"&gt;HSE urged not to drag cancer victims to court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The HSE has been urged to agree to early mediation talks for terminally or seriously ill patients caught up in the X-ray and scan failures in University Hospital Kerry. Padraig O'Connell, a Killarney solicitor who is representing a number of victims, said they had been treated very badly by health authorities. He was speaking after a report revealed that a review of 46,234 diagnostic procedures overseen by a locum consultant in the hospital found 11 patients who were wrongly given the all-clear suffered a delayed diagnosis of cancer. Four of the patients have now died and others are serious...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>'It is going to benefit patients hugely' - Reilly opens primary care facility at centre of 2012 row - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/it-is-going-to-benefit-patients-hugely-reilly-opens-primary-care-facility-at-centre-of-2012-row-37599100.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMyT88U82MxQII8s3rlNz8YqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:44:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/it-is-going-to-benefit-patients-hugely-reilly-opens-primary-care-facility-at-centre-of-2012-row-37599100.html" target="_blank"&gt;'It is going to benefit patients hugely' - Reilly opens primary care facility at centre of 2012 row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former health minister Dr James Reilly has defended his role in the opening of a controversial new Primary Care Centre in his constituency, saying his efforts have shown results. The €10m facility in Balbriggan was at the centre of a 2012 row after it was among a number of late additions to a HSE priority list. Dr Reilly said he wants to leave the controversy in the past, adding it is important locals take ownership of the facility. “It is nice to see concrete results from efforts you've made,” he said. “I watched the facility going up over the last number of years and it is a very impressi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>‘I tried to take my own life. They told me I’d have to wait a month for help’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/05/take-own-life-young-people-mental-health-services</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOL8TQmp1yUilH299wNt2r0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:00:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/05/take-own-life-young-people-mental-health-services" target="_blank"&gt;‘I tried to take my own life. They told me I’d have to wait a month for help’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The word “crisis” comes up a lot whenever children and young people’s mental health is mentioned. Whether it’s youngsters in desperate need of acute care being sent hundreds of miles away for treatment due to local bed shortages, failure to receive help even after their GP has referred them for specialist care, or enduring problems with NHS child and adolescent mental health services (Camhs), patients under 18 find it increasingly difficult to access the support they need. Related: Young people’s mental health is a ‘worsening crisis’. Action is needed | Mary O’Hara Today, for the first time...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>GPs: Huge amount to be done by abortion deadline - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/gps-huge-amount-to-be-done-by-abortion-deadline-889661.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB6JaSLPKjtvjcwTZnBa3GkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/gps-huge-amount-to-be-done-by-abortion-deadline-889661.html" target="_blank"&gt;GPs: Huge amount to be done by abortion deadline&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Family doctors have “yet to see the evidence” that systems will be in place to allow the delivery of an abortion service from January 1, according to the vice-president of the Irish Irish College of General Practitioners. Mary Favier, a Cork-based GP, said it was “an exceptionally demanding deadline”. “It’s a deadline constructed by the minister [Simon Harris] and it’s his deadline. There is a huge amount to be put in place, such as referral pathways. “The minister has assured us it will happen, but we have yet to see the evidence. We are concerned.” Dr Favier said introducing an abortion s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Abortion pill approved for the first time - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/abortion-pill-approved-for-first-time-889664.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEpmo6pNcROLWcJWL3Ep5XAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 06:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/abortion-pill-approved-for-first-time-889664.html" target="_blank"&gt;Abortion pill approved for the first time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first ever abortion pill has been approved for use in Ireland. The Health Products Regulatory Authority (HPRA) confirmed to the Irish Examiner last night that it has “received and approved Mifepristone for termination of pregnancy”. The tablet was authorised on November 30. The tablet is taken as a single 600 mg oral dose, followed 36 to 48 hours later by the administration of prostaglandin analogue. The Nordic Group BV, with an address in the Netherlands, is listed by the HPRA as the marketing authorisation holder. The Irish Examiner asked if the HPRA was confident that the company wil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Four out of 10 cancer patients initially misdiagnosed, finds report warning of pressures in testing - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/cancer-diagnosis-missed-gp-referral-testing-treatment-report-nhs-a8665636.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4E3v3oMTCEI0a-oLk_Z1YqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 07:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/cancer-diagnosis-missed-gp-referral-testing-treatment-report-nhs-a8665636.html" target="_blank"&gt;Four out of 10 cancer patients initially misdiagnosed, finds report warning of pressures in testing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four out of ten people with cancer in the UK are misdiagnosed at least once before their disease is identified, according to a report calling for more investment in early testing. The report, by the All.Can cancer initiative, warns that one in five (21 per cent) of UK patients surveyed said they waited more than six months to get the correct diagnosis. This failure to provide a quick, accurate diagnosis is costing patients their lives and the NHS money, the group warns. Though the NHS and government have targeted earlier diagnosis, successive reports have found the UK is lagging behind othe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Update: Obstetricians, hospitals and GPs 'will not be ready' to provide abortions in January - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/dept-orders-hse-to-ensure-abortions-available-from-january-889436.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDBQ8sZypp3kjw5LJMLOddQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/dept-orders-hse-to-ensure-abortions-available-from-january-889436.html" target="_blank"&gt;Update: Obstetricians, hospitals and GPs 'will not be ready' to provide abortions in January&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Update 10.58am: Obstetricians, hospitals and general practitioners are not going to be ready to provide abortion services on January 1, 2019, says a GP who specialises in gynaecology and paediatrics. There are not enough details available yet on the proposed helpline or the website, Dr Illona Duffy told RTE’s Today with Sean O’Rourke show. Dr Duffy was responding to a walkout by a number of doctors yesterday at a meeting of GPs to discuss concerns about the provision of abortion. More than 300 members of the Irish College of General Practitioners attended the three-hour extraordinary genera...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>GPs should prescribe protein powders and strength training to elderly, say experts - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/04/gps-should-prescribe-protein-powders-strength-training-elderly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI-o9nhJEdTIKevRzIrjDp4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/04/gps-should-prescribe-protein-powders-strength-training-elderly/" target="_blank"&gt;GPs should prescribe protein powders and strength training to elderly, say experts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GPs should prescribe protein powders and weight lifting to pensioners to help reverse frailty, health experts have recommended. Increases in life expectancy have led to rising numbers of frail elderly people and it is estimated that one in 10 people suffers with infirmity, rising to half of those over 80. In the new study, published in the British Journal of General Practice, researchers from University College Dublin conducted a systematic review on studies on frailty interventions. They identified 46 studies in which 15,690 people were asked to take part in either exercise programmes, hea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Reilly seeks extra resources for €10m care centre that 'caused controversy' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/reilly-seeks-extra-resources-for-10m-care-centre-that-caused-controversy-37592512.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELOC4mnnjFFoR8VfgpOgNH8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/reilly-seeks-extra-resources-for-10m-care-centre-that-caused-controversy-37592512.html" target="_blank"&gt;Reilly seeks extra resources for €10m care centre that 'caused controversy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former health minister James Reilly is to officially open a primary care centre in the heart of his constituency that caused controversy during his term in office. The selection of Balbriggan for the €10m facility caused uproar in 2012 after it was among a number of late additions to a HSE priority list. The ensuing row contributed to the resignation of Mr Reilly's then-junior health minister, Róisín Shortall. Ahead of the opening, Mr Reilly told the Irish Independent he is now lobbying his successor, Simon Harris, to provide funding for extra services including X-ray and ultrasound equipme...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Thousands won't have access to scan of baby - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/thousands-wont-have-access-to-scan-of-baby-37592526.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFxytplADmOvH2JhJ554v4sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/thousands-wont-have-access-to-scan-of-baby-37592526.html" target="_blank"&gt;Thousands won't have access to scan of baby&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of expectant mothers will still be without routine access to a 20-week pregnancy scan to tell them if their baby had a fatal foetal abnormality as the Government prepares to implement abortion legislation. The legislation liberalising abortion may be in place next month and will include a provision to allow termination for a pregnant woman who is told her unborn baby has a diagnosed fatal foetal abnormality and will not survive. But five maternity hospitals still do not provide a routine scan around 20 weeks into the pregnancy to diagnose an anomaly. It will be next year before al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>GP convicted of running illegal transgender clinic for children - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/03/gp-convicted-running-illegal-transgender-clinic-children/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEONubs33cUl5CtJTu16y9gwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:52:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/03/gp-convicted-running-illegal-transgender-clinic-children/" target="_blank"&gt;GP convicted of running illegal transgender clinic for children&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A GP has been convicted of running an illegal transgender clinic, providing hormones to children as young as 12 despite being refused a licence by the NHS regulator. Dr Helen Webberley, 49, ran the clinic from her home, treating children who wanted to change sex, charging between £75 and £150 an hour. She also provided online advice, calling herself the Gender GP, prescribing children and teenagers who had been denied treatment on the NHS. Webberley’s clinic was last year refused a license to operate by watchdog Healthcare Inspectorate Wales (HIW), Merthyr Tydfil Magistrates Court heard. Bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Abortion services crisis as GPs walk out - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/abortion-services-crisis-as-gps-walk-out-889424.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECcbwWsoQ4Zs8XiKxbD78fcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 06:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/abortion-services-crisis-as-gps-walk-out-889424.html" target="_blank"&gt;Abortion services crisis as GPs walk out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prospect of women being able to access abortion services in Ireland in just four weeks’ time is looking increasingly uncertain following the escalation of a row between family doctors and their training body — and the snail’s pace at which the proposed legislation is moving through the Dáil. An extraordinary general meeting of the Irish College of General Practitioners (ICGP) held at the behest of members was thrown into disarray yesterday when dozens of doctors walked out in protest that their views were not being taken onboard ahead of the January 1 deadline for the introduction of ab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Proton beam failure leaves hundreds of child cancer patients at risk - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/02/proton-beam-failure-leaves-hundreds-child-cancer-patients-risk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPqMdujBe6Y9Ndao3rbFkMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/02/proton-beam-failure-leaves-hundreds-child-cancer-patients-risk/" target="_blank"&gt;Proton beam failure leaves hundreds of child cancer patients at risk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of children with cancer are resorting to inferior treatment because of a failure to open two flagship specialist centres, experts have warned. NHS officials have admitted that no patient has yet received state-of-the-art proton beam therapy (PBT) at either its new London or Manchester sites, despite a Government pledge to be treating 1,500 a year by 2018. Leading oncologists have called for transparency after two promised opening dates at The Christie NHS Foundation Trust were missed this year and the deadline quietly pushed back. The centre represents the best hope for more than t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>GP surgery closures 'will see 3 million patients lose out in the next year' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/02/gp-surgery-closures-will-see-3-million-patients-lose-next-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBYfXxyjUovUew-gwt2kJSkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 12:11:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/02/gp-surgery-closures-will-see-3-million-patients-lose-next-year/" target="_blank"&gt;GP surgery closures 'will see 3 million patients lose out in the next year'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GP surgery closures will see 3 million patients lose out in the next year, according to a survey by the Royal College of Practitioners. A total of five per cent of GPs reported their practice was likely to close within the next year - equating to over 350 practices in the UK. It comes amid widespread concern over the ability to fill roles in the sector as more and more GPs retire early or move to work in the private sector. The poll of GPs found more than a third (37 per cent) of vacancies in their practice had been open for more than three months. The results were described as "gravely con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>GPs holding EGM over concerns about introduction to abortion services - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/gps-holding-egm-over-concerns-about-introduction-to-abortion-services-37586342.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHEUCI2Fak-00v71HtOVQ8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 10:54:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/gps-holding-egm-over-concerns-about-introduction-to-abortion-services-37586342.html" target="_blank"&gt;GPs holding EGM over concerns about introduction to abortion services&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GPs are holding an Extraordinary General Meeting today over their concerns about the introduction to abortion services. Hundreds are worried about the upcoming GP-led service and are concerned about how they will manage the extra workload. Others have said they will not provide the service due to their personal beliefs. The Irish College of General Practitioners (ICGP), the professional and training body for family doctors, said the purpose of the meeting is to listen to the members' concerns and to consult on the issue. It is understood 650 GPs signed the EGM petition. Writing on Twitter a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>World AIDS Day: How to get yourself checked for HIV - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/world-aids-day-check-your-status-hiv-test-nhs-home-kit-a8659056.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGJdtocbMyThHoUDVoVvX4wqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/world-aids-day-check-your-status-hiv-test-nhs-home-kit-a8659056.html" target="_blank"&gt;World AIDS Day: How to get yourself checked for HIV&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right now there are more than 100 ,000 people in the UK living with human immunodeficiency virus (HIV), the incurable illness that damages the cells in the immune system, making it harder for your body to fight everyday infections. Acquired immune deficiency syndrome (AIDS) is the name given to describe the potentially life-threatening infections that can happen as a result of an immune system that has been damaged by the HIV virus and early diagnosis is crucial to prevent these from developing. To mark World AIDS Day, which takes place on Saturday and aims to encourage people to get tested...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Up to 50 GPs walk out of meeting over concerns about new abortion legislation - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/up-to-50-gps-walk-out-of-meeting-over-concerns-about-new-abortion-legislation-37586819.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED7iFWHwYUGDo18GIAtNuPgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 17:41:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/up-to-50-gps-walk-out-of-meeting-over-concerns-about-new-abortion-legislation-37586819.html" target="_blank"&gt;Up to 50 GPs walk out of meeting over concerns about new abortion legislation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A row has broken out between GPs over the Government’s proposed abortion law. Up to 50 GPs walked out of a meeting of family doctors in Dublin this afternoon to discuss concerns about how the new abortion service will operate on the ground. The doctors left the meeting of the Irish College of General Practitioners (ICGP), the professional and training body for doctors, which was convened to discuss the abortion service, saying their voices were not heard. Following the walk out, the group said “several hundred GPs have totally lost confidence in the ICGP board” and that “a serious crisis no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Millions could lose GP next year as staff shortages and stress force doctors to close surgeries, study claims - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/doctor-shortages-nhs-gp-surgery-closed-england-figures-number-stress-a8663536.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGxNAUAoSMRFvvmQXbJggboqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 14:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/doctor-shortages-nhs-gp-surgery-closed-england-figures-number-stress-a8663536.html" target="_blank"&gt;Millions could lose GP next year as staff shortages and stress force doctors to close surgeries, study claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Millions of patients could lose their GP surgery within the next 12 months as factors such as stress contribute to a shortage of doctors, a new study has warned. More than 350 practices in England alone could face closure within a year as doctors quit the profession over working conditions, according to a new survey by the Royal College of General Practitioners (RSGP). In its study of 1,094 doctors across England, the RCGP found almost a third said they would not be working in general practice in five years, with stress and retirement cited as the most common reasons. A total of 37 per cent...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Breast cancer survivors complain screening letters force them to relive mastectomy trauma - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/01/breast-cancer-survivors-complain-screening-letters-force-relive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPjVD-XQFelJrFfB1qUitCgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 20:20:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/01/breast-cancer-survivors-complain-screening-letters-force-relive/" target="_blank"&gt;Breast cancer survivors complain screening letters force them to relive mastectomy trauma&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breast cancer survivors have complained that screening letters are forcing them to relive the trauma of their battle. Women who have had double mastectomies to remove the disease have said they are still receiving invitations for mammograms, even though they have do not need to be screened. Now, charities are calling on the NHS to better link its IT systems in order to prevent the distress. The NHS system automatically posts letters to British women between the ages of 50 and 70 who are registered to a GP to invite them for regular breast screenings, including the time and date of the appoi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>More than 40 GPs walk out of abortion services meeting - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/more-than-40-gps-walk-out-of-abortion-services-meeting-4371678-Dec2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI_F_tjeImOfR7z7T8-KrsEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 18:22:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/more-than-40-gps-walk-out-of-abortion-services-meeting-4371678-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;More than 40 GPs walk out of abortion services meeting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT LEAST 40 GPs have walked out of an Extraordinary General Meeting of the Irish College of General Practitioners (ICGP) in Malahide this afternoon over the issue of conscientious objection to abortion services. The meeting was being held ahead of the introduction of abortion services in January. The group who walked out had wanted a vote on a series of motions but were refused that request. Over 300 doctors attended today’s meeting in the Grand Hotel in Malahide at which a number of doctors left after 30 minutes, objecting to the official procedure of the meeting. Members of the College - ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Benefits of economic recovery yet to trickle down to deprived areas, new report reveals - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/benefits-of-economic-recovery-yet-to-trickle-down-to-deprived-areas-new-report-reveals-37582674.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPMelSR5UNrBKyHnNwDwtx0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 18:03:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/benefits-of-economic-recovery-yet-to-trickle-down-to-deprived-areas-new-report-reveals-37582674.html" target="_blank"&gt;Benefits of economic recovery yet to trickle down to deprived areas, new report reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The benefits of the economic recovery have yet to trickle down to many deprived areas and improve the mental health of the least well off, it emerged today. A new report on Tallaght – the sprawling suburb in south west Dublin- has found 66pc of people in deprived housing estates experienced stress over the last 12 months. This compared to 55pc in the better off estates. The report 'Physical and Mental Health in Post-Recession Ireland: A Community Study from Tallaght, Dublin' was commissioned by the Meath Foundation and presented at the annual Meath Research Symposium at Tallaght Universit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>NHS chiefs look to scrap four-hour A&amp;E maximum wait - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/02/nhs-four-hour-maximum-wait-patients-minor-ailments-miss-out</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENXGtOW9acuOh99CUfbVaNUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 08:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/02/nhs-four-hour-maximum-wait-patients-minor-ailments-miss-out" target="_blank"&gt;NHS chiefs look to scrap four-hour A&amp;E maximum wait&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NHS bosses are considering a shake-up of A&amp;E care that could lead to patients with only minor ailments no longer being guaranteed that they will be treated within four hours. Under the plans being examined, people with non-urgent medical needs would be advised to seek help at a GP surgery, walk-in centre or pharmacy instead – or face a long wait in A&amp;E. Senior figures in the NHS are also looking at bringing in extra targets to complement the four-hour waiting time standard under which the most urgent cases are seen within an hour. Sources close to NHS England’s development of its forthcomin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Women with abnormal smears face nine-month wait for help - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/women-with-abnormal-smears-face-ninemonth-wait-for-help-37583679.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAUnHARgbGR-yTrYsnF-5cEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/women-with-abnormal-smears-face-ninemonth-wait-for-help-37583679.html" target="_blank"&gt;Women with abnormal smears face nine-month wait for help&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some women who undergo cervical screening and have abnormalities can wait up to nine months for investigation, the Irish Independent has learned. Swamped clinics, where women who have an abnormal smear test result under CervicalCheck are referred to for examination, are now in some cases taking three to four months to provide appointments. It has already been revealed that pressure on laboratories servicing CervicalCheck has left thousands of women who have a test waiting up to five months for return of their result. It means a woman can wait five months for a test result - and then another...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Fears rise that abortion rollout will be delayed by Dáil debates - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/fears-rise-that-abortion-rollout-will-be-delayed-by-dil-debates-37580585.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENWOg2xpmaARlRZFHkl8TOYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/fears-rise-that-abortion-rollout-will-be-delayed-by-dil-debates-37580585.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fears rise that abortion rollout will be delayed by Dáil debates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The abortion legislation faces further debate at report stage in the Dáil next week, piling pressure on the January deadline for services. The legislation is making its way through the Houses of the Oireachtas and despite hopes that the report stage would conclude last night after three days of debate it will return to the Dáil floor next week. Some 65 amendments have been proposed to the legislation, sparking lengthy debate. A number of amendments were defeated last night including one proposing that abortions are not sought on grounds of race, sex or disability and another provision seeki...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Non-urgent cases should avoid A&amp;E as long waits 'inevitable', warns Harris - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/nonurgent-cases-should-avoid-ae-as-long-waits-inevitable-warns-harris-37587751.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPTkF9PsNPiCJapdolj9PLoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/nonurgent-cases-should-avoid-ae-as-long-waits-inevitable-warns-harris-37587751.html" target="_blank"&gt;Non-urgent cases should avoid A&amp;E as long waits 'inevitable', warns Harris&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Longer hospital waits will "inevitably" be a factor over the coming Christmas period, Health Minister Simon Harris has starkly admitted. After nurses reported the worst-ever November on record for hospital overcrowding, Mr Harris appealed to people to reserve A&amp;Es for emergency cases. He asked the public to avoid making the situation more difficult for doctors by showing up with complaints that could be dealt with by a GP. "I do need and ask for the support of everybody this winter period in terms of keeping our emergency departments for emergencies. And we use alternatives where available....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>First medical abortions expected early in the new year as 50 GPs protest - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/first-medical-abortions-expected-early-in-the-new-year-as-50-gps-protest-37587749.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED5VOUCQs4PhV4NHl5_FpMMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/first-medical-abortions-expected-early-in-the-new-year-as-50-gps-protest-37587749.html" target="_blank"&gt;First medical abortions expected early in the new year as 50 GPs protest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first medical abortion in Ireland may take place as early as January 8, despite the escalation of a row between GPs over how the new service will run. The Government is determined to meet the January target to implement the new law extending the grounds for terminations if the Health (Regulation of Termination of Pregnancy) Bill is passed before the Christmas break. It would mean a woman seeking an abortion could visit a participating GP on January 2 and, if assessed as suitable, be eligible for an abortion early the following week. However, up to 50 GPs with strong anti-abortion views ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Health secretary mocked for claiming 1,000 GP rise, despite fall in qualified practitioners - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/gp-staffing-crisis-nhs-matt-hancock-jeremy-hunt-general-practice-a8649176.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMQMbgFzl4mR3V3Ohkoy1q8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 18:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/gp-staffing-crisis-nhs-matt-hancock-jeremy-hunt-general-practice-a8649176.html" target="_blank"&gt;Health secretary mocked for claiming 1,000 GP rise, despite fall in qualified practitioners&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health and social care secretary has been accused of misleading the public by claiming a “terrific rise” of more than 1,000 GPs in just three months, when in reality figures show numbers of qualified doctors fell. Matt Hancock took to Twitter on Thursday linking to NHS workforce figures which he says show the number of GPs had risen – calculated as full-time GP roles it shows numbers rose by 33,012 in June to 34,132 in September. “Terrific figures out today show GP numbers rose by over a thousand from June-Sept this year,” he said. Terrific figures out today show GP numbers rose by over...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Don't come to us, we'll come to you': The doctors making inroads in Aboriginal Australia - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-01/on-country-healthcare-improving-outcomes-remote-aboriginal-towns/10573202</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOe4mBaRKEbNH4CGW70pQcAqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 01:08:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-01/on-country-healthcare-improving-outcomes-remote-aboriginal-towns/10573202" target="_blank"&gt;'Don't come to us, we'll come to you': The doctors making inroads in Aboriginal Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the last 10 years, progress towards closing the health gap has not just been slow — in some areas, it's going backwards. Key points: - Medical professionals have established a specialist on-country outreach service - It means patients don't have to travel more than 500 kilometres for treatment - Katherine Hospital believes the move will see a reduction in admissions For all the good will and money, why haven't we made strides towards closing the Indigenous health gap once and for all? Katherine Hospital's general physician Dr Simon Quilty believes solutions don't necessarily lie in medic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Release of GP medical card scheme earnings criticised - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1123/1012971-gps-hse-medical-card-scheme/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOaNGllIxgZE1Q6dMMOXS4oqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 16:55:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1123/1012971-gps-hse-medical-card-scheme/" target="_blank"&gt;Release of GP medical card scheme earnings criticised&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two medical unions have criticised the HSE for releasing the payments made to GPs or GP practices last year, under the medical card scheme. The figures show that the highest paid GP practice last year received over €1.1 million. Both the Irish Medical Organisation and the National Association of GPs have criticised the release of the data, saying the figures are misleading, are not net income and that practices have a large number of staff and other costs that must be considered. Padraig McGarry, chairman of the IMO GP Committee, said that the HSE figures were utterly misleading and implied...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>GPs ordering increasing numbers of tests to get rid of patients who won't accept they are not ill, experts say - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/gps-ordering-increasing-numbers-tests-get-rid-patients-wont/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0SzRXF8CyBe5Pd-GCKQOkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/gps-ordering-increasing-numbers-tests-get-rid-patients-wont/" target="_blank"&gt;GPs ordering increasing numbers of tests to get rid of patients who won't accept they are not ill, experts say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients refusing to be told there is nothing wrong with them has fueled a tripling of tests ordered by GPs over the last 15 years, according to researchers. A study led by Oxford University found there has been a 8.5 per cent annual increase of diagnostic procedures in surgeries since 2000, in part because of “strategic, non-medical reasons”. Generic inflammation tests, as well as iron and folate checks, are increasingly reached for by GPs to placate internet-savvy patients with “set ideas” about what their doctor should say, the authors said. Fear of being sued for missing an illness and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Top-earning GP practice receives €1.1m for treating patients with medical cards - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/topearning-gp-practice-receives-1-1m-for-treating-patients-with-medical-cards-37560861.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEqp-tCeqwXD_68h1b2Yi58qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/topearning-gp-practice-receives-1-1m-for-treating-patients-with-medical-cards-37560861.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top-earning GP practice receives €1.1m for treating patients with medical cards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top-earning GP practice in the medical card scheme earned more than €1.1m last year. The practice in Tallaght, south-west Dublin is run by Dr Andrew Jordan, chairman of the National Association of General Practitioners. The HSE said payments worth €551m were made under the scheme to GPs last year - up from €453m in 2014. Dr Jordan said the payment had to be put in context and pointed out it was a gross sum which covered the running of a business with a large staff including six doctors and nurses. "We provide a seven-day service and do not rely on an out-of-hours service," he said. His ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Revealed: Top earning GP practice in medical card scheme made over €1.1m last year - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/revealed-top-earning-gp-practice-in-medical-card-scheme-made-over-1-1m-last-year-37559776.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAbKia5p7R4RB3BRyarUKlgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 18:59:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/revealed-top-earning-gp-practice-in-medical-card-scheme-made-over-1-1m-last-year-37559776.html" target="_blank"&gt;Revealed: Top earning GP practice in medical card scheme made over €1.1m last year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top earning GP practice in the medical card scheme made over €1.1m last year. The practice in Tallaght in south west Dublin is run by Dr Andrew Jordan, chairman of the National Association of General Practitioners. The HSE said today the payments worth €551m were made under the scheme to GPs last year – up from €453m in 2014. However, Dr Jordan said the payment had to be put in practice and pointed out it is a gross sum which covers the running of a business with a large staff including six doctors and nurses. “We provide a seven day service and do not rely on an out of hours service,” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Matt Hancock accused of breaching code over GP app endorsement - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/nov/30/matt-hancock-accused-of-breaching-code-over-gp-app-endorsement</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbELwnitRnuKNBnteMNXtwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:13:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/nov/30/matt-hancock-accused-of-breaching-code-over-gp-app-endorsement" target="_blank"&gt;Matt Hancock accused of breaching code over GP app endorsement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Labour is demanding an inquiry after Matt Hancock, the health secretary, was accused of breaking the ministerial code by endorsing a private healthcare company in a sponsored newspaper supplement. An interview with Hancock appeared in the Evening Standard’s Future London Health supplement, which was paid for by Babylon. In the feature, Hancock praised the company’s GP at Hand app, which allows users to have video consultations with doctors via their smartphone. Hancock is an ally of George Osborne, the editor of the Evening Standard. A section in the supplement titled “Matt’s Apps” listed t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Type 2 diabetes now affects nearly 7,000 young Britons - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/22/type-2-diabetes-obesity-now-affects-nearly-7000-young-britons</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJejzckG_6ApgY-UGAIrsq8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 06:28:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/22/type-2-diabetes-obesity-now-affects-nearly-7000-young-britons" target="_blank"&gt;Type 2 diabetes now affects nearly 7,000 young Britons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly 7,000 children and young Britons under 25 have been diagnosed with type 2 diabetes, the chronic condition linked to obesity that can lead to amputations and blindness. Type 2 diabetes used to be virtually unknown in young people. It usually develops over the age of 40 in white Europeans, or after the age of 25 in people who are African-Caribbean, black African, or south Asian. The startling new figures come from Diabetes UK, which has combined the numbers of children seen by hospital specialists with those for the young people up to age 25 who are looked after by their GP. Only 715 a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Health Secretary Matt Hancock deletes '1,000 more GPs' claim after statistics watchdog censure - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/health-secretary-matt-hancock-gps-statistics-uksa-censure-false-facts-a8655961.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELfZY6QrJ9O7tuR_rNUFjgsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDyxv0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/health-secretary-matt-hancock-gps-statistics-uksa-censure-false-facts-a8655961.html" target="_blank"&gt;Health Secretary Matt Hancock deletes '1,000 more GPs' claim after statistics watchdog censure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health secretary has deleted claims of a “terrific” increase of 1,000 GPs joining the NHS in just three months, after being censured by the government statistics watchdog. Matt Hancock made the claimed in a tweet last week and was widely criticised by doctors and health groups who said he was misleading the public, as the actual figures showed qualified doctor numbers fell. Those figures were also drastically inflated by the new intake of junior doctors who started GP specialty training in August. Even counting these doctors, who work under supervision but by third year are seeing patie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Safety regulations for medical implants condemned by review chair - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/26/implant-files-safety-review-chair-regulations-not-fit-for-use</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBBPliQ02j6d81Q3fvl4h7QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 07:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/26/implant-files-safety-review-chair-regulations-not-fit-for-use" target="_blank"&gt;Safety regulations for medical implants condemned by review chair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients cannot rely on existing regulations to protect them from dangerous products that could lead to pain and physical harm, the chair of the government’s safety review of medical devices has warned. Responding to findings of a global investigation into the medical device industry, Julia Cumberlege said there were such serious failings with the licensing rules for medical implants that “patients certainly can’t rely on that system”. Related: Revealed: faulty medical implants harm patients around world “If you look at the regulation of medicines, it’s pretty strict. We know it takes nine ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UK doctors help train Irish medics in abortion - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/uk-doctors-help-train-irish-medics-in-abortion-37553918.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAZglKbTqjLrDo0uYE0uum4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/uk-doctors-help-train-irish-medics-in-abortion-37553918.html" target="_blank"&gt;UK doctors help train Irish medics in abortion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Irish doctors have called on their UK colleagues to help train them in carrying out abortions in advance of the new law extending the grounds for termination of pregnancy. The Irish Independent has learned Irish medics have enlisted the expertise of the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists and the British Association of Abortion Care Providers. The Regulation of the Termination of Pregnancy Bill returns to the Dáil for report stage with the aim of having it passed in December and made law by January. For the first time, maternity hospitals here will be allowed to carry out an a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Hundreds still go to Britain for abortion as concern rises of delays here - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/hundreds-still-go-to-britain-for-abortion-as-concern-rises-of-delays-here-37564786.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECJZdyCH_ZQDIVWMLY_OJQMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/hundreds-still-go-to-britain-for-abortion-as-concern-rises-of-delays-here-37564786.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hundreds still go to Britain for abortion as concern rises of delays here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of women a month have travelled to Britain for abortions since May's Repeal the Eighth referendum, figures reveal. The British Pregnancy Advisory Service (BPAS) - the country's leading abortion provider - says 133 Irish women used its services in June. There were 110 in July, 115 in August and 120 in September. The BPAS has clinics in more than 60 locations and many of them are close to ports and airports with direct budget travel from Ireland. It is understood the BPAS figures only represent a proportion of women who are continuing to take the abortion trail to Britain. An estimat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>GP body claims salary reveal is data breach - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/gp-body-claims-salary-reveal-is-data-breach-887477.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJtsa5uQULlHaZV1vHsh5WIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 05:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/gp-body-claims-salary-reveal-is-data-breach-887477.html" target="_blank"&gt;GP body claims salary reveal is data breach&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Association of General Practitioners (NAGP) has warned the HSE that it intends to complain to the Data Protection Commission (DPC) after it released details of the doctors who earn most under its Primary Care Reimbursement Service (PCRS). The highest earning doctor is the association’s chairman, Andrew Jordan, Dublin South West, who received in excess of €1.1m gross last year, which includes practice support. Jordan employs 26 staff and treats 10,000 GMS (General Medical Services) patients. Fianna Fáil senator Keith Swanick, from Co Mayo, is also among the top 100 earners, rece...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Dozens of NHS trusts fail key targets on waiting times for a year - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/nhs-trusts-waiting-time-targets-hospital-funding-performance-a8643781.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN0DaT3agBDva87xksTzaPUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 20:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/nhs-trusts-waiting-time-targets-hospital-funding-performance-a8643781.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dozens of NHS trusts fail key targets on waiting times for a year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly one in five NHS hospital services has failed to hit any key national waiting-time targets in the past year, analysis shows. Some 29 hospital trusts and boards out of 157 had not hit a single target for 12 months running, an investigation by the BBC found. The figures will almost certainly reignite rows over NHS funding and the use of private contractors by the health service. Read more - UK failing women with slow ovarian cancer diagnosis, charity warns - Quarter of weekend and evening GP appointments unbooked - NHS A&amp;E waiting times hit record high in February, show latest figures -...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>How to fight for your sick child in the health system - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/life/advocating-for-your-sick-child-in-the-health-system/10427970</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPu_wsmNnyij1CUJdy7O-dAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 19:08:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/life/advocating-for-your-sick-child-in-the-health-system/10427970" target="_blank"&gt;How to fight for your sick child in the health system&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Patrick Wright Image Dealing with a health crisis is always confronting, but there are some things you can do to make it easier. (Unsplash/ABC Life: Nathan Nankervis) That was the question Sharon Denny was asked as she sat by the bed of her 10-year-old son in hospital. While no-one knew it at the time, her son Patrick, now 19, was suffering from a rare condition known as Kawasaki disease. Image Patrick Denny, now 19, was about 10 when he was suffered from Kawasaki disease. (Supplied: Sharon Denny) His body was running so hot that his skin was peeling from his hands, his feet and his ears...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Vow to train the next generation of working-class doctors - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/17/medical-school-vows-to-train-generation-working-class-doctors-sunderland</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM_utObqyH9LvBBGgJQITwgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 14:59:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/17/medical-school-vows-to-train-generation-working-class-doctors-sunderland" target="_blank"&gt;Vow to train the next generation of working-class doctors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A medical school at the University of Sunderland will be launched next year with the aim of breaking down social barriers to medicine and training a new generation of working-class doctors. The university’s vice chancellor, Sir David Bell, likened Sunderland to an “insurgent” in medicine, since the school was established under the umbrella of government policy to widen participation in education. The head of the medical school and professor of general practice and primary care, Scott Wilkes, has been a GP for almost 25 years. He knows the importance of raising the aspirations of disadvantag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Eilish O'Regan: 'GPs have now agreed abortion fee - but where's the training?' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/eilish-oregan-gps-have-now-agreed-abortion-fee-but-wheres-the-training-37537649.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHaBswE1tV-BVxXzzjfEDs8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/eilish-oregan-gps-have-now-agreed-abortion-fee-but-wheres-the-training-37537649.html" target="_blank"&gt;Eilish O'Regan: 'GPs have now agreed abortion fee - but where's the training?'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GPs agreed to a €450 fee for a medical abortion this week, despite not yet being trained in how to deliver the service. It's one of the many hurdles to overcome with just six weeks to go to the introduction of a far-reaching abortion regime we could not have forecast a year ago. The medical abortions, involving three visits to the GP and two medications, will be free to women who are up to nine weeks pregnant. GPs, who will be paid by the HSE per patient, will be written to next week asking them if they are interested in participating. Training courses for family doctors are now being final...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Why we need Mental Health First Aiders in the battle for wellbeing - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/body/need-mental-health-first-aiders-battle-wellbeing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC05MC-y3ogk-MEKADT_rWkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDg2rcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:58:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/body/need-mental-health-first-aiders-battle-wellbeing/" target="_blank"&gt;Why we need Mental Health First Aiders in the battle for wellbeing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christmas Charity Appeal 2018 banner The workplace has never looked so well. From fitness groups to blood pressure monitoring and revamped canteens, companies are finally considering their employees’ physical fitness needs. Take, as example, the words of Prince William, who recently spoke out about the emotional turmoil he suffered while working as an air ambulance pilot. The Prince said that seeing children injured and killed in road traffic accidents left him feeling "very down" – and that talking to colleagues helped him to "come to terms with the enormous sadness" of what had happened....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>People with severe mental health problems forced to wait longer for NHS help than those with mild depression - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/18/people-severe-mental-health-problems-forced-wait-longer-nhs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED_3WMUa1D8VwJWNl6BAe1gqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/18/people-severe-mental-health-problems-forced-wait-longer-nhs/" target="_blank"&gt;People with severe mental health problems forced to wait longer for NHS help than those with mild depression&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with severe mental health problems are being forced to wait longer for NHS help than those with mild depression, experts have warned. Research shows that patients with conditions such as schizophrenia and personality disorder are being denied help despite feeling suicidal. Charity Rethink Mental Illness urged health officials to introduce NHS waiting targets for mental health problems, including a two week maximum wait for those suffering from psychosis. The study found that such patients faced an average wait of two months for treatment. Meanwhile, nine in ten of those seeking couns...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Community activity as a path to better health - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4e971172-d82e-11e8-aa22-36538487e3d0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJh7OxVTsHIjs67Ux0Y8WgMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 04:31:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4e971172-d82e-11e8-aa22-36538487e3d0" target="_blank"&gt;Community activity as a path to better health&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Arabella Tresilian, a management consultant, suffered a mental breakdown in 2015, her doctor recognised that her autism had combined with other events to cause post-traumatic stress disorder and chronic fatigue. Ms Tresilian did not want to return to the antidepressants she had taken on and off over the previous 27 years. Luckily, her doctor’s surgery offers “social prescribing” — patient referral to community activities as an alternative therapy. These range from art classes, singing, knitting, cookery and reading groups to walking clubs, gardening, yoga and museum visits. A “link wor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>More NHS cyber-attacks 'inevitable', warn experts - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/16/more-nhs-cyber-attacks-inevitable-warn-experts</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIkA94rFMvbPGxunBRScb7EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 10:40:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/16/more-nhs-cyber-attacks-inevitable-warn-experts" target="_blank"&gt;More NHS cyber-attacks 'inevitable', warn experts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health service insiders fear the NHS will be hit by another cyber-attack similar to the WannaCry ransomware outbreak that caused widespread disruption to hospitals and GP surgeries last year. Poor leadership, budgetary constraints, deficient IT systems and a lack of qualified staff mean another attack on the health service is inevitable, according to experts at a Guardian event supported by DXC. Guardian technology reporter Alex Hern spoke about the impact of the 2017 WannaCry cyber-attack, and clinicians, cybersecurity specialists, policy advisers and politicians discussed how to best prot...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>GPs to be paid around €400 per abortion as roll-out of service nears - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/gps-to-be-paid-around-400-per-abortion-as-rollout-of-service-nears-37522662.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBI4oxI7cEFL1_SWo3PIXBsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/gps-to-be-paid-around-400-per-abortion-as-rollout-of-service-nears-37522662.html" target="_blank"&gt;GPs to be paid around €400 per abortion as roll-out of service nears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GPs who deliver medical abortions are expected to be paid a fee in the region of €400 per patient. The fee is expected to be finalised in talks between the Department of Health and the Irish Medical Organisation tomorrow. Under the proposed legislation GPs will be allowed deliver a medical abortion up to 12 weeks of pregnancy. This will involve two visits and possibly a third follow up visit. The service will be free of charge to patients, with the HSE paying the expected fee of €400. In practice GPs are expected to provide a medical abortion up to nine weeks of pregnancy. Women who are bet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>NHS staff shortages could triple in a decade, think tanks warn - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/15/nhs-staff-shortages-could-triple-decade-think-tanks-warn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOa1Qq6z9z5d7ZzAQng8SDwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/15/nhs-staff-shortages-could-triple-decade-think-tanks-warn/" target="_blank"&gt;NHS staff shortages could triple in a decade, think tanks warn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NHS staff shortages could triple in a decade, without a radical boost to recruitment efforts, major thinktanks have warned. Analysis by the King’s Fund, the Health Foundation and the Nuffield Trust suggests the health service could be short of more than 350,000 staff if it continues to lose staff and cannot attract enough from abroad. On such trends, one in four posts would be vacant, compared with one in eight today. The think tanks said “worryingly” high numbers of hospital doctors and nurses were taking early retirement, and not being replaced in sufficient numbers. It follows research w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Contract agreed for provision of abortion services - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1114/1010973-imo-contract-abortion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELMnHUbSAP_PaKq6Z0xuKvMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 21:08:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1114/1010973-imo-contract-abortion/" target="_blank"&gt;Contract agreed for provision of abortion services&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A contract for the provision of abortion services in community settings has been agreed between the Irish Medical Organisation and the Minister for Health. The contract will be offered by the HSE to medical practitioners who express an interest in providing terminations up to nine weeks, the majority of which will occur in community settings. General Practitioners, the Irish Family Association and the Well Woman Clinic are expected provide the service in these settings. In a statement tonight, the Minister for Health Simon Harris described the contract agreement as a "significant step" in t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>UK cancer and children’s wards being hit by closures - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/18/uk-cancer-and-childrens-wards-being-hit-by-closures-nhs-staffing-crisis</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDyt3nAG3lzWmffvdlt3d8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 15:23:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/18/uk-cancer-and-childrens-wards-being-hit-by-closures-nhs-staffing-crisis" target="_blank"&gt;UK cancer and children’s wards being hit by closures&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growing numbers of hospital units that provide cancer care and children’s services are among those being forced to shut because the NHS’s deepening staffing crisis means it has too few doctors and nurses to operate them safely. The closures are leading to patients having to travel further to receive care as NHS bosses increasingly decide to centralise services in fewer hospitals in response to gaps in rotas. The trend prompted the Royal College of Nursing (RCN) to warn that “skeleton staffing” means patients are suffering. “Every day brings fresh and devastating examples of patients paying ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Capita’s cancer screening blunder hits 50,000 NHS patients - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/14/capitas-cancer-screening-blunder-hits-50000-nhs-patients</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK6-m7PucX1Gn6nF51oaFA8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 14:55:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/14/capitas-cancer-screening-blunder-hits-50000-nhs-patients" target="_blank"&gt;Capita’s cancer screening blunder hits 50,000 NHS patients&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 40,000 women have not received information on cervical cancer screening after the NHS contractor Capita failed to send out letters. The problem, which occurred between January and June, affected 43,200 women who were supposed to receive an invitation or a reminder but received only one of the two, and also led to the delays of 4,508 results letters, the company said. Capita said only a small proportion of the results required further examination, and the affected patients should all have been contacted directly by their GP. NHS England said there was no evidence so far that anyone...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>GPs to receive written requests for abortions from January following agreement on fees - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/gps-to-receive-written-requests-for-abortions-from-january-following-agreement-on-fees-37529702.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBmGANNM16Fcti4gB-mP7O4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 20:08:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/gps-to-receive-written-requests-for-abortions-from-january-following-agreement-on-fees-37529702.html" target="_blank"&gt;GPs to receive written requests for abortions from January following agreement on fees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GPs are to receive a written request to provide medical abortions from January following an agreement on fees of €450. The service will be free to women and will entitle them to three visits to the GP as well as access to medication. Health Minister Simon Harris announced tonight that agreement had been reached on the contract for the service with the Irish Medical Organisation. GPs will be asked to opt in but they are not obliged to provide the medical abortions. They will get €150 for a first visit when a woman can request an termination and undergo a medical examination. The woman may ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>In rural France, Macron seeks remedy for 'healthcare deserts' - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-health-idUSKCN1NJ0HX</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKWcFyFX2Wg_NCCZ6iUWTXMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 06:28:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-health-idUSKCN1NJ0HX" target="_blank"&gt;In rural France, Macron seeks remedy for 'healthcare deserts'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Joelle Dupas falls ill, she goes to a medical center in her home town in rural western France where all 12 doctors have come out of retirement. The 66-year-old tried for months to find a doctor after retiring to Laval, a quiet town of 50,000 residents surrounded by rolling fields. Her search ended at the simple center managed by the 12 veteran doctors, aged between 67 and 70, on the ground floor of an apartment bloc. "You need to wait at least a year to get an appointment with an ophthalmologist," Dupas, a former secretary and salesperson, told Reuters in the waiting room. "It was not ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Employers must do more to protect the mental health of staff - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/12/employers-do-more-protect-mental-health-staff</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIT7rnFVG2XpoZmZTQjiQs0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 09:00:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/12/employers-do-more-protect-mental-health-staff" target="_blank"&gt;Employers must do more to protect the mental health of staff&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly 20 years ago I had a breakdown. I was approaching 40. I was not in a serious relationship and had no children of my own, but I was devoted to my job; married to it, some said. I was a senior executive at this paper. Related: Preventing mental health problems is better than curing them | Mark Rice-Oxley I fought and lost a battle with my GP, who wanted to sign me off work. I didn’t feel I’d have a recognisable identity without my job; she said I might struggle to live if I didn’t take a break. I had five months off work. Sleep evaded me, eating felt a battle not worth winning, a psych...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Flu Season: How Can We Stop The NHS Catching A Cold? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/benmaruthappu/2018/11/12/flu-season-how-can-we-stop-the-nhs-catching-a-cold/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC7PZh3XN2cfjCLwKxkdZiYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 13:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/benmaruthappu/2018/11/12/flu-season-how-can-we-stop-the-nhs-catching-a-cold/" target="_blank"&gt;Flu Season: How Can We Stop The NHS Catching A Cold?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increased funding and innovative technologies at the heart of prevention this winter Blur background clinic or hospital waiting hall and corridor with patient on wheelchair near nurse station Last winter saw the highest rise in flu cases since 2010/11. According to the Guardian, almost three times as many people died of the influenza virus in the UK than the previous year. And while it’s generally harmless to the average adult, the elderly are most at risk, with 90% of deaths in people who are 65 and older. This, in addition to the particularly aggressive winter weather the UK experienced, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Arrival of new abortion facility stalled as Tas Premier is challenged on 'see your GP' advice - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-07/hobart-abortion-clinic-return-date-unclear/10472578</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKTJNYe8Ct6826ctS50pVM4qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 03:55:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-07/hobart-abortion-clinic-return-date-unclear/10472578" target="_blank"&gt;Arrival of new abortion facility stalled as Tas Premier is challenged on 'see your GP' advice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By state political reporter Rhiana Whitson Tasmania's Premier has been unable to guarantee that women will have access to a new low-cost surgical abortion provider by the end of the year, despite the Government previously announcing the service would open in October. A new clinic was supposed to open in Hobart in October, but on the last day of the month Tasmanian Health Service (THS) confirmed it was on hold due to stalled negotiations between the provider and the property owner. Today Premier Will Hodgman was asked if he could guarantee the service would open by the end of year. "That is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>NHS cancer treatment wait statistics 'set to be worst on record' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/08/nhs-cancer-treatment-wait-statistics-2018-standards</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECZmd8DBba4QNt3iiwuEMa8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 13:50:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/08/nhs-cancer-treatment-wait-statistics-2018-standards" target="_blank"&gt;NHS cancer treatment wait statistics 'set to be worst on record'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NHS is on course for its worst annual cancer waiting statistics on record, official figures suggest. In eight out of nine published cancer targets, between April and September, the health service treated the lowest or joint lowest percentage of patients since the standards were introduced, according to official figures published on Thursday. The percentage of people in England who receive a first treatment for cancer within 62 days of an urgent GP referral fell to 78.6% in the second quarter of this year They show that with half of the year gone, 133,843 cancer patients have not been tr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Women who have a medical abortion 'likely to need three visits to GP', says health chairman - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/women-who-have-a-medical-abortion-likely-to-need-three-visits-to-gp-says-health-chairman-37505041.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN4z4vQT_CcT5Rm9QICYhCsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/women-who-have-a-medical-abortion-likely-to-need-three-visits-to-gp-says-health-chairman-37505041.html" target="_blank"&gt;Women who have a medical abortion 'likely to need three visits to GP', says health chairman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women who are certified for a medical abortion are likely to have to make three visits to their GP, the Oireachtas health committee has heard. Dr Michael Harty, chairman of the committee and who is also a GP, said it was important the woman gets a face-to-face consulation with the doctor. He was commenting as the committee continued to debate more of the 180 amendments to The Health (Regulation of Termination of Pregnancy) Bill 2018, which will allow for medical abortion up to 12 weeks of pregnancy. Pro-choice TDs said the proposed legislation, forcing a three-day pause from the time a wome...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Today is Stress Awareness Day and we talked to an expert on how to avoid burnout - Her.ie</title><link>https://www.her.ie/life/today-is-stress-awareness-day-and-we-talked-to-an-expert-on-how-to-avoid-burnout-434909</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENvh5e6zrBMhAsI3M_Y50tcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8w6a6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 15:35:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.her.ie/life/today-is-stress-awareness-day-and-we-talked-to-an-expert-on-how-to-avoid-burnout-434909" target="_blank"&gt;Today is Stress Awareness Day and we talked to an expert on how to avoid burnout&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first Wednesday of every November marks Stress AwarenessDay and we have some tips to help you recognise and deal with burnout. We all know what it's like to suffer from stress. Some people are more prone to experiencing it, while others merely feel flutters of nerves before an exam, a deadline or a presentation. Stress is a spectrum and we all slot in somewhere on the scale. via GIPHY Stress AwarenessDay was set up by UK charity, Mind, who want people to notice when stress is prolonged and affecting their health: "We all know what its like to feel stressed - being under pressure is a no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>GP body to hold EGM over abortion services provision - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/gp-body-to-hold-egm-over-abortion-services-provision-882902.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPQBzyG_HjSca_bx6jzG_dwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/gp-body-to-hold-egm-over-abortion-services-provision-882902.html" target="_blank"&gt;GP body to hold EGM over abortion services provision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Irish College of General Practitioners is to hold an emergency general meeting next month to discuss GP concerns about providing abortion services. The ICGP, the professional and training body for general practice here, was responding to a petition signed by hundreds of GPs. The college said the meeting of its members, which will be held on December 2, will allow a detailed discussion on the provision of termination of pregnancy services by GPs. Doctors who sought the meeting had proposed a number of motions, including one stating that “external clinical settings” would be more appropri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>I had to quit my hospital job when I resented patients who got better - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/08/quit-job-resented-patients-got-better-cancer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPIBjBaxGdKG99tRCO7k4WMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 11:16:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/08/quit-job-resented-patients-got-better-cancer" target="_blank"&gt;I had to quit my hospital job when I resented patients who got better&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working in waiting list administration can bring its fair share of bad days. Bed shortages, disgruntled patients, irritated clinicians and cancellations make the job a fast-paced, high-pressure juggling act. I’d worked in a waiting list office for four years, booking thousands of outpatient endoscopic tests, and thrived on the chaos. That was until 5 June 2012, when I encountered my worst day at work when my mum was diagnosed with cancer in my department. Mum had been suffering from stubborn indigestion for a few months which wasn’t eased by medication. She’d lost a little weight and was le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>GPs critical of timing of ICGP meeting on abortion - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1102/1008343-icgp-meeting-abortion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3mLl0REJEuOKsk4S6XjwQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 21:00:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1102/1008343-icgp-meeting-abortion/" target="_blank"&gt;GPs critical of timing of ICGP meeting on abortion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GPs who organised a petition calling on the Irish College of General Practitioners to hold an Extraordinary General Meeting on the provision of abortion services in Ireland, have described the decision to hold it in four weeks time as "wholly unacceptable". The 2 December EGM was announced in a statement by the ICGP board this evening, after it received a petition from hundreds of General Practitioners, who are concerned about the introduction of GP-led abortion services here. This evening, the ICGP wrote to all its members to inform them of the EGM, "to enable detailed discussion" of the p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Report warns of inequality in Ireland's 'two-tiered' health system - Newstalk Newsfeed</title><link>https://www.newstalk.com/Report-warns-of-inequality-in-Irelands-twotiered-health-system</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELN1DYp0nIAm1Xo0OU3-mvsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowmeSfCTCcwW8wmpuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 07:51:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newstalk.com/Report-warns-of-inequality-in-Irelands-twotiered-health-system" target="_blank"&gt;Report warns of inequality in Ireland's 'two-tiered' health system&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newstalk Newsfeed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A report has warned that people with incomes just above the medical card threshold are left in a "twilight zone" with poorer health outcomes. It's among the findings of a Europe-wide report on healthcare published by the think tank TASC. The report highlights potentially high levels of inequality in the 'two-tier' Irish healthcare system - noting that Ireland remains the only western European country to not have universal health coverage of primary care. It found that people Ireland had the best self-reported health in the EU. However, the study says Irish people in higher income groups wer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newstalk.com">Newstalk Newsfeed</source></item></channel></rss>