<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>University Hospital Kerry - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRzVmTm0xMGFoSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:05:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Kerry scans review finds 11 cancer diagnoses delayed - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/munster/2018/1205/1015282-kerry-hospital-scans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780127069553</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:40:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/munster/2018/1205/1015282-kerry-hospital-scans/" target="_blank"&gt;Kerry scans review finds 11 cancer diagnoses delayed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/three-legal-cases-started-over-delayed-diagnoses-cases-in-kerry-university-hospital-37602027.html" target="_blank"&gt;Three legal cases started over delayed diagnoses cases in Kerry University Hospital&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/solicitor-calls-on-hse-not-to-force-kerry-patients-to-run-the-full-gamut-of-high-court-proceedings-890370.html" target="_blank"&gt;Solicitor calls on HSE not to force Kerry patients to 'run the full gamut' of High Court proceedings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/harris-kerry-scan-4379135-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'His family believes that if his cancer was detected in any of the 3 x-rays, his prognosis wouldn't be terminal'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.irishmirror.ie/news/irish-news/health-news/four-people-die-new-cancer-13693728" target="_blank"&gt;Four people die in new cancer scandal as report reveals one consultant at centre of tragedy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Mirror&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWp4eXVhbGpZQU1FWWozanIwSjFYOFFLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Scan reading errors at Kerry hospital linked to four premature deaths - The Irish Times</title><link>https://www.irishtimes.com/news/health/scan-reading-errors-at-kerry-hospital-linked-to-four-premature-deaths-1.3721602</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO8rMxwBkfgfbPUExTuzHR8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqfqFCzD7v4MDMIO9jQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:19:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishtimes.com/news/health/scan-reading-errors-at-kerry-hospital-linked-to-four-premature-deaths-1.3721602" target="_blank"&gt;Scan reading errors at Kerry hospital linked to four premature deaths&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Irish Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Audit finds 11 patients suffered delayed diagnosis and serious impact on their health.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishtimes.com">The Irish Times</source></item><item><title>Four UHK patients whose diagnoses were 'delayed' have since died, HSE report into scandal reveals - The Kerryman</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/regionals/kerryman/news/four-uhk-patients-whose-diagnoses-were-delayed-have-since-died-hse-report-into-scandal-reveals-37598708.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMinwFodHRwczovL3d3dy5pbmRlcGVuZGVudC5pZS9yZWdpb25hbHMva2VycnltYW4vbmV3cy9mb3VyLXVoay1wYXRpZW50cy13aG9zZS1kaWFnbm9zZXMtd2VyZS1kZWxheWVkLWhhdmUtc2luY2UtZGllZC1oc2UtcmVwb3J0LWludG8tc2NhbmRhbC1yZXZlYWxzLTM3NTk4NzA4Lmh0bWzSAeoBaHR0cHM6Ly9hbXAtaW5kZXBlbmRlbnQtaWUuY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy9hbXAuaW5kZXBlbmRlbnQuaWUvcmVnaW9uYWxzL2tlcnJ5bWFuL25ld3MvZm91ci11aGstcGF0aWVudHMtd2hvc2UtZGlhZ25vc2VzLXdlcmUtZGVsYXllZC1oYXZlLXNpbmNlLWRpZWQtaHNlLXJlcG9ydC1pbnRvLXNjYW5kYWwtcmV2ZWFscy0zNzU5ODcwOC5odG1sP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/regionals/kerryman/news/four-uhk-patients-whose-diagnoses-were-delayed-have-since-died-hse-report-into-scandal-reveals-37598708.html" target="_blank"&gt;Four UHK patients whose diagnoses were 'delayed' have since died, HSE report into scandal reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Kerryman&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four patients whose cancers were missed on initial examination of scans at University Hospital Kerry are now dead. The four were among 11 patients in total ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">The Kerryman</source></item><item><title>Moves to cap hospital parking fees - The Kerryman</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/regionals/kerryman/news/moves-to-cap-hospital-parking-fees-37572290.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmluZGVwZW5kZW50LmllL3JlZ2lvbmFscy9rZXJyeW1hbi9uZXdzL21vdmVzLXRvLWNhcC1ob3NwaXRhbC1wYXJraW5nLWZlZXMtMzc1NzIyOTAuaHRtbNIBrgFodHRwczovL2FtcC1pbmRlcGVuZGVudC1pZS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL2FtcC5pbmRlcGVuZGVudC5pZS9yZWdpb25hbHMva2VycnltYW4vbmV3cy9tb3Zlcy10by1jYXAtaG9zcGl0YWwtcGFya2luZy1mZWVzLTM3NTcyMjkwLmh0bWw_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/regionals/kerryman/news/moves-to-cap-hospital-parking-fees-37572290.html" target="_blank"&gt;Moves to cap hospital parking fees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Kerryman&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parking at University Hospital Kerry (UHK) could become cheaper following news that Health Minister Simon Harris is planning to put a cap on hospital-parking ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">The Kerryman</source></item><item><title>Radiology staff and resources ‘in short supply’ - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/radiology-staff-and-resources-in-short-supply-890442.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJATk_OHXp8j3wDb_H0TWhIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/radiology-staff-and-resources-in-short-supply-890442.html" target="_blank"&gt;Radiology staff and resources ‘in short supply’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All public radiology departments are under pressure as they are neither staffed nor resourced adequately to meet demand, according to the Faculty of Radiologists. University Hospital Kerry The faculty, the professional and academic body for radiologists, was responding to the publication on Wednesday of a report which found a cancer diagnosis had either been delayed or missed in 14 patients attending University Hospital Kerry (UHK), four of whom have died. The diagnosis of one patient with lung cancer was delayed by 76 weeks. The report, a review of more than 46,000 medical images involving...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Kerry hospital issue 'greater than a single doctor', says councillor - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/kerry-hospital-issue-greater-than-a-single-doctor-says-councillor-890255.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHIonZUXSi2Xu2O-4H9O2CgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/kerry-hospital-issue-greater-than-a-single-doctor-says-councillor-890255.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kerry hospital issue 'greater than a single doctor', says councillor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Kerry councillor says she is concerned a single doctor is being scapegoated for wider systems failings at University Hospital Kerry. Yesterday, a review of radiology scans found that 11 patients at the hospital had their cancer diagnoses delayed, four of them have since died. A report into the matter calls for an external review of management at the radiology department. Sinn Féin councillor Toireasa Ferris says senior managers were made aware of problems in the department yet they failed to act. She says yesterday's report could have delved into the issue a little further. "It's bizarre ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>11 patients had their cancer diagnosis delayed and four have since died, Kerry review shows - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/uhk-report-cancer-4377687-Dec2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFEZgO-MixL1i0B99Itpv2MqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:37:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/uhk-report-cancer-4377687-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;11 patients had their cancer diagnosis delayed and four have since died, Kerry review shows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A REPORT ON a review of tens of thousands of radiology scans at University Hospital Kerry has found that 11 patients had their cancer diagnosis delayed and four have since died. The review looked at over 46,000 thousand individual images (CT scans, ultrasound scans and chest x-ray examinations) reported by a single consultant radiologist relating to 26,754 individual patients. The time period examined was between March 2016 and July 2017. The consultant in question no longer works at the hospital. The review was ordered after three serious reportable events were identified in summer 2017 r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>11 patients had cancer diagnoses delayed and four have since died: Kerry hospital review finds - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/11-patients-had-cancer-diagnoses-delayed-and-four-have-since-died-kerry-hospital-review-finds-890061.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELw0cr6gEGRESjn9lzpsEyoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/11-patients-had-cancer-diagnoses-delayed-and-four-have-since-died-kerry-hospital-review-finds-890061.html" target="_blank"&gt;11 patients had cancer diagnoses delayed and four have since died: Kerry hospital review finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A total of eleven people had their cancer diagnoses delayed and four have since died, according to “a look-back review” of more than 46,000 scans, belonging to more than 26,000 patients at University Hospital Kerry. The single biggest such review of images and scans ever conducted in the State got underway last year after serious concerns came to light in July/August 2017 about three patients whose conditions were either missed or misread. The look back was into the work of a single radiologist who no longer works at the hospital. The consultant radiologist had been responsible for 46,234 i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Eilish O'Regan: 'Review is catalogue of tragedy in scan failure' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/eilish-oregan-review-is-catalogue-of-tragedy-in-scan-failure-37600194.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHw1SuHxB1bBajjgAhYzucAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/eilish-oregan-review-is-catalogue-of-tragedy-in-scan-failure-37600194.html" target="_blank"&gt;Eilish O'Regan: 'Review is catalogue of tragedy in scan failure'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The review of scans overseen by a locum radiologist at University Hospital Kerry over 16 months reads like another catalogue of tragedy for 11 patients whose cancers were missed - four of whom are now dead. While the review was thorough, the report from the South/South West Hospital Group, which includes the Kerry hospital, is very unsatisfactory. It is particularly short on analysis of what went wrong. The work of one locum radiologist was examined. But this was not prompted by an internal audit at the hospital. It followed the return of several patients over the summer of 2017 who had sca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Radiology review at University Hospital Kerry reveals 11 delayed diagnoses - Newstalk Newsfeed</title><link>https://www.newstalk.com/Radiology-review-at-University-Hospital-Kerry-reveals-11-delayed-diagnoses</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHYbIe2E-pyzgUBuFdDwOgcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowmeSfCTCcwW8wmpuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:56:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newstalk.com/Radiology-review-at-University-Hospital-Kerry-reveals-11-delayed-diagnoses" target="_blank"&gt;Radiology review at University Hospital Kerry reveals 11 delayed diagnoses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newstalk Newsfeed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A review of radiology cases at University Hospital Kerry has found that 11 patients had their cancer diagnoses delayed, and four of these patients have since died. A look-back report has been published by the South/South West Hospital Group. The review was of all radiology images reported by a single consultant radiologist at the hospital between March 2016 to July 2017. It was prompted by the notification of three "serious reportable events", each resulting in a diagnostic error, in July and August 2017. It said 11 patients had their diagnosis delayed, which had a "serious impact on their ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newstalk.com">Newstalk Newsfeed</source></item><item><title>59 patients requiring further follow-up or investigation in Kerry diagnosis scandal - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/59-patients-requiring-further-follow-up-or-investigation-in-kerry-diagnosis-scandal-890366.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYONG6YJYSmNn-ktHsadYcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/59-patients-requiring-further-follow-up-or-investigation-in-kerry-diagnosis-scandal-890366.html" target="_blank"&gt;59 patients requiring further follow-up or investigation in Kerry diagnosis scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A total of 59 patients were identified as requiring further clinical follow-up and or investigation as part of the recall caused by the missed diagnosis scandal at Kerry Hospital, the Dáil has heard. Following repeat imaging during the recall, some ten further patients were referred to other hospitals for specialist care, Tánaiste Simon Coveney confirmed under questioning. He said all imaging relating to one individual consultant radiologist between March 24, 2016, and July 27, 2017, had been reviewed. The HSE advised the scope agreed for the review was focused solely on University Hospital...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Review finds University Hospital Kerry delayed cancer diagnoses in 11 patients, four of which have died - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/review-finds-university-hospital-kerry-delayed-cancer-diagnoses-in-11-patients-four-of-which-have-died-890043.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA6Ah6IB6ppWaQA5jyCX9hoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/review-finds-university-hospital-kerry-delayed-cancer-diagnoses-in-11-patients-four-of-which-have-died-890043.html" target="_blank"&gt;Review finds University Hospital Kerry delayed cancer diagnoses in 11 patients, four of which have died&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;11 patients had their cancer diagnoses delayed at University Hospital Kerry and four of these patients have since died. Those findings form part of a report published today on a review of 46,000 radiology scans, which was ordered after three serious reportable events. It concluded that the delays had a serious impact on the patients' health. Since the delayed diagnoses were found, four of the patients have died. The review examined the work of a locum consultant who no longer works there. The report reveals that eight serious reportable events have been found since the start of the review. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Patients launch cases on missed cancers at Kerry hospital - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/patients-launch-cases-on-missed-cancers-at-kerry-hospital-890219.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEyxAydUqm5qG6QF3OeJn1gqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 06:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/patients-launch-cases-on-missed-cancers-at-kerry-hospital-890219.html" target="_blank"&gt;Patients launch cases on missed cancers at Kerry hospital&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A number of patients whose cancer diagnosis was delayed or missed at University Hospital Kerry (UHK) have begun legal action. The move comes as an audit revealed that four out of 11 patients whose diagnoses were delayed have died. The delay in one case was 76 weeks. The patient has since died of lung cancer. In addition to the 11, another three patients’ cancer went undiagnosed. Among the deceased are: - A patient with advanced bone metastases whose diagnosis was delayed 37 weeks; - A patient with a rectal tumour whose diagnosis was delayed by seven weeks; - A patient with pancreatic cancer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>HSE spent €114m on agency staff up to September - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/ireland/2018/1128/1013987-hse-agency-staff/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOXyfpAfNDQW4dCSbzZ2hc0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 23:48:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/ireland/2018/1128/1013987-hse-agency-staff/" target="_blank"&gt;HSE spent €114m on agency staff up to September&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Health Service Executive has spent over €114m this year on agency staff up to September, according to figures released to Sinn Féin’s health spokesperson Louise O'Reilly. Agency staff are hired to plug staffing gaps, but can be significantly more expensive than direct employees. However, they do not enjoy job security, nor do they receive pension contributions. The hospitals with the highest agency spend so far this year were: the Midland Regional Hospital Portlaoise (€8.143m), University Hospital Limerick (€7.851m), Cavan Monaghan General Hospital (€6.970m), the Midland Regional Hospit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Cost of HSE’s €35m IT system continues to rise - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/cost-of-hses-35m-it-system-continues-to-rise-793164.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFHQfZJJ45S5H2Brh9u7QoYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 06:45:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/cost-of-hses-35m-it-system-continues-to-rise-793164.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cost of HSE’s €35m IT system continues to rise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An IT system for maternity hospitals that came with a €35m price tag has cost the HSE hundreds of thousands in additional consultancy fees, writes Catherine Shanahan. However, the final bill is likely to run to millions as 17 more maternity units have yet to have the system implemented. The rollout of the Maternal and Newborn Clinical Management System (MN-CMS) cost an additional €500,000 at Cork University Maternity Hospital (CUMH) and an extra €200,000 at University Hospital Kerry, with Deloitte brought in to get the project over the line. The Irish Examiner obtained the information follo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Man dies in fall on Co Kerry farm - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0116/845343-kerry-death/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAqwd1O_QpdN1f-OWA5jTsUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 21:01:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0116/845343-kerry-death/" target="_blank"&gt;Man dies in fall on Co Kerry farm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man in his 30s has died after he fell from a roof of a building in Co Kerry while carrying out maintenance work. The accident happened just before 12pm on a farm at Currow Village, near Farranfore. The man was taken by ambulance to Kerry General Hospital but was pronounced dead on arrival.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Boy critical after fall from upstairs window - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0223/854986-child-fall/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC7NdnUmf64jiMimtoL5eqsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 07:31:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0223/854986-child-fall/" target="_blank"&gt;Boy critical after fall from upstairs window&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A five-year-old boy is in a critical condition after falling from an upstairs window at his home in Co Kerry. The accident occurred on Tuesday in the family's rented home in Castleisland. The family are originally from Tralee. The boy sustained serious injuries as a result of the fall and was brought to Kerry University Hospital. He was later transferred to Temple Street Children's hospital in Dublin. Gardaí are treating the incident as an accident.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Boy who suffered 'devastating' brain injures settles case for €17.8m - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/courts/boy-who-suffered-devastating-brain-injures-settles-case-for-178m-35552254.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAXtZ3p3TGqVQb2f49vkd5kqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 17:04:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/courts/boy-who-suffered-devastating-brain-injures-settles-case-for-178m-35552254.html" target="_blank"&gt;Boy who suffered 'devastating' brain injures settles case for €17.8m&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A BOY who was brain damaged at birth is to receive a €15million lump sum payment in final settlement of his High Court case. It brings to €17.8m the total paid out to Tadgh Costello (10) in settlement of his action over "devastating" injuries suffered during his birth at Kerry General Hospital. Tadgh, of Gurrane East, Sunhill, Killorglin, Co Kerry, needs 24 hour care, cannot speak, and is confined to a wheelchair, the court heard. Approving the settlement, the President of the High Court, Mr Justice Peter Kelly, paid tribute to Tadgh's parents, Mary and Gerard Costello for the "extraordinar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Cyclist dies in collision with tractor in Kerry - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0510/874155-cyclist-death-kerry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDMZ41sk1XcHQ3VTm7IpYDIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 08:38:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0510/874155-cyclist-death-kerry/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyclist dies in collision with tractor in Kerry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A cyclist has died following in a collision with a tractor in Killarney, Co Kerry. The woman, who was in her 40s and from the area, was cycling with a group when she was involved in a collision with a tractor on the by-pass in Killarney at the junction with Lewis Road at around 7pm. The tractor was towing agricultural equipment. She was pronounced dead at the scene. The road has been closed for a forensic investigation. Gardaí say it will remain closed overnight. A post-mortem examination will be conducted on the woman's body at University Hospital Kerry in Tralee. Gardaí are appealing to w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Man in 60s dies after his van collides with a lorry - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/man-in-60s-dies-after-his-van-collides-with-a-lorry-36083156.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBNGQAl0VDI5Y-9PhHRSrzgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/man-in-60s-dies-after-his-van-collides-with-a-lorry-36083156.html" target="_blank"&gt;Man in 60s dies after his van collides with a lorry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man has died after his van collided with an articulated lorry. The man, aged in his 60s, whose name has not been released, was brought to Kerry University Hospital after the van he was driving collided with the truck at around 1pm yesterday. He later died of his injuries. The accident occurred at Ballyduff, Knocknagoshel, in Co Kerry, on the N21 Castleisland to Abbeyfeale Road. The truck driver was uninjured. Meanwhile, a pedestrian remained in a serious condition in hospital last night after being struck by a car in west Dublin. The incident occurred on the Ninth Lock Road, in Clondalkin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Man in his 60s has died following collision with articulated truck - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/man-in-his-60s-has-died-following-collision-with-articulated-truck-803840.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEORjIiL4ZIwqQzE7MJ1ja-wqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:15:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/man-in-his-60s-has-died-following-collision-with-articulated-truck-803840.html" target="_blank"&gt;Man in his 60s has died following collision with articulated truck&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gardaí in Listowel are investigating a two vehicle fatal road traffic collision that occurred at approximately 1pm today. The incident occurred at Ballyduff, Knocknagoshel, County Kerry on the N21 Castleisland to Abbeyfeale Road. A man in his 60s was seriously injured after his van was involved in a collision with an articulated truck. He was brought to Kerry University Hospital but was later pronounced dead. The driver of the truck was uninjured. This stretch of road is currently closed while it is being examined by Garda Forensic Collision Investigators. Gardaí wish to appeal for witnesse...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>HSE spends almost €300k burying patients - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/hse-spends-almost-300k-burying-patients-804618.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_ACA_dklGvbizwHsDkN9kqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 05:57:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/hse-spends-almost-300k-burying-patients-804618.html" target="_blank"&gt;HSE spends almost €300k burying patients&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The HSE has spent almost €300,000 over the past three years on burial expenses on patients who died in its care, writes Gordon Deegan. Some of those who the HSE assisted included those who were made homeless prior to admission to hospital and had no family. Figures from the HSE 2016 annual report shows that the executive last year spent €94,277 on “burial expenses”. [timgcap=Over three years Cork University Hospital spent more than €400,000 on burial expenses.]CUHUSETHISONE_large.jpg[/timg] This followed a spend under the same heading of €91,000 in 2015 and €106,000 in 2014. The detailed br...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Man remains in hospital after Kerry stabbing; Gardaí release four in connection with investigation - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/man-remains-in-hospital-after-kerry-stabbing-gardai-release-four-in-connection-with-investigation-807204.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAPjg5SI8v0FUxLfalh3AFgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 06:31:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/man-remains-in-hospital-after-kerry-stabbing-gardai-release-four-in-connection-with-investigation-807204.html" target="_blank"&gt;Man remains in hospital after Kerry stabbing; Gardaí release four in connection with investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One man remains in hospital this morning following a stabbing in County Kerry. Two men in their 20s were stabbed on Strand Street inTralee between 1.30am and 2am yesterday morning. One of them is still in University Hospital Kerry with non life-threatening injuries. Two men and two women were arrested in relation to the attack, but have since been released.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Man dies in two-vehicle collision in Co Kerry - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/munster/2017/0829/900890-ballyduff-fatal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIoTIhPrhrPoZ5YBIND3PwoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:56:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/munster/2017/0829/900890-ballyduff-fatal/" target="_blank"&gt;Man dies in two-vehicle collision in Co Kerry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man in his 60s has died following a two-vehicle collision in Co Kerry. The crash happened at Ballyduff on he N21 Castleisland to Abbeyfeale road at around 1pm. The man was seriously injured after the van he was driving collided with an articulated lorry. He was brought to University Hospital Kerry in Tralee where he was later pronounced dead. The driver of the lorry was not injured. The road was closed for a forensic examination. Anyone with any information is asked to contact Listowel Garda Station on 068-50820, the Garda Confidential line on 1800 666 111 or any garda station.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Four people arrested after two men stabbed in Co Kerry - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/four-people-arrested-after-two-men-stabbed-in-co-kerry-807168.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIhT68FuDW6iV6BhBQ4KYAIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 19:17:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/four-people-arrested-after-two-men-stabbed-in-co-kerry-807168.html" target="_blank"&gt;Four people arrested after two men stabbed in Co Kerry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four people have been arrested after two young men were stabbed in Tralee, Co Kerry in the early hours of this morning. The two men, both in their early 20s, suffered stab wounds at Strand Street, Tralee sometime between 12.30am and 1am. Both men were taken to University Hospital Kerry where one man's injuries were described as not serious and he was later released. The other victim remains in hospital but gardai understand his condition is not life-threatening. Four people - two men and two women who are foreign nationals - were arrested and are detained at Listowel, Killarney and Castleis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Young child in critical condition after falling from upstairs window of home - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/young-child-in-critical-condition-after-falling-from-upstairs-window-of-home-35477895.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG9GLEHThOJE0CvQVFVQDpcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 22:49:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/young-child-in-critical-condition-after-falling-from-upstairs-window-of-home-35477895.html" target="_blank"&gt;Young child in critical condition after falling from upstairs window of home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A young child is in critical condition after falling from an upstairs window at his home in Co Kerry. The incident occurred on Tuesday at about 3.40pm in the family's home at Hogan's Place in the centre of Castleisland. The boy suffered serious injuries as a result of the fall and was immediately rushed to University Hospital Kerry. Gardai also attended the scene, but have not confirmed how they will be treating this incident.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>HSE forgets to link maternity system to GPs - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/hse-forgets-to-link-maternity-system-to-gps-805724.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwQU2kCV-VSaaoOEuRjbEoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 06:51:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/hse-forgets-to-link-maternity-system-to-gps-805724.html" target="_blank"&gt;HSE forgets to link maternity system to GPs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A €35m IT system designed to improve care for mothers and babies and cut down on paperwork has created more work for staff and more room for error because of a failure to link it up with GP IT systems,writes Catherine Shanahan. The oversight means the electronic health record in the hospital and the electronic record held by family doctors cannot ‘talk’ to each other — even though GPs and maternity hospitals operate a shared-care model for mums-to-be. Sources told the Irish Examiner this “digital gap” had resulted in significant duplication, requiring double entry of information when resour...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Mixed sex wards as bed crisis deepens - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/mixed-sex-wards-as-bed-crisis-deepens-35503025.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP-uwQkNsAZ3h2XOXKMO12sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/mixed-sex-wards-as-bed-crisis-deepens-35503025.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mixed sex wards as bed crisis deepens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women and men are being treated together in 'mixed gender' wards due to the ongoing shortage of hospital beds, the Sunday Independent has learned. Many of the country's 52 hospitals are now ditching the traditional gender divide, because of the acute pressure on bed space. Despite concerns this practice can be "extremely distressing" for certain patients, it is increasingly used in coronary care, intensive care, high dependency units, acute medical assessment centres, as well as day ward and admission areas. Elderly women, in particular, are often uncomfortable when asked to share a mixed-s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Boy critical after falling from window - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/boy-critical-after-falling-from-window-35478451.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBznyiuMdP7kp1IerWO5PHEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/boy-critical-after-falling-from-window-35478451.html" target="_blank"&gt;Boy critical after falling from window&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A young child is in critical condition after falling from an upstairs window at his home in Co Kerry. The incident occurred on Tuesday at about 3.40pm in the family's home at Hogan's Place in the centre of Castleisland. The boy suffered serious injuries as a result of the fall and was immediately rushed to University Hospital Kerry. Gardai also attended the scene, but have not confirmed how they will be treating this incident.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Boy brain injured at birth settles case for €17.8m - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/courts/2017/0321/861493-tadgh-costello/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENp7I94xg5Qy3FGZoEtR9DQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 12:00:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/courts/2017/0321/861493-tadgh-costello/" target="_blank"&gt;Boy brain injured at birth settles case for €17.8m&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The High Court has approved a settlement of €15m in the case of a 10-year-old boy who was brain injured at birth. It brings to €17.8m the total awarded to Tadgh Costello from Killorglin Co Kerry, one of the highest awards on record. The money will be held and managed by the High Court on his behalf for what will be complex medical and care needs for the rest of his life. In emotional testimony to the High Court the boy's mother said "all the millions in the world would not fix" what had happened to her son. She told the judge the family was happy if the court approved a lump sum award and m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>German tourist (61) airlifted to hospital after breaking ankle in hiking beauty spot - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/news/german-tourist-61-airlifted-to-hospital-after-breaking-ankle-in-hiking-beauty-spot-35627549.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECV3ZXVum2k-_skhDoMljMAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 18:20:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/irish-news/news/german-tourist-61-airlifted-to-hospital-after-breaking-ankle-in-hiking-beauty-spot-35627549.html" target="_blank"&gt;German tourist (61) airlifted to hospital after breaking ankle in hiking beauty spot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A German tourist has been airlifted to hospital after breaking an ankle while hiking in a beauty spot in West Cork this afternoon. The 61-year-old woman sustained the injury while hiking near Gougane Barra. But due to the remote location where she was injured, the Shannon Rescue helicopter 115 was dispatched to the scene to aid members of the Kerry Mountain Rescue team. The woman was then airlifted to Kerry University Hospital in Tralee.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Cork University Hospital tops table for car parking fees - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/cork-university-hospital-tops-table-for-car-parking-fees-785379.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPyUnfmZhQDbRQze4sTxgFAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 13:33:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/cork-university-hospital-tops-table-for-car-parking-fees-785379.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cork University Hospital tops table for car parking fees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eight hospitals collected just over €11.2m in car parking fees last year, it has been reported. According to a report on Today with Sean O'Rourke on RTÉ Radio 1, parking rates ranged from €3.20 for the first hour in Our Lady’s Childrens’ Hospital in Crumlin, to €4 for three hours in Waterford. Two hospitals in Dublin and six from around the rest from around the country were looked at. Of the eight surveyed, Cork University Hospital collected the most parking fees last year (€3.1m). University Hospital Kerry the least (€636,000). Cork University Hospital said that the income is used for the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Fianna Fáil: Key services at risk in Kerry Hospital - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fianna-fail-key-services-at-risk-in-kerry-hospital-881936.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEImFrLnSIgGbI53sa1cmorUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 02:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fianna-fail-key-services-at-risk-in-kerry-hospital-881936.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fianna Fáil: Key services at risk in Kerry Hospital&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pending loss of a key clinician at University Hospital Kerry (UHK) could jeopardise surgical services and cancer screening services, according to Fianna Fáil health spokesman Stephen Donnelly. The hospital’s only consultant pathologist gave notice of intention to leave last July and will finish up at UHK on December 31. Fianna Fáil health spokesman Stephen Donnelly Mr Donnelly said one doctor he spoke to said there were concerns future histopathology work would be carried out by a locum, or with "some form of patchwork cover” from other hospitals in the South/South- West group, and if t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Healy-Rae sends patients to Belfast for hip and knee replacements to avoid a four-year wait - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/healy-rae-buses-patients-to-belfast-for-hip-and-knee-replacements-4317747-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjt9If61Che1GBNFyzPRAEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 06:01:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/healy-rae-buses-patients-to-belfast-for-hip-and-knee-replacements-4317747-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Healy-Rae sends patients to Belfast for hip and knee replacements to avoid a four-year wait&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEPUTY MICHAEL HEALY-RAE is booking buses to take people from Kerry to Belfast for hip and knee replacements because they are waiting between three to four years for the operations in Kerry. Tomorrow, 14 people awaiting cataract surgery will make the six-hour journey from Kerry to Belfast, joining 2,234 Irish patients who have had to travel outside of the State for healthcare in 2018. “In our hospital here in Kerry we have not done an operation on a hip or a knee since June,” said Healy-Rae. It is ridiculous to think that people are on a list, but what they don’t realise is that there is no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>HSE says 'there is no question' of downgrading University Hospital Kerry despite local concerns - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/hospital-kerry-4199956-Aug2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENLNt65-nfGq7htoxHS0EC4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 05:15:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/hospital-kerry-4199956-Aug2018/" target="_blank"&gt;HSE says 'there is no question' of downgrading University Hospital Kerry despite local concerns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HSE HAS moved to reassure patients in the south about the status of University Hospital Kerry following fears that it could be downgraded. The Tralee hospital has previously been the focus of attention over missed diagnoses within the radiology department and a local politician has now questioned the standard of management within the hospital. This week, Sinn Féin councillor Toiréasa Ferris told Radio na Gaeltachta that she feared the hospital could be effectively downgraded due to what she says was a lack of investment. The councillor said that she spoke to one particular patient recen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Heart attack death rates much higher in some hospitals - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/heart-attack-death-rates-much-higher-in-some-hospitals-37082803.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBfLCIkTCkyIyBFrsD8N-9cqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/heart-attack-death-rates-much-higher-in-some-hospitals-37082803.html" target="_blank"&gt;Heart attack death rates much higher in some hospitals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A number of hospitals have significantly higher death rates due to heart attacks and strokes than the national average, according to a new report from the Department of Health. Portiuncula Hospital in Ballinasloe, Co Galway, has the highest death rate from heart attack within 30 days of admission, at 8.71 per 100 cases over 2015-2017. Other hospitals with high mortality include St Vincent's Hospital in Dublin at 8.53 per 100 cases. It is also high in Cavan General Hospital, Bantry General Hospital, Waterford Regional Hospital and Kerry General Hospital. The national average, according to th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Investigation after baby girl stillborn following assault - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/investigation-after-baby-girl-stillborn-following-assault-37049842.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECB1qsgHxlzosBjOMEpig10qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/investigation-after-baby-girl-stillborn-following-assault-37049842.html" target="_blank"&gt;Investigation after baby girl stillborn following assault&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gardaí are investigating after a baby was stillborn following an assault on a woman in Listowel, Co Kerry, over the weekend. The incident, involving a woman who was around 32 weeks pregnant, occurred on Saturday evening in the vicinity of a house in the town. The woman, who is a mother to other children and is in her 30s, attended University Hospital Kerry (UHK) in Tralee, Co Kerry, for treatment to her injuries on Sunday. Bruising Sources told the Irish Independent that she suffered significant bruising to her abdomen and to other parts of her body. It is understood the woman subsequently ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Girl who suffered brain damage in birth at Kerry General Hospital secures further payout - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/girl-who-suffered-brain-damage-in-birth-at-kerry-general-hospital-secures-further-payout-828254.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENk3oiEoNhex2HsqcFQ3b0IqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 13:51:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/girl-who-suffered-brain-damage-in-birth-at-kerry-general-hospital-secures-further-payout-828254.html" target="_blank"&gt;Girl who suffered brain damage in birth at Kerry General Hospital secures further payout&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Ann O'Loughlin A young girl who suffered brain damage during her birth at Kerry General Hospital has secured a further interim payment under a settlement of her action against the HSE, increasing to more than €3.8m her total damages to date. The President of the High Court, Mr Justice Peter Kelly, paid warm tribute to Skye Worthington's mother Colleen for her "admirable" care for her daughter, including moving from Kerry to Rochestown, Co. Cork, to be close to the Enable Ireland school the child attends. It had proved very difficult to access the necessary services for Skye, now aged six...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Ten patients now affected by scan recheck at UHK - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/munster/2018/0126/936136-kerry-hospital-scans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFEDfyanzAz8MB8SD7r0XAwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 14:17:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/munster/2018/0126/936136-kerry-hospital-scans/" target="_blank"&gt;Ten patients now affected by scan recheck at UHK&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of patients affected by a delayed or missed diagnosis, arising from the University Hospital Kerry scans recheck, has risen to ten. Two more cases have emerged in the past week and the hospital has confirmed that all ten patients require a further follow-up. The total number of patients recalled so far for repeat scans is 180. At least three of the delayed diagnosis cases involve cancer. The health status of the patients affected is not known. The problem at the Kerry hospital was first revealed in December and so far over 38,200 of the 46,200 X-rays, ultrasound or CAT scans invol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Another missed diagnosis at Kerry hospital as 180 patients asked back for repeat scans - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/kerry-missed-diagnoses-3817395-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFpyueqsCD_Chdeg8v5NcwgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 20:10:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/kerry-missed-diagnoses-3817395-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Another missed diagnosis at Kerry hospital as 180 patients asked back for repeat scans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANOTHER PATIENT HAS been notified of a missed diagnosis as part of the comprehensive review of radiology scans at University Hospital Kerry. This brings the total number of patients who have been informed of missed diagnoses to 10. Furthermore, the total number of patients who have been recalled for repeat scans to date is now 180. Some 46,000 patient files, including x-rays, scans and ultrasounds are being re-examined after it emerged a locum radiologist missed or misdiagnosed seven serious cases involving cancer and other diseases. As of today, South/South West Hospital Group has said tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Three cancer cases among 10 Kerry Hospital patients affected by missed scan diagnosis - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/at-least-three-cancer-cases-among-10-kerry-scan-follow-ups-824924.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEAyS8CdujOVlX0Fb_XIUEEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 09:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/at-least-three-cancer-cases-among-10-kerry-scan-follow-ups-824924.html" target="_blank"&gt;Three cancer cases among 10 Kerry Hospital patients affected by missed scan diagnosis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Catherine Shanahan The number of patients affected by either missed or delayed diagnoses at University Hospital Kerry following a review of scans has risen to 10. The figure includes at least three cancer cases. To date, 180 patients have been recalled for repeat imaging. Last week, four of those recalled required further investigation, in addition to another four the previous week. This week, the South South West Hospital Group said an additional two patients will require further investigation. This brings to 10 the overall number in need of additional follow-ups. University Hospital Ke...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>University Hospital Kerry has recalled 72 patients for a re-scan during review - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/news/university-hospital-kerry-72-patients-612509</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG6ZC7aI9_pEB8K_aOKfN9EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8wsb2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 13:13:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/news/university-hospital-kerry-72-patients-612509" target="_blank"&gt;University Hospital Kerry has recalled 72 patients for a re-scan during review&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;University Hospital Kerry is over three-quarters of the way through one of the largest medical reviews in Irish History. University Hospital Kerry has recalled 72 patients for repeat scanning as of 11 January, after it was discovered in December 2017 that seven people had received a delayed cancer diagnosis over the previous five months. In total, the hospital has been required to review over 46,000 images after management was notified back in July that staff had missed a cancer diagnosis. With two more patients presenting themselves in August, each being described as an obvious case of can...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Garda probe after man (20s) found with serious head injuries - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/garda-probe-after-man-20s-found-with-serious-head-injuries-36486230.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-YNloH9W-mLlfuaSibyoEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 13:19:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/garda-probe-after-man-20s-found-with-serious-head-injuries-36486230.html" target="_blank"&gt;Garda probe after man (20s) found with serious head injuries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gardai are investigating after a man (20s) was found with serious head injuries in Co Kerry. The injured man was found by neighbours lying on a street near his home at St Stephen's Park, Castleisland at around 5.30am this morning. He was unconscious and had suffered severe head injuries. The man was taken by ambulance to University Hospital Kerry in Tralee, from where he has been transferred to Cork University Hospital. Gardai said the man remains in a serious condition in hospital. An investigation is underway and gardai are appealing for witnesses to contact them. They have cordoned off t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>At least 72 patients called back for scan review at Kerry hospital - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/kerry-hospital-scan-review-3793874-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE7sM4kgJZ785vK5c3C8eucqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 09:28:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/kerry-hospital-scan-review-3793874-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;At least 72 patients called back for scan review at Kerry hospital&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A KERRY HOSPITAL has confirmed that the scans of 72 people need to be reviewed after concerns were raised about a radiologist who worked at the hospital. Today, the Irish Examiner reported that four of those patients were found to need additional treatment after the review. The South/South West Hospital Group confirmed that a review was underway at University Hospital Kerry, which as of today is 73.4% completed. Of 46,235 images that have been earmarked for review, 33,950 have been completed. The scans that have been reviewed so far represent a total of 20,367 patients, with 6,389 patients ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>'Badly injured' man found in Kerry housing estate - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/man-found-injured-in-kerry-housing-estate-3797099-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGCmJN3ktNph0zfdRsDWHvYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 14:03:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/man-found-injured-in-kerry-housing-estate-3797099-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'Badly injured' man found in Kerry housing estate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GARDAÍ ARE INVESTIGATING the discovery of a badly injured man at a housing estate in Kerry. The man was found in St Stephens Park, Castleisland, County Kerry at 5.30am this morning. The man in his late 20s was taken to University Hospital Kerry and subsequently transferred to Cork University Hospital, where he is in a serious condition. The area where the man was found is sealed off pending an examination of the scene by Garda crime scene examiner. Gardaí are appealing for anyone with information or anyone who was in the St Stephen’s Park area of Castleisland to contact them at Tralee Garda...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>The 9 at 9: Friday - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/news-irish-friday-3793714-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFbVvHMn23UeMr6oE3djvSwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 08:55:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/news-irish-friday-3793714-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;The 9 at 9: Friday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVERY MORNING, TheJournal.ie brings you the stories you need to know as you start your day. 1. #CRITICISM: US President Donald Trump asked why the US would accept more immigrants from Haiti and “shithole countries” in Africa rather than places like Norway. 2. #HPV VACCINE: The HSE has advised parents to base decisions about the cervical cancer vaccine on medical advice and not from anonymous social media posts. 3. #LONDON AIN’T CALLING: Donald Trump has cancelled a planned brief visit to London, citing a sale by the Obama administration as his reason. 4. #SCANS: At least 72 patients at Univ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Danny Healy-Rae denies asking hospital to allow patient to jump queue for treatment - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/danny-healy-rae-denies-asking-hospital-to-allow-patient-to-jump-queue-for-treatment-822159.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA4K9Rpsquzk-8I-kX9ds4YqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 17:18:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/danny-healy-rae-denies-asking-hospital-to-allow-patient-to-jump-queue-for-treatment-822159.html" target="_blank"&gt;Danny Healy-Rae denies asking hospital to allow patient to jump queue for treatment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Kerry TD says he did not ask University Hospital Kerry to prioritise a constituent. Deputy Danny Healy-Rae admits calling the hospital's Emergency Department earlier this month during the ongoing trolley crisis. However, he claims the call was made to represent a constituent and source information and it is something he has done on numerous occasions. However, the Independent TD adds he never asked staff to fast-track a constituent. He said: "At no point did I ask that anyone be allowed to jump the queue, whether it was a trolley or whether it was a bed. "And if it was pointed out to me t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Kerry Cllr calls for HSE to clarify cancelled surgery reports - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/kerry-cllr-calls-for-hse-to-clarify-cancelled-surgery-reports-821556.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKClR0VfsJ_Q79J8UXGdpSAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 18:52:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/kerry-cllr-calls-for-hse-to-clarify-cancelled-surgery-reports-821556.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kerry Cllr calls for HSE to clarify cancelled surgery reports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Kerry County Councillor has called on the HSE to clarify reports of cancelled surgeries in University Hospital Kerry. Toiréasa Ferris says she received reports that all scheduled surgeries have been cancelled at the hospital, due to the ongoing crisis over the shortage of beds. She says patients have to, already, spend unacceptably long periods on waiting lists, and for them to be now told that planned surgeries are being cancelled is shattering. Councillor Ferris is calling on the HSE and UHK management to clarify the situation. She said: "We received information yesterday afternoon that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Harris has 'open mind' over independent review on scans - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/1229/930046-kerry-hospital-scans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOuiPC-tIGCgr-Kl8YOeMRIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 17:52:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/1229/930046-kerry-hospital-scans/" target="_blank"&gt;Harris has 'open mind' over independent review on scans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minister for Health Simon Harris has said he will keep "an open mind" in relation to asking the Health Information and Quality Authority to carry out an independent review into how the University Hospital Kerry scans issue was handled. Mr Harris was speaking to RTÉ News at Temple Theatre in Dublin this morning, where the Department of Health published new figures showing record organ transplant and donor numbers this year. It was revealed that the number of patients recalled as a result of the University Hospital Kerry scans review has now increased to 45. According to the minister, 60% of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Being recalled for scan should not be viewed as a 'bad thing' - Harris - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/being-recalled-for-scan-should-not-be-viewed-as-a-bad-thing-harris-36445382.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIalp6lm8iQpBm6sREUbzqUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/being-recalled-for-scan-should-not-be-viewed-as-a-bad-thing-harris-36445382.html" target="_blank"&gt;Being recalled for scan should not be viewed as a 'bad thing' - Harris&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simon Harris has said the majority of people being recalled for scans at University Hospital Kerry were being contacted as a "precautionary measure". The Health Minister said it was of the utmost importance that it wasn't viewed as a "bad thing" that people were being recalled for scans. The number of patients recalled as a result of the University Hospital Kerry scans review has now increased to 45. The review was launched after seven patients had a serious delayed diagnosis, of which at least three involve cancer. The Health Information and Quality Authority (Hiqa) is carrying out the ind...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>The 5 at 5: Friday - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/5-at-5-friday-52-3773318-Dec2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDBX5tJx2IdBB0YZ-YesDpQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 17:00:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/5-at-5-friday-52-3773318-Dec2017/" target="_blank"&gt;The 5 at 5: Friday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVERY WEEKDAY EVENING, TheJournal.ie brings you the five biggest stories of the day. 1. #STORM DYLAN A snow-ice warning has been issued for 14 counties ahead of tonight’s arrival of Storm Dylan. 2. #I DO Fine Gael senator Jerry Buttimer tied the knot in Cork today. 3. #EGYPT A gunman killed nine people in an attack on a church. 4. #PASSPORTS A record number of passports were issued in Ireland this year. 5. #KERRY HOSPITAL Two new patients need further treatment after their scans were reviewed at Kerry Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Almost 22,000 scans reviewed at University Hospital Kerry - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/almost-22000-scans-reviewed-at-university-hospital-kerry-819880.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFp4y6kG9OQH4f3aiGRpTsAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 20:23:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/almost-22000-scans-reviewed-at-university-hospital-kerry-819880.html" target="_blank"&gt;Almost 22,000 scans reviewed at University Hospital Kerry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A review of scans at University Hospital Kerry is more than half-way complete. The South/South West Hospital Group says almost 22,000 images have been reviewed to date. It says so far, 34 patients have been recalled - but no further clinical follow up has been required. The review was announced earlier this week covering scans between March 2016 to July 2017. A 9-to-5 helpline set up for those affected remains open Monday to Friday, on 1800-742-900. - Digital Desk&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Missing walker on Carrauntouhil found safe and well - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/news/missing-walker-carrauntouhil-found-safe-well-611110</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJqmWlZoeEBZVRMtHn1CilIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8woL6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 11:46:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/news/missing-walker-carrauntouhil-found-safe-well-611110" target="_blank"&gt;Missing walker on Carrauntouhil found safe and well&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The alarm was raised yesterday when the man phoned the Guards to inform them that he was missing. A walker who had been missing on Carrauntoohil since last night has been found safe and well by the team at Kerry Mountain Rescue. The missing man is believed to be of German descent, and in his 30s. He has since been airlifted to University Hospital Kerry by Shannon-based R115. It's believed that the man was located high on the mountain in a notoriously tricky area called the Bone. A search to find the man began yesterday, but was was suspended at about 1am due to extreme weather. It's underst...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>34 patients recalled so far in Kerry hospital review - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/health/2017/1222/929146-kerry-hospital-review/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIjmIWrEj8TaXYQ01NYzdvEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 15:54:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/health/2017/1222/929146-kerry-hospital-review/" target="_blank"&gt;34 patients recalled so far in Kerry hospital review&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;University Hospital Kerry has said that 34 patients have so far been recalled following a review of scans. The review was ordered after concern was raised during the summer over a number of cases. It relates to X-rays, ultrasound and CAT scans carried out between March 2016 and July of this year. The hospital has admitted a number of serious delayed diagnoses. The latest update from the hospital has said that 21,850 images have now been reviewed of 46,300 still to be checked. A helpline remains open daily from 9am-5pm and can contacted on 1800 742 900. It is expected to take around six week...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Patient claims he has devloped inoperable tumour after delayed Kerry hosptial diagnosis - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/siptu-to-attend-talks-with-senior-uhk-management-819339.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQJoDVIZpV0yRnJW7YmeOQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 10:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/siptu-to-attend-talks-with-senior-uhk-management-819339.html" target="_blank"&gt;Patient claims he has devloped inoperable tumour after delayed Kerry hosptial diagnosis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Update 10am: The family of a patient at University Hospital Kerry claim he has developed an inoperable tumour after a delayed diagnosis. A re-check of 46,000 scans is underway after errors were found with a number of results. The problems are being linked to a single radiographer who worked there during March 2016 and July of this year. So far University Hospital Kerry has acknowledged that seven serious cancer cases were missed or misdiagnosed. Tralee Sinn Féin Councillor, Toiréasa Ferris, has been approached by the family of one of those patients. "There was a six-month delay between when...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>HSE boss admits Kerry scans ‘a serious issue’ - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/hse-boss-admits-kerry-scans-a-serious-issue-819735.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEClqu0EmnsVkgmbvfZGUK0wqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 09:24:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/hse-boss-admits-kerry-scans-a-serious-issue-819735.html" target="_blank"&gt;HSE boss admits Kerry scans ‘a serious issue’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HSE director general Tony O’Brien has described the Kerry University Hospital scans controversy as “a serious issue”, writes Evelyn Ring. Mr O’Brien said that around 20,000 images had already been checked before the lookback became public and there had been 700 follow-up clinical reviews. He pointed out that the review of 46,000 patient scans that began in October had found “five serious reportable events and five serious incidents”. Mr O’Brien described it as a “quality assurance process” that was being carried out effectively and efficiently and in a way that was in the best interests of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Helpline opens for patients affected by University Hospital Kerry review - Newstalk Newsfeed</title><link>http://www.newstalk.com/Helpline-opens-for-patients-affected-by-University-Hospital-Kerry-review</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJj8Bvb2YNMrkS9H-_hire8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowmeSfCTCcwW8wmpuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 10:19:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.newstalk.com/Helpline-opens-for-patients-affected-by-University-Hospital-Kerry-review" target="_blank"&gt;Helpline opens for patients affected by University Hospital Kerry review&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newstalk Newsfeed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Updated: 10.20 A helpline has opened for patients worried about scans at University Hospital Kerry. It comes as a review is being conducted of some 46,000 x-rays, cat scans and ultra sounds amid patient safety concerns at the hospital. This follows the notification of three Serious Reportable Events (SREs) over the course of the summer. Scans of some 26,000 people are involved in the process, with two or three scams per person in some cases. A dedicated information line has been established at 1800-742-900. It will operate from 9.00am to 5.00pm Monday to Friday. The review, which was starte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.newstalk.com">Newstalk Newsfeed</source></item><item><title>Consultant at centre of Kerry scan review was a locum - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/1219/928367-kerry-hospital-scan-review/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIGUK9N0usITZhM1hjVy5TAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 18:02:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/1219/928367-kerry-hospital-scan-review/" target="_blank"&gt;Consultant at centre of Kerry scan review was a locum&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consultant radiologist at the centre of a scans re-check at University Hospital Kerry, who worked at the hospital until recently, was a locum and not a permanent member of staff, RTÉ News has confirmed. The doctor was employed through a locum agency based in Ireland. RTÉ News has also established that the doctor worked as a consultant radiologist at the Mater Hospital in Dublin in January and February 2006. The doctor also worked at the same hospital from June 1996 to July 1997. Yesterday, the Health Service Executive said that no issue arose in relation to the doctor's time in two sepa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>University Hospital Kerry reviewing over 46,000 scans after concerns raised - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/hospital-scan-review-3755329-Dec2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECaA7a-zW0l5eacgWUG4mSsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 15:26:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/hospital-scan-review-3755329-Dec2017/" target="_blank"&gt;University Hospital Kerry reviewing over 46,000 scans after concerns raised&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A REVIEW IS being carried out on 46,000 x-rays, cat scans and ultra sounds by University Hospital Kerry. The South/ South West Hospital Group (SSWHG) confirmed today that it is investigating patient safety concerns at UHK. The investigation comes following the notification of three Serious Reportable Events (SREs) over the course of the summer. The scans relates to 26,000 people, with two or three per person in some cases. A hospital spokesperson confirmed that of Friday, 18,000 files had been reviewed and a small number of these have resulted in patient call back. The “look back” process i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Employee suspended as University Hospital Kerry conducts review of over 46,000 files - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/employee-suspended-as-university-hospital-kerry-conducts-review-of-over-46000-files-36415275.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFk4kAf5J_h7XYl98NR980UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 13:47:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/employee-suspended-as-university-hospital-kerry-conducts-review-of-over-46000-files-36415275.html" target="_blank"&gt;Employee suspended as University Hospital Kerry conducts review of over 46,000 files&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A hospital employee has been suspended as University Hospital Kerry conducts a review of over 46,000 scans or files. The files involve over 26,700 patients in an area that includes Kerry, north Cork and south Limerick. RTE News reports today that the reports are from the period of March 2016 to July 2017. The review involves a range of scans including x-rays, ultrasound and MRIs. Concerns were first raised during the summer, when three "serious reportable events" were notified regarding a specialist. An initial audit of a sample of scans was conducted, which since lead to a major review of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Here's What Happened Today: Sunday - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/evening-fix-93-3755793-Dec2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFWYKVPTS8VsIesWPYWdbgsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 19:44:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/evening-fix-93-3755793-Dec2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's What Happened Today: Sunday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEED TO CATCH up? TheJournal.ie brings you a round-up of today’s news. IRELAND - Ryanair management and Impact union officials are set to meet on Tuesday to avert a planned strike on Wednesday. - The Communications Minister confirmed he would ask the broadcasting authority to provide clarity to over referenda coverage after the Children’s Minister was axed from appearing on a popular cooking show. - It’s been revealed that the busiest day in the Dáil bar was 14 June – the day Leo Varadkar became Taoiseach and announced his new Cabinet. - University Hospital Kerry said that it was reviewing ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>26-year-old woman has died after she was hit by car in Kerry - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/26-year-old-woman-has-died-after-she-was-hit-by-car-in-kerry-816774.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAQ3n1H_B_wsjWNriuN-TbgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 08:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/26-year-old-woman-has-died-after-she-was-hit-by-car-in-kerry-816774.html" target="_blank"&gt;26-year-old woman has died after she was hit by car in Kerry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 26-year-old woman has died after she was hit by a car in Kerry. The woman was struck on the N22 at Glenflesk village shortly after 7 o'clock yesterday evening. The Coroner was notified and the body of the woman has been removed to University Hospital Kerry for a post-mortem examination. The road was closed to facilitate a forensic examination but has since reopened to traffic. Gardaí are appealing for witnesses.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Cyclist killed in Kerry road crash - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/munster/2017/1122/921936-cyclist-kerry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJOc8PBcSsllADo_n0QI910qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 16:29:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/munster/2017/1122/921936-cyclist-kerry/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyclist killed in Kerry road crash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man has died following a road crash near Tralee, Co Kerry last night. The 39-year-old cyclist was involved in a collision with two cars at Tonevane shortly after 8pm. He was taken to University Hospital Kerry where he was pronounced dead. A man and a woman driving the two cars were taken to hospital with minor injuries. Gardaí have appealed for witnesses to contact them at Tralee Garda Station on 066-7102300.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Motorcyclist killed in Co Kerry collision - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/munster/2017/1120/921588-kerry-collision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFNJy5o2wvHYIW82Oft8pdAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 08:06:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/munster/2017/1120/921588-kerry-collision/" target="_blank"&gt;Motorcyclist killed in Co Kerry collision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A motorcyclist has died following a collision with a car in Listowel, Co Kerry. The man, who was in his 50s, was seriously injured in the collision and pronounced dead at the scene. His body has been removed to University Hospital Kerry in Tralee. The collision happened on the R523 at Shanacool Cross. An appeal for witnesses has been issued and anyone who travelled along the Listowel to Athea Road at Shanacool Cross between 4.45pm and 5.15pm are asked to contact Listowel Garda Station on 068 50820, the Garda Confidential Line on 1800 666 111 or any garda station.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Motorcyclist (50s) dies after collision with car, investigation underway - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/motorcyclist-50s-dies-after-collision-with-car-investigation-underway-36338493.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGfLp8Nn1-Zx-OAjRsl75K4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 21:31:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/motorcyclist-50s-dies-after-collision-with-car-investigation-underway-36338493.html" target="_blank"&gt;Motorcyclist (50s) dies after collision with car, investigation underway&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A motorcyclist in his 50s has died after he was involved in a collision with a car. The man was pronounced dead at the scene of the crash which occurred on the R523 at Shanacool Cross, Listowel this evening at approximately 5pm. Gardai in Listowel are investigating the crash. The victim was removed to University Hospital Kerry in Tralee. This scene of the crash is currently closed to facilitate an examination by garda forensic collision investigators and local diversions are in place. The road is expected to remain closed overnight. "Gardai wish to appeal for witnesses who were travelling...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Cyclist dies in accident involving two cars in Kerry - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/cyclist-dies-in-accident-involving-two-cars-in-kerry-815288.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELAaz3uTDvvWmy7sR2UcDMQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 08:06:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/cyclist-dies-in-accident-involving-two-cars-in-kerry-815288.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cyclist dies in accident involving two cars in Kerry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A cyclist has died after being involved in a collision with two cars in Co. Kerry last night. It happened in Tonevane near Tralee at around 8.15pm last night. A 39-year-old man who was riding a bicycle was seriously injured and taken to Kerry University Hospital where he later passed away. The two car drivers, a man in his early 40s and a woman in her mid-50s, were taken to hospital with minor injuries. The road is closed for a forensic examination and diversions are in place. It is expected to stay closed for the morning. Gardaí wish to appeal for witnesses who were in the townland of Tone...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Cyclist (39) dies following collision involving two cars - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/cyclist-39-dies-following-collision-involving-two-cars-36342923.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECo5MnxXYw7fkMezj3Kfs0UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 08:08:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/cyclist-39-dies-following-collision-involving-two-cars-36342923.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cyclist (39) dies following collision involving two cars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A male cyclist was killed following a collision involving his bicycle and two cars in Kerry last night. Gardaí are investigating the fatal road traffic collision that occurred in the townland of Tonevane, Tralee at approximately 8.15pm last night. The cyclist (39) was seriously injured and removed to Kerry University Hospital where he later passed away. Both drivers, one man in his early forties and one woman in her mid-fifties, were removed to hospital with minor injuries. The road is currently closed to facilitate an examination by Garda Forensic Collision Investigators and local diversio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>HSE staff urged to attend 2-hour 'kindness' workshops - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/hse-staff-urged-to-attend-2-hour-kindness-workshops-815104.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO5ACjGIaNbwm1X8PPmVuakqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 07:38:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/hse-staff-urged-to-attend-2-hour-kindness-workshops-815104.html" target="_blank"&gt;HSE staff urged to attend 2-hour 'kindness' workshops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Catherine Shanahan Kindness costs nothing, as the saying goes — unless you are a HSE employee, whereupon it could cost two hours of your working day. For an organisation with no real ratings on the warm and fuzzy scale, staff were left bemused by a recent internal circular inviting them to participate in ‘Kindness Workshops’. “The two-hour workshop aims to share the most recent evidence and research on human kindness and establishes the link between kindness and productivity,” the circular said. A cynic might suggest the “link between kindness and productivity” is the real driver of this...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Motorcyclist dies in Kerry traffic accident - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/motorcyclist-dies-in-kerry-traffic-accident-815054.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGVKRuoiCq7_93gAKIZ2CncqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 21:18:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/motorcyclist-dies-in-kerry-traffic-accident-815054.html" target="_blank"&gt;Motorcyclist dies in Kerry traffic accident&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A motorcyclist has died in a road accident in Co Kerry this evening. The incident happened on the R523 at Shanacool Cross, Listowel at around 5pm. The man, aged in his 50s, was fatally injured when his motorcycle and a car were in collision. He was pronounced dead at the scene and his body was removed to University Hospital Kerry in Tralee. This stretch of road is currently closed to facilitate an examination by Garda Forensic Collision Investigators and local diversions are in place. The road is expected to remain closed overnight. Gardaí wish to appeal for witnesses who were travelling al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Cyclist dies following road collision with two cars in Kerry - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/cyclist-fatality-tralee-kerry-3710008-Nov2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-t-yrjbjuJDnpoFWp1oE8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 08:21:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/cyclist-fatality-tralee-kerry-3710008-Nov2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyclist dies following road collision with two cars in Kerry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A CYCLIST HAS died following a road collision with two cars in Tralee, Co Kerry last night. The incident happened in the townland of Tonevane, Tralee at around 8.15pm. The male cyclist (39) was seriously injured in the collision. He was taken to Kerry University Hospital where he later passed away. Both drivers, a male in his early 40s and a woman in her mid 50s, were taken to hospital with minor injuries. The road is currently closed to facilitate an examination by garda forensic collision investigators and local diversions are in place. The road is expected to remain closed for the rest o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item></channel></rss>