<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Seanad Éireann - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREV6Y3psdEVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:04:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Ronan Mullen pledges to 'fight the good fight' in Seanad abortion debate - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ronan-mullen-pledges-to-fight-the-good-fight-in-seanad-abortion-debate-890661.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILBBgfn3gesw-mFrLqch8kqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ronan-mullen-pledges-to-fight-the-good-fight-in-seanad-abortion-debate-890661.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ronan Mullen pledges to 'fight the good fight' in Seanad abortion debate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health Minister Simon Harris is set to reject amendments to his controversial abortion legislation when it is debated in the Seanad on Monday. Concerns have been expressed by senators on both sides of the debate with pro-life opponents to the bill criticising attempts to rush the legislation through, while pro-choice senators have expressed concern over elements of the bill as currently drafted. Particularly, they have expressed concern at the inclusion of the three-day waiting period before an abortion can be carried out, a provision which was inserted to assuage Tanaiste Simon Coveney ear...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Slow passage: All eyes on Seanad as delays risk timeline of abortion bill - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/slow-passage-all-eyes-on-seanad-as-delays-risk-timeline-of-abortion-bill-37603274.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK8X9XFzJKVllTyoAr1ssaMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/slow-passage-all-eyes-on-seanad-as-delays-risk-timeline-of-abortion-bill-37603274.html" target="_blank"&gt;Slow passage: All eyes on Seanad as delays risk timeline of abortion bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senators are wont to complain that nobody pays attention to the upper house - they won't have that to say over the coming days, as their handling of the abortion legislation will come under intense scrutiny. The painfully slow passage of the legislation through the Dáil - which saw extensive debate, some old-fashioned mudslinging, and no meaningful change to the bill in the end - put the timeline for services at risk. That timeline now depends largely on those in the Seanad. It is expected that substantial amendments will be tabled again, but there is muted hope in some quarters that the de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Seanad passes second stage of Government's abortion legislation 27 votes to 3 - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/seanad-passes-second-stage-of-governments-abortion-legislation-27-votes-to-3-890395.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO5JeagmMdOX_7jKplmeSHUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/seanad-passes-second-stage-of-governments-abortion-legislation-27-votes-to-3-890395.html" target="_blank"&gt;Seanad passes second stage of Government's abortion legislation 27 votes to 3&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Seanad has passed the second stage of the Government's controversial abortion legislation by 27 votes to 3. The Upper House is due to sit on Monday especially to try to pass the Bill's remaining stages in order to enable abortion services to be in place by January 1. Health Minister Simon Harris said the Bill delivers on the will of the Irish people as expressed in last May's referendum, where two-thirds of the electorate voted to repeal the Eighth Amendment: “We have our rights and they have their rights so we need to make sure that we pass this legislation in as swift a manner as poss...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Abortion legislation has passed the Dáil and it's now on to the Seanad, so what next? - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/abortion-legislation-what-next-4379676-Dec2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELk2D2Ddmk38L0lv50T1wGwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:00:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/abortion-legislation-what-next-4379676-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Abortion legislation has passed the Dáil and it's now on to the Seanad, so what next?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LANDMARK LEGISLATION which will allow women to access an abortion within the first 12 weeks of pregnancy with no restrictions was passed by the Dáil last night. The Regulation of Termination of Pregnancy Bill was passed by 90 votes to 15 with 12 abstentions. So, what are the next steps? The legislation has now move to the Seanad, and this afternoon senators had their first vote on the Bill. It will now proceed on to Committee Stage next week. Senators will then go through the legislation section by section, and it is expected some senators will table a number of amendments to the Bill. The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Harris hails passing of abortion bill as a "new era for Irish women" - Newstalk Newsfeed</title><link>https://www.newstalk.com/Harris-hails-passing-of-abortion-bill-as-a-new-era-for-Irish-women</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENN6nZV7BNkLvuRdxf7dzWQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowmeSfCTCcwW8wmpuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:25:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newstalk.com/Harris-hails-passing-of-abortion-bill-as-a-new-era-for-Irish-women" target="_blank"&gt;Harris hails passing of abortion bill as a "new era for Irish women"&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newstalk Newsfeed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The abortion bill has passed all stages in the Dáil. It was approved during a late night sitting of the Dáil and will now go to the Seanad for final sign-off. The Health Minister Simon Harris expects it to be signed into law before the end of the year. After the vote he said the people had spoken and said the new legislation will offer women facing crisis pregnancy “care and compassion in our own country.” Tonight Dáil Éireann has passed legislation to legalise abortion in Ireland. On to the Seanad now. I think of all the women who have had to travel to receive care - we say, no more. The p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newstalk.com">Newstalk Newsfeed</source></item><item><title>Abortion bill passes all stages in Dáil - Newstalk Newsfeed</title><link>https://www.newstalk.com/Dil-debate-on-abortion-resumes-as-Government-hopes-to-get-legislation-passed-tonight</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPqshiPhPP2Kym-NsyWHqqIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowmeSfCTCcwW8wmpuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 06:39:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newstalk.com/Dil-debate-on-abortion-resumes-as-Government-hopes-to-get-legislation-passed-tonight" target="_blank"&gt;Abortion bill passes all stages in Dáil&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newstalk Newsfeed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The abortion bill has passed all stages in the Dáil. Deputies extended their sitting until midnight in order to vote on the last of more than 60 proposed amendments. And that’s it. The Dáil approves the bill to allow abortions to happen in Ireland. It now goes to the Seanad for final approval #legisl8 pic.twitter.com/HKHIAOrNGu — Sean Defoe (@SeanDefoe) December 5, 2018 The legislation now goes back to the Seanad, and is expected to be signed into law before the end of the year. Commenting after the vote, Health Minister Simon Harris said he was thinking of "all the women who have had to t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newstalk.com">Newstalk Newsfeed</source></item><item><title>Opposition raise concerns over last-minute changes to new laws regarding mayors introduced by Minister - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/opposition-raise-concerns-over-last-minute-changes-to-new-laws-regarding-mayors-introduced-by-minister-890044.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFpo1wDOGDh-1GfC21YG9FsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:36:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/opposition-raise-concerns-over-last-minute-changes-to-new-laws-regarding-mayors-introduced-by-minister-890044.html" target="_blank"&gt;Opposition raise concerns over last-minute changes to new laws regarding mayors introduced by Minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Housing Minister Eoghan Murphy has told opposition parties to allow more than 30 pages of amendments to new laws allowing directly elected mayors to pass despite a backlash over the last-minute changes. Mr Murphy called for the support after Labour, Sinn Féin, the Social Democrats, Solidarity-People Before Profit and the Greens hit out at the major alterations, saying late changes risk delaying the new rules. Under long-flagged plans, the Government intends to allow Cork, Limerick, Galway and Waterford to directly elected their mayor in the future. The potential move will be outlined in a p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>The legislation legalising abortion in Ireland has been passed by the Dáil - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/abortion-bill-passed-through-dail-4377798-Dec2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO5YfjkOcbFfaaWn2aEejwwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 23:56:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/abortion-bill-passed-through-dail-4377798-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;The legislation legalising abortion in Ireland has been passed by the Dáil&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABORTION LEGISLATION HAS passed through the Dáil. The vote on the Health (Regulation of Termination of Pregnancy) Bill came at the end of days of debate in the Dáil on the stroke of midnight. The Bill passed by 90 votes to 15, and will now pass onto its next stage in the Seanad. The fact the bill has passed means that it is keeping within the timeline so that abortion services can be introduced in Ireland in January. Minister for Health Simon Harris said in a statement that it’s a “really significant step forward”. “We pass this Bill today just six months after the people had their say,” he...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Irish parliament's lower house passes historic bill to legalise abortion - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/ireland-abortion-irish-parliament-dail-bill-legalise-oireachtas-a8669661.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGIF0siNUdzByoH4pVwpcToqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 04:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/ireland-abortion-irish-parliament-dail-bill-legalise-oireachtas-a8669661.html" target="_blank"&gt;Irish parliament's lower house passes historic bill to legalise abortion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lower house of Ireland's parliament has passed historic legislation to make abortion legal for the first time, after members voted overwhelmingly in favour at the stroke of midnight on Wednesday. The bill put before the lower house, the Dáil, would legalise free access to abortion up to 12 weeks. After that, it would permit abortion only in cases where the woman was at risk of serious harm or death, or where a doctor has given a diagnosis of a fatal foetal abnormality. It was passed by 90 votes to 15, with 12 abstentions. According to the Irish Times, a total of 65 amendments were appro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Referendum to decide on cutting divorce waiting times - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/referendum-to-decide-on-cutting-divorce-waiting-times-889920.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJLAABAgjORBaYALYCbeGSkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 04:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/referendum-to-decide-on-cutting-divorce-waiting-times-889920.html" target="_blank"&gt;Referendum to decide on cutting divorce waiting times&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The public will be asked to cut divorce waiting times in half and allow millions of Irish citizens living abroad to vote in future presidential elections in two referenda on the same day as the local and European elections next May. Officials confirmed the plans last night after calls from the Government and opposition parties for both questions to be clarified as part of a public vote. After the Government’s weekly Cabinet meeting, a spokesperson for Taoiseach Leo Varadkar said ministers had provisionally agreed to hold the divorce and Irish abroad referenda on Friday, May 24. The divorce ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Kevin Doyle: 'TDs have one eye on Brexit and the other on Christmas' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/kevin-doyle-tds-have-one-eye-on-brexit-and-the-other-on-christmas-37587725.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOiZ4A9ljhH_JwzcdlQ9TgAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/kevin-doyle-tds-have-one-eye-on-brexit-and-the-other-on-christmas-37587725.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kevin Doyle: 'TDs have one eye on Brexit and the other on Christmas'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leinster House is in total wind down ahead of the Christmas break, which is still more than a fortnight away. The Dáil spent most of last week being filibustered on abortion while over in the Seanad there's a filibuster trying to prevent the Judicial Appointment Bill from progressing. Brexit is the burning issue, but we're in a holding pattern until at least December 11, when the House of Commons votes on the deal. To fill time and look busy, the Government has been going around launching 'funds' for rural folk, urbanites and even climate change. And in the background, the talks on a new co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Ceann comhairle lends support to Leinster House LGBT forum - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ceann-comhairle-lends-support-to-leinster-house-lgbt-forum-889656.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDwQlQldvu_S_G7IdnoSffcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ceann-comhairle-lends-support-to-leinster-house-lgbt-forum-889656.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ceann comhairle lends support to Leinster House LGBT forum&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An LGBT group is set to be established in Leinster House to organise conferences, campaigning, and social events. In addition it will provide a supportive space for staff and politicians. Ceann comhairle Sean Ó Fearghaíl has told Cork senator Jerry Buttimer he supports his proposal for the special forum and models in other parliaments are being examined. Mr Buttimer, who recently married his partner Conchobar Ó Laoghaire, told the Irish Examiner he is delighted and hopes the group would be set up early in the New Year. Members and staff will co-ordinate legislation and efforts to support th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Judges to be appointed by year’s end - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/judges-to-be-appointed-by-years-end-889355.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBAAFj22XS9NzJcLu4Zx1s4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 05:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/judges-to-be-appointed-by-years-end-889355.html" target="_blank"&gt;Judges to be appointed by year’s end&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Government will be appointing judges in the coming weeks, despite anger from Independent Transport Minister Shane Ross, according to Justice Minister Charlie Flanagan. Speaking after Taoiseach Leo Varadkar was accused of blaming judges for the delays in hearing cases, the justice minister said it is his hope that more judges will be appointed before Christmas. However, Mr Ross is said to be very unhappy at the “snail’s pace” at which his Judicial Appointments Bill is being progressed through the Seanad by Mr Flanagan. Mr Ross’s pet project aims to remove from the political realm the pow...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Senator accused of misogynistic remark would 'absolutely' have said the same to male colleague - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/senator-accused-of-misogynistic-remark-would-absolutely-have-said-the-same-to-male-colleague-37580572.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOXgQZDaPHcP-k09J8pKILgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/senator-accused-of-misogynistic-remark-would-absolutely-have-said-the-same-to-male-colleague-37580572.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senator accused of misogynistic remark would 'absolutely' have said the same to male colleague&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Fine Gael senator who was accused of making a misogynistic remark in the Seanad has said he would have said the same thing to a male colleague. Jerry Buttimer, the leader of the Seanad, was accused of using gendered language during an exchange while the Order of Business was being discussed. "I know Senator Clifford-Lee is trying to assert herself here... it is important though to listen as well," he said during the debate. Fianna Fáil Senator Lorraine Clifford-Lee, who was recently appointed deputy leader for the party in the Seanad, took exception, terming the language used as "very gen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach to get picture of election candidate off Government website - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/taoiseach-to-get-picture-of-election-candidate-off-government-website-37575876.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHC0ElLXtbdS3ggGZTO7pv8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:25:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/taoiseach-to-get-picture-of-election-candidate-off-government-website-37575876.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach to get picture of election candidate off Government website&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has committed to removing a photograph of a Fine Gael election candidate from a Government website. Senator Michelle Mulherin, who is running for the Dáil in Mayo, was pictured alongside a line-up of ministers at the launch of an urban regeneration fund on Monday. However, her appearance on an official Government website raised the ire of Sinn Féin leader Mary Lou McDonald who suggested taxpayer funds were being used to raise the profile of party candidates. She told the Dáil that the Strategic Communications Unit was scrapped because it was seen as promoting Fine Gae...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Justice Minister prevented from working on legislation to combat online harassment by filibustering in the Seanad - Taoiseach - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/justice-minister-prevented-from-working-on-legislation-to-combat-online-harassment-by-filibustering-in-the-seanad-taoiseach-37575869.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELbyhNw3gVl9KBJahULeEMsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:21:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/justice-minister-prevented-from-working-on-legislation-to-combat-online-harassment-by-filibustering-in-the-seanad-taoiseach-37575869.html" target="_blank"&gt;Justice Minister prevented from working on legislation to combat online harassment by filibustering in the Seanad - Taoiseach&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Minister Charlie Flanagan is being prevented from working on important legislation to combat online harassment by filibustering in the Seanad, the Taoiseach has claimed. Tensions are growing in Leinster House over new laws to deal with how judges are appointed. The Judicial Appointments Commission Bill is the brainchild of Independent Alliance Minister Shane Ross – but it is Justice Minister’s duty to bring it through the Dáil and Seanad. Mr Flanagan has faced days of debate in the Seanad which the Government claims amounts to a deliberate attempt to block the passage of the Bill. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Seanad passes Occupied Territories Bill despite government opposition - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/occupied-territories-bill-2-4365694-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELyDZ5Tr-xCO-i4Q8Pv-orcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:38:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/occupied-territories-bill-2-4365694-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Seanad passes Occupied Territories Bill despite government opposition&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE SEANAD HAS passed the Occupied Territories Bill to the next stage this evening. The Bill, which was voted on this evening, aims to prohibit Ireland from trading in goods and services from Israeli-occupied territories by prohibiting “the import and sales of goods, services and natural resources originating in illegal settlements in occupied territories”. Speaking about her Bill, Senator Frances Black wanted to clarify that the proposed legislation does not single out any state, adding that there is no mention of any particular region. Despite government opposition, the Bill has cross-par...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Amendment on grounds sought for abortion defeated - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1129/1014230-abortion-amendment-dail/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8nLCESTc7iRIGsEVyGly0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:25:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1129/1014230-abortion-amendment-dail/" target="_blank"&gt;Amendment on grounds sought for abortion defeated&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An amendment proposing that abortions are not sought on grounds of race, sex or disability under the Regulation of Termination of Pregnancy Bill has been defeated in the Dáil. Following a lengthy and often tense Report Stage debate which began last night, TDs voted against the amendment by 71 votes to 21. There were two abstentions. Independent TD Michael Collins, who was among the proposers of the bill, accused Minister for Health Simon Harris of misleading the public because he said the bill "was silent" abortion on the grounds of disability. He cautioned against Ireland following the UK,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>In Ireland, Bid to Restore Birthright Citizenship Gains Ground - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/24/world/europe/ireland-birthright-citizenship.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFf2O6ZvmHQhdsARmz5nlkcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 16:12:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/24/world/europe/ireland-birthright-citizenship.html" target="_blank"&gt;In Ireland, Bid to Restore Birthright Citizenship Gains Ground&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Correction: November 26, 2018 This article has been revised to reflect the following correction: An earlier version of this article referred incorrectly to an organization that promotes migrants’ rights in Ireland. It is the Immigrant Council of Ireland, not the Irish Council for Immigrants. DUBLIN — Ireland, which seems intent on bucking the illiberal tide in the West, is at it again: As other countries move to tighten restrictions on immigration, the Irish public is overwhelmingly in favor of a proposal to reinstate birthright citizenship. A proposed law on the subject passed a preliminar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Leo prepares for a rolling maul in Brussels - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/leo-prepares-for-a-rolling-maul-in-brussels-37562800.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOampxIQdi-oq187TY1LGSsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/leo-prepares-for-a-rolling-maul-in-brussels-37562800.html" target="_blank"&gt;Leo prepares for a rolling maul in Brussels&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar flies to Brussels this morning to scrum down with other EU leaders for the Brexit summit and yesterday he got in some last-minute training with the Dail and Seanad rugby team. Mr Varadkar joined politicians taking on members of Dublin fire brigade in a rugby challenge in Donnybrook. Given the diplomatic flash-fires which will inevitably accompany the talks today over the so-called backstop and the Border, the Taoiseach might have been tempted to garner a few tips from the firefighting professionals. Surprisingly, the Oireachtas team proved doughty competitors against ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach makes his rugby comeback in charity match - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/taoiseach-makes-his-rugby-comeback-in-charity-match-37561414.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBeSRd6OvXeJP3LzKM7q0IEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 14:43:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/taoiseach-makes-his-rugby-comeback-in-charity-match-37561414.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach makes his rugby comeback in charity match&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar took part in a rugby match against Dublin Fire Brigade in Energia Park this afternoon. The Dáil and Seanad XV secured a win of 7-0 against the Dublin Fire Brigade team. The match took place in aid of Suicide or Survive, a suicide prevention charity. On the Dáil and Seanad XV side, Taoiseach Leo Varadkar was joined by Senator Neale Richmond among other politicians. The Dáil and Seanad XV rugby team consists of members and staff from the Houses of the Oireachtas. The team takes part in ‘promoting the sport of rugby, fostering relations with other Parliaments and raising...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Availability of second doctor sought in abortion cases - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1128/1013989-abortion-dail/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELdUPW1sZYyGdYwBcuBDlrQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 07:38:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1128/1013989-abortion-dail/" target="_blank"&gt;Availability of second doctor sought in abortion cases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Minister for Health has put forward an amendment to the Regulation of Termination of Pregnancy Bill allowing a second practitioner to carry out an abortion procedure if the first practitioner is unavailable. The amendment relates to the three day wait period, which allows for 72 hours between a woman's first visit and the second visit. Speaking in the Dáíl, Simon Harris said his amendment recognises that a woman may not see the same practitioner on her return if, for example, the first practitioner is ill. The minister described it as "a sensible amendment" in order to address the pract...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Seanad suspended over 'misogyny' row - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/seanad-suspended-over-misogyny-row-37552911.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELiBhsQyYBoNJBMVxPmCFg0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 18:04:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/seanad-suspended-over-misogyny-row-37552911.html" target="_blank"&gt;Seanad suspended over 'misogyny' row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A ROW over alleged misogyny led to the suspension of the Seanad today. A remark made by Fine Gael Senator Jerry Buttimer to Fianna Fáil Senator Lorraine Clifford Lee led to chaotic scenes, as the Seanad was suspended by the Cathaoirleach, Denis O’Donovan, who described the back and forth as “nonsense”. Ms Clifford Lee was faced with accusations of “damaging the cause of women” after she called on Mr Buttimer to withdraw a remark she described as misogynistic. Mr Buttimer said: “I know Senator Clifford-Lee is trying to assert herself here but it is important to listen as well.” Sinn Féin Sen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Seanad briefly suspended over 'misogyny' row - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/seanad-misogyny-row-4353419-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBpfxafs2Yw8Fod42P6DUWsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 20:05:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/seanad-misogyny-row-4353419-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Seanad briefly suspended over 'misogyny' row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE SEANAD WAS briefly suspended today after a row over a comment made by Fine Gael Senator Jerry Buttimer. During a debate in the upper house this afternoon, attention turned to the subject of ‘spin units’ for political parties. Buttimer said: “On the subject of spin units, the Fianna Fáil party, which was in government for a while, had a particular unit.” Independent Senator David Norris then interjected: “They had a one-man spin unit, namely PJ O’Mara (a political adviser to former Taoiseach Charles Haughey).” To which Buttimer replied: “They had a couple, actually.” Fianna Fáil Senator ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Seanad suspended as Cork Senator Jerry Buttimer accused of making misogynistic comments - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/seanad-suspended-as-cork-senator-jerry-buttimer-accused-of-making-misogynistic-comments-886898.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGLKfIcg04w7FptwUfqhPFwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/seanad-suspended-as-cork-senator-jerry-buttimer-accused-of-making-misogynistic-comments-886898.html" target="_blank"&gt;Seanad suspended as Cork Senator Jerry Buttimer accused of making misogynistic comments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Seanad was suspended amid chaotic scenes after a senator was accused of making misogynistic comments in the chamber. The Upper House was suspended for 15 minutes yesterday after a row broke out over remarks made by Cork Senator Jerry Buttimer. During discussions on the business of the week, Mr Buttimer claimed that fellow senator and deputy leader of the Fianna Fáil group in the Seanad, Lorraine Clifford Lee was "trying" to assert herself. When Ms Clifford-Lee interjected in the debate, Mr Buttimer said: "I know Senator Clifford-Lee is trying to assert herself here but it is important t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Kilkenny People article 'hugely contributed' to loss of Dáil seat, FG's Paudie Coffey tells court - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/kilkenny-people-article-hugely-contributed-to-loss-of-dail-seat-fgs-paudie-coffey-tells-court-886930.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED6X-UtsUBhveftDpeLfV2AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 18:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/kilkenny-people-article-hugely-contributed-to-loss-of-dail-seat-fgs-paudie-coffey-tells-court-886930.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kilkenny People article 'hugely contributed' to loss of Dáil seat, FG's Paudie Coffey tells court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Fine Gael senator suing over a newspaper story which he says described him as a robber told the High Court he was shocked and upset when he saw the article. "I just could not believe what it contained", said Sen Paudie Coffey. Senator Paudie Coffey, pictured at the Four Courts today for the second day of a High Court action for damages. Pic: Collins Courts. He said the article "hugely contributed" to the loss of his Dáil seat in 2016, was "a pure fabrication" and caused him to be subject to public ridicule. He was forced to bring defamation proceedings because the paper, the Kilkenny Peop...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Michael McDowell rejects claims 2004 referendum on citizenship rights was 'mean-minded' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/michael-mcdowell-rejects-claims-2004-referendum-on-citizenship-rights-was-meanminded-37553264.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQe4cggPUwcfWXsrsRxjP4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 20:14:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/michael-mcdowell-rejects-claims-2004-referendum-on-citizenship-rights-was-meanminded-37553264.html" target="_blank"&gt;Michael McDowell rejects claims 2004 referendum on citizenship rights was 'mean-minded'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FORMER Justice Minister Michael McDowell has rejected claims that a 2004 referendum on citizenship rights was “mean-minded” and suggested it would pass again by a considerable majority if put to the people. The 2004 referendum saw the Constitution amended to take away the automatic right to Irish citizenship for children born in Ireland. The referendum also ensured that the Oireachtas would be in a position to pass legislation which governs how other people born in Ireland may become Irish citizens. Speaking in the Seanad on a Labour Party law proposed by Senator Ivana Bacik that would see ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Children born in Ireland to foreign parents would be eligible for citizenship under new law - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/children-born-in-ireland-to-foreign-parents-would-be-eligible-for-citizenship-under-new-law-37547618.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMz0-kLAPWiot0Ou29aCjMIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 13:03:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/children-born-in-ireland-to-foreign-parents-would-be-eligible-for-citizenship-under-new-law-37547618.html" target="_blank"&gt;Children born in Ireland to foreign parents would be eligible for citizenship under new law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children born in Ireland to foreign parents would be eligible for citizenship if they’ve been resident here for three years under a proposed new law. The Labour Party has said the change to the law is needed to deal with the “injustice” of a small number of children facing deportation, despite having never lived in any other country. Such cases were highlighted in recent weeks when Eric Zhi Ying Xue (9) – who was born in Ireland - faced deportation to China. There is a review of his case and the Bray schoolboy faces no imminent threat of deportation. Labour Senator Ivana Bacik said there is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Calls for automatic citizenship for children born in Ireland to non-national parents - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/calls-for-automatic-citizenship-for-children-born-in-ireland-to-non-national-parents-886581.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOSstpTidOw_3yqEFKK5k2UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 12:39:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/calls-for-automatic-citizenship-for-children-born-in-ireland-to-non-national-parents-886581.html" target="_blank"&gt;Calls for automatic citizenship for children born in Ireland to non-national parents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2004 citizenship referendum which removed the right of children born in Ireland to non-national parents to have automatic Irish citizenship should be reversed in light of a series of recent high profile cases. Labour demanded the move this morning in response to the recent case of nine-year-old Eric Zhi Ying Zhu from Bray, Co Wicklow, who was threatened with deportation to China despite being born in Ireland. Eric Zhi Ying Zhu Speaking to reporters before the party tables a new bill seeking to reform the 2004 referendum's impact in the Seanad tomorrow evening, party senator Ivana Bacik ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>FG senator: article called me a 'robber' and cost me my Dáil seat - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/courts/fg-senator-article-called-me-a-robber-and-cost-me-my-dil-seat-37550628.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBw60ps_MRWxKcLeCYmwx_IqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/courts/fg-senator-article-called-me-a-robber-and-cost-me-my-dil-seat-37550628.html" target="_blank"&gt;FG senator: article called me a 'robber' and cost me my Dáil seat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fine Gael Senator Paudie Coffey believes the loss of his Dáil seat in 2016 by 300 votes was due to a newspaper article about county boundary changes which likened him to an 18th-century robber, the High Court heard. He is suing Iconic Newspapers, publishers of the 'Kilkenny People', over the June 15, 2016, article headed "Coffey the Robber". It contained comments from his FG colleague John Paul Phelan TD accusing the then minister for state, now Senator Coffey, of trying to "rob" a chunk of south Kilkenny. Mr Phelan was then quoted as saying: "We've all heard of Crotty the robber - the 18th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Row brewing between Finian McGrath and Catherine Noone over CF unit in Beaumont - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/row-brewing-between-finian-mcgrath-and-catherine-noone-over-cf-unit-in-beaumont-884829.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOkWMqWhgyip-kiAKuy---4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 09:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/row-brewing-between-finian-mcgrath-and-catherine-noone-over-cf-unit-in-beaumont-884829.html" target="_blank"&gt;Row brewing between Finian McGrath and Catherine Noone over CF unit in Beaumont&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A row is brewing between Fine Gael and the Independent Alliance in Dublin. Disabilities Minister Finian McGrath tweeted a newspaper column suggesting Fine Gael Senator Catherine Noone had tried to steal credit for the new cystic fibrosis unit in Beaumont Hospital. Minister McGrath has campaigned for the unit for a number of years and it was in the programme for government. Senator Noone says the allegation that she was trying to take credit for the opening is unfair and untrue, saying she just tabled a Seanad debate after a request from a constituent. The two politicians will both compete f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>'We will name and shame companies' Leo Varadkar speaks out on the gender pay gap - Her.ie</title><link>https://www.her.ie/news/will-name-shame-companies-leo-varadkar-speaks-gender-pay-gap-435793</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIuQxhu8_oI8JgynxbnsXekqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8wgJehAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 18:04:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.her.ie/news/will-name-shame-companies-leo-varadkar-speaks-gender-pay-gap-435793" target="_blank"&gt;'We will name and shame companies' Leo Varadkar speaks out on the gender pay gap&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We invited the Taoiseach onGirls With Goalsrecently and he did not disappoint. It's not the first time we've entertained high-ranking politicians on our show, our health minister Simon Harris and Sinn Fein leaderMary Lou McDonald have both provided insights into the world of law-making and politics in the past, but when the leader of the country comes knocking... the pressure is certainly on. Keeping with show tradition, we began with our game 'Six words or less', it's a fan favourite with a certain Ronseal appeal. The guest simply describes themselves in six words or less and it's for our ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>John Downing: 'Micheál Martin has shown some steel – but he still risks missing the big prize' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/john-downing-michel-martin-has-shown-some-steel-but-he-still-risks-missing-the-big-prize-37511975.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHE2DeFWibLdAIBL1x-rhoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:45:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/john-downing-michel-martin-has-shown-some-steel-but-he-still-risks-missing-the-big-prize-37511975.html" target="_blank"&gt;John Downing: 'Micheál Martin has shown some steel – but he still risks missing the big prize'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;To many people away from the Leinster House “political bubble” it looked like a storm in an eggcup. But sometimes the smaller dramas can reveal a lot. And there was a funny side to this little Fianna Fáil melodrama. Two political tearaways, Éamon Ó Cúiv, now aged 68, and Senator Mark Daly, aged 45, literally made a break for the border one night last month. The pair went to Omagh in Co Tyrone to launch the Fianna Fáil election campaign of Cllr Sorcha McAnespy for next year’s Northern Ireland local elections. On the plus side, the party has committed itself to organising in the North in time...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Fianna Fáil: Gender pay gap the next big issue in society - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fianna-fail-gender-pay-gap-the-next-big-issue-in-society-884921.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG32rU0lPlbuRbkdd6huw4AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 18:44:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fianna-fail-gender-pay-gap-the-next-big-issue-in-society-884921.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fianna Fáil: Gender pay gap the next big issue in society&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removing the gender pay gap will be the next big issue that must be tackled in society, a Fianna Fáil senator has claimed. The party's Seanad deputy leader Lorraine Clifford-Lee will join others in Leinster House tomorrow raising awareness of gaps in the workplace and the need for gender equality. Ms Clifford-Lee and others will promote 'Dress for Success', a campaign which promotes the economic independence of women by providing career development services and advocates equal opportunities for women in the workplace. Ahead of briefing colleagues in Leinster House, the senator called for an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Éamon O Cuív sacked from Fianna Fáil front bench over Northern Ireland 'election unveiling' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/amon-o-cuv-sacked-from-fianna-fil-front-bench-over-northern-ireland-election-unveiling-37507591.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN-gzHuJ11LqEpqNwlkwuAUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 17:09:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/amon-o-cuv-sacked-from-fianna-fil-front-bench-over-northern-ireland-election-unveiling-37507591.html" target="_blank"&gt;Éamon O Cuív sacked from Fianna Fáil front bench over Northern Ireland 'election unveiling'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eamon Ó Cuív has been sacked from the Fianna Fail front bench over his involvement in unveiling a candidate in a Northern Ireland election without the party’s permission. Yesterday, Kerry Senator Mark Daly was stripped of his title as Fianna Fail’s deputy leader in the Seanad for his role in the event. Mr Daly also lost his title of Fianna Fail’s Seanad spokesperson on Foreign Affairs. Mr Daly along with Fianna Fail TD Eamon Ó Cuív used an event in Fermanagh to unveil former Sinn Fein councillor Sorhca McAnespy as the party’s first election candidate in the North. Soon after the unveiling, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Ó Cuív in firing line over unveiling of first Fianna Fáil candidate in the North - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/cuv-in-firing-line-over-unveiling-of-first-fianna-fil-candidate-in-the-north-37505141.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFe7ZcOLy9FvDSHc-AWSzTkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/cuv-in-firing-line-over-unveiling-of-first-fianna-fil-candidate-in-the-north-37505141.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ó Cuív in firing line over unveiling of first Fianna Fáil candidate in the North&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-serving Fianna Fáil TD Éamon Ó Cuív was in the firing line last night over his involvement in the apparent unveiling of the party's first candidate for a Northern Ireland election. Mr Ó Cuív was central to organising an event which claimed to be the unveiling of former Sinn Féin councillor Sorcha McAnespy as Fianna Fáil's first election candidate in the North. Fianna Fáil issued a statement soon after the announcement, saying it was not an official event and insisted the party had not made a decision on running candidates in the North. The party later issued disciplinary proceedings ag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Life after politics: Hayes steps down to be lobbyist for the banking sector - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/life-after-politics-hayes-steps-down-to-be-lobbyist-for-the-banking-sector-37501018.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBAjAKL8wOJFSnbpmcSWfPEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/life-after-politics-hayes-steps-down-to-be-lobbyist-for-the-banking-sector-37501018.html" target="_blank"&gt;Life after politics: Hayes steps down to be lobbyist for the banking sector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fine Gael MEP Brian Hayes will retire from politics next year to become a lobbyist for the banking industry. Mr Hayes made the shock announcement yesterday after informing Taoiseach Leo Varadkar he won't be defending his European Parliament seat for Dublin. The former junior minister is leaving political life to become chief executive of Banking and Payments Federation Ireland. Mr Hayes was thought to be planning a return to the Dáil in a future general election. He was expected to ultimately replace Richard Bruton in the Dublin Bay North constituency. The announcement was greeted by well-w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin to decide Eamon Ó Cuív's fate today for launching candidate without permission - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/eamon-cuiv-fianna-fail-4329018-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVL_YsitSH4qHly7l-WF-EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 10:16:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/eamon-cuiv-fianna-fail-4329018-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin to decide Eamon Ó Cuív's fate today for launching candidate without permission&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIANNA FÁÍL LEADER Micheál Martin has said he will consider Eamon Ó Cuív’s frontbench position after he went rogue and announced a local election candidate in Tyrone without Martin’s permission. At an event late last month, councillor Sorcha McAnespy, who is already a member of the party’s national executive, was announced as Fianna Fáíl’s candidate in the local elections – the party’s first steps across the border. Standing next to TD Éamon Ó Cuív, the spokesperson on Regional Development, Rural Affairs and the Gaeltacht, as well as Senator Mark Daly, McAnespy is holding a photo of herself...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Éamon Ó Cuív escapes demotion after Mark Daly sanctioned - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/eamon-o-cuiv-escapes-demotion-after-mark-daly-sanctioned-883946.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOOl4eXrkb3R3pAo5nelwqAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 05:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/eamon-o-cuiv-escapes-demotion-after-mark-daly-sanctioned-883946.html" target="_blank"&gt;Éamon Ó Cuív escapes demotion after Mark Daly sanctioned&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil Galway West TD Éamon Ó Cuív appears to have escaped sanction from party leader Micheál Martin after the pair met face to face last night. It had been expected that Mr Ó Cuív would be sacked as the party’s rural affairs spokesman after senator Mark Daly was relieved of his double position of deputy Seanad leader and foreign affairs spokesman. However, party sources said that Mr Ó Cuív was not likely to be demoted, despite being a persistent thorn in the side of Mr Martin. The decision comes after Mr Daly and Mr Ó Cuív participated in an apparent launch of a party candidate in Nor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Daly 'accepts' sacking over NI candidate - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1107/1009313-mark-daly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN-7DxXYTC8Fmc3jOndTD3YqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 14:38:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1107/1009313-mark-daly/" target="_blank"&gt;Daly 'accepts' sacking over NI candidate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil Senator Mark Daly has said that he accepts the decision of Micheál Martin to sack him as the party's deputy Seanad leader and spokesperson for Foreign Affairs. The move follows Senator Daly and TD Éamon Ó Cuív's role in appearing to launch a Fianna Fáil candidate in Northern Ireland recently. Party Headquarters would later clarity that it had not endorsed the election launch of Fermanagh Councillor Sorcha McAnespy. Senator Daly said today that he would continue to work hard on behalf of his constituents. "In my position as foreign affairs spokesperson, for the last number of yea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Profile: Man often tipped as a 'future Taoiseach' will bow out of politics next summer - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/profile-man-often-tipped-as-a-future-taoiseach-will-bow-out-of-politics-next-summer-37500997.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHiwAQrfHsfixwb9WLsKe9gqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/profile-man-often-tipped-as-a-future-taoiseach-will-bow-out-of-politics-next-summer-37500997.html" target="_blank"&gt;Profile: Man often tipped as a 'future Taoiseach' will bow out of politics next summer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Often tipped as a future Taoiseach, Brian Hayes has announced he will quit politics next summer just weeks ahead of his 50th birthday. The Fine Gael MEP for Dublin arrived at Leinster House in December 1995 as a senator appointed in controversial circumstances by the surprise Taoiseach of the day, John Bruton, who was heading a rainbow coalition after an extraordinary series of political events. Brian Hayes's rise was swift - but over time more than a little political rain fell upon him. Co-opted onto Dublin South County Council in 1995 at the age of 25, he was quickly being groomed as a Dá...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Fianna Fail Senator stripped of title over involvement in candidate 'launch' in Northern Ireland - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/fianna-fail-senator-stripped-of-title-over-involvement-in-candidate-launch-in-northern-ireland-37502916.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGkoXtQjgG1ZDTb_h8imAd0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 14:10:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/fianna-fail-senator-stripped-of-title-over-involvement-in-candidate-launch-in-northern-ireland-37502916.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fianna Fail Senator stripped of title over involvement in candidate 'launch' in Northern Ireland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senator Mark Daly has been stripped of his role as deputy leader of the Seanad over his involvement in an event which alleged to announce Fianna Fail’s first candidate in Northern Ireland election. Mr Daly has also been stripped of his title as Fianna Fail’s Seanad spokesperson for Foreign Affairs as part of disciplinary action taken ordered by party leader Micheal Martin. Mr Daly along with Fianna Fail TD Eamon O’Cuiv used an event in Fermanagh to unveil former Sinn Fein councillor Sorhca McAnespy as the party’s first election candidate in the North. Soon after the unveiling, Fianna Fail i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Creighton could end political exile as EU candidate - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/creighton-could-end-political-exile-as-eu-candidate-37501016.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKGFzt37nTFYOg4u_DdhdNkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/creighton-could-end-political-exile-as-eu-candidate-37501016.html" target="_blank"&gt;Creighton could end political exile as EU candidate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Fine Gael minister Lucinda Creighton is being tipped for a return to politics to replace Brian Hayes in the EU parliament. Ms Creighton quit Fine Gael over abortion legislation, before setting up her own party and ultimately losing her seat. However, it was suggested in political circles she could make a return to the party and run in the European elections next summer. Ms Creighton has a long-running friendship with Taoiseach Leo Varadkar. Former Tánaiste Frances Fitzgerald was also suggested as a possible Dublin candidate to run in EU elections. Fine Gael Senator Neale Richmond, wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Fine Gael MEP Brian Hayes leaving politics - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1106/1008952-brian-hayes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIsQgNwR361koMBssQNrdY0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 12:05:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1106/1008952-brian-hayes/" target="_blank"&gt;Fine Gael MEP Brian Hayes leaving politics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fine Gael MEP Brian Hayes has announced that he will not contest the European Parliament elections next year. The high profile MEP for Dublin said he has made the decision for professional and family reasons. He told RTÉ’s Today with Sean O'Rourke programme that he informed the Taoiseach and Fine Gael leader Leo Varadkar of his decision yesterday. Mr Varadkar was very understanding, he said, and reminded Mr Hayes that he had once given an interview to Hot Press magazine vowing to leave politics before the age of 50. Mr Hayes, who is now 49 years old, will take up a role as CEO at Banking an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Fine Gael MEP Brian Hayes to quit politics to become CEO of Banking and Payments Federation Ireland - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/brian-hayes-mep-quits-politics-4324624-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIyoe51ldFzDqjS4BggyskIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 10:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/brian-hayes-mep-quits-politics-4324624-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Fine Gael MEP Brian Hayes to quit politics to become CEO of Banking and Payments Federation Ireland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FINE GAEL MEP Brian Hayes has announced he will leave politics next year. The 49 year-old is set to become the CEO of the Banking and Payments Federation Ireland after the current European Parliament term ends next May. Announcing the news on Today With Sean O’Rourke on RTÉ Radio 1 this morning, Hayes revealed that he had made the decision for family reasons. “I suppose someone said ‘never say never’, it’s a bad thing to do,” he said. “But I’ve spent 25 years fighting eight different elections at local, European and national level and I think it’s enough.” Hayes informed the Taoiseach of hi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Tánaiste claims no deal Brexit scenario is unlikely - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/world/2018/1106/1009036-backstop-irish/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPIWEhNLAjYxtgstFRz41C8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wi5WhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 21:26:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/world/2018/1106/1009036-backstop-irish/" target="_blank"&gt;Tánaiste claims no deal Brexit scenario is unlikely&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Tánaiste has told the Seanad that while difficulties remain in the current Brexit negotiations, a no deal scenario is unlikely. "No one wants a no deal endgame. Everyone loses," Simon Coveney said during statements on Brexit in the Seanad this evening. However, he said it was the Government’s responsibility to prepare for all scenarios. He said as a result of this, work had intensified on a deal scenario and a no deal scenario. Mr Coveney also said the Irish and British governments would hold annual summits to strengthen relations. Independent Senator and former Ulster Farmer's Union pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Labour members asked to allow senators run as party leader - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/labour-leadership-4319482-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKEfkNil2tZHYTYc7KcdQV4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 07:00:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/labour-leadership-4319482-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Labour members asked to allow senators run as party leader&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A MOTION AT this year’s Labour conference has called for members of Seanad Éireann to be allowed run as leader of the party. If passed, senators such as Ivana Bacik and Aodhán Ó Ríordáin would be eligible for election. There has been a lot of speculation about the future of the Labour leadership, with the focus narrowing on who might lead the party into the next election ever since Alan Kelly threw his party leader down the gauntlet stating that he believes a change in leadership is needed. The Tipperary TD has previously said the party needs radical change and that Howlin should reflect on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Senator sues paper over FG colleague's remarks - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/courts/senator-sues-paper-over-fg-colleagues-remarks-37484486.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJ0rHl10fly3JGcUbkSQD4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/courts/senator-sues-paper-over-fg-colleagues-remarks-37484486.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senator sues paper over FG colleague's remarks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Fine Gael senator is suing a newspaper over comments made about him by one of the party's ministers. Senator Paudie Coffey, himself a former minister, is suing the 'Kilkenny People' over remarks made about him by local government minister of state John Paul Phelan. Mr Coffey claims he has suffered damage to his reputation because of the publication of the article. Mr Coffey is not suing Mr Phelan personally over the comments, which were first made in a press release sent to the newspaper. High Court listings show the Senator has taken his case against Iconic Newspapers Limited trading as ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Labour to discuss motion on entering coalition - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/labour-to-discuss-motionon-entering-coalition-882460.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHh0ZLleKg0ar-MzI98g8bkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 04:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/labour-to-discuss-motionon-entering-coalition-882460.html" target="_blank"&gt;Labour to discuss motion on entering coalition&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Labour will consider a motion on entering a Government coalition at its conference this weekend as well as allowing a future leader to come from the Upper House. The motions will be tabled after a difficult few months for the Opposition party, following a challenge to Brendan Howlin’s authority as leader by Alan Kelly. Labour will make women’s health, housing, and workers’ rights priority issues at the three-day national conference which is being held in Ballsbridge, Dublin. Guest speakers at the party’s event will include Dr Louise Kenny, a consultant and professor of obstetrics, Threshold...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Women's Council chairperson Ellen O'Malley Dunlop to run for Fine Gael in next election - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/ellen-omalley-dunlop-fine-gael-4315429-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPiWPfroDfDZwxZZSmolHlEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 15:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/ellen-omalley-dunlop-fine-gael-4315429-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Women's Council chairperson Ellen O'Malley Dunlop to run for Fine Gael in next election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE CHAIRPERSON OF the Women’s Council of Ireland (NWCI), Ellen O’Malley-Dunlop, has been named as a Fine Gael candidate in the hotly contested Dublin South West constituency. The women’s rights campaigner will join sitting TD Colm Brophy on the Fine Gael ticket. The party came close to securing two seats in the constituency in the 2016 election when candidate Anne Marie Dermody narrowly lost out to Katherine Zappone. Dermody secured 2,000 more first preference votes then Zappone but was eventually pipped by the now Minister for Children and Youth Affairs on the 16th count. John Lahart of F...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>UK demand for Irish passports surges as Brexit nears - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1031/1007668-brexit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF2ydrtaBuZ7XUs1FfUOcasqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 13:25:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1031/1007668-brexit/" target="_blank"&gt;UK demand for Irish passports surges as Brexit nears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Irish Embassy in London has seen a surge in demand for Irish passports as the clock ticks down to Brexit. Almost as many applications were received in the first half of 2018 as in the whole of 2015, the year before the European Union referendum. Figures released to Fine Gael Senator Neale Richmond, chairman of the Brexit Committee in the Seanad, showed there were almost 45,000 applications in the first half of 2018. Mr Richmond suggested that the "looming disaster of Brexit" was prompting eligible Britons to reconnect with their Irish heritage. He said: "Since the people of the UK voted...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Still turning up - Michael D Higgins in for 2nd term - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/presidential-election/2018/1027/1007104-michael-d-higgins/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOVNM5_R_DIliBUq46R3mugqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 19:33:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/presidential-election/2018/1027/1007104-michael-d-higgins/" target="_blank"&gt;Still turning up - Michael D Higgins in for 2nd term&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With results in from across the country, Michael D Higgins has been elected for a second term as President of Ireland. The writer and poet has served at almost every level of public life over the last five decades. Turning up since 1969, as he said himself, Mr Higgins first ran for election in Galway West, then a young academic in Galway, and part of a growing Labour organisation in the city. Unsuccessful then, he was appointed to the Seanad in 1973, and became a passionate voice of the left. Electoral success finally came in 1981 when he became TD for Galway West, and was later mayor of Ga...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Post Brexit rush for Irish passports in UK continues - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/post-brexit-rush-for-irish-passports-in-uk-continues-37470295.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPHyQJoZSwNy7IzD11GpFpEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wr8qiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 13:09:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/post-brexit-rush-for-irish-passports-in-uk-continues-37470295.html" target="_blank"&gt;Post Brexit rush for Irish passports in UK continues&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Figures released to Fine Gael Senator, Neale Richmond, have shown that the post Brexit rush for Irish passports in the UK continues with 2018 set to be the busiest year so far. “Since the people of the UK voted, narrowly, to leave the EU in 2016; we have seen a continuing rise in the number of applications for Irish passports in the UK. “Current rules entitle those born to Irish parents or Grandparents to apply for an Irish passport through a claim to citizenship. “At least 10% of the UK’s population, not including Northern Ireland, are estimated to qualify for an Irish passport and in ligh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Joan Freeman: The senator and mental health advocate running in the Irish presidential election - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/joan-freeman-ireland-presidential-election-2018-pieta-house-mental-health-independent-a8522421.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwf6R3_Mo-W3ISYcyjLGC8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/joan-freeman-ireland-presidential-election-2018-pieta-house-mental-health-independent-a8522421.html" target="_blank"&gt;Joan Freeman: The senator and mental health advocate running in the Irish presidential election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senator Joan Freeman has secured a nomination to stand in the upcoming Irish presidential election. The election has been called for 26 October, and will see the current President Michael D Higgins seek a second term, while facing competition from Sinn Féin candidate Liadh Ní Riada, and a few potential independents. Who is Joan Freeman? Joan Freeman is a psychologist from Dublin who is best known for Pieta House, a suicide intervention charity she established in 2006. There are 13 centres around Ireland which provide free services for people in suicidal distress or engaging in self-harm. Fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Analysis: Presidency is a pretty powerless role in Ireland but there are important rules and responsibilities - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/presidential-election-2018/analysis-presidency-is-a-pretty-powerless-role-in-ireland-but-there-are-important-rules-and-responsibilities-37448338.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRAJUGMZi_OHnZZ1-fw6MYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/presidential-election-2018/analysis-presidency-is-a-pretty-powerless-role-in-ireland-but-there-are-important-rules-and-responsibilities-37448338.html" target="_blank"&gt;Analysis: Presidency is a pretty powerless role in Ireland but there are important rules and responsibilities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President of Ireland is a pretty powerless position, but it is not wise to write it off as entirely ineffectual. The election, role and powers of the president are dealt with in a small number of articles in the Constitution. These amount to about a dozen pages. The president has formal constitutional powers, a small number of ceremonial roles and has reasonable scope to exert soft power. Dáil The president dissolves the Dáil on the advice of the Taoiseach - but there is one circumstance in which the president has a powerful say. When a Taoiseach loses the confidence of the Dáil, the presid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Second stage of abortion legislation passed by Dáil - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1023/1006170-abortion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcmQdKdFfwmbNnJlRyfbZcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 18:35:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1023/1006170-abortion/" target="_blank"&gt;Second stage of abortion legislation passed by Dáil&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second stage of the Regulation of Termination of Pregnancy Bill has passed by a large majority in the Dáil. The bill now moves to committee stage where amendments to the bill will be considered and discussed. Introduced to the Dáil the week before the Budget, the second stage of the legislation passed by 102 votes to 12. Seven TDs abstained. Many of those abstentions came from the Fianna Fáil party, whose TDs are free to vote with their conscious. Sinn Féin on the other hand are subject to a party whip on this issue, which means Meath West TD Peadar Tóibín now faces suspension from the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>All you need to know about Ireland's 2018 presidential candidates - Her.ie</title><link>https://www.her.ie/news/everything-need-know-irelands-2018-presidential-candidates-431230</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEITbVyeuG5fJCUNQhz8ZAWIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8wgJehAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 16:19:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.her.ie/news/everything-need-know-irelands-2018-presidential-candidates-431230" target="_blank"&gt;All you need to know about Ireland's 2018 presidential candidates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's a presidential election coming up. It's on Friday, October 26. Six candidates are running - here's everything you need to know about them. Michael D Higgins What's his background? Michael D Higgins is an academic, politician, and current president of Ireland. He joined Ireland's Labour Party in the 1960s and sat in the Dil between1987 and 2011. He also served as a senator in the 1980s. Higgins has been the president of Ireland since 2011 after running as a Labour candidate. He is running as an independent this time. Why is he running? Higgins says that his track record of "wisdom an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>Former Fine Gael TD Seymour Crawford dies aged 74 - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/former-fine-gael-td-seymour-crawford-dies-aged-74-877172.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDrpUHETKLh76dr5nx7WJCkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/former-fine-gael-td-seymour-crawford-dies-aged-74-877172.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Fine Gael TD Seymour Crawford dies aged 74&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Fine Gael TD, Seymour Crawford, has died aged 74. Mr Crawford served as a TD for the Cavan-Monaghan constituency from 1992 to 2011, when he retired from politics following the General Election. He was from Drumkeen, Aghabog, Co Monaghan and was a member of Monaghan County Council from 1991 to 2003. He was also the Vice-President of the Irish Farmers' Association in the 1980s. Tributes have been paid to Mr Crawford, who died yesterday in Cavan General Hospital. Taoiseach Leo Varadkar said Mr Crawford was passionate about many issues and played a crucial role in the British-Irish Inter...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Unanswered question on McCourt meetings an 'oversight' - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1022/1005979-dail-politics-broadband-plan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP8YijBRmC24N4amFJCuIs0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 20:02:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1022/1005979-dail-politics-broadband-plan/" target="_blank"&gt;Unanswered question on McCourt meetings an 'oversight'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An unanswered Dáil question about meetings between a junior minister and the last remaining National Broadband Plan bidder was the result of an administrative oversight, a Government Department has said. It follows an official complaint made by Social Democrats TD Catherine Murphy after her question seeking details of Minister Pat Breen's engagements with David McCourt was not answered last week. The Department of Business Enterprise and Innovation said tonight the mistake was brought to its attention this morning and a full answer was issued. "Minister Breen approved the content of the rep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Alcohol Bill passes all stages of Oireachtas - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1010/1002310-alcohol-bill/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGO3A3pPB3eVIJY8GMlzOM4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 17:38:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1010/1002310-alcohol-bill/" target="_blank"&gt;Alcohol Bill passes all stages of Oireachtas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Legislation that will lead to more stringent rules around the sale of alcohol, including minimum pricing and cancer warnings on alcohol products, is to go to the President to be signed into law. The Public Health (Alcohol) Bill passed the final stage in the Seanad this evening. The controversial legislation was passed in the Dáil last week. The bill has been before the Oireachtas since 2015 and seeks to reduce alcohol consumption in Ireland. Minister for Health Simon Harris has welcomed the passage of the bill through the Seanad. In a statement he said: "This legislation has been debated fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Minister 'did pay' for broadband bidder's Dáil lunch - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1010/1002207-denis-naughten-dail/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECYjt945R5DrtNwLsDlVgjkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 06:02:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1010/1002207-denis-naughten-dail/" target="_blank"&gt;Minister 'did pay' for broadband bidder's Dáil lunch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A spokesperson for the Minister for Communications has said Denis Naughten paid for lunch for a businessman involved in the tender for the National Broadband Plan. The lunch for David McCourt and members of his family cost €37 and it was deducted from Minister's Naughten's salary in July under the Oireachtas payments system, the spokesperson said. The minister also said that he met Mr McCourt on one other occasion, as part of a meeting attended by the Secretary General and Assistant Secretary of the Department of Communications on 26 June. This afternoon, Mr Naughten had said he did not kno...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Alcohol Bill, first published in 2015, finally passes through Oireachtas - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/alcohol-bill-ireland-4279415-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJvW20F13D_xrOPNvKFrucqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 20:27:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/alcohol-bill-ireland-4279415-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Alcohol Bill, first published in 2015, finally passes through Oireachtas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE PUBLIC HEALTH (Alcohol) Bill is to go to President Michael D Higgins to be signed into law. The much-debated legislation passed through the Seanad this evening, having been passed in the Dáil last week. The wide-ranging piece of legislation was first published in 2015, and provides for changes such as minimum pricing on alcohol, restrictions on advertising and stark warning labels on alcohol products. In a statement released this evening, Health Minister Simon Harris noted that the legislation “has been debated for over 1,000 days” and “has been the subject of the most intense lobbying ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Alcohol Bill passes Dáil after more than 1,000 days - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1003/1000785-alcohol-bill/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEAgihLASMmJebBpACoDXPYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 07:16:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1003/1000785-alcohol-bill/" target="_blank"&gt;Alcohol Bill passes Dáil after more than 1,000 days&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Controversial legislation bringing more stringent rules around the sale of alcohol has passed all stages in the Dáil, paving the way for the introduction of measures such as minimum unit pricing and cancer warnings on alcohol products. The Public Health (Alcohol) Bill, which has been before the Oireachtas since 2015, seeks to reduce alcohol consumption in Ireland. The bill will pave the way for measures such as minimum unit pricing, cancer warnings, and segregation of alcohol sales in shops to be introduced. The legislation has had a lengthy journey through the Oireachtas, as it took two ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Ireland Bill Aims to Crack Down on Excessive Drinking With Health Warning Labels - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/06/world/europe/ireland-drinking-bill.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFN45P_yfHXqf8RFi0HGgTUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 11:25:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/06/world/europe/ireland-drinking-bill.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ireland Bill Aims to Crack Down on Excessive Drinking With Health Warning Labels&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Legislation passed by the lower house of Parliament orders sweeping restrictions on how alcohol is sold and advertised.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Minister admits 'serious' housing crisis - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1003/1000687-dail-housing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPYffogPHa2vIeGb_SqLSoEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1003/1000687-dail-housing/" target="_blank"&gt;Minister admits 'serious' housing crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Minister for Housing has acknowledged there is a serious housing crisis as the Dáil debates a private members' motion on the issue. However, Eoghan Murphy reiterated that emergency responses were being put in place. He was responding to the Solidarity/People Before Profit motion, which seeks a declaration of a housing and homelessness emergency. The motion has cross-party support, including that of Fianna Fáil. The debate takes place following a large protest in Dublin to highlight the housing crisis. The minister said the Government needed to do more and to do better. He said it was un...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Senator claims understaffing has stopped Navy from setting sail - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/senator-claims-understaffing-has-stopped-navy-from-setting-sail-872481.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAPJLSnndVB7j6_kl0qPNBEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 09:31:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/senator-claims-understaffing-has-stopped-navy-from-setting-sail-872481.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senator claims understaffing has stopped Navy from setting sail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Irish Navy is so understaffed that sometimes they cannot set sail, according to Senator Gerald Craughwell. The Senator said even when they do go to sea the inexperienced crews are a source of danger. In The Irish Mail on Sunday, Senator Craughwell added that low numbers mean the Naval service cannot fulfil its role. He also said that ships were going out to sea to create an illusion that Ireland has a good Navy presence.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Freeman on €120k loan: 'No I didn't need to do a background check. This guy is a very good guy' - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/joan-freeman-des-walsh-loan-4262542-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEOyjd-iVEDL4OS2xXj0_FQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 11:15:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/joan-freeman-des-walsh-loan-4262542-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Freeman on €120k loan: 'No I didn't need to do a background check. This guy is a very good guy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;INDEPENDENT SENATOR JOAN Freeman has said that she has received a loan of €120,000 from businessman Des Walsh to fund her presidential campaign – but asserted that “it is a loan” and she intends to pay it back. The founder of Pieta House said that she has also set up a GoFundMe account in order to raise funds for the campaign. In an interview on Today with Sean O’Rourke, Freeman said that she was not playing “the poor mouth” but that she did not have the same financial backing as the other candidates. Freeman is running against Áras incumbent Michael D Higgins, Sinn Féin candidate Liadh Ní ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Smoke-free Ireland still 34 years off as 100 die every week - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/smokefree-ireland-still-34-years-off-as-100-die-every-week-37370531.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECRkdLYB4wvLZRbEZNwtUC8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/health/smokefree-ireland-still-34-years-off-as-100-die-every-week-37370531.html" target="_blank"&gt;Smoke-free Ireland still 34 years off as 100 die every week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ireland risks missing its tobacco-free target date of 2025 by 27 years, the HSE has warned. The shocking delay is putting new pressure on Health Minister Simon Harris to soften his stance on e-cigarettes to help more smokers quit. The Government is committed to being "tobacco-free" - with less than 5pc of the population still smokers - by 2025. But the HSE report says that, based on current trends, this target will not be met until 2052. At present, 18pc of Irish people smoke daily. Smoking, which includes the effects of second-hand smoke, is deemed responsible for 100 deaths and more than ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Harris secures Cabinet approval for abortion laws - Newstalk Newsfeed</title><link>https://www.newstalk.com/Abortion-laws-are-set-to-be-approved-by-Cabinet-today</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsdD7w-_CXAIYsOSQbucIAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowmeSfCTCcwW8wmpuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 13:09:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newstalk.com/Abortion-laws-are-set-to-be-approved-by-Cabinet-today" target="_blank"&gt;Harris secures Cabinet approval for abortion laws&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newstalk Newsfeed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Updated 14:10 Laws to make abortion legal have been approved by the Cabinet. More than four months after the Irish people voted overwhelmingly to repeal the Eighth Amendment, the laws allowing abortion to take place have been signed off by ministers. The Thirty-Sixth Amendment of the Constitution Bill 2018 was signed into law by President Michael D Higgins last week. The proposed legislation, if approved by the Dáil, will allow for abortion without restriction for up to 12 weeks into pregnancy and in limited circumstances after that. Minister Harris has said the Government is committed to p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newstalk.com">Newstalk Newsfeed</source></item><item><title>Cancer warning labels on alcohol products will not be ditched from Public Health Alcohol Bill - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/cancer-warning-labels-alcohol-4253945-Sep2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOHcGAfk4TBkYoN2q5WHoZEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 19:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/cancer-warning-labels-alcohol-4253945-Sep2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Cancer warning labels on alcohol products will not be ditched from Public Health Alcohol Bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CANCER WARNING LABELS on alcohol products will be kept in the new alcohol laws, despite opposition for them to be scrapped. Last week there were reports that warnings on alcohol products linking excessive consumption to fatal cancers were to be removed from the Public Health Alcohol Bill when it returns to the Dáil. The Irish Cancer Society, as well as Independent Senator Frances Black, were critical of Health Minister Simon Harris and urged him to retain the cancer warning labels. It is now understood it is the minister’s intention that the link between alcohol and cancer will be achieved...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item></channel></rss>