<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Central Bureau of Investigation - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZxTkRGakVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:29:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Key accused in Agusta Westland chopper scam extradited to India - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-agustawestland-extradition/key-accused-in-agusta-westland-chopper-scam-extradited-to-india-idUSKBN1O32KW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ7wwLINLS75Qunl4YnwzQEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:00:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-agustawestland-extradition/key-accused-in-agusta-westland-chopper-scam-extradited-to-india-idUSKBN1O32KW" target="_blank"&gt;Key accused in Agusta Westland chopper scam extradited to India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key accused and alleged middleman in India's abortive, scandal-tainted helicopter deal with Anglo-Italian firm Agusta Westland was extradited to India from Dubai late on Tuesday, according to local media. The Indian federal Police said earlier in the day that Christian Michel would arrive in New Delhi and be taken into custody by the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) before being presented in court on Wednesday. The CBI alleges that Michel paid bribes to senior Indian government officials to secure the chopper deal for Agusta in 2010. He has denied the accusations. His extradition is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Indian journalists protest against raid on NDTV news channel - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-media-idUSKBN19028I</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPVXP7FRB1d80zbwxVjShRIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:05:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-media-idUSKBN19028I" target="_blank"&gt;Indian journalists protest against raid on NDTV news channel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW DELHI (Reuters) - Indian journalists protested on Friday against raids conducted by the federal police into the founders of news channel NDTV, a move they described as an attack on the country's freedom of press.The Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) this week brought a fraud case against the founders of NDTV, India's oldest English-language all-news channel, raiding their homes after accusing them of failing to repay a multi-million-dollar bank loan. The company refuted allegations that the bank loan was unpaid and accused the CBI of "concerted harassment", saying the move had been ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>NDTV founder’s home raided in India bank loan probe - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/62949e62-49c6-11e7-919a-1e14ce4af89b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKiaynVdhJtLtHl5L0CsasqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 17:36:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/62949e62-49c6-11e7-919a-1e14ce4af89b" target="_blank"&gt;NDTV founder’s home raided in India bank loan probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigators have raided the home of the founder of a top Indian television channel in connection with a loan from ICICI Bank, sparking accusations from NDTV that the country’s crime agency is trying to undermine free speech. New Delhi’s Central Bureau of Investigation searched four properties in the capital and Dehradun in northern India on Monday, including the office and homes of Prannoy Roy and his wife Radhika, officials told local media. NDTV confirmed the raids. According to people familiar with the case, the CBI is investigating what it says are irregularities in a loan Mr Roy took...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>In India, Concerns About Media Freedom After Raids on Broadcaster - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/india-mediia-freedom/3890302.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHdo-DBBShvDhWs6Fx47PggqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 12:20:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/india-mediia-freedom/3890302.html" target="_blank"&gt;In India, Concerns About Media Freedom After Raids on Broadcaster&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India’s Information and broadcasting minister, M. Venkaiah Naidu has refuted allegations that raids carried out by the country’s main investigative agency on a top broadcaster were an infringement on press freedom. His comments on Wednesday came in response to widespread concern that the action against the promoters of a TV news channel that has often been critical of the government’s policies could undermine press freedom in the world’s largest democracy. Government action The Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) searched several premises of Prannoy and Radhika Roy, the promoters of NDTV ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Vijay Mallya hits back at India’s $1.3bn debt claim - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/09aef41a-e43f-11e6-8405-9e5580d6e5fb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELgsCtzjRE09bCCGwd3t4ncqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 04:15:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/09aef41a-e43f-11e6-8405-9e5580d6e5fb" target="_blank"&gt;Vijay Mallya hits back at India’s $1.3bn debt claim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vijay Mallya has denied that he fled India leaving behind $1.3bn of unpaid loans, after Indian authorities this week charged the billionaire industrialist with criminal conspiracy, dishonesty and corruption in an effort to secure his extradition from the UK. In a series of tweets late on Thursday night, Mr Mallya said that there was “no final judicial determination on what Kingfisher Airlines owes to banks and what I may owe in my personal capacity after trial”. “Yet it is reported that I have fled or run away owing money to banks that I never even borrowed in the first place.” India’s Cent...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Leading BJP figures to face trial in Babri mosque case - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/leading-bjp-figures-face-trial-babri-mosque-case-170419063408261.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDkNH8DQDEmLN5qi1A7SX6IqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 13:45:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/leading-bjp-figures-face-trial-babri-mosque-case-170419063408261.html" target="_blank"&gt;Leading BJP figures to face trial in Babri mosque case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's Supreme Court has ordered that the co-founder of the ruling Bharatiya Janata Party, LK Advani, and other leaders be tried for criminal conspiracy in the demolition of a 16th century mosque about 25 years ago. The Babri Masjid in Ayodhya, in the northern Uttar Pradesh state, was pulled down by Hindu activists on December 6, 1992, leading to widespread riots in which more than 2,000 people died. Advani, 89, along with Murli Manohar Joshi and Uma Bharti, has previously been charged with making inflammatory speeches which incited the activists to demolish the structure. The Supreme Cour...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Six found guilty of involvement in 1993 blasts in India's financial hub - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-court-blast-idUSKBN19718O</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAFv8OB04Bpk9muDC13vuq4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 12:44:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-court-blast-idUSKBN19718O" target="_blank"&gt;Six found guilty of involvement in 1993 blasts in India's financial hub&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Abhirup Roy MUMBAI (Reuters) - An Indian court on Friday found six men guilty of involvement in a series of blasts in the city of Mumbai in 1993 that killed 257 people and wounded 800, the latest in scores of convictions related to India's most deadly bombings. The special anti-terrorism court said the six had transported weapons and planted bombs, which targeted landmark buildings in the financial hub, including the main stock exchange. A seventh man was acquitted on a lack of evidence. Investigators had said the bombs were ordered by India's most-wanted man, gangster Dawood Ibrahim, to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Indian guru Gurmeet Ram Rahim Singh sentenced to 20 years for rape - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/28/asia/guru-india-rape-sentencing/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK42KpHz8rpTb7wfZfy-GfEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 17:46:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/28/asia/guru-india-rape-sentencing/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian guru Gurmeet Ram Rahim Singh sentenced to 20 years for rape&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A controversial Indian spiritual guru has been sentenced to 20 years in prison for rape, India's Central Bureau of Investigation announced Monday. Gurmeet Ram Rahim Singh, head of the spiritual sect Dera Sacha Sauda, was convicted on Friday of raping two of his followers in a case that dates back to 1999. The minimum sentence for rape is seven years. He was sentenced to two consecutive 10-year terms, one for each conviction. Singh was sentenced behind locked doors inside Rohtak jail, where he arrived by helicopter Friday from a courthouse in the northern city of Panchkula. The move came in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Indian army on standby on eve of guru's rape charges verdict - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/aug/24/indian-army-on-standby-on-eve-of-gurus-charges-verdict</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMP4bBJFrjpvFYo5-AIdocQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 14:37:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/aug/24/indian-army-on-standby-on-eve-of-gurus-charges-verdict" target="_blank"&gt;Indian army on standby on eve of guru's rape charges verdict&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parts of two northern Indian states are in lockdown as tens of thousands of followers of a flamboyant “godman” nicknamed the “guru of bling” await a verdict on long-standing rape charges against the spiritual leader. The Indian army is on standby in Punjab and Haryana, surveillance drones are circling, and schools and roads have been shut in the city of Panchkula, over fears that supporters of Ram Rahim Singh may turn violent if he is found guilty. About 150,000 members of Dera Sacha Sauda, a “social welfare and spiritual organisation” led by Singh, are reported to have descended on Panchku...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Calls for criminal inquiry into Lib Dem donor over ‘links to Rolls-Royce scandal’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2017/mar/17/calls-for-criminal-inquiry-in-india-into-choudhries-links-to-rolls-royce-scandal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtch1qyIeSwZfm1KWGXgXoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 09:52:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2017/mar/17/calls-for-criminal-inquiry-in-india-into-choudhries-links-to-rolls-royce-scandal" target="_blank"&gt;Calls for criminal inquiry into Lib Dem donor over ‘links to Rolls-Royce scandal’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anti-corruption campaigners have demanded a criminal investigation in India into a businessman and major Liberal Democrat donor over his alleged links to the Rolls-Royce bribery scandal. In a letter to India’s Central Bureau of Investigation, the lawyer and politician Prashant Bhushan asked that the country’s authorities launch an investigation into the role of Sudhir Choudhrie and other middlemen for the British engineering giant. Bhushan wrote: “As per the British media reports, one Sudhir Choudhrie, who figures in the list of Undesirable Contact Men prepared by your department, and his s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Riot fears as 'Guru of Bling' jailed for raping two women - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/world-news/asia-pacific/riot-fears-as-guru-of-bling-jailed-for-raping-two-women-36079185.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgvVXLXCM5V_IwFEPaGY-EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wmtSiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/world-news/asia-pacific/riot-fears-as-guru-of-bling-jailed-for-raping-two-women-36079185.html" target="_blank"&gt;Riot fears as 'Guru of Bling' jailed for raping two women&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indian judge sentenced a self-styled "godman", whose followers went on a deadly rampage after he was convicted of rape last week, to 20 years' jail yesterday, but a shoot-to-kill order, curfew and heavy police presence kept protesters at bay. A spokesman for the Central Bureau of Investigation, which investigated the case, said Gurmeet Ram Rahim Singh would serve two consecutive 10-year-terms for the two rape convictions. Tens of thousands of police enforced a lockdown in large parts of the northern states of Haryana and Punjab where Singh (50) has a mass following. Police in Haryana iss...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Homes of Indian ex-finance minister, son searched in criminal probe - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-raids-idUSKCN18C0D4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMo2vx4Am1ONXtHSqqBrkLEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 05:42:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-raids-idUSKCN18C0D4" target="_blank"&gt;Homes of Indian ex-finance minister, son searched in criminal probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Rupam Jain and Douglas Busvine NEW DELHI (Reuters) - India's Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) searched the homes of former finance minister P. Chidambaram and his son on Tuesday, in a probe into suspected criminal misconduct related to approvals of investment deals. The dawn raids marked an escalation in pressure by federal investigators against Chidambaram, a senior leader of the opposition Congress party who has been a vocal critic of Prime Minister Narendra Modi. The CBI, India's main federal crime-fighting agency, conducted searches at locations in the cities of Mumbai, Delhi, G...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Business tycoon Vijay Mallya arrested in London over money laundering charges in India - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/18/business-tycoon-vijay-mallya-arrested-london-money-laundering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN4FKTCe5eAnsYcfZTnu16YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 11:53:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/18/business-tycoon-vijay-mallya-arrested-london-money-laundering/" target="_blank"&gt;Business tycoon Vijay Mallya arrested in London over money laundering charges in India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;British police on Tuesday arrested Indian business tycoon Vijay Mallya in London on behalf of authorities in India, where he is wanted on charges of money laundering and bank demands that he pay back nearly a billion pounds in loans extended to his now-defunct airline. Mallya was arrested after showing up in a police station and will appear in court for a preliminary hearing later Tuesday, said a statement from the Metropolitan Police in London. India's Enforcement Directorate, now investigating the liquor baron's debts totaling 94 billion rupees (£977 million), asked a New Delhi court last...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Freedom of the Press in India - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/06/15/opinion/freedom-of-the-press-in-india.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEiY_zceHZpL407AVVufp6UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwpoIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 17:25:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/06/15/opinion/freedom-of-the-press-in-india.html" target="_blank"&gt;Freedom of the Press in India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A spokesman for the Central Bureau of Investigation objects to an editorial critical of actions against news media.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>India requests Vijay Mallya's extradition from Britain - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/india-requests-vijay-mallya-extradition-britain-170209162733557.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAQDPXpbtAPZChcb9H6zIq4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 20:07:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/india-requests-vijay-mallya-extradition-britain-170209162733557.html" target="_blank"&gt;India requests Vijay Mallya's extradition from Britain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India has submitted an official extradition request to Britain to send back Vijay Mallya, a former liquor tycoon, to face trial after he fled the country owing more than $1bn. The Indian foreign ministry said on Thursday that it lodged a formal request with the British high commission in the capital, New Delhi, after investigators demanded that Mallya be brought home to face charges of financial fraud and defaulting on loans. "We have today handed over the request for extradition of Mr Vijay Vittal Mallya as received from the CBI [Central Bureau of Investigation] to the UK High Commission,"...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Controversial Indian 'god man' sentenced to 20 years - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0828/900494-controversial-indian-god-man-sentenced/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKwsUH4ZFhGMmWmoC6A4-P4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wjpahAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 14:43:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2017/0828/900494-controversial-indian-god-man-sentenced/" target="_blank"&gt;Controversial Indian 'god man' sentenced to 20 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indian court has sentenced a controversial religious leader to 20 years in prison for raping two of his followers, authorities said. Gurmeet Ram Rahim Singh was found guilty of sexually assaulting two of his female followers last Friday, in a case that dates back to 2002. A lawyer for the victims had said Gurmeet Ram Rahim Singh had been sentenced to ten years in jail, but India's Central Bureau of Investigations (CBI) later clarified he received two consecutive ten-year sentences. There were no reports of violence after he was sentenced. Ten of thousands of police had enforced a lockdow...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Raids in India Target Founders of News Outlet Critical of Government - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/06/05/world/asia/india-ndtv-raids-narendra-modi-prannoy-roy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENtbVC8_ViGkIRUkxq4kU6YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 11:33:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/06/05/world/asia/india-ndtv-raids-narendra-modi-prannoy-roy.html" target="_blank"&gt;Raids in India Target Founders of News Outlet Critical of Government&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cable company, NDTV, called the raids a politically motivated “witch hunt.” The government cited an investigation into bank losses.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>India moves to secure extradition of Vijay Mallya - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/216164ec-e2ca-11e6-8405-9e5580d6e5fb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIC2-ITd1p4CtZB720kkJ_8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 09:02:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/216164ec-e2ca-11e6-8405-9e5580d6e5fb" target="_blank"&gt;India moves to secure extradition of Vijay Mallya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian authorities have charged Vijay Mallya with criminal conspiracy, dishonesty and corruption following months of investigation, in an effort to secure the billionaire industrialist’s extradition from the UK. The Central Bureau of Investigation on Tuesday filed charges against Mr Mallya, his now defunct Kingfisher Airlines, and nine other executives and bankers, alleging he dishonestly induced the delivery of property and illegally obtained pecuniary advantage — charges that can carry a sentence of up to seven years in prison. Lawyers said the Indian government would now be able to make ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>India lawmaker calls for prosecution of Ratan Tata - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d02cf284-c4f7-11e6-8f29-9445cac8966f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH1U3qyFS66olW6l5fRO3LEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 12:50:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d02cf284-c4f7-11e6-8f29-9445cac8966f" target="_blank"&gt;India lawmaker calls for prosecution of Ratan Tata&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The controversy engulfing India’s Tata Group has deepened after a senior ruling party lawmaker filed a complaint calling for the prosecution of its chairman Ratan Tata in connection with a fraud allegation. The complaint by Subramanian Swamy, a former justice minister, accuses criminal investigators of having failed to follow up evidence linking Mr Tata to an allegedly corrupt telecoms transaction. His filing, made on Friday at New Delhi’s Central Bureau of Investigation Court (CBI), included a preliminary report apparently produced in 2013 by officials at India’s Serious Fraud Investigatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Indian guru found guilty of rape; army brought in to monitor thousands of his supporters outside court - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/world/army-patrols-indian-town-as-thousands-turn-out-in-support-of-guru-accused-of-rape-803367.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDptX8FKnZ16V6JFYkGsLSIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwzaShAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:03:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/world/army-patrols-indian-town-as-thousands-turn-out-in-support-of-guru-accused-of-rape-803367.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian guru found guilty of rape; army brought in to monitor thousands of his supporters outside court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A court in northern India has convicted a flamboyant guru of raping two of his followers. Prosecution lawyer HPS Verma said the guru, who calls himself Saint Dr Gurmeet Ram Rahim Singh Ji Insan, had been found guilty in the 15-year-old case. Tens of thousands of supporters who had been waiting for hours near the court shouted in anger after the ruling was announced in Panchkula. More than 15,000 police and paramilitary soldiers were posted in and around the court where the guru appeared before a judge, as administrators feared an outbreak of violence. The court will announce a sentence on M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Indian police raid premises linked to NDTV founders - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/indian-police-raid-premises-linked-ndtv-founders-170605134740494.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELmeKiQcj9KjEVGmbDL0c9YqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 14:48:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/indian-police-raid-premises-linked-ndtv-founders-170605134740494.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian police raid premises linked to NDTV founders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's federal police have conducted raids on offices and residences linked to founders of NDTV, the country's oldest English-language news channel, which termed it a "witch-hunt" and an attempt to "undermine free speech". "NDTV and its promoters will fight tirelessly against this witch-hunt by multiple agencies. We will not succumb to these attempts to blatantly undermine democracy and free speech in India," the broadcaster, which is seen as critical towards the government of Prime Minister Narendra Modi, said in a statement on Monday. It dismissing the raids as "concerted harassment of N...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Indian agents raid former finance minister’s home - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/825b1250-39f7-11e7-821a-6027b8a20f23</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH32MYwTLQCKetujxeZgLtcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 10:17:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/825b1250-39f7-11e7-821a-6027b8a20f23" target="_blank"&gt;Indian agents raid former finance minister’s home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian agents have raided the home of the country’s former finance minister as part of an investigation into alleged violations of strict foreign investment rules. India’s Central Bureau of Investigation said it had visited locations in the southern city of Chennai on Tuesday morning, including the home of Karti Chidambaram, which he shares with his father P Chidambaram, a Congress party politician whose most recent cabinet post was as finance minister from 2012 to 2014. The CBI said its officers had also searched locations in Delhi, Mumbai and Gurgaon — the business hub to the south of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Indian guru is jailed amid heightened security for 10 years for raping two of his followers - Irish Examiner</title><link>http://www.breakingnews.ie/world/indian-guru-is-jailed-amid-heightened-security-for-10-years-for-raping-two-of-his-followers-803676.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIxVBiu1tscsbpVzz_06hKoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwzaShAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 11:05:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.breakingnews.ie/world/indian-guru-is-jailed-amid-heightened-security-for-10-years-for-raping-two-of-his-followers-803676.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian guru is jailed amid heightened security for 10 years for raping two of his followers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A controversial Indian spiritual guru has been jailed for 10 years on charges of raping two female followers. The sentence was announced on Monday amid intense security at a prison in the northern town of Rohtak, where the guru, who calls himself Dr Saint Gurmeet Singh Ram Rahim Insan, has been in prison since his conviction on Friday. The conviction sparked violent protests by his followers that left at least 38 people dead. A curfew was imposed in Rohtak and in Sirsa town, where the guru's Dera Sacha Sauda sect has a sprawling ashram. Both towns are in Haryana state. Thousands of police, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>India removes investigative agency head amid probe of deputy - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/65110dec5634479b8b89db6143b3d05a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMMw1WQccJQS4rPzOkPb1MYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 00:32:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/65110dec5634479b8b89db6143b3d05a" target="_blank"&gt;India removes investigative agency head amid probe of deputy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — The government of India placed the director of the federal investigative agency and his deputy on leave on Wednesday days after the agency filed a case against the deputy alleging that he took bribes to settle a money laundering case. A government appointment committee headed by Prime Minister Narendra Modi put out an order around 2 a.m. Wednesday sending the Central Bureau of Investigation's top two officials on leave and appointing a joint director as the interim head. India's Central Vigilance Commission, an autonomous anti-corruption body, had recommended the removal of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>India's CBI chief removed, critics say 'misuse of power' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/india-cbi-chief-removed-critics-misuse-power-181024085438865.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYg_XZaBL5Kdy2vezpULfsqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 14:58:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/india-cbi-chief-removed-critics-misuse-power-181024085438865.html" target="_blank"&gt;India's CBI chief removed, critics say 'misuse of power'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's government removed the head of the country's top investigating agency and his deputy in a pre-dawn raid on Wednesday - a move the opposition parties and constitutional experts said amounted to "misuse of power". Director of the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI), Alok Verma, and Special Director Rakesh Asthana were asked to go on leave after the premier agency filed a corruption case against Asthana. A feud between the two men has been simmering since before Asthana, who is allegedly close to Prime Minister Narendra Modi, was promoted to the agency's second-highest post last year...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>India's FBI-style police agency hit by infighting, government orders probe - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-police/indias-fbi-style-police-agency-hit-by-infighting-government-orders-probe-idUSKCN1MY1LI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIDkrMqFcxREeoUHmLAn_vAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 12:01:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-police/indias-fbi-style-police-agency-hit-by-infighting-government-orders-probe-idUSKCN1MY1LI" target="_blank"&gt;India's FBI-style police agency hit by infighting, government orders probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's government on Wednesday ordered a probe at the country's top crime fighting bureau after its two senior officers accused each other of bribery and interference in police investigations. The weeks-long public spat between Alok Verma, director of the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI), and his second-in-command, Rakesh Asthana, has embarrassed an agency that serves a similar role as the U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation. The CBI is leading several high profile investigations such as the $2 billion fraud at Punjab National Bank involving fugitive diamond billionaire Nirav Modi, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Indian police scrutinize major law firm in PNB fraud probe after documents moved - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-fraud-punjab-natl-bank-exclusiv/exclusive-indian-police-scrutinize-major-law-firm-in-pnb-fraud-probe-after-documents-moved-idUSKCN1LY370</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPtPAcqXIbgknPmcQmmPoDsqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 23:10:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-fraud-punjab-natl-bank-exclusiv/exclusive-indian-police-scrutinize-major-law-firm-in-pnb-fraud-probe-after-documents-moved-idUSKCN1LY370" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Indian police scrutinize major law firm in PNB fraud probe after documents moved&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's largest law firm, Cyril Amarchand Mangaldas (CAM), is being scrutinized by federal agents after they seized documents related to the $2 billion fraud at state-run Punjab National Bank (PNBK.NS: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) from CAM’s premises in February, a lawyer representing the government and a police source told Reuters. In what has been dubbed as India's biggest bank fraud, PNB in January alleged that billionaire diamond jeweler Nirav Modi and his uncle had for years fraudulently raised billions of dollars in foreign credit by conspiring with staff at the bank. In mid-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Extradition ruling for Indian tycoon set for December 10 - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8f28e5c4-b69d-11e8-b3ef-799c8613f4a1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEMAZEujdJoApwEYW_LYG-YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 16:34:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8f28e5c4-b69d-11e8-b3ef-799c8613f4a1" target="_blank"&gt;Extradition ruling for Indian tycoon set for December 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vijay Mallya, the Indian tycoon, will have to wait until mid December before he finds out whether he will be extradited from the UK to India to face fraud charges. Emma Arbuthnot, the chief magistrate at Westminster Magistrates Court, said she would issue her decision on December 10 after she heard closing arguments in the case on Wednesday. Mr Mallya, 62, who has been living in London since 2016, denies wrongdoing and is fighting the Indian government’s request that he be extradited to stand trial in India, where he faces allegations of financial misconduct relating to the 2012 collapse of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>India's CBI to investigate Facebook-Cambridge Analytica data theft - Reuters</title><link>https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-india-cbi/indias-cbi-to-investigate-facebook-cambridge-analytica-data-theft-idUSKBN1KG1SI?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGYeuRkDtQRRxJvwy15hhCEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 13:12:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-india-cbi/indias-cbi-to-investigate-facebook-cambridge-analytica-data-theft-idUSKBN1KG1SI?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" target="_blank"&gt;India's CBI to investigate Facebook-Cambridge Analytica data theft&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Indian government has asked the Central Bureau of Investigation to probe political consultancy Cambridge Analytica's misuse of Facebook user data, India's law minister Ravi Shankar Prasad told parliament on Thursday. "It is suspected that Cambridge Analytica may have been involved in illegally obtaining data of Indians which could be misused," Prasad said. Facebook has faced increased scrutiny in the United States and the European Union over how Cambridge Analytica obtained the personal data of 87 million Facebook users. The consultancy allegedly used the data to support U.S. President ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://internal.www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India's federal police charge former finance minister Chidambaram over telecoms deal - Reuters</title><link>https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-india-politics-corruption/indias-federal-police-charge-former-finance-minister-chidambaram-over-telecoms-deal-idUSKBN1K922L?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHrbLYh6zaRDxhFS0RgarkYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 14:01:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-india-politics-corruption/indias-federal-police-charge-former-finance-minister-chidambaram-over-telecoms-deal-idUSKBN1K922L?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" target="_blank"&gt;India's federal police charge former finance minister Chidambaram over telecoms deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's federal police have charged former finance minister P. Chidambaram with abuse of his official position and criminal conspiracy over the approval of a telecoms deal in 2006, they said on Thursday. The accusations center on the role of Chidambaram, now a senior leader of the main opposition Congress party, his son Karti Chidambaram, and several former government officials, in approving the acquisition of an Indian telecoms company, Aircel Ltd, by a Malyasian firm, Maxis Bhd. The individuals accused in the case face charges of "abuse of official position and criminal conspiracy in givi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://internal.www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India ruling party lawmaker charged with rape of minor - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/12/asia/india-bjp-lawmaker-rape-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENRO6ThV3rxCAEZf4pF0A0YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 12:06:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/12/asia/india-bjp-lawmaker-rape-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;India ruling party lawmaker charged with rape of minor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lawmaker from India's ruling party has been charged with raping a teenage girl, whose father was allegedly beaten to death when the family complained. The Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) has charged Kuldeep Singh Sengar -- an elected member of the Uttar Pradesh state legislative assembly -- with rape, abduction, criminal conspiracy, criminal intimidation and rape of a minor under the Protection of Children from Sexual Offenses Act. He has denied all charges. The girl, now 17, claims she was attacked by Sengar on June 4, 2017 when she was taken to his home on the pretext of getting a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Interpol seeks arrest of Indian billionaire jeweller Nirav Modi - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/interpol-seeks-arrest-indian-billionaire-jeweler-nirav-modi-180703083223932.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIIFp0A8apwt4gZtO_ZXKy8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 07:25:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/interpol-seeks-arrest-indian-billionaire-jeweler-nirav-modi-180703083223932.html" target="_blank"&gt;Interpol seeks arrest of Indian billionaire jeweller Nirav Modi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interpol has issued a red notice for the arrest of Indian billionaire jeweller Nirav Modi, who is at the centre of an alleged $2bn bank fraud. India's Central Bureau of Investigation is probing a multibillion-dollar scam, allegedly involving Modi, and several Indian courts have issued arrest warrants over his failure to appear before them. Interpol issued a red notice for Modi on Tuesday, a call to international police forces when a suspect is wanted for prosecution or to serve a sentence based on an arrest warrant or court decision. Earlier this year, India's state-run Punjab National Bank...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>How the International Police Dragnet Now Tightens Around Former-Billionaire Diamond Mogul Nirav Modi - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/guymartin/2018/06/30/how-the-international-police-dragnet-now-tightens-around-former-billionaire-diamond-mogul-nirav-modi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP1Cy2UnClwh_OtEAjDXC2cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 03:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/guymartin/2018/06/30/how-the-international-police-dragnet-now-tightens-around-former-billionaire-diamond-mogul-nirav-modi/" target="_blank"&gt;How the International Police Dragnet Now Tightens Around Former-Billionaire Diamond Mogul Nirav Modi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Icarus, Rising Before The Fall: Nirav Modi, center, flanked by South Korean singer and actor Rain (Jung Ji-Hoon), left, and actress Zhang Ziyi, right, at the gala opening of Modi’s flagship Hong Kong store in 2016. (Photo by VCG/VCG via Getty Images) With his cherub-like cheeks and his trademark Cheshire Cat grin, former Forbes-List billionaire Nirav Modi bears a welcoming, if preternatural, charm. But lately, the diamond merchant-turned-jewelry designer has been otherwise engaged in what we can describe as a long bout of touch-and-go travel – quite awkwardly, with five reportedly invalid ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Fugitive Indian billionaire Nirav Modi last seen in Britain in March - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/19/fugitive-indian-billionaire-nirav-modi-last-seen-in-britain-in-march</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMQihGis1-kY5mkIEiWY1xcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 01:26:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/19/fugitive-indian-billionaire-nirav-modi-last-seen-in-britain-in-march" target="_blank"&gt;Fugitive Indian billionaire Nirav Modi last seen in Britain in March&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fugitive billionaire jeweller Nirav Modi was last seen in Britain in March, Indian federal investigators have said. The Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) is probing a multi-billion dollar scam allegedly involving Modi, who is worth $1.73bn according to Forbes, placing him 85th on India’s rich list. “Request letters were written to six countries, namely USA, France, Singapore, Brussels, UAE and UK. Only UK replied to request letter stating Nirav Modi was last seen on March 31 there,” said CBI spokesman Abhishek Dayal. Media reports in India and Britain in the last few days have said ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>India charges 22 over alleged $2bn fraud at Punjab National Bank - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/3ec1627e-5792-11e8-bdb7-f6677d2e1ce8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBvkdXHorYauiAKyU0hFmj4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 18:38:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3ec1627e-5792-11e8-bdb7-f6677d2e1ce8" target="_blank"&gt;India charges 22 over alleged $2bn fraud at Punjab National Bank&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian investigators probing an alleged $2bn fraud at Punjab National Bank have filed charges against 22 people including a former chief executive of the bank, amid a scandal that has sparked fears about governance standards at the country’s huge state-owned lenders. The Central Bureau of Investigation launched its probe on January 31 after a complaint from PNB about a major fraud using improperly obtained bank guarantees. In a claim that has added to huge public interest in the case, PNB alleged that the scheme involved the celebrity jeweller Nirav Modi, whose lawyer has denied involvement...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>​Jiah Khan's ex-partner Sooraj Pancholi charged over death of Bollywood star - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jan/31/jiah-khans-ex-partner-sooraj-pancholi-charged-over-death-of-bollywood-star</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBl9MUge1kl0CcplwBVunr0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 11:34:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jan/31/jiah-khans-ex-partner-sooraj-pancholi-charged-over-death-of-bollywood-star" target="_blank"&gt;​Jiah Khan's ex-partner Sooraj Pancholi charged over death of Bollywood star&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A court in Mumbai has charged the Bollywood actor Sooraj Pancholi with abetting the suicide of his former partner, the actor Jiah Khan, who was found dead in her apartment by her mother in June 2013. Khan had made a sensational debut in the industry, starring opposite the veteran actor Amitabh Bachchan in the 2007 film Nishabd. Khan was 25 and had been in a relationship with Pancholi for nine months when she killed herself. According to Indian police and the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) she had spent two days with Pancholi in his flat before her death. Pancholi was 22 at the time. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Indian human traffickers 'used fake rugby tour to smuggle boys to France' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/12/30/indian-human-traffickers-used-fake-rugby-tour-smuggle-boys-france/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHnMIWJgqs0_YWDlRdvCcdsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 15:27:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/12/30/indian-human-traffickers-used-fake-rugby-tour-smuggle-boys-france/" target="_blank"&gt;Indian human traffickers 'used fake rugby tour to smuggle boys to France'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian police have broken up an alleged human trafficking ring which transported young boys to France on the pretext of sending them on rugby tours. The Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) arrested three men after they allegedly tricked the families of 25 children into sending them to France for what they said was a rugby camp. Once the boys arrived in France in early 2016 they were reportedly taken to a gurudwara, a Sikh temple, in Paris and stripped of their passports. The case only came to light this year after two of the boys escaped and another was found by French police, who passed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>‘No evidence’ that Vijay Mallya committed fraud, lawyers say - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/40c3aeac-d9c4-11e7-a039-c64b1c09b482</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJJppqpjTGMT_v3yC19GmCsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 16:02:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/40c3aeac-d9c4-11e7-a039-c64b1c09b482" target="_blank"&gt;‘No evidence’ that Vijay Mallya committed fraud, lawyers say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is “no evidence” to support claims of fraud against Vijay Mallya, a lawyer for the flamboyant Indian tycoon told a London court on Tuesday. Mr Mallya, 61, who has been living in London since early last year, is fighting the Indian government’s request that he be extradited to stand trial in India, where he faces allegations of financial misconduct relating to the 2012 collapse of his former company, Kingfisher Airlines. His case is the subject of a two-week extradition hearing at Westminster magistrates’ court in London. The hearing is not a trial to determine Mr Mallya’s innocence or...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Vijay Mallya never ‘intended to repay’ Indian bank loans - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/068297c0-d902-11e7-a039-c64b1c09b482</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPwv_2jGEZG-ae3b4fsSXP8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 17:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/068297c0-d902-11e7-a039-c64b1c09b482" target="_blank"&gt;Vijay Mallya never ‘intended to repay’ Indian bank loans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flamboyant tycoon Vijay Mallya never “intended to repay” loans from a government-owned Indian bank, lawyers for the Indian government told a London court on Monday. Mr Mallya, who has been living in London since early last year, is fighting the Indian government’s request that he be extradited to stand trial in India, where he faces allegations of financial misconduct relating to the 2012 collapse of his former company, Kingfisher Airlines. Mr Mallya and nine other bankers and former Kingfisher Airlines executives have been handed criminal charges from India’s Central Bureau of Investigatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>