<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>French fries - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNREo1Tm00U0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:56:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Wendy's' $1 Any Size Fry Offer For December 2018 Is Perfect For Holiday Snacking - Elite Daily</title><link>https://www.elitedaily.com/p/wendys-1-any-size-fry-offer-for-december-2018-is-perfect-for-holiday-snacking-13226756</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC1ngw8qviIzSToEIfe3uisqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowxqzzCjCF2-ACMI-HwAU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 18:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.elitedaily.com/p/wendys-1-any-size-fry-offer-for-december-2018-is-perfect-for-holiday-snacking-13226756" target="_blank"&gt;Wendy's' $1 Any Size Fry Offer For December 2018 Is Perfect For Holiday Snacking&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Elite Daily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is quite literally nothing in this world that says "holiday cheer" like a solid food discount. And in the name of Christmas, Hanukkah, and Kwanzaa, Wendy's ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.elitedaily.com">Elite Daily</source></item><item><title>Harvard Dietitian: You Should Only Be Eating 6 French Fries Per Serving - WFMYNews2.com</title><link>https://www.wfmynews2.com/mobile/article/news/health/harvard-dietitian-you-should-only-be-eating-6-french-fries-per-serving/83-620947906</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiiAFodHRwczovL3d3dy53Zm15bmV3czIuY29tL21vYmlsZS9hcnRpY2xlL25ld3MvaGVhbHRoL2hhcnZhcmQtZGlldGl0aWFuLXlvdS1zaG91bGQtb25seS1iZS1lYXRpbmctNi1mcmVuY2gtZnJpZXMtcGVyLXNlcnZpbmcvODMtNjIwOTQ3OTA20gH1AWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LXdmbXluZXdzMi1jb20uY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy93d3cud2ZteW5ld3MyLmNvbS9hbXAvYXJ0aWNsZT9zZWN0aW9uPW5ld3Mmc3Vic2VjdGlvbj1oZWFsdGgmaGVhZGxpbmU9aGFydmFyZC1kaWV0aXRpYW4teW91LXNob3VsZC1vbmx5LWJlLWVhdGluZy02LWZyZW5jaC1mcmllcy1wZXItc2VydmluZyZjb250ZW50SWQ9ODMtNjIwOTQ3OTA2JmFtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.wfmynews2.com/mobile/article/news/health/harvard-dietitian-you-should-only-be-eating-6-french-fries-per-serving/83-620947906" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Dietitian: You Should Only Be Eating 6 French Fries Per Serving&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;WFMYNews2.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Harvard nutrition professor said a good side would be a salad and six French fries.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.wfmynews2.com">WFMYNews2.com</source></item><item><title>Jack In The Box's New Sauced &amp; Loaded Fries Are A Cozy Bite This Winter - Elite Daily</title><link>https://www.elitedaily.com/p/jack-in-the-boxs-new-sauced-loaded-fries-are-a-cozy-bite-this-winter-13248325</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAyQ4tQm9TKBsXD-SCeEbEwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowxqzzCjCF2-ACMI-HwAU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.elitedaily.com/p/jack-in-the-boxs-new-sauced-loaded-fries-are-a-cozy-bite-this-winter-13248325" target="_blank"&gt;Jack In The Box's New Sauced &amp; Loaded Fries Are A Cozy Bite This Winter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Elite Daily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the temperatures dropping and snow on the way, this is the perfect time of year to fire up your crockpot and cook up a cozy meal. If you are like me and don't ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.elitedaily.com">Elite Daily</source></item><item><title>Harvard professor mocked for saying a portion of fries should only contain six - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/french-fry-portion-harvard-professor-six-obesity-portion-control-diabetes-potatoes-a8661986.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4fsl6CU403kFeOF5hyxd0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/french-fry-portion-harvard-professor-six-obesity-portion-control-diabetes-potatoes-a8661986.html" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard professor mocked for saying a portion of fries should only contain six&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Harvard professor said it would be “nice” if an order of fries only contained six - to which people have reacted with outrage and disbelief. Despite being one of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Scientist called safe for the health portion of fries - The Kozweek</title><link>https://kozweek.com/scientist-called-safe-for-the-health-portion-of-fries/24353/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiUGh0dHBzOi8va296d2Vlay5jb20vc2NpZW50aXN0LWNhbGxlZC1zYWZlLWZvci10aGUtaGVhbHRoLXBvcnRpb24tb2YtZnJpZXMvMjQzNTMv0gGYAWh0dHBzOi8va296d2Vlay1jb20uY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy9rb3p3ZWVrLmNvbS9zY2llbnRpc3QtY2FsbGVkLXNhZmUtZm9yLXRoZS1oZWFsdGgtcG9ydGlvbi1vZi1mcmllcy8yNDM1My9hbXAvP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:56:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://kozweek.com/scientist-called-safe-for-the-health-portion-of-fries/24353/" target="_blank"&gt;Scientist called safe for the health portion of fries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Kozweek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The potato itself is full of calories, deep roasting, which prepares katiel fries, makes the caloric *content* of this dish even more impressive. Abuse of French fries ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://kozweek.com">The Kozweek</source></item><item><title>This is what happens when a school swaps french fries for quinoa - World Economic Forum</title><link>https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2018/12/this-city-is-swapping-french-fries-for-quinoa-in-school-dinners/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiZ2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LndlZm9ydW0ub3JnL2FnZW5kYS8yMDE4LzEyL3RoaXMtY2l0eS1pcy1zd2FwcGluZy1mcmVuY2gtZnJpZXMtZm9yLXF1aW5vYS1pbi1zY2hvb2wtZGlubmVycy_SAQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:16:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2018/12/this-city-is-swapping-french-fries-for-quinoa-in-school-dinners/" target="_blank"&gt;This is what happens when a school swaps french fries for quinoa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;World Economic Forum&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quito in Ecuador is tackling the childhood obesity crisis, one school dinner at a time.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.weforum.org">World Economic Forum</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/qV6QOwbLcPaygl5av3NNf4G2_dZwArBu_Rg5ExqCi4N4g_XWN_UhQkNqlM2o27_87mOHv-EOLq2uD-Wn8D9-rtpZ1-Nfyo0PNJXkXL1Rm-RjLFpu0V_e4p2V3izBxBmo0jXyH6HD2M6CAc76uKQaabnV=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>The Only Way to Get Fresh Fries at McDonald's - Reader's Digest</title><link>https://www.rd.com/food/fun/get-fresh-mcdonalds-fries/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiNmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnJkLmNvbS9mb29kL2Z1bi9nZXQtZnJlc2gtbWNkb25hbGRzLWZyaWVzL9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 07:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rd.com/food/fun/get-fresh-mcdonalds-fries/" target="_blank"&gt;The Only Way to Get Fresh Fries at McDonald's&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reader's Digest&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might not go to McDonald's when you're looking for farm-*fresh* fare, but you'd at least hope your meal hasn't been sitting around for hours before you ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rd.com">Reader's Digest</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/5uthWxnaTG4jCZ3AuKX4z66-vG1dj6jVLwzMOtby_hHZitqAJV84g3fwIhqaTJ-4EY-je9ntDiyd1OswYf6vRzuPeoMHrp6nwcfrpUbvu_mBgOsNdtdC2yJ0lZQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Bites: In London, a Simple Approach and a Complex Finish - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/08/travel/bites-london-cora-pearl.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE3JKBxdjdL_CRhrL3sQSlQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4UY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:00:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/08/travel/bites-london-cora-pearl.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bites: In London, a Simple Approach and a Complex Finish&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;London’s Covent Garden district is not short of restaurants. Lots of them are links in British and international chains (anyone for Shake Shack?), but there are plenty of excellent independents too. One of the newest is Cora Pearl, named after a woman whose dates were 1835-86 and whose occupation Wikipedia gives as “courtesan.” A sister restaurant, Kitty Fisher, also takes its name from a scandalous woman, albeit one who had her portrait painted by Joshua Reynolds. Evidently, this is meant to evoke the high life of ages past. But apart from some Beardsley-esque artwork there’s little about ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>This nutritionist says you shouldn't eat more than six chips at once and thank u, next - Her.ie</title><link>https://www.her.ie/food/nutritionist-says-shouldnt-eat-six-chips-thank-u-next-439457</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIgmAMpW5j-KGdu4Dxb2ZYIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8w6a6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:00:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.her.ie/food/nutritionist-says-shouldnt-eat-six-chips-thank-u-next-439457" target="_blank"&gt;This nutritionist says you shouldn't eat more than six chips at once and thank u, next&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We don't need that kind of negativity in our lives. We all have ourfavourite types of chips, from sweet potatoesfries, chunky, skinny or peri salted - we'll take the lot! Whether McDonald'sis more your vibe or you're a fan of chips from a van at a festival with the cheap ketchup (delish) almost everyone loves a hearty few chips every now and then. Obviously, we shouldn't really be consuming them every day but look when we're going to treat ourselves, we're going to TREAT ourselves! via GIPHY We honestly couldn't believe when a New York nutritionist, Dr Eric Rimm, has some prettyharsh opinio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>Burger King trolls McDonald's with 1 cent burger promotion - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/business/burger-king-1-cent-burger/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENPFDFxApm9XnrmVGzOzom0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:04:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/business/burger-king-1-cent-burger/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Burger King trolls McDonald's with 1 cent burger promotion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burger King wants people to download its app. So it's sending them to McDonald's for access to a one-cent Whopper. Here's how it works: If you're within 600-feet of a McDonald's you can unlock a deal for a penny Whopper using the Burger King app. The app then offers directions to a nearby participating Burger King, where you can pick up the burger. The company announced the deal on Tuesday. It runs through December 12, and customers can only access it once. Burger King's not the only fast food chain trying out creative ways to get people to download its mobile app. McDonald's recently ran a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>You Can Have More Than 6 French Fries, Just Try To Do This - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/12/05/you-can-have-more-than-6-french-fries-just-try-to-do-this/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI_BF5NJ7LXNium9cN_rxZYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/12/05/you-can-have-more-than-6-french-fries-just-try-to-do-this/" target="_blank"&gt;You Can Have More Than 6 French Fries, Just Try To Do This&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;French fries. (Photo by: BSIP/UIG via Getty Images) Do you want fry with that? Not fries as in multiple French Fries, but fry as in a single French Fry. How about 2 fries? Maybe 3? Or if you really want to indulge, perhaps even 6 fries? You may be more used to thinking about French Fries in mounds, fistfulls, or even buckets rather than such specific single-digit numbers. However, Christopher Mele writing for the New York Times quoted Eric Rimm, ScD, Professor of Epidemiology and Nutrition at the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health, as saying, “I think it would be nice if your meal ca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Subtleties of Vietnamese Food Are An Education At New York's Bocaphe - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnmariani/2018/12/05/the-subtleties-of-vietnamese-food-are-an-education-at-new-yorks-bocaphe/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELZVnshiAlkXNGYpWOyqaDIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnmariani/2018/12/05/the-subtleties-of-vietnamese-food-are-an-education-at-new-yorks-bocaphe/" target="_blank"&gt;The Subtleties of Vietnamese Food Are An Education At New York's Bocaphe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A panoply of dishes at Bocaphe shows how Vietnamese food differs and resembles others of Southeast Asia. My avoidance of restaurants big and small south of Houston Street is based on way too many experiences in rooms unconscionably cacophonous, shrill, clamorous and ear-shattering, owing both to raucously loud patrons and owners who refuse to baffle the sound but instead add to it with boom box pounding speakers. So it was with some trepidation that I visited Bocaphe in SoHo, which from the outside looks very much like one of those decibel-busting eateries. I was so happy to find that this ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Latkes Are A Lot More Than Basic Fried Potatoes At These Spots Around The Country - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alywalansky/2018/12/03/latkes-are-a-lot-more-than-basic-fried-potatoes-at-these-spots-around-the-country/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENbv-gZQGFZJPuBPZI4IyUkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alywalansky/2018/12/03/latkes-are-a-lot-more-than-basic-fried-potatoes-at-these-spots-around-the-country/" target="_blank"&gt;Latkes Are A Lot More Than Basic Fried Potatoes At These Spots Around The Country&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While a hot stack of fried potato pancakes is always an exciting way to celebrate Hanukkah, these spots around the country are taking the traditional latke and turning it into something rather special. Build Your Own Latke Board The Build Your Own Latke Board at Reserve Cut in New York City. There’s few things we enjoy more than playing with our food. This fun spin on a traditional latke order is served on a charcuterie board with the option to add chives, pastrami smoked salmon, house pickled onions, ginger apple chutney, harissa aioli, salmon roe or hollandaise. “Instead of a traditional...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Burger King/Nigeria: whoppertunity - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b966d7ca-f47c-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOOgAfW93cwmmC3kp12Bc5EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 18:33:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b966d7ca-f47c-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;Burger King/Nigeria: whoppertunity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blink and another Burger King will have opened somewhere across the globe, serving up french fries and double cheeseburgers to a world hungry for fast food. Next on the company’s radar is Nigeria, the oil-driven regional powerhouse that is Africa’s largest economy. With its 190m population and average age a burger-lovin’ 18, it is ready for a Whopper. At least Daniel Schwartz, chief executive of Restaurant Brands International (Burger King’s parent), hopes so. Since Mr Schwartz, 37, took the helm four years ago, he has looked outside the US for growth. The global fast food market grew 4.9 p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>You Don’t Want Fries With That - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/29/health/french-fries-nutrition.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECdsLqVxCKxeIrFS3YcJNWgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:53:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/29/health/french-fries-nutrition.html" target="_blank"&gt;You Don’t Want Fries With That&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If French fries come from potatoes, and potatoes are a vegetable, and vegetables are good for you, then what’s the harm in eating French fries? Plenty, say experts and nutritionists, including Eric Rimm, a professor in the departments of epidemiology and nutrition at the Harvard T. H. Chan School of Public Health, who called potatoes “starch bombs.” Potatoes rank near the bottom of healthful vegetables and lack the compounds and nutrients found in green leafy vegetables, he said. If you take a potato, remove its skin (where at least some nutrients are found), cut it, deep fry the pieces in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Felicity Cloake's perfect sweet potato fries – recipe - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/food/2018/nov/28/felicity-cloakes-perfect-sweet-potato-fries-recipe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAfj_h-inUsHp2QpHn9fPG8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 12:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/food/2018/nov/28/felicity-cloakes-perfect-sweet-potato-fries-recipe" target="_blank"&gt;Felicity Cloake's perfect sweet potato fries – recipe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until recently, I was suspicious of sweet potato fries as a concept: they seemed a misguided attempt to make chips healthy, with recipes that sang the praises of “non-starchy carbs” inevitably turning out sadly soggy results. Frankly, five-a-day points aren’t one of the things I look for in a fish supper – that’s what mushy peas were invented for, surely. Then, while travelling in the Caribbean, I had a revelation: crisp sweet potato fries that made a virtue of the tuber’s natural sugars to give a deliciously caramelised result. They weren’t trying to be potato chips – which is fortunate, b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How long do Thanksgiving leftovers last? - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-long-do-thanksgiving-leftovers-last-2018-11-23</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbl4u0a9tqRs5S-8lK8XtgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwuJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 16:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-long-do-thanksgiving-leftovers-last-2018-11-23" target="_blank"&gt;How long do Thanksgiving leftovers last?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Alessandra Malito Everything you need to know about storing food over the holidays Don’t throw out those leftovers just yet. 20th Century Fox Licensing/Merchandising / Everett Collection Thanksgiving may be over, but many Americans have plenty of leftover turkey, green bean casseroles, stuffing and pie. What to do with them? Americans throw out billions of dollars of uneaten food every year — $293 million of which happens with Thanksgiving turkey alone, according to government data. People are expected to throw away about 200 million pounds of turkey during the holidays, the Natural Reso...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Five Clever Ways To Use Thanksgiving Leftovers - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/nomanazish/2018/11/24/five-clever-ways-to-use-thanksgiving-leftovers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4xRm8aJAMyG_T0dtpfpHkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 20:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/nomanazish/2018/11/24/five-clever-ways-to-use-thanksgiving-leftovers/" target="_blank"&gt;Five Clever Ways To Use Thanksgiving Leftovers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Homemade Turkey Chili with beans and scallions. Photo Credit: Getty Now that Thanksgiving dinner is over and expensive china has been put away, it’s time to come up with new ideas to use up all those leftovers stocked in the fridge. After all, there are only so many turkey sandwiches anyone can stomach. Wondering what to cook for your next meal? Fret not! I’ve got you covered! Here are five creative ways to make the most of all those Turkey Day leftovers: - Turkey And Gravy: Besides burgers and sandwiches, leftover turkey can be reinvented into a variety of delish dishes like soup, salad, b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What belongs on a pizza? And seven more all-time epic food wars - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2018/nov/22/are-you-ready-to-fight-eight-of-the-most-epic-food-wars-of-all-time</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3BhCQ0HMl9V5QQTlYRX6IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCw3Gc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 08:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2018/nov/22/are-you-ready-to-fight-eight-of-the-most-epic-food-wars-of-all-time" target="_blank"&gt;What belongs on a pizza? And seven more all-time epic food wars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;People mostly love to use the internet to fight – a lot, about anything. This is particularly evident when it comes to fighting about food, with a seemingly endless flood of folks on social media arguing about everything from the relative merits of putting salt on watermelon to whether it’s appropriate to eat macaroni and cheese with a spoon. Some arguments, though, are greater than others. These showdowns are grounded in cultural differences, steeped in history or even cause politicians to get their hackles up: the kind of disagreements that inspire breakups, family meltdowns and (potentia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>What to Cook: What to Cook Right Now - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/26/dining/what-to-cook-right-now-newsletter.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEGxtFMy81aep8EJzjCgmlAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 15:30:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/26/dining/what-to-cook-right-now-newsletter.html" target="_blank"&gt;What to Cook: What to Cook Right Now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good morning. They’re gone now, your family and guests, and the house is yours again after the long holiday weekend. Or you’re gone now, out of that town that you can’t believe you lived in for 18 years, with all those people and what they believe, back to your real life, the one you built yourself. Either way, I hope there was joy in Thanksgiving for you, whether you celebrated in fire-ravaged California or frozen New England, after walking down Florida beaches or toward the last day of elk season in Montana, whether in the suburbs of St. Louis or in the Catalina foothills, near Tucson. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>The Beyond Burger Is Now Available At Tesco, The UK's Largest Supermarket - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/elizabethrushe/2018/11/22/the-beyond-burger-is-now-available-at-tesco-the-uks-largest-supermarket/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJC2Et4qW9lSxkKpJnZh9WEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/elizabethrushe/2018/11/22/the-beyond-burger-is-now-available-at-tesco-the-uks-largest-supermarket/" target="_blank"&gt;The Beyond Burger Is Now Available At Tesco, The UK's Largest Supermarket&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Beyond Burger, a plant-based burger that bleeds beetroot and is made with pea protein Beyond Burger’s eagerly awaited arrival in the UK is finally here, the bleeding plant-based burger is now available in Tesco – Britain’s largest retailer, which has approximately 28.4% of the market. The plant-based burger, which is vegan (and soy free and gluten free for that matter), gives a realistic burger experience with beetroot drippings. Pea protein is one of the main ingredients, along with coconut oil and smoke flavouring. The launch was initially planned for three hundred and fifty Tesco sto...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Chrissy Teigen asked Twitter for healthy fast food recommendations - and the responses were useful - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/chrissy-teigen-fast-food-twitter-healthy-taco-bell-chipotle-nandos-a8645456.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPr6eepWoM_3DSKVKlv8xcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 17:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/chrissy-teigen-fast-food-twitter-healthy-taco-bell-chipotle-nandos-a8645456.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chrissy Teigen asked Twitter for healthy fast food recommendations - and the responses were useful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chrissy Teigen recently asked her Twitter followers for healthy fast food recommendations - and they actually delivered. The model and cookbook author who regularly shares her cravings with fans asked the question of her 10.6m followers, writing: “What do you think is the healthiest meal (not side) of any normally junky fast food chain?” Teigen then informed her followers that she was looking for “serious” responses only. - Read more Vegetarian meals at fast food outlets no healthier than meat options “NO JOKE ANSWERS PLEASE this is serious,” she wrote. While many of the more than 2,000 res...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>McDonald's Makes More Happy Meal Changes, Bringing It Closer To A Healthy Meal - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michelinemaynard/2018/11/16/mcdonalds-makes-more-happy-meal-changes-bringing-it-closer-to-a-healthy-meal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHWPS4aSPjEW8NRmI9SdzGAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 16:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/michelinemaynard/2018/11/16/mcdonalds-makes-more-happy-meal-changes-bringing-it-closer-to-a-healthy-meal/" target="_blank"&gt;McDonald's Makes More Happy Meal Changes, Bringing It Closer To A Healthy Meal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;McDonald’s has been tweaking the Happy Meal in a quest to bring down its calories. (AP Photo/Rogelio V. Solis) For generations, the McDonald’s Happy Meal was a little burger, small fries and a little soda, plus a little toy. Then, advocacy groups asking for changes so kids could have healthier options, and the burger chain responded. Now, McDonald’s is making more tweaks to make the Happy Meal even leaner. On Thursday, McDonald’s said it would make a 16.9 ounce bottle of Dasani brand water an option on the kids’ menu at no additional cost, and also is removing preservatives from low-fat st...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What to Cook: What to Cook This Weekend - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/23/dining/what-to-cook-this-weekend.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEST4kSorYT13Fsa8BzCxyEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4UY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/23/dining/what-to-cook-this-weekend.html" target="_blank"&gt;What to Cook: What to Cook This Weekend&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good morning. Black Friday and the malls jammed with revelers looking for good deals on gigantic screens they’ll rarely watch. They’d rather snuggle into the covers to take in “Fauda” on their cracked and beloved phones. That’s not my scene. Today’s a day for walking in a park, along a beach, through a wood, in advance of leftovers from the fridge, lunch into dinner where we’ll give thanks again. NYT Cooking has a cornucopia of recipes for Thanksgiving leftovers. I like Margaux Laskey’s instructions for a turkey enchilada pie. Also, Samin Nosrat’s recipe for turkey tikka masala (above). You...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>The Bird Rules the Thanksgiving Magazine Cover - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/dining/thanksgiving-magazine-cover.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECoAkKO1yiYH6QFaaiaqXfwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 17:13:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/dining/thanksgiving-magazine-cover.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Bird Rules the Thanksgiving Magazine Cover&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;No matter how colorful they are, or how perfectly crimped their crusts, pies are unreliable cover stars. So are heaps of mashed potatoes, even when melted butter, the color of pure sunlight, pools in their dimples. As a general rule, November’s food magazines lead with the birds. Turkeys: Voluptuous, browned and gloriously crisp, freckled with salt and pepper. Their flawless skins reflect the studio lights, and on closer inspection seem to glow, as if from within. For seasoned teams of stylists, photographers and editors, producing a stunning Thanksgiving cover image is as much an annual ob...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Beyond Meat Continues To Sizzle, Announces IPO - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelpellmanrowland/2018/11/18/vegan-ipo-beyond-meat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKYpFoAs1UhC1_srm2YodAQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelpellmanrowland/2018/11/18/vegan-ipo-beyond-meat/" target="_blank"&gt;Beyond Meat Continues To Sizzle, Announces IPO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumers say it’s hard to distinguish from the real thing Less than a month after rumors began that Beyond Meat might decide to go public, the California plant-based powerhouse has put its chips on the table and filed for an IPO . In documents filed Friday, the company said it had applied to list its common stock on the Nasdaq under the symbol “BYND,” with an initial offering size of $100 million. This dollar amount is a placeholder and likely to change. They’ve also announced that they’ve appointed Ned Segal, Twitter’s chief financial officer, and Kathy Waller, who has the same role at th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>11 food combinations only Irish people eat - Her.ie</title><link>https://www.her.ie/life/11-random-food-combinations-only-irish-people-eat-222674</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOIwYXzucTt-S0Tu2OX8SRwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8wnpqhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 09:55:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.her.ie/life/11-random-food-combinations-only-irish-people-eat-222674" target="_blank"&gt;11 food combinations only Irish people eat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theres some things that are immediately recognised as being traditionally Irish such as our penchant for a good old crisp sandwich or our belief that a cup of tea solves every problem. However, the Irish are also pretty well known for having a lot of random food combinations that many others just dont really get. Here are some of our weird and wonderful favourites. _________________________________________ Crisp sandwiches There is only one snack that can take the number one spot for Irish people. Regardless of whether you are a King or Tayto lover, crisp sandwiches are the ultimate comfort...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>How Burger King fell behind - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/13/business/burger-king-strategy/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMr_bQtNAMoo6G4lNuuZTWYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:52:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/13/business/burger-king-strategy/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;How Burger King fell behind&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burger King wants to move into the future, but it's still stuck in the past. The fast food chain's parent company, Restaurant Brands International (QSR), said last month that it plans to modernize Burger King's locations across the country in a plan it calls "Burger King of Tomorrow." Despite the project's name, Burger King's efforts are nothing new. The updated restaurants will feature self-order kiosks and sleeker restaurants — changes Burger King's competitors started making years ago. While its competitors were upgrading their stores, Burger King focused on marketing campaigns and menu ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>What to Cook: What to Cook This Week - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/11/dining/what-to-cook-this-week.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIMtzGLpxdQSoQbbhjE3cu0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4UY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 20:46:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/11/dining/what-to-cook-this-week.html" target="_blank"&gt;What to Cook: What to Cook This Week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Correction: November 14, 2018 This article has been revised to reflect the following correction: An earlier version of this article described incorrectly David Tanis’s recipe for a Jell-O mold. It contains pomegranate and citrus. There are no cranberries. Good morning. I’ll get to the cooking soon enough, to the soups and stir-fries, the pastas and bakes, a week’s worth of recipes, our usual Sunday brief. But we’re 10 days out from Thanksgiving, and I’m the coach running vicious practices because I want you to win. There is stuff to do before we cook. I want you to clear out your freezer an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>A Good Appetite: A Dish to Comfort on Those Cold, Dark Days - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/09/dining/sweet-potato-aligot.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECuiUtyzheJwpLniceZHRboqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 18:40:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/09/dining/sweet-potato-aligot.html" target="_blank"&gt;A Good Appetite: A Dish to Comfort on Those Cold, Dark Days&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a perfect French pommes aligot, it’s hard to know where the potatoes end and the cheese begins. A molten, creamy mass of potatoes permeated with mountain cheeses, aligot combines the stretchy pull of fondue with the silky suppleness of potato purée. Soft, gooey and eminently soothing, it’s just the thing to make on an icy, dark day, or at least, when it feels that way deep in your soul. I first saw aligot potatoes, a dish from the wind-swept Aubrac plateau in France, being whipped up tableside at a restaurant in the Auvergne. Into a well-used copper pot, the waiter beat boiled yellow pot...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>A Cork girl filmed her granny's reaction to trying fast food for the first time and it's GOLDEN - Her.ie</title><link>https://www.her.ie/life/cork-girl-filmed-grannys-reaction-trying-fast-food-first-time-golden-434476</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHFNCe9Fd8hggOYZdE-58jIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8w6a6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 14:36:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.her.ie/life/cork-girl-filmed-grannys-reaction-trying-fast-food-first-time-golden-434476" target="_blank"&gt;A Cork girl filmed her granny's reaction to trying fast food for the first time and it's GOLDEN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eva McCarthy filmed her eighty-three-year-oldgranny trying a variety of fast food items and now we all want to replicate the experiment. If youre lucky enough to have a grandparent in your life, youll know how special they are. Theres so much they can teach you, but theres also modernrevelations you can enlighten them on. Eva McCarthy, a twenty-two-year-old student from Cork has a very special best friend, her eighty-three-year-old granny. Eva says her granny is a firm favourite among friends on Snapchat and that she was inundated with requests to post more videos with nana, Margaret McCart...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>This Tex Mex BBQ is the real deal - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/valentinas-tex-mex-bbq-austin-texas/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELpdmWP9ZOmW2yexCsbzsWMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 14:43:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/valentinas-tex-mex-bbq-austin-texas/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;This Tex Mex BBQ is the real deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miguel Vidal remembers the moment when he knew what he would serve at his new restaurant, even though it was still a dream. Vidal grew up in San Antonio, Texas, and has worked in restaurants since he was 15 -- refining his technique and palate, training himself to eventually open his own restaurant. "I went home, and my dad had made a brisket. My mom had made homemade tortillas," Vidal told CNN Travel. "We had fresh salsa and avocado, and I'm thinking to myself, this is it," Vidal said. That's how Valentina's Tex Mex BBQ was born in 2013. Currently two food trailers and four barbecue pits p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Five Weeknight Dishes: Cozy and Clever - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/09/dining/cozy-and-clever.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDCQa6VN2Mf2Eo8TQja4vdEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 18:22:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/09/dining/cozy-and-clever.html" target="_blank"&gt;Five Weeknight Dishes: Cozy and Clever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi and welcome to Five Weeknight Dishes. I have something unsexy to discuss with you, and that is pilaf. And yet! Pilaf, versions of which are found the world over, is one of my recent favorites, adorably homely and the definition of comfort. It’s also a great way to use up chicken. My husband is our chief pilaf-maker; along with super-thin pancakes, it’s one of his specialties. (He uses a recipe from “How to Cook Everything.”) But I made it the other night, using shredded chicken, golden raisins and stock, topping each bowl with yogurt and a heap of parsley. So you could do this with lefto...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Nachos Are Fun But These Creative Spins Are Next Level Delicious - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alywalansky/2018/11/01/nachos-are-fun-but-these-creative-spins-are-next-level-delicious/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED67bQ5wfX_83mXbQjseWb0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alywalansky/2018/11/01/nachos-are-fun-but-these-creative-spins-are-next-level-delicious/" target="_blank"&gt;Nachos Are Fun But These Creative Spins Are Next Level Delicious&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether for happy hour or a late night get-together, nachos are always a welcome menu option. But even something as wonderful as chips covered in cheese can be elevated to a dish even more wonderful, as in these examples across the country. Guy Fieri’s Trash Can Nachos Trash Can Nachos at Guy Fieri’s Foxwoods Kitchen + Bar Available at Guy Fieri’s Foxwoods Kitchen + Bar in Mashantucket, CT, these nachos are not for the faint of heart! What makes this recipe one-of-a-kind is the unique “trash can” presentation, which reveals a towering stack of tortilla chips, SMT (or “super melty cheese” sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Honey &amp; Co’s hearty, flavourful cabbage and potato pie recipe - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b973d484-e09a-11e8-8e70-5e22a430c1ad</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMNiVCx0Rkgl7D5q1Kdx2d0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 11:03:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b973d484-e09a-11e8-8e70-5e22a430c1ad" target="_blank"&gt;Honey &amp; Co’s hearty, flavourful cabbage and potato pie recipe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cabbage is one of the most versatile vegetables, yet it rarely gets the love it deserves. Other brassicas have a much better rep: purple sprouting broccoli is regarded as a winter treat; Brussels sprouts pretty much own Christmas; black cabbage leaves got themselves a sexy Italian name, cavolo nero, and are now considered worth a trip to the farmers’ market. But plain old cabbage is just there, like a friend who’s a bit boring but around when you need them. Cabbage is available throughout the year in some form or another, and it always seems to find a way to suit the weather. In spring, we ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Forget marshmallows! Five great dishes to cook over the bonfire - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/shortcuts/2018/nov/02/forget-marshmallows-five-great-dishes-to-cook-over-the-bonfire</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBGN19g21KL9dCyUmbEx2AqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCcwRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 19:07:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/shortcuts/2018/nov/02/forget-marshmallows-five-great-dishes-to-cook-over-the-bonfire" target="_blank"&gt;Forget marshmallows! Five great dishes to cook over the bonfire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marshmallows on sticks, baked potatoes in tinfoil – there are few joys like cooking on an open fire, especially around bonfire night. Cooking over an open flame is experiencing a revival on the UK restaurant scene – and there was even a “cooking with fire challenge” on Bake Off this week. “It had fallen by the wayside in England, but it has come back into fashion,” says chef Rich Turner, the executive chef at the steakhouse Hawksmoor and the man behind London’s new “live-fire cooking” restaurant Gridiron. Here are some suggestions to get you started at home: Hotdogs This is a traditional st...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>World Vegan Day: Meet the chef bringing ‘chicken shop culture’ to veganism - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/world-vegan-day-rudeboy-chicken-shop-burgers-culture-a8610901.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEoIpLO9accLoEULvqEjgfYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 09:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/world-vegan-day-rudeboy-chicken-shop-burgers-culture-a8610901.html" target="_blank"&gt;World Vegan Day: Meet the chef bringing ‘chicken shop culture’ to veganism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chicken shops might be a staple of British culture, but it’s not quite the same for vegans, who typically avoid such establishments – for obvious reasons. Historically, those following a plant-based diet have missed out on the UK’s thriving chicken shop scene, which connoisseurs will know is about a lot more than a buckets of wings. - READ MORE A vegan fish and chip shop has just opened in London Today, the humble chicken shop has become a gentrified cult, populated by classic chains like Nando’s and trendy spin-offs like Soho House’s Chicken Shop. And now, after years of being left out in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>How to make Jeremy Pang's black pepper and short rib bao buns - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/recipes/jeremy-pang-black-pepper-short-rib-bao-buns-cooking-instructions-a8588346.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDwI8Ql6YHhUInkME7HZANYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 16:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/recipes/jeremy-pang-black-pepper-short-rib-bao-buns-cooking-instructions-a8588346.html" target="_blank"&gt;How to make Jeremy Pang's black pepper and short rib bao buns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black pepper glazed short rib bao Bao, burgers and sliders have been setting food trends around the world for years now. We tried a version of this slider in a new organic restaurant called Sohofama in Hong Kong, which seems to be leading the way in urban farming and healthier cooking styles while still managing to maintain the best part of traditional Chinese cooking techniques to create delicious dishes like this. When cooking this short rib bao, feel free to try out the different folds – the hirata bun fold or burger bao fold will both work well with the slow-cooked short rib. Make sure ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Take a Number: Fast Food: It’s What’s for Dinner. And Lunch. And Breakfast. - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/22/health/fast-food-consumption.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFJep7X2lC1s5MHiVgVNgQQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4UY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 16:57:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/22/health/fast-food-consumption.html" target="_blank"&gt;Take a Number: Fast Food: It’s What’s for Dinner. And Lunch. And Breakfast.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Correction: October 28, 2018 This article has been revised to reflect the following correction: An earlier version of this article miscalculated the dollar equivalent of 350 percent of the federal poverty line for a family of four. It is $87,850 a year, not $112,950. More than a third of adults in the United States patronize fast-food restaurants and pizza parlors on any given day. And the higher their income, the more likely they are to do so. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has released data on fast food consumption gathered from 2013 to 2016 in the National Health and Nutr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Birds Eye have launched sweet potato waffles and we can't wait to try them - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/life-style/sweet-potato-waffles-birds-eye-645409</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM6hA7KDd_LTCLs6ZUN0HkAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8w3pmhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 19:53:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/life-style/sweet-potato-waffles-birds-eye-645409" target="_blank"&gt;Birds Eye have launched sweet potato waffles and we can't wait to try them&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wow. We can safely say that every single child in Ireland grew up having Birds Eye waffles for literally every single meal. We mean that. They went with everything. And even now as adults, they make for the perfect hangover food. So you can imagine that we're pretty damn excited to hear about Birds Eye's latest endeavour. Birds Eye are redesigning the potato waffle. And we know we can hear you thinking to yourself: "But how could they improve something that is already so perfect?" Three words: Sweet potato waffles. Yep. According to The Sun, this heavenly snack will be available in Tesco fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Tesco is now selling CAMEMBERT flavoured crisps, and we're literally drooling - Her.ie</title><link>https://www.her.ie/food/camembert-flavoured-crisps-432859</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEErfcfmUbQzpdHf9eA_CoEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8w6a6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 10:25:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.her.ie/food/camembert-flavoured-crisps-432859" target="_blank"&gt;Tesco is now selling CAMEMBERT flavoured crisps, and we're literally drooling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holy MOLY. Whether you're ready to admit it or not, the festive season is literally just around the corner. The weather is chilly, the Christmas decorations are starting to appear, and the food special have begun. Every year our favourite supermarkets release some special treats for Christmas... and frankly, it may be the best part of the whole season. Well lads, the fun has begun! Tesco will be offering their customers camembert flavoured crisps, and they sound delicious (if you're into cheese like we are). The salty treats will be part of the Tesco Finest range, so you're almost guarantee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>A Third of Americans Dine Out Nightly at Fast-Food Restaurants: A Nutritionist Speaks Out - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/garystern/2018/10/25/a-third-of-americans-dine-out-nightly-at-fast-food-restaurants-a-nutritionist-speaks-out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDRy06TML2vyUGVxmmGF39cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 15:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/garystern/2018/10/25/a-third-of-americans-dine-out-nightly-at-fast-food-restaurants-a-nutritionist-speaks-out/" target="_blank"&gt;A Third of Americans Dine Out Nightly at Fast-Food Restaurants: A Nutritionist Speaks Out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over one third of Americans are dining out nightly at fast-food eateries such as McDonald’s. But are they paying a price health-wise or not? According to the Center for Disease Control between 2013 and 2016, 36% of adult Americans consumed fast food on any given day. That’s one of three Americans are eating a meal at fast-food eateries such as McDonald’s, Burger King, or KFC. In fact, Americans who were younger dined on fast food more than older folks: nearly 45% of people aged 20-39 did compared to only 24% of consumers 60 years and older. African Americans chose fast food at higher pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>McRib is coming back to McDonald's - but not everywhere is getting it - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/mcrib-mcdonalds-tracker-when-where-coming-back-2018-release-date-a8601696.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN34aVeuTFdXfFyFnv3eYTEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 19:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/mcrib-mcdonalds-tracker-when-where-coming-back-2018-release-date-a8601696.html" target="_blank"&gt;McRib is coming back to McDonald's - but not everywhere is getting it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;McDonald’s fans are rejoicing after the fast-food chain announced the highly-anticipated return of a cult-favourite menu item. The beloved McRib, a sandwich stuffed with a boneless pork patty covered in "tangy, delicious" barbecue sauce, pickles and onions, will officially be returning to stores on Monday October 29, the chain announced - and some stores already have it. “We know our fans love this limited time classic,” McDonald’s chef Mike Haracz said in a statement today. - Read more McDonald's new flagship store looks just like an Apple store The McRib, which was first released 36 years...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pho, pierogies and a 7-pound burger: The NFL's strangest stadium foods - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/01/us/strangest-nfl-stadium-foods-2018-tailgating/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhSpP3YvWx7pVugVOD_AIsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 16:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/01/us/strangest-nfl-stadium-foods-2018-tailgating/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pho, pierogies and a 7-pound burger: The NFL's strangest stadium foods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stadium concessions have come a long way since stale pretzels and popcorn were about all that hungry fans could look forward to. As we scoured the menus at NFL stadiums, we learned there are some seriously innovative dishes out there. Dessert nachos, anyone? And then there are others -- like a 7-pound burger topped with chicken fingers, fries, hotdogs and more -- that beg the question, "Why?" From the ingenious to the borderline bizarre, here are the 10 noteworthy food items hitting NFL concession stands this season: Gridiron Challenge Burger Available at: The Arizona Cardinals' University ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Southern Barbecue With a Fiery Dip and a Deep History - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/23/dining/monroe-county-pork-steaks-bbq.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIlZ7ROnzcj16SlPDqaY3rgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 16:27:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/23/dining/monroe-county-pork-steaks-bbq.html" target="_blank"&gt;Southern Barbecue With a Fiery Dip and a Deep History&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TOMPKINSVILLE, Ky. — This is the Southern barbecue you’ve probably never heard of. Not baby back ribs thickly crusted with spice rub and served “dry,” as it’s done in Memphis. Not slow-smoked chicken dipped in mayonnaise-based “white” barbecue sauce — a longstanding specialty of Decatur, Ala. Not even mutton, smoked the better part of a day, then sauced with a Worcestershire-and lemon-based “black dip” — the barbecue calling card of Owensboro, Ky. No, you’ll find this barbecue chiefly here in Monroe County, and a handful of surrounding counties in southern Kentucky and northern Tennessee, w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>McDonald's adds its first new breakfast sandwich in 5 years - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/business/mcdonalds-new-breakfast-sandwich/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOwj2jHm8-6C6sR4q0thfioqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 13:02:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/business/mcdonalds-new-breakfast-sandwich/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;McDonald's adds its first new breakfast sandwich in 5 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;McDonald's is hoping a big new breakfast sandwich will help bring in more customers. Triple Breakfast Stacks will hit menus on November 1. They're modified versions of McDonald's popular Egg McMuffin -- they will include two slices of American cheese, two sausage patties, bacon and an egg, The sandwiches are available on a McMuffin, biscuit, or McGriddles cakes. The new items are designed to help McDonald's solve a problem: Fewer Americans are eating at the fast food chain. A new breakfast could help bring them back. In a statement on Tuesday, the company said that the items are inspired by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Deliveroo is serving up NACHO spice bags this Sunday and we're all ears - Her.ie</title><link>https://www.her.ie/food/deliveroo-serving-nacho-spice-bags-sunday-ears-431577</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQwmtGk3oAwgiewMuOffLsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyN-fCTD7um8w6a6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 14:43:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.her.ie/food/deliveroo-serving-nacho-spice-bags-sunday-ears-431577" target="_blank"&gt;Deliveroo is serving up NACHO spice bags this Sunday and we're all ears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Her.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Say goodbye to your Sunday roast. Because this Sunday we're eating nachos. Yep, to celebrate International Nacho Day, Deliveroo has teamed up with Little Ass Burrito Bar to create a nacho spice bag that sounds like our new favourite dish. View this post on Instagram A post shared by Little Ass Burrito Bar (@littleassdub) on Apr 27, 2018 at 7:16am PDT For just one day only, you can order the fiery feast of hand-cut Blanco Nio corn tortilla chips topped with grilled Jack cheese, roasted sweet potato, spicy West Cork Gubbeen chorizo, and a sprinkle of fresh coriander, all served with guacamole...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.her.ie">Her.ie</source></item><item><title>Vegan Company Sets Sights On IPO - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelpellmanrowland/2018/10/21/beyond-meat-ipo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-OC-iivbujHhdcl1QVmUsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelpellmanrowland/2018/10/21/beyond-meat-ipo/" target="_blank"&gt;Vegan Company Sets Sights On IPO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The meat-like quality of the Beyond Burger even has carnivores throwing them on the grill. Vegan meat is everywhere these days. Now rumor has it you can add Wall Street to the mix. According to CNBC this week, Beyond Meat, the upstart California company famous for its ‘Beyond Burger’ and impressive list of investors, intends to go public. A publicly traded vegan company. Kinda hard to believe. Apparently JP Morgan, Credit Suisse, and Goldman Sachs are being targeted to lead the deal. It’s funny to think of alpha investment bankers, infamous for brash personalities and steak dinners, doing a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Creamy carbonara and jackfruit tacos – four vegan recipes from BOSH! - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/food/2018/oct/20/four-vegan-recipes-bosh-chinese-caribbean-italian-mexican-students</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGPExj_haL4Ssc_yR765Wi8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 06:00:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/food/2018/oct/20/four-vegan-recipes-bosh-chinese-caribbean-italian-mexican-students" target="_blank"&gt;Creamy carbonara and jackfruit tacos – four vegan recipes from BOSH!&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creamy carbonara (pictured above) Prep 10 min Cook 45 min Serves 4 250g portobello mushrooms 5 tbsp soy sauce 20ml maple syrup 20ml cider vinegar 20ml olive oil 130g cashew nuts 5 garlic cloves 190ml plant-based milk 10g nutritional yeast 150g silken tofu 300g spaghetti 125g peas 1 handful flat-leaf parsley or rocket, to serve Related: From tamari to tamago: four star bento boxes Heat the oven to 200C/390F/gas 6, and line a baking tray with baking paper. Slice the mushrooms thinly. Pour the soy sauce, maple syrup, cider vinegar and olive oil into a bowl, and whisk to combine. Add the mushro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Hy-Vee meat Salmonella recall: 6 products to avoid right now - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90254021/hy-vee-fda-meat-salmonella-recall-6-products-to-avoid-right-now</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIXYCPm6rmPT_bCaSRT-qlAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 11:50:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90254021/hy-vee-fda-meat-salmonella-recall-6-products-to-avoid-right-now" target="_blank"&gt;Hy-Vee meat Salmonella recall: 6 products to avoid right now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grocery chain Hy-Vee is voluntarily recalling six of its meat and potato products due to possible contamination with Salmonella and Listeria monocytogenes, the company said yesterday. The recall affects products in all eight states where the company operates: Illinois, Iowa, Kansas, Minnesota, Missouri, Nebraska, South Dakota, and Wisconsin. According to the recall notice published by the FDA, the potential contamination was discovered after McCain Foods—a supplier for the West Des Moines-based Hy-Vee—said it was recalling caramelized mushrooms and fire-roasted tomatoes, which are ingredien...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Ten vegan-friendly versions of tailgate classics - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/health/vegan-tailgating-food-drayer/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIXuFSzGrripWPI_V4j8ZYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 09:36:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/health/vegan-tailgating-food-drayer/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ten vegan-friendly versions of tailgate classics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Super Bowl is one of the biggest calorie fests of the year. The average football fan eats about a day's worth of calories during the game, and the U.S. Calorie Control Council estimates that Americans pack away 11 million pounds of chips on Super Bowl Sunday. Instead, snack on these 11 delicious and healthy game day recipes. Photo Illustration/Thinkstock These spiked wings have a tangy lemon taste and are baked, not fried. Plus, they only have 173 calories per serving! Try this recipe: Lemon-drop chicken wings Health.com Use lima beans, cream cheese, Tabasco sauce, capers and mustard fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Help Arby’s get over its identity crisis by trying the duck - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90252798/help-arbys-get-over-its-identity-crisis-by-trying-the-duck</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHQMOAwfrjC8FdzB8mS5lkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 13:56:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90252798/help-arbys-get-over-its-identity-crisis-by-trying-the-duck" target="_blank"&gt;Help Arby’s get over its identity crisis by trying the duck&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arby’s is quacking up. First, after over 50 years of serving up roast beef, the fast food chain decided that roast beef wasn’t cool anymore and that it would instead be a sandwich shop. Now, it’s decided that regular old turkey sandwiches aren’t enough and it needs new poultry options. Namely: duck. That’s right, Arby’s is going to sell quack. Starting on Saturday, October 20, the chain will start serving a seared duck breast sandwich, complete with smoked cherry sauce and crispy onions on “a signature Arby’s bun,” according to Nation’s Restaurant News. [Photo: courtesy of Arby’s]The $6.99 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Asian fast food restaurant Jollibee is coming to London and it might become your new favourite place to eat - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/jollibee-asian-fast-food-restaurant-chicken-spaghetti-london-when-uk-menu-britain-a8589726.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELRE3tr9h2ge54fkdH3V1kEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 09:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/jollibee-asian-fast-food-restaurant-chicken-spaghetti-london-when-uk-menu-britain-a8589726.html" target="_blank"&gt;Asian fast food restaurant Jollibee is coming to London and it might become your new favourite place to eat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jollibee, Asia’s biggest fast food chain, is opening its first ever UK branch in London this weekend. The restaurant, which will open on 20 October, will be located in a former Wagamama outlet in Earl’s Court and is set to be only the second Jollibee branch in Europe after one launched in Milan earlier this year. The chain first started as an ice cream parlour in Manila in 1975. Today, it serves up a fusion of US and Asian-inspired dishes including fried chicken with spaghetti covered in a red sauce and loaded with slices of hotdog and ground beef. - Read more The dirty keto diet claims you...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Unboxing Taco Bell's Awesome Xbox One X Platinum Limited Edition Bundle - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mitchwallace/2018/10/17/unboxing-taco-bells-awesome-xbox-one-x-platinum-limited-edition-bundle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIjRSQsXr3YJCnZyQOBh29oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mitchwallace/2018/10/17/unboxing-taco-bells-awesome-xbox-one-x-platinum-limited-edition-bundle/" target="_blank"&gt;Unboxing Taco Bell's Awesome Xbox One X Platinum Limited Edition Bundle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The color gradient is especially apparent from this angle. When Taco Bell contacted me a few days ago regarding a ‘special delivery’ they wanted to send over, I was initially somewhat skeptical. I mean, what could they possibly be shipping to a writer? 30 pounds of raw, uncooked Nacho Fries? A giant, anthropomorphic chalupa plushie? A literal gallon of artificial cheese sauce? A quesadilla Snuggie? As it turns out, the actual delivery was way cooler than any of those possibilities, and still decidedly hot sauce-flavored. Coinciding with the official announcement of their Fall 2018 gaming co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How to make Mexican veggie chilli and nachos - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/recipes/mexican-veggie-chilli-nachos-cooking-instructions-a8585856.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKH-0KRonylSxTZCIq8pyoYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 13:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/recipes/mexican-veggie-chilli-nachos-cooking-instructions-a8585856.html" target="_blank"&gt;How to make Mexican veggie chilli and nachos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mexican veggie chilli and sweet potato nachos Serves 2 ½ tsp red chilli flakes 150g courgette 1 avocado 1 lime 1 red onion 1 tbsp Mexican spice mix 1 tbsp oil 20g creamed coconut 240g kidney beans (drained) 2 garlic cloves 300g sweet potato 400g chopped tomatoes Preheat the oven to 200C/gas 6. Finely dice the onion and courgette and finely chop the garlic. Peel and thinly slice the sweet potato. Toss with half a tablespoon of oil and season with sea salt. Place the slices of sweet potato on a baking tray in the oven for 20 mins, turning halfway through. Heat a medium-sized pan with half a t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Tortilla town sides with underdog no-onionists in recipe rivalry - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/12/tortilla-town-betanzos-no-onionists-spanish-omelette-recipe-rivalry</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECETbMMzy7ueU734GQtumt8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 14:37:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/12/tortilla-town-betanzos-no-onionists-spanish-omelette-recipe-rivalry" target="_blank"&gt;Tortilla town sides with underdog no-onionists in recipe rivalry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Spain’s bitterest battles, a long-festering confrontation that predates the ugly international skirmishes over paella and even the rivalry between Real Madrid and FC Barcelona, could finally be reaching its endgame. The town council of Betanzos, the Galician municipality whose tortillas de patatas, or Spanish omelettes, are regularly hailed as the finest in the land, has spoken. And the message to those entering this year’s tortilla competition is simple: leave out the onions. The issue of whether cebollas belong in the emblematic fried dish runs like a faultline under the nation’s b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>New York Eateries October 2018: Where to Go -- And Not - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/restaurants-go-consider-stop/2018/10/09/coco-pazzo-east-pole-fish-bar-mimi-kyma-the-polynesian-new-york/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO3StkogyRLIOE28tVRAavMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 17:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/restaurants-go-consider-stop/2018/10/09/coco-pazzo-east-pole-fish-bar-mimi-kyma-the-polynesian-new-york/" target="_blank"&gt;New York Eateries October 2018: Where to Go -- And Not&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story appears in the October 31, 2018 issue of Forbes.Subscribe Edible enlightenment from our eatery experts and colleagues Richard Nalley, Monie Begley and Randall Lane, as well as brothers Bob, Kip and Tim. Coco Pazzo 160 Prince St., at Thompson St. (Tel.: 917-261-6318) Pino Luongo, proprietor of this updated version of the UES original, brought Tuscan fare to NYC in the mid-1980s. Offerings sound classic but are prepared with updated creativity. Begin with insalata carciofi, a light salad of raw baby artichokes, Parmigiano and fennel tossed in olive oil and lemon. The oven-roasted c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>City Kitchen: Roasted Squid, by Way of Mexico - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/12/dining/squid-salad.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMU4ZeQ5wiTQ4mGtayYNOGsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 15:45:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/12/dining/squid-salad.html" target="_blank"&gt;City Kitchen: Roasted Squid, by Way of Mexico&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All I know is I went to the fishmonger, who had some beautiful small squid, and suddenly an urge came over me: I had to take them home and give them a Mexican twist. It was a little funny to head in a south-of-the-border culinary direction, because, for some reason, I didn’t usually associate squid with Mexican cooking. I’ve been to Mexico dozen of times and eaten plenty of fish and shellfish. But somehow any memory of having squid there evades me, which seems odd, especially since squid, or calamares, are indeed quite popular in Mexico. Was I daft? I got in touch with Gilbert Pilgram, the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Five Weeknight Dishes: Get It Done - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/12/dining/get-it-done.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKpQaW6JazjzpL9nivEqdIoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4UY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 16:30:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/12/dining/get-it-done.html" target="_blank"&gt;Five Weeknight Dishes: Get It Done&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi, it’s Emily, here with your five weeknight dishes, food for busy people who still want something good to eat. My daughter is turning 1 this week, so I’m deep in yellow-cake recipes and buttercream, contemplating sprinkles and candles and round cake vs. sheet. (Round is so classic, no?) This week also marks the debut of my beloved friend and colleague Samin Nosrat’s Netflix show, “Salt Fat Acid Heat,” based on her cookbook of the same name. Samin has been very busy of late, busier than you or I can imagine, as the world embraces her and she flies the width of it, shooting her show and wri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Britons face chips shortage after dry summer hits potato crop - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c66c497a-c86a-11e8-ba8f-ee390057b8c9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJYhZNM1Tt3c7RNtSLCZZ_wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:25:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c66c497a-c86a-11e8-ba8f-ee390057b8c9" target="_blank"&gt;Britons face chips shortage after dry summer hits potato crop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A dry summer has shrunk the British potato crop and raised a daunting prospect for Britons: a shortage of chips. Fish and chip shops say they will have to reduce portion sizes and raise prices for the national dish. Potato prices have already doubled this year and could go even higher, said the National Federation of Fish Fryers, which speaks for the country’s 10,500 chip shops. Andrew Crook, the NFFF president, said: “We have to cover our costs. Prices will go up and many will reduce the size of a portion. A lot of small shops will probably sell up.” A 25kg sack of potatoes, enough for abo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Why you shouldn't use the phrase 'food swamp' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/features/fast-food-swamp-unhealthy-eating-systems-a8552406.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVkk_1YXmjxUeg5SzudRqUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 16:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/features/fast-food-swamp-unhealthy-eating-systems-a8552406.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why you shouldn't use the phrase 'food swamp'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food is sold everywhere – at the petrol station, at the pharmacy, at the coffee shop, the corner store, even where you go to buy discount homewares you’ll find caramel corn to go with your towels. Then there are the ubiquitous fast food joints promising to nip your hunger at any time of day, and supermarkets selling baked goods and chips and ready-to-go just about anything. Generally, what’s for sale at these places is not the kind of food that is good for your body. That’s why in public health several years ago, people began to call this retail landscape a “food swamp”. Food swamp describe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Vegan fish and chip shop opens in London - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/vegan-fish-chips-london-daniel-sutton-a8569006.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIhzB0I6efs9p9B_Kiyw4ncqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 16:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/vegan-fish-chips-london-daniel-sutton-a8569006.html" target="_blank"&gt;Vegan fish and chip shop opens in London&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you think of vegan food, it’s unlikely that the first dish to spring to mind is fish and chips. This is because fish is an animal and the general idea of veganism is that you don’t eat those. However, change could be afoot as a new vegan fish and chip shop has just opened in London. - Read more Vegan receives pizza topped with raw onions and sauce Cue confusion as one tries to reckon with the concept of fish that contains no fish. Proving that anything is possible in today’s experimental foodie landscape is Daniel Sutton, whose family-run fish and chip shop in east London has been serv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cheeseburger spring rolls are gluttonous hangover food – and I instantly want more - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/food/2018/oct/03/cheeseburger-spring-rolls-are-gluttonous-hangover-food-and-i-instantly-want-more</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH6SsQMDd6BWTKc2p6JCLnAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 12:11:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/food/2018/oct/03/cheeseburger-spring-rolls-are-gluttonous-hangover-food-and-i-instantly-want-more" target="_blank"&gt;Cheeseburger spring rolls are gluttonous hangover food – and I instantly want more&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is hard to imagine the size of the night out that led to the invention of the cheeseburger spring roll. It must have produced a hangover so monstrous that neither a Chinese takeaway nor a dirty burger alone could begin to solve it. A craving for junk and comfort so intense that someone must have deemed the burger’s bread – the bread! – too healthy, and conjured up an acceptable way to deep fry it instead. Whichever brave soul suffered for the concept, their work has not been in vain. At Manchester restaurant Solita, cheeseburger spring rolls are bestsellers (and as a place that has been ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>From escargots to le Big Mac: how the land of haute cuisine fell for fast food - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/food/2018/sep/29/how-france-fell-in-love-with-the-burger</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPWw-fhxSmSKxlGwHmoldLgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 13:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/food/2018/sep/29/how-france-fell-in-love-with-the-burger" target="_blank"&gt;From escargots to le Big Mac: how the land of haute cuisine fell for fast food&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;French food: so good that the wise heads at Unesco declared it part of the world’s intangible cultural heritage, so celebrated that the love of it defined a nation. “Tell me what you eat and I will tell you what you are,” as the original foodie, the gastronome Jean Anthelme Brillat-Savarin, put it in 1825. And he was somebody who undoubtedly knew his lentilles vertes du puy et caviar from his langoustines à la nage and his poulette du perche from his poitrine de grive. For years, France’s eating habits – and not just in restaurants – have been a model: portion control; lots of basics (eggs,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item></channel></rss>