<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>John McCaffrey - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNREp3ZEhrMlloSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:37:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Dublin hurler Johnny McCaffrey announces retirement | GAA News - SkySports</title><link>https://www.skysports.com/gaa/hurling/news/30543/11573367/dublin-hurler-johnny-mccaffrey-announces-retirement</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780128637357</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:53:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.skysports.com/gaa/hurling/news/30543/11573367/dublin-hurler-johnny-mccaffrey-announces-retirement" target="_blank"&gt;Dublin hurler Johnny McCaffrey announces retirement | GAA News&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SkySports&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/1206/1015662-dubs-leinster-title-winning-captain-mccaffrey-retires/" target="_blank"&gt;Dubs' Leinster title-winning captain McCaffrey retires&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/dublins-leinsterwinning-captain-johnny-mccaffrey-calls-time-on-intercounty-career-37602543.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dublin's Leinster-winning captain Johnny McCaffrey calls time on inter-county career&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/johnny-mccaffrey-retires-inter-county-hurling-dublin-4380413-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Dublin's 2013 Leinster-winning captain calls time on inter-county hurling career&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWl0bzhhbWpZQU1FUmwzNjByb1BoLW9LQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.skysports.com">SkySports</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/9eZgz8YNTzUQd788K4pghVa7Gs4MJGPeZAiNvsNow_tHm0HR4Wv2acGrchtFhlxe45OzyAWs2RMBaqdkXySgb4TWV7BYLuuEox8nLiYwFP-QSpuqwJ55lulYuDlX_womZP2S5bJK_Kx_B6U=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Offaly dual star Ryan retires while Lynch and McCaffrey also call time - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/offaly-dual-star-ryan-retires-while-lynch-and-mccaffrey-also-call-time-37603040.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDV1offYkE6tmeJoBytyNBsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/offaly-dual-star-ryan-retires-while-lynch-and-mccaffrey-also-call-time-37603040.html" target="_blank"&gt;Offaly dual star Ryan retires while Lynch and McCaffrey also call time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Offaly dual star Seán Ryan has called time on his inter-county career after 13 seasons of service to the Faithful which saw him accumulate 95 competitive appearances between league and championship in both codes. The diminutive Birr clubman debuted for the footballers under Kevin Kilmurray in 2006 when Offaly were plying their trade in Division 1A and featured off the bench against Cork, Mayo, Tyrone, Kerry and Monaghan. Ryan tried both codes the following year with great success and made his senior hurling debut at midfield under John McIntyre in their four-point Qualifier defeat to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>John Kiely named Munster manager of the year - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/gaa/john-kiely-named-munster-manager-of-the-year-890455.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOrMn--0XN2n4Ofrrr7-EJgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/sport/gaa/john-kiely-named-munster-manager-of-the-year-890455.html" target="_blank"&gt;John Kiely named Munster manager of the year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Kiely, for the leading role he played in delivering Limerick a first All-Ireland hurling title in 45 years, is the 2018 Munster GAA Manager of the Year. This is the second occasion that Kiely, a native of Galbally, has been crowned manager of the year by the Munster Council, first winning the award back in 2015 after guiding Limerick to Munster and All-Ireland U21 glory. Prior to their famine-ending run this summer, Kiely steered the Treaty back into Division 1A of the Allianz hurling league after eight seasons mired in the second tier. His greatest act, of course, was winning Liam Mac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Mounting weight of evidence leaves Cunningham reign on thin ice - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/mounting-weight-of-evidence-leaves-cunningham-reign-on-thin-ice-35763077.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVGiKrahiZ2r197zsPf4g4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 11:00:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/mounting-weight-of-evidence-leaves-cunningham-reign-on-thin-ice-35763077.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mounting weight of evidence leaves Cunningham reign on thin ice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In February 2015, a month after Michael Carton gave a ringing endorsement of his management, Ger Cunningham described the news that Tommy Dunne was leaving as coach as "very disappointing". Dunne had been the only member of Anthony Daly's entourage retained when Cunningham took over the previous autumn. The reasons cited for Dunne's exit were two-fold: a college course which he had been accepted on to in UL and increased business commitments. A year and a half later, no longer involved in the Dublin set-up after quitting the previous summer before a qualifier match, Carton revealed a differ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>'It really couldn't be anymore professional for a senior inter-county set-up:' Dublin hurlers' goalkeeping coach - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/david-herity-2-3426391-Jun2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBGLYIJSb-CeNTklkEFNSSsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 06:30:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/david-herity-2-3426391-Jun2017/" target="_blank"&gt;'It really couldn't be anymore professional for a senior inter-county set-up:' Dublin hurlers' goalkeeping coach&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT HAS BEEN a challenging time for the Dublin hurlers. Rumours of unrest have surrounded them throughout the season, amidst a major panel overhaul which saw several seasoned campaigners omitted from the cause. Former captain Johnny McCaffrey, Peter Kelly, forward Paul Ryan, Daire Plunkett, Niall Corcoran and Glenn Whelan were all among those who were excluded, while other notable players have withdrawn from the squad for different reasons. Manager Ger Cunningham has endeavored to place a heightened emphasis on youth this year, but his vision has triggered a frosty reaction, with many feelin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Ballyboden gun down reigning All-Ireland champions Cuala in Dublin opener - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/ballyboden-cuala-dublin-shc-3366104-Apr2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELtgsnBLHdRrI7U8XmFXrq0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 17:58:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/ballyboden-cuala-dublin-shc-3366104-Apr2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Ballyboden gun down reigning All-Ireland champions Cuala in Dublin opener&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cuala 1-18 Ballyboden St Enda’s 0-17 Kevin O’Brien reports from Parnell Park THE ALL-IRELAND champions were welcomed back to the Dublin SHC with a four-point defeat to Ballyboden St Enda’s in the opening group game. Former Dublin hurler Conal Keaney kicked a stoppage-time goal to seal the win for Ballyboden, who last lifted the county title in 2013. This was Cuala’s first championship match since their All-Ireland final win over Ballyea on St Patrick’s Day, and the defeat shows the strength of club hurling in the capital. Unlike the football championship, the Dublin SHC has group stages in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Capital losses - Sky Blue hurlers who have moved on - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/capital-losses-sky-blue-hurlers-who-have-moved-on-35196571.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGYkvb2tbirDRyoqsXxbdtUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/capital-losses-sky-blue-hurlers-who-have-moved-on-35196571.html" target="_blank"&gt;Capital losses - Sky Blue hurlers who have moved on&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ger Cunningham's latest shake-up of the Dublin senior hurling squad means that of the 20 players used by Anthony Daly for their breakthrough Leinster championship win in 2013, 12 have either stepped away from the panel or been axed by management. Niall Corcoran, Peter Kelly (above), Stephen Hiney, Mikey Carton Johnny McCaffrey, Conal Keaney, Danny Sutcliffe, Paul Ryan, Shane Durkin, Simon Lambert, Joey Boland and Callum McCormack are no longer part of the panel for a variety of reasons. 2017 Dublin training panel - Shane Barrett (Na Fianna); Chris Bennett (Faughs), Cian Boland (St Oliver Pl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Capital gain needed after exodus from out of Blue - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/capital-gain-needed-after-exodus-from-out-of-blue-35753301.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO1NChos6YXg2vtFm4lfdaEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/capital-gain-needed-after-exodus-from-out-of-blue-35753301.html" target="_blank"&gt;Capital gain needed after exodus from out of Blue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Anthony Daly vacated his position as the Dublin hurling manager in 2014 there was some acceptance that a fresh face might coax out whatever was left from the core of a team that had delivered a Leinster and league title in a six-year spell at the end of which the Clare man left them in a lot better state than how he had found them. Daly himself acknowledged how a fresh approach might benefit all, and how good players still remained. Almost three years on though, the team he has left behind is barely recognisable. From 20 players used in their All-Ireland quarter-final defeat to Tippera...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Diarmuid Connolly helped St Vincent's to a big win in the Dublin SHC tonight - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/dublin-shc-wrap-3362621-Apr2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMohfZ9YGQN0wto-trbSctcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 21:27:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/dublin-shc-wrap-3362621-Apr2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Diarmuid Connolly helped St Vincent's to a big win in the Dublin SHC tonight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE WERE WINS for St Vincent’s, Lucan Sarsfields and Crumlin in the opening round of the Dublin SHC tonight. John Hetherton, Keith Connolly, Rory Fallon and county player Rian McBride bagged goals as St Vincent’s ran out convincing 4-21 to 0-16 winners over St Jude’s. Dublin footballer Diarmuid Connolly lined out at midfield for the Marino club, scoring a point and setting up the third goal. John McCaffrey, who captained them to a Leinster title in 2013, and Chris Crummey helped Lucan Sarsfields to a convincing 14-point win over St Brigid’s. Finally, Crumlin enjoyed a narrow one-point vic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Dublin have waved goodbye to the Blue Wave - Newstalk Newsfeed</title><link>http://www.newstalk.com/Dublin-have-waved-goodbye-to-the-Blue-Wave</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGNzWrXXaVoggNd3Bm1HP50qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowmeSfCTCcwW8wmpuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.newstalk.com/Dublin-have-waved-goodbye-to-the-Blue-Wave" target="_blank"&gt;Dublin have waved goodbye to the Blue Wave&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newstalk Newsfeed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sorry to play the same old tune, but it feels like we're watching re-runs, so what else is to be done? Dublin hurling has been slowly circling the drain for three seasons now and, until a manager with fresh ideas and a unifying approach comes in, the Blue Wave will continue to wash away. The Dublin county board put together a strategic report under this title for 2011-17, aimed at winning an All-Ireland football title every three years and a hurling equivalent every five years. The former half is papering over the cracks of the latter. Chairman Sean Shanley went on Off The Ball on Monday ev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.newstalk.com">Newstalk Newsfeed</source></item><item><title>Davy Fitzgerald, Jim McGuinness and where all went wrong for the Dublin hurlers - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/dublin-hurlers-cunningham-3415216-May2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG6KcyXzCP0SeizDuYSWOvIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 05:15:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/dublin-hurlers-cunningham-3415216-May2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Davy Fitzgerald, Jim McGuinness and where all went wrong for the Dublin hurlers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE LEAD up to Wexford’s Leinster championship opener against Carlow, Seamus ‘Banty’ McEnaney made an interesting observation about the responsibilities of an inter-county manager. “I like to bring unity and create a bond in the dressing room,” he told The42. “I believe it’s the manager’s responsibility to have the best players playing with the group. “I’d like to think I’m quite good at that. We’ve got the best players in Wexford. I had to talk with more experienced players before I took the job to make sure they were going to be there.” Wexford’s subsequent defeat to Carlow doesn’t tak...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Dooley primed to look after No 1 ahead of Galway clash - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/dooley-primed-to-look-after-no-1-ahead-of-galway-clash-35698541.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL83TWOXFT4bJn1JKY9ZSzQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/dooley-primed-to-look-after-no-1-ahead-of-galway-clash-35698541.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dooley primed to look after No 1 ahead of Galway clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conor Dooley finds himself in a most unusual position. He's Dublin's No 1 right now and will be expected to start between the posts when they face Galway at the end of the month in the Leinster Championship. But, bizarrely, he found himself on the bench for the opening round of the Dublin club SHC, with Ballyboden opting to go with former All-Star and fellow Dublin panellist Gary Maguire instead. There is logic to it from the club's perspective. Blessed with two quality 'keepers, they realised that Dooley can be used as a outfield player so picking Maguire in goals gives them an extra optio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Dublin sacrificing experience for youth - Keaney - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0208/851229-conal-keaney/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEp4bVZsvlHDbHhgEwu1gBIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 10:16:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0208/851229-conal-keaney/" target="_blank"&gt;Dublin sacrificing experience for youth - Keaney&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conal Keaney believes Dublin hurling manager Ger Cunningham is taking a gamble in putting so much faith in an inexperienced panel for the coming season. The former Dublin hurler, who retired from inter-county duties last year, says Cunningham’s decision to dispense with a number of high-profile players “could be very worrying” as the Dubs prepare for the visit of All-Ireland champions Tipperary to Croke Park for the opening round of the Allianz League. The likes of Paul Ryan, Shane Durcan, Johnny McCaffrey, Peter Kelly and Joey Boland are no longer involved, while the absence of Danny Sutcl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Brendan Cummins: Toxic cloud hangs over Dublin as vultures circle - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/brendan-cummins-toxic-cloud-hangs-over-dublin-as-vultures-circle-35765424.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHxRg2K39x5NKIRyZ5OgWRgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 16:04:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/brendan-cummins-toxic-cloud-hangs-over-dublin-as-vultures-circle-35765424.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brendan Cummins: Toxic cloud hangs over Dublin as vultures circle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I scanned through the Dublin team for yesterday's match with Galway, it struck me that only two players who lined out against Tipperary in the 2014 All-Ireland quarter-final were named to start. The survivors were Ryan O'Dwyer and Liam Rushe. No team can survive that rate of flux in such a short period of time. Transition, evolution, call it what you want, must happen much more slowly but there's a toxic cloud hanging over the Dublin hurling panel at the moment. Even before a ball was thrown in, the vultures were circling over manager Ger Cunningham. I read the piece during the week ab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Daly surprised by Dublin changes but understands Cunningham's desire for change - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/anthony-daly-dublin-munster-interpro-3114620-Dec2016/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFbEhJ4h20eLo02XOnsOuVoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 06:00:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/anthony-daly-dublin-munster-interpro-3114620-Dec2016/" target="_blank"&gt;Daly surprised by Dublin changes but understands Cunningham's desire for change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANTHONY DALY SAYS he is surprised by the way Dublin hurling has gone since his departure as manager in 2014 but understands his successor Ger Cunningham’s desire to mix things up. The Dubs enjoyed long-awaited success during the Clare native’s six-year tenure, including a Division 1 league triumph in 2011 and the first provincial title for the county’s hurlers in 52 years in 2013. But the transition to Cunningham’s management certainly hasn’t been smooth, mixed results on the field being overshadowed by unrest among some of the stalwarts during the Daly era. Some of Daly’s regulars have wal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>No divide in the Dublin camp as Liam Rushe and Dublin turn to youth for 2017 - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/liam-rushe-dublin-3-3082117-Nov2016/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFR8zpdK0tSGlMkjaStPGIQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 06:30:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/liam-rushe-dublin-3-3082117-Nov2016/" target="_blank"&gt;No divide in the Dublin camp as Liam Rushe and Dublin turn to youth for 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WITH THE BULK of Dublin’s 2013 Leinster SHC winning team no longer part of the squad, Liam Rushe isn’t starting to panic. A number of players who shared that historic triumph with Rushe three years ago have either withdrawn or been omitted from Ger Cunningham’s 2017 panel. That’s not something that comes as a shock for the centre-back. “(I’m) not too surprised by that because..that team, you could probably say, peaked in 2011. There was a gap.” Rush says. “We were at the height of our powers, and then the following year we were robbed of a couple of lads by injury and by even more injuries ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Ger Cunningham axes seven Dublin hurlers for next season - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/ger-cunningham-axes-seven-dublin-hurlers-for-next-season-35194597.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENuxVyKu2iFLcpvrSlZHcRcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 11:10:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/ger-cunningham-axes-seven-dublin-hurlers-for-next-season-35194597.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ger Cunningham axes seven Dublin hurlers for next season&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEVEN of last year’s Dublin senior hurling panel will not be involved next season, the Herald has learned. Former captain Johnny McCaffrey and 2013 All Star Peter Kelly are the two highest profile exits, with Paul Ryan, Daire Plunkett, Niall Corcoran and Glenn Whelan informed over the weekend that they were surplus to Ger Cunningham’s requirements. Shane Durkin, meanwhile, has opted out for 2017. Kelly hasn’t played with Dublin since April of last year due to a serious knee injury and speaking in a newspaper interview published yesterday, the Lucan Sarsfields man explained that he made his ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Threadbare Dublin are on a tough road - Anthony Daly - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0529/878806-dublin-are-on-a-tough-road/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMJ5-vztojkUmAxcHO9uOJcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 07:07:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/0529/878806-dublin-are-on-a-tough-road/" target="_blank"&gt;Threadbare Dublin are on a tough road - Anthony Daly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anthony Daly believes Dublin now have no choice but to stick with a young, inexperienced panel on a "tough road". Ger Cunningham's Sky Blues started their Leinster SHC with a chastening 14-point loss to Galway in Tullamore on Sunday. Shorn of several seasoned campaigners who've left the panel over the last 12 months, the Dubs camp has been plagued by rumours of discontent and criticism of the management. Clare man Daly, who led the capital to a Leinster crown in 2013 during a six-year spell in charge, described Cunningham as a "very, very astute guy", but admitted things look badly from the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>'Leader' Rushe to captain Dubs again - Independent.ie</title><link>http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/leader-rushe-to-captain-dubs-again-35436090.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPEdC0HJDnKMvbP5Xy0H7WwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/leader-rushe-to-captain-dubs-again-35436090.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Leader' Rushe to captain Dubs again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ger Cunningham has confirmed that Liam Rushe will captain the Dublin senior hurlers again this year - and described the centre-back as an "inspirational leader on and off the pitch". Rushe was co-captain with Peter Kelly in 2015 before assuming sole responsibility last season. And as Cunningham attempts to oversee a period of transition for the Sky Blues, he was keen to retain the continuity that Rushe brings to the captain's role. "He's been a good captain for us for the last couple of years - our inspirational leader on and off the pitch," Cunningham said. "It's a continuation from last y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Dubs to start 2017 with Parnell Park double-header - RTÉ News</title><link>http://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2016/1220/840165-dubs-to-start-2017-with-parnell-park-double-header/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBLkEeM7hphMGVy6LPUdIswqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 11:23:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2016/1220/840165-dubs-to-start-2017-with-parnell-park-double-header/" target="_blank"&gt;Dubs to start 2017 with Parnell Park double-header&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dublin footballers and hurlers will get their 2017 campaigns under way with a Parnell Park double-header next month. Jim Gavin's All-Ireland SFC champions will take on DCU in the first round of the Bord na Mona O'Byrne Cup on Sunday, 8 January at 4.0. Before that, at 2.0, Ger Cunningham's hurlers will begin the defence of their Walsh Cup title against Carlow, who start life under new manager Colm Bonnar. After another league and championship double, the relentless Dubs will be eyeing another silver-laden season. The Dublin team of 1921-23 were the last from the county to claim a hat-tri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Ballyboden claim extra-time victory over brave Clonkill after emotional Leinster club hurling clash - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/ballyboden-st-endas-leinster-club-hurling-4326088-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMi3NaGVQu99I_1DsYjrA_cqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 22:35:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/ballyboden-st-endas-leinster-club-hurling-4326088-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Ballyboden claim extra-time victory over brave Clonkill after emotional Leinster club hurling clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ballyboden St Enda’s 2-25 Clonkill 2-19 Paul Keane reports from Parnell Park BALLYBODEN ST-ENDA’S prevailed at the end of a tense and emotional evening at Parnell Park to take their place, as expected, in the semi-finals of the AIB Leinster club SHC. Yet the manner of the win which was achieved after extra-time was anything but routine as Paul Ryan’s 0-15 haul ultimately tipped the balance in the Dubliners’ favour. Substitute Paul Doherty hit a crucial 1-2 in the extra period also as Joe Fortune’s side progressed through to a semi-final clash with Coolderry of Offaly on Sunday week. Progres...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>'Warrior' Keaney rolls back the years in Enda's triumph - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/warrior-keaney-rolls-back-the-years-in-endas-triumph-37468768.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIuX5RSLyvEMUlRzE3RiWdoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/warrior-keaney-rolls-back-the-years-in-endas-triumph-37468768.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Warrior' Keaney rolls back the years in Enda's triumph&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there was a single player symbolic of Ballyboden St Enda's seventh Dublin title, won at the expense of Kilmacud Crokes in Parnell Park yesterday in their replayed final, it was Conal Keaney. At 36, but clearly ageless in sporting years, Keaney was the game's prevailing force in a team that hadn't so much as contested a county final in five years and were, therefore, considered to be over the championship-winning hill. "An incredible warrior," was how Boden's manager, Joe Fortune described Keaney afterwards and, as the last of the natural light faded in Donnycarney, it would have been dif...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Ballyboden crowned Dublin hurling champions after narrow replay win over Kilmacud - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/ballyboden-kilmacud-crokes-dublin-shc-final-replay-4310901-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELSdVqXxb6yWg6oQLEx3AEsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 18:31:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/ballyboden-kilmacud-crokes-dublin-shc-final-replay-4310901-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Ballyboden crowned Dublin hurling champions after narrow replay win over Kilmacud&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ballyboden St Endas 2-15 Kilmacud Crokes 1-15 Stephen O’Meara reports from Parnell Park AFTER THE NORMAL and extra-time drama in the drawn final last week, Kilmacud Crokes and Ballyboden St Endas drew swords for the second time in eight days, today in Parnell Park, in the Dublin senior hurling championship replay. With Boden having shown their value over 80 minutes last week, Joe Fortune’s charges had seen their odds on taking their first championship since 2013 slashed to even money since having come in as outsiders before the drawn final. In the end, the even odds would prove more than ju...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>'The age issue is massively overblown in GAA' - Liam Rushe - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/liam-rushe-dublin-hurling-2-4313550-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgE2yF1E56CKc-f7KSNopwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 07:05:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/liam-rushe-dublin-hurling-2-4313550-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'The age issue is massively overblown in GAA' - Liam Rushe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DUBLIN ARE EXPECTED to appoint their third manager in as many years later this week, with Anthony Daly and Mattie Kenny believed to be in a two-horse race for the position. Kilmacud Crokes’ Dublin SHC final defeat to Ballyboden St Enda’s on Sunday has freed up Daly’s schedule to take up the county job for a second time. There have been whispers around the capital in recent days that the Clare native has moved into pole position, but Kenny and Anthony Cunningham have also been heavily linked to the role. Liam Rushe, who will be a key player for whoever is appointed, says he’s open to a secon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Extra-time can't separate Boden and Kilmacud in decider - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/1021/1005719-extra-time-cant-separate-boden-and-kilmacud-in-decider/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDmgQHq0op8vXqfnn69ZVZUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 17:21:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/1021/1005719-extra-time-cant-separate-boden-and-kilmacud-in-decider/" target="_blank"&gt;Extra-time can't separate Boden and Kilmacud in decider&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ballyboden St Enda's 2-17 Kilmacud Crokes 1-20 (aet) Key duo Niall McMorrow and Paul Ryan struck at the end of an extra-time epic at Parnell Park to secure a Dublin SHC final draw for Ballyboden St Enda's. Anthony Daly's Kilmacud Crokes, beaten in the last two finals, looked all set to make it third time lucky when they led by two with 78 minutes on the clock. But ex-county man McMorrow and free-taker Ryan struck to tie the game up for the sixth time and ensure a replay despite 80 minutes of action. It throws up a logistical problem for Crokes whose footballers have already qualified for th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>All-Ireland club champions Cuala dumped out in Dublin semi-final by Dalo's Kilmacud - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/cuala-kilmacud-crokes-reports-4272983-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGGNzvw2iX8_oSdeY4fnMv4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 17:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/cuala-kilmacud-crokes-reports-4272983-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;All-Ireland club champions Cuala dumped out in Dublin semi-final by Dalo's Kilmacud&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kilmacud Crokes 3-13 Cuala 1-17 Stephen O’Meara reports from Parnell Park THE MARQUEE GAME of this year’s Dublin senior hurling championship saw the semi-final clash of three in-a-row Dublin, and two-in-a-row All-Ireland champions, Cuala, face southside rivals and 2014 champions, Kilmacud Crokes. A repeat of the 2016 and 17 finals, this one had some added spice, with the respective managers, Cuala’s Mattie Kenny and Crokes’ Anthony Daly, each being whispered about as potential replacements for Pat Gilroy at the helm for the Dublin senior hurlers. In the end it would prove to be Daly’s men ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>After sudden Gilroy exit, will Dublin turn to Galway to solve hurling manager issue? - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/pat-gilroy-dublin-hurling-5-4239807-Sep2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEA2QNsVS8py317KpqTwlocqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 16:31:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/pat-gilroy-dublin-hurling-5-4239807-Sep2018/" target="_blank"&gt;After sudden Gilroy exit, will Dublin turn to Galway to solve hurling manager issue?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;APPOINTED IN OCTOBER 2017, departed in September 2018. Pat Gilroy’s first spell as Dublin senior manager may have been a wide-ranging one, overseeing an exhaustive process to overhaul the fortunes of the county’s football side, but his second tenure, at the helm of the county hurling team, ended up being brief as it lasted just a single season. He pulled the plug officially last night as he cited work commitments, reasoning that provided a neat symmetry with his previous departure. “It has been a challenging four years for me balancing my role with Dublin along with family and work commitme...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>There's only one man to replace Pat Gilroy - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/theres-one-man-replace-pat-gilroy-177424</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE4rMMMHEsgtmGZgMdKjQyIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wg46hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 07:29:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/theres-one-man-replace-pat-gilroy-177424" target="_blank"&gt;There's only one man to replace Pat Gilroy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just when things were starting to look up. Jesus, what a blow for Dublin. What a blow for Dublin hurling and what a blow for the Dublin county board. Befor 2018, their county's hurlers had been in the wilderness for way too long. Anthony Daly left the scene back in 2014 and that sent Dublin hurling into an extended hangover. Ger Cunningham was appointed as Daly's successor and his tenure was put mildly, a disaster. The camp always looked like a divided one and the bottom line was that players didn't seem to want to play hurling for Dublin anymore. You'd players like Mark Schutte leaving to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Win secures Championship hurling for Dubs - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/sport/gaa/win-secures-championship-hurling-for-dubs-846720.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEm2vH2BnHB0wzJtAv5dNeMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 16:02:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/sport/gaa/win-secures-championship-hurling-for-dubs-846720.html" target="_blank"&gt;Win secures Championship hurling for Dubs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Paul Keane Dublin 2-24 Offaly 0-13 Captain Chris Crummey powered Dublin to a significant Leinster SHC win at Parnell Park which secures their status in the competition for 2019. The wing-back boomed over four points and was involved in both of Dublin's goals which were scored by Paul Ryan and Fergal Whitely. Shane Barrett also fired four points from the half-back line as Dublin overcame a sluggish start to speed clear and eventually win with 17 points to spare. There was just two points between the teams after 30 minutes as Offaly, in action for the fourth weekend running, attempted to s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Dublin see off Laois with 15 points to spare to advance to quarter-finals - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/sport/gaa/dublin-see-off-laois-with-15-points-to-spare-to-advance-to-quarter-finals-832001.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBKV71VSM7fIWKzbEusHzZMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUw2pahAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 17:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/sport/gaa/dublin-see-off-laois-with-15-points-to-spare-to-advance-to-quarter-finals-832001.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dublin see off Laois with 15 points to spare to advance to quarter-finals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dublin 3-23 - Laois 0-17: Dublin led throughout as Pat Gilroy's charges booked a home date with Tipperary in the Allianz Hurling League quarter-finals, finishing with 15 points to spare against Laois at O'Moore Park, Portlaoise. The visitors, who are still without their Cuala contingent gave a very impressive display, and powered to a 1-10 to 0-2 lead after just 20 minutes. Danny Sutcliffe of Dublin in action against James Ryan of Laois. Picture: Philip Fitzpatrick/Sportsfile Dublin's half-back line also showed very well in the opening stages, while the Metropolitians were also hugely domin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>It just felt like the time to step away from Dublin - O'Callaghan - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/it-just-felt-like-the-time-to-step-away-from-dublin-ocallaghan-36571736.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECoTY_bMFPK4ohsNsTjaysAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/it-just-felt-like-the-time-to-step-away-from-dublin-ocallaghan-36571736.html" target="_blank"&gt;It just felt like the time to step away from Dublin - O'Callaghan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;David 'Dotsy' O'Callaghan thought about giving it another shot. Pat Gilroy had been installed as Dublin hurling manager and it was the sort of appointment that could only intrigue any prospective hurler in the county. At 34, he had already put in 15 seasons as a Dub in one form or another. And the last couple of those were ravaged by injury. But when Gilroy came on board, he asked himself if there was anything left in the tank. As it turned out, there wasn't. "You would have heard a lot of things about the lads," he said of the new management team. "I did push it out myself, I trained mysel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Offaly brought back down to earth with 17-point hammering by Limerick - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/division-1b-wrap-3833892-Feb2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDmdRcyEhqw0M5y9mmKhlkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 19:47:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/division-1b-wrap-3833892-Feb2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Offaly brought back down to earth with 17-point hammering by Limerick&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Limerick 1-24 Offaly 0-10 OFFALY WERE BROUGHT back down to earth with a 17-point hammering by Limerick in Tullamore this afternoon. The Faithful enjoyed an impressive victory over Dublin last weekend, but were unable to build on that Croke Park win. Offaly’s Damien Egan missed a first-half penalty before they lost Dermot Shortt to a red card 10 minutes into the second-half. They were seven points down at that stage and from there Limerick powered to the 1-24 to 0-10 success. All-Ireland U21 winner Aaron Gillane posted 1-8 for the Shannonsiders, while Shane Dooley made his 101st appearance f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Pat Gilroy's Dublin register Antrim win but only by the skin of their teeth - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/pat-gilroys-dublin-register-antrim-win-but-only-by-the-skin-of-their-teeth-36565765.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH5aiOHpgWz9btXDn_FJZp4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 16:38:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/pat-gilroys-dublin-register-antrim-win-but-only-by-the-skin-of-their-teeth-36565765.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pat Gilroy's Dublin register Antrim win but only by the skin of their teeth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Dublin hurlers are back in the winning zone – but only just. It required a 76th minute free from Donal Burke to secure a nerve-shredding one-point win in Corrigan Park, just when it appeared that Antrim's grandstand finish had secured a share of the Division 1B spoils. Pat Gilroy's side led by six points at the break and twice extended this to seven, but the Neil McManus-inspired Saffrons came with a late surge to parity. Four minutes of stoppage time had been signalled and this had just elapsed when McManus nailed an 85m free for his 16th point of an intriguing, full-blooded contest pl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>First victory for Offaly at Croke Park since 2005 with convincing 13-point defeat of Dublin - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/offaly-dublin-report-3820279-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHsrAIDe28SqQ4YpPTwlYw8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 18:43:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/offaly-dublin-report-3820279-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;First victory for Offaly at Croke Park since 2005 with convincing 13-point defeat of Dublin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Offaly 2-25 Dublin 1-15 Kevin O’Brien reports from Croke Park KEVIN MARTIN’S TENURE in charge of Offaly got off to a flying start with a 13 point hammering of Dublin in the Division 1B opener tonight. This was Offaly’s first league win at Croke Park since 1991 and their first victory of any kind at HQ since 2005. Second-half goals from substitutes Shane Dooley and Liam Langton helped Offaly to the comfortable win, and consigned Pat Gilroy to a heavy defeat in his first game over Dublin. Both sides came into this game under new management, but it was Offaly boss Martin who left Croke Park in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Sutcliffe admits he 'couldn't say no' to new boss Gilroy - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/sutcliffe-admits-he-couldnt-say-no-to-new-boss-gilroy-36549721.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEELsZ6Xjla-WLRCWnCKFxS4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/sutcliffe-admits-he-couldnt-say-no-to-new-boss-gilroy-36549721.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sutcliffe admits he 'couldn't say no' to new boss Gilroy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a way, Donald Trump has come to the aid of the Dublin hurlers. Danny Sutcliffe returned from New York last year, where he had played in the Connacht Championship with the Big Apple's footballers, to rejoin Pat Gilroy's hurling panel for the 2018 season. But it wasn't necessarily in the plan for the St Jude's man. And in some ways, the US President helped him make up his mind. "Just it's tough now with the visa situation," Sutcliffe said of his decision to return to Ireland. "Any other year you probably would have got an 18-month extension on your grad visa, but that wasn't available with...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Pat Gilroy names Dublin team for Saturday night's Croke Park double-header - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/dublin-hurling-team-offaly-allianz-league-3818804-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHl78HUfdQXpKzAp2f_7P3EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 15:35:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/dublin-hurling-team-offaly-allianz-league-3818804-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Pat Gilroy names Dublin team for Saturday night's Croke Park double-header&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DUBLIN HURLING MANAGER Pat Gilroy has named his team for the Allianz Hurling League opener against Offaly on Saturday evening at Croke Park. Despite reports earlier in the week which suggested captain Liam Rushe would be fit to feature in Gilroy’s first league game in charge, the 27-year-old isn’t included in Dublin’s starting XV. Returning players such as Danny Sutcliffe, Conal Keaney and Joey Boland are also absent but former captain Johnny McCaffrey does start in midfield. Kevin Martin’s Offaly will travel to HQ enthused by a couple of encouraging performances in the Walsh Cup ahead of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Sobering start to Gilroy era as Faithful run riot at headquarters - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/sobering-start-to-gilroy-era-as-faithful-run-riot-at-headquarters-36537935.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELIitQzTLWonbhN3WvxM6NkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/sobering-start-to-gilroy-era-as-faithful-run-riot-at-headquarters-36537935.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sobering start to Gilroy era as Faithful run riot at headquarters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than five years have passed since Pat Gilroy and Mickey Whelan last stood together on the sideline in Croke Park. On that occasion in August 2012, Mayo ended Dublin's reign as All-Ireland football champions. Last night there was less excitement in the stadium for the return of Gilroy and Whelan to headquarters in a managerial role - though this time around their mission is arguably more challenging. And the size of the task they face was underlined by an experienced Offaly side being managed for the first time by All-Ireland winner Kevin Martin. The visitors' 13-point winning margin di...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Offaly run riot in Croke Park to stun Pat Gilroy's Dubs - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/0127/936446-offaly-run-riot-in-croke-park-to-stun-pat-gilroys-dubs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHD2EsAm9h12TEOHTSFsEaMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 18:55:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/0127/936446-offaly-run-riot-in-croke-park-to-stun-pat-gilroys-dubs/" target="_blank"&gt;Offaly run riot in Croke Park to stun Pat Gilroy's Dubs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Offaly 2-25 Dublin 1-15 Resurgent Offaly got the Kevin Martin era off to a storming start with a shock Allianz Hurling League Division 1B win over Dublin at Croke Park. The opening round of the new campaign looked certain to mark Dublin's first significant win under new boss Pat Gilroy. But the 1/12 hot tips couldn't deliver as Offaly conjured a display of hungry hurling that left the hosts chasing shadows all evening. The Faithful County, who hadn't won a League or Championship game at Croke Park since 2005, led by five at half-time and sealed victory with goals from subs Shane Dooley and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>10 most intriguing storylines on the first Sunday of the Allianz Leagues - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/gaa-storylines-2018-3820169-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJrzUvbtqfk1CDTPVTBGR-8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 08:00:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/gaa-storylines-2018-3820169-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;10 most intriguing storylines on the first Sunday of the Allianz Leagues&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WITH 27 INTER-COUNTY games on the agenda today and four in the books from last night, the GAA season is well and truly underway. Here’s a look at the 10 topics of interest in hurling and football we’re most interested in over the next couple of months. *** 1. The most unpredictable of leagues How do you approach the league? That’s the question that’ll have been rattling around the heads of most inter-county managers for the past few weeks. The introduction of the round robin format in the hurling provinces means inter-county sides effectively have another league to worry about come the mid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>GAA teams: Brogan and Macauley start for Dublin - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/0125/936079-gaa-digest-obrien-returns-for-tipperary-footballers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBOKf_CwcJfItK7Sh4D4HfoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 15:27:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/0125/936079-gaa-digest-obrien-returns-for-tipperary-footballers/" target="_blank"&gt;GAA teams: Brogan and Macauley start for Dublin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All-Ireland champions Dublin have named a strong team for their opening Allianz League game against Kildare this evening (7pm). Jim Gavin’s selection contains only seven of the side that started last September’s victory over Mayo but can afford to call in former footballer of the year Bernard Brogan, Michael Fitzsimons and midfield stalwart Michael Darragh Macauley. See the Dublin team named to take on @KildareGAA today in the first round of the #AllianzLeagues ?? pic.twitter.com/Dg5WphA5pU — Dublin GAA (@DubGAAOfficial) January 27, 2018 Kildare boss Cian O'Neill is missing injured duo Keit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Hurling 1B preview: Second-tier no obstacle to glory - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/0124/935759-hurling-preview-division-1b-is-not-too-b/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHTc6EycmaDq6R9sFMlDCjcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:00:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/0124/935759-hurling-preview-division-1b-is-not-too-b/" target="_blank"&gt;Hurling 1B preview: Second-tier no obstacle to glory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When does A not really come before B? In the weird, wonderful world that is the Allianz Hurling League. In 2012, the GAA decided to replace the old eight-team Division 1 structure - which still applies in football - with two tiers of six sides: Division 1A and 1B. That meant promoted Division 2 winners Limerick and runners-up Clare had effectively been relegated overnight. As a sort of compromise/bonus to promotion, the 1B winners were handed a place in the new format's semi-finals. By 2014, that had expanded to pit the top four in 1B against the top four in 1A in quarter-finals. And so we ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>2013 Leinster winner Rushe returns to Dublin hurlers - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/0123/935291-2013-leinster-winner-rushe-returns-to-dublin-hurlers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_dGMDSjtsWf0fawzmvgesqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 11:19:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2018/0123/935291-2013-leinster-winner-rushe-returns-to-dublin-hurlers/" target="_blank"&gt;2013 Leinster winner Rushe returns to Dublin hurlers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dublin hurlers have been boosted by the return of 2013 Leinster winner Liam Rushe, who has rejoined the panel after recovering from a groin injury, according to the We Are Dublin GAA website. It was also reported on RTÉ's Morning Ireland on Tuesday morning. The return of the former team captain will bring a major boost to Pat Gilroy's side as they look to begin their Division 1B campaign this weekend. All-Star recipient Danny Sutcliffe, along with Conal Keaney and Joey Boland are among the other players who have rejoined the Dublin hurlers in recent weeks. Controversy surrounded the Dublin ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>First defeat for Dublin under Pat Gilroy as Wexford book Kilkenny showdown - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/dublin-wexford-report-3797097-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4m2So60YLAc5vk50yr2OAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 15:41:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/dublin-wexford-report-3797097-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;First defeat for Dublin under Pat Gilroy as Wexford book Kilkenny showdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wexford 1-20 Dublin 0-16 Kevin O’Brien reports from Parnell Park WEXFORD WILL PLAY Kilkenny in the Walsh Cup final next Sunday after overturning a five-point deficit to easily defeat Dublin in Parnell Park. It was a first defeat for Dublin under Pat Gilroy in the pre-season competition as a second yellow card for Paul Winters in the 46th minute proved extremely costly. Dublin were ahead by 0-15 to 0-10 at that stage, but they faded alarmingly after that incident. The victory for Davy Fitzgerald’s side looked unlikely before Winters was dismissed, but they posted 1-10 without reply to seal a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Boost for Pat Gilroy as another star returns to Dublin hurling panel - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/boost-for-pat-gilroy-as-another-star-returns-to-dublin-hurling-panel-36482659.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBJeihTua03Qip3MhscsD64qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 15:42:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/boost-for-pat-gilroy-as-another-star-returns-to-dublin-hurling-panel-36482659.html" target="_blank"&gt;Boost for Pat Gilroy as another star returns to Dublin hurling panel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOEY Boland has become the latest ‘former’ Dublin hurler to rejoin the county squad this week as Pat Gilroy continues to experiment with both old and new recruits in these early passages of his reign. However, contrary to reports, The Herald understands that former Limerick hurler, Tom Ryan, is not currently part of Gilroy’s panel. After news this week that Conal Keaney was back in training after almost three years of inter-county inactivity, Boland’s return is somewhat less surprising. At 30, the Na Fianna man is five years younger than Keaney but left the squad in the summer of 2016 after...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Second game in two days for Dublin as Pat Gilroy's men book Wexford showdown - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/dublin-antrim-report-3785316-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBm3nD3EWEhtj2hYdka7SgUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 15:39:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/dublin-antrim-report-3785316-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Second game in two days for Dublin as Pat Gilroy's men book Wexford showdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dublin 4-16 Antrim 0-17 Kevin O’Brien reports from Parnell Park PAT GILROY AND Davy Fitzgerald will meet on the sideline for the first time next Sunday after Dublin advanced to the last four of the Walsh Cup with a facile 11-point win over Antrim. This was Dublin’s second game in the space of 26 hours following their 17-point defeat in a challenge game to Tipperary on Saturday. Pat Gilroy’s starting line-up this afternoon included 11 players who began yesterday’s game in Thurles as he continues to assess his options ahead of the National League opener against Offaly at the end of the month....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>'There was nothing to heal' - all well in Gilroy's Dublin camp as players return - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/pat-gilroy-dublin-hurling-2-3782050-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHt6OWjflPUtDnr7X3DpmE8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 06:15:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/pat-gilroy-dublin-hurling-2-3782050-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'There was nothing to heal' - all well in Gilroy's Dublin camp as players return&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DUBLIN HURLING BOSS Pat Gilroy insists he has not had to heal any rifts in their squad since taking charge last October after a number of players have returned to the fold for the 2018 season. Gilroy took the reins after a 2017 campaign that saw Dublin scarred by heavy championship losses to Galway and Tipperary. It was a season characterised by the Dublin players that were not involved. Some had been omitted while others opted to walk. A bunch have been drafted back into the setup with goalkeeper Alan Nolan and midfielder Johnny McCaffrey notable presences in Wednesday night’s Walsh Cup op...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Pat Gilroy means business and his team line-ups for two games in two days highlight that - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/pat-gilroy-means-business-team-line-ups-two-games-two-days-highlight-146438</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO8L4vi9A051W9_AsvAdbcMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 16:53:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/pat-gilroy-means-business-team-line-ups-two-games-two-days-highlight-146438" target="_blank"&gt;Pat Gilroy means business and his team line-ups for two games in two days highlight that&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's no rest for the wicked. Dublin played against Tipperary in a challenge match on Saturday in Dr. Morris Park, Thurles. This was their starting fifteen that lined out to face the Premier county. Here's a quick match report from our Senior Hurlers' challenge match against @TipperaryGAA in Thurles yesterday https://t.co/CqDU7Aq1P6 — Dublin GAA (@DubGAAOfficial) January 7, 2018 Alan Nolan Paddy Smyth, Bill O'Carroll, Cian Hendricken; Shane Barrett, Darren Kelly, Chris Crummey; Johnny McCaffrey, Tom Connolly; Danny Sutcliffe, Fergal Whitely, Daire Gray; Alan Moore, Paul Winters, John Heth...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>There is no rift between players who stayed and those who left - Gilroy - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/there-is-no-rift-between-players-who-stayed-and-those-who-left-gilroy-36460452.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENzfJyK5Z0i2DV8JJrj8afcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/there-is-no-rift-between-players-who-stayed-and-those-who-left-gilroy-36460452.html" target="_blank"&gt;There is no rift between players who stayed and those who left - Gilroy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the history of Pat Gilroy's spell as Dublin hurling manager is written, their win over Meath in Abbotstown, their first competitive game, will hardly get a mention. Still, it was on a freezing January Wednesday night this week where the latest chapter of the small-ball game began in the capital. Dublin were much too strong for their neighbours, hitting four goals and keeping a clean sheet. In truth, little could be read into the 70 minutes of action but at least the experiment is officially up and running. It will pick up pace this weekend, too. Tomorrow they'll face Tipperary in a cha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>All-Ireland winners as players and bosses, this Leinster hurling trio set for 2018 start tonight - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/pat-gilroy-brian-cody-davy-fitzgerald-3778421-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIvuI_f4ihTAbwRcRQ4iVYgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 06:00:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/pat-gilroy-brian-cody-davy-fitzgerald-3778421-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;All-Ireland winners as players and bosses, this Leinster hurling trio set for 2018 start tonight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMIDST THE DARK gloom of early January, the 2018 GAA season will roll into action for three figures tonight who are accustomed to the marquee days in summer. It’s the 20th season at the helm of the Kilkenny hurlers for Brian Cody, a man with 14 Liam MacCarthy Cup successes to his credit between playing and managing. It’s the second season in charge of Wexford for Davy Fitzgerald, who scaled the hurling summit in September on the pitch and on the sideline with his native Clare. But it’s a first campaign as boss of the Dublin hurlers for Pat Gilroy, a figure more celebrated for his football a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>'We wouldn’t be losing sleep over it' - a low-key January start for the Gilroy hurling era in Dublin - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/pat-gilroy-dublin-hurling-3780944-Jan2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHsFYMNf50nRPAHB3LWCWrwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8w4cihAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 19:21:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/pat-gilroy-dublin-hurling-3780944-Jan2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'We wouldn’t be losing sleep over it' - a low-key January start for the Gilroy hurling era in Dublin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS BEGINNINGS GO, last night was low-key. It’s only just over seven miles from Croke Park to the National Sports Campus in Abbotstown but the contrast was stark between the venue where Pat Gilroy finished his stint in charge with the Dublin footballers to the ground where he started out with the Dublin hurlers. After four years in charge of the Dublin footballers – during which he produced the act of deliverance by halting that 16-year wait for Sam Maguire – his last outing was the 2012 All-Ireland semi-final when a second-half comeback fell short against Mayo. He bowed out with his reputat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>Gilroy is 'mad keen to get going' after Dubs workout - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/gilroy-is-mad-keen-to-get-going-after-dubs-workout-36437072.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAkdVcKO6ENX4eZZJ503Gs0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/gilroy-is-mad-keen-to-get-going-after-dubs-workout-36437072.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gilroy is 'mad keen to get going' after Dubs workout&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pat Gilroy and Mickey Whelan were on the green, green grass of home. Two celebrated names of St Vincent's; a club with much to celebrate and their Dublin hurlers out dancing with the stars. Before the throw-in they were looking at the warm-up, along with coach Anthony Cunningham, for the Dublin Bus/Herald Dubs Stars contest at Páirc Naomh Uinsionn. A Dublin fan asked the duo for a picture. No problem. On the pitch, the game had a real intensity to it. It was not an afternoon for passing around the cranberry sauce. At the end, 'Giller' was content with the workout. "Both teams really went at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Alan Nolan makes his return to the Dublin jersey but Paul Winters points Dubs Stars to victory - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/dublin-dubs-stars-hurling-3768431-Dec2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFW2v0CY6n0ameeFqqrP578qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 18:56:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/dublin-dubs-stars-hurling-3768431-Dec2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Alan Nolan makes his return to the Dublin jersey but Paul Winters points Dubs Stars to victory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dubs Stars 1-24 Dublin 0-21 Kevin O’Brien reports from Páirc Naomh Uinsionn, Marino PAT GILROY WATCHED an experimental Dublin team lose to the Dubs Stars in their annual challenge game in his home club of St Vincent’s this afternoon. Alan Nolan became the latest player outcast by Ger Cunningham to make his return in the blue jersey, following in the footsteps of Peter Kelly, Johnny McCaffrey and Danny Sutcliffe in rejoining the panel. McCaffrey was part of the victorious Dubs Stars side, which also included fellow Dublin pannelists Gary Maguire, Chris Crummey, Paul Winters, Fergal Whitely a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>McCaffrey and Kelly set for Dublin comebacks - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/1213/927052-mccaffrey-and-kelly-set-for-dublin-comebacks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGjisDlpicyw3kusgrchM_UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 08:53:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/gaa/2017/1213/927052-mccaffrey-and-kelly-set-for-dublin-comebacks/" target="_blank"&gt;McCaffrey and Kelly set for Dublin comebacks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dublin hurling manager Pat Gilroy has boosted his squad for 2018 with the inclusion of former captain Johnny McCaffrey, with a number of other players also set for inter-county returns. It has been confirmed that McCaffrey, still involved with Lucan Sarsfields, will rejoin the fold for the coming season. Former manager Ger Cunningham axed the 2013 Leinster winning captain last season along with a number of other high-profile players including Peter Kelly. Speaking to the press for the first time as a member of Pat Gilroy's management team, Anthony Cunningham confirmed that McCaffrey and 201...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>2013 Leinster-winning captain and former All-Star have rejoined the Dublin hurling squad - The42</title><link>http://www.the42.ie/johnny-mccaffrey-peter-kelly-dublin-3746727-Dec2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHlAoGuPIA5NICQ9-k_7rMEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowgOufCTCbyG8wwM2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:05:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.the42.ie/johnny-mccaffrey-peter-kelly-dublin-3746727-Dec2017/" target="_blank"&gt;2013 Leinster-winning captain and former All-Star have rejoined the Dublin hurling squad&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The42&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUST OVER A year after he was dropped by Ger Cunningham, Johnny McCaffrey has rejoined the Dublin senior hurling panel. New Dublin coach Anthony Cunningham confirmed yesterday that the former Sky Blues captain is back in training with Pat Gilroy’s squad ahead of the 2018 campaign. McCaffrey was among several experienced players who didn’t see eye-to-eye with the former Cork goalkeeper during his tenure and he was axed from the panel in November 2016 along with Peter Kelly. The Lucan Sarsfields clubman skippered Dublin to the Leinster hurling title in 2013 under Anthony Daly and just turned ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.the42.ie">The42</source></item><item><title>It looks like Pat Gilroy hasn't given up on securing Con O'Callaghan's services for the Dublin hurlers in 2018 - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/it-looks-like-pat-gilroy-hasnt-given-up-on-securing-con-ocallaghans-services-for-the-dublin-hurlers-in-2018-36404407.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG0a6MlJ5bTqyXr0xbZ7LgIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 08:37:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/it-looks-like-pat-gilroy-hasnt-given-up-on-securing-con-ocallaghans-services-for-the-dublin-hurlers-in-2018-36404407.html" target="_blank"&gt;It looks like Pat Gilroy hasn't given up on securing Con O'Callaghan's services for the Dublin hurlers in 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAT GILROY hasn’t given up on luring Con O’Callaghan into the Dublin hurling fold, it would seem. “He will concentrate with Mattie Kenny and all the Cuala boys to win an All-Ireland back-to-back,” explained Dublin selector Anthony Cunningham. “Every hurling person in the country would love to see Con O’Callaghan play Kilkenny and Wexford ... a dream come true, but that’s for others to decide.” Cunningham also expressed an interest in Paul Schutte and his brother Mark, who switched to the footballers last summer - but only once Cuala’s campaign ends. Johnny McCaffrey and Peter Kelly are also...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Calling Lucan Sarsfields pair in from the cold is a smart move by Pat Gilroy - SportsJOE.ie</title><link>https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/calling-lucan-sarsfields-pair-cold-smart-move-pat-gilroy-144201</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKMl5n6cGHvRi66dfUQ_xBwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowuN-fCTD7vG8wtLuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 14:59:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.sportsjoe.ie/gaa/calling-lucan-sarsfields-pair-cold-smart-move-pat-gilroy-144201" target="_blank"&gt;Calling Lucan Sarsfields pair in from the cold is a smart move by Pat Gilroy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SportsJOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A good start to the new era. One of Pat Gilroy's first big decisions since he took over the Dublin senior hurlers was bringing Peter Kelly and Johnny McCaffrey back into the set-up. Gilroy's first decision was indeed a great decision. Peter Kelly and Johnny McCaffrey were dropped from the Dublin hurling panel by Ger Cunningham for the 2017 season. The Lucan Sarsfields pair had been leaders of Dublin hurling for 10 years before being axed by the Cork man. Drafted into the capital city's hurling panel in 2006, McCaffrey was introduced to Dublin hurling when it was in the doldrums, when it had...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.sportsjoe.ie">SportsJOE.ie</source></item><item><title>‘That chapter is well and truly over’ - Cunningham - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/that-chapter-is-well-and-truly-over-cunningham-36403590.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAbIetOHoRfNk1F5xai_h4IqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w_8yiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/sport/gaelic-games/hurling/that-chapter-is-well-and-truly-over-cunningham-36403590.html" target="_blank"&gt;‘That chapter is well and truly over’ - Cunningham&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone who opens the foreword to Gerry Callan's book 'The Complete Record Of Dublin Football' will get quite the insight into how passionate Pat Gilroy is about the city, not just its football constituency. It is emotive stuff, drenched in history and context. But those words are scarcely required to understand Gilroy's sense of place. By putting himself forward for the Dublin hurling management job, despite a dearth of experience in the game at the top level, his commitment to the blue cause is self-evident. Anthony Cunningham is happy to be his pillion passenger. Since departing Galway in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Recap: Your morning sports updates - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/sport/other-sport/2017/1213/927020-your-morning-sports-update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAxDnWk3DWtwwkHd6toVRcUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28w-6qhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 12:02:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/sport/other-sport/2017/1213/927020-your-morning-sports-update/" target="_blank"&gt;Recap: Your morning sports updates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ed Leahy's preview of Katie Taylor's world title defence against Jessica McCaskill Chris Froome promises to help UCI get to the bottom of abnormal urine test results Burnley are into the Champions League spots - and their manager is bursting with pride Shelbourne confirm death of Under-16 player Izzy Dezu Johnny McCaffrey and Peter Kelly set for Dublin comebacks Former world number one Victoria Azarenka has been awarded a wildcard for the Australian Open Real Madrid take on Al Jazira in the World Club Championship this evening (live, RTÉ2, 5pm) Comment: @RTEsport #RTEsport&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item></channel></rss>