<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Micheál Martin - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZ5YTNwckVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-IE&amp;gl=IE&amp;ceid=IE:en</link><language>en-IE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:59:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Micheál Martin sacks Eamon Ó Cuív from Fianna Fáil frontbench - The Irish Times</title><link>https://www.irishtimes.com/news/politics/miche%C3%A1l-martin-sacks-eamon-%C3%B3-cu%C3%ADv-from-fianna-f%C3%A1il-frontbench-1.3691235</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG8ESxbXYMz5etCkrnUOGmQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowqfqFCzD7v4MDMIO9jQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishtimes.com/news/politics/miche%C3%A1l-martin-sacks-eamon-%C3%B3-cu%C3%ADv-from-fianna-f%C3%A1il-frontbench-1.3691235" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin sacks Eamon Ó Cuív from Fianna Fáil frontbench&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Irish Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Party says Ó Cuív 'aware in advance' of plans to hold unauthorised candidate launch.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishtimes.com">The Irish Times</source></item><item><title>Micheál needed to take action after two politicians went 'rogue' - but is he facing a storm over FF's northern merger? - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/micheal-martin-eamon-ocuiv-sdlp-4308125-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQLVCzV2U_sT45a7gsUrk8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/micheal-martin-eamon-ocuiv-sdlp-4308125-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál needed to take action after two politicians went 'rogue' - but is he facing a storm over FF's northern merger?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sacking of two FF politicians from their roles this week was a headache for Micheál Martin.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Leo Varadkar responds to Micheál Martin's Ireland Unfiltered comments on homelessness - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/shows/leo-varadkar-responds-650925</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGueDUbUgKc9bdo6Rx7aWDYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8woL6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:32:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/shows/leo-varadkar-responds-650925" target="_blank"&gt;Leo Varadkar responds to Micheál Martin's Ireland Unfiltered comments on homelessness&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Fianna Fil leader Michel Martin joined Dion Fanning for Ireland Unfiltered. Among other things, the pair discussed the ever-deepening homelessness crisis that currently sees 10,000 Irish people many of them children without a roof over their head. On last night's Late Late Show, host Ryan Tubridy put this to Varadkar, saying: "You're looking at Michel Martin saying on JOE.ie this week that there is genteel, upper-middle class resistance to building local authority housing. Ultimately suggesting that it's a class problem." Varadkar dismissed the criticism by saying that he grew up...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin says the housing crisis is a class issue - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/shows/housing-crisis-fianna-fail-650700</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMaXO2sE4jcBQvY5Nm0GEFYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8woL6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:40:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/shows/housing-crisis-fianna-fail-650700" target="_blank"&gt;Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin says the housing crisis is a class issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Theyre not on any statistic but theyre there and theyre waiting and waiting." Michel Martin has said that he thinks the housing crisis in Ireland is partly to do with what he calls a, "gentile upper-middle class resistance to building local authority houses". He was this week's guest onIreland Unfilteredand hespoke with host Dion Fanning about his belief that the current housing crisis in Ireland boils down to a class issue combined with a saturation of the private housing market. Here's how the conversation transpired. Michel: What people dont get in the statistics at all is the number of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Fianna Fáil councillor in Cavan to join Peadar Tóibín's new party - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fianna-fail-councillor-in-cavan-to-join-peadar-toibins-new-party-890685.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKjo5oovlzkJzAkmei0xAJQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fianna-fail-councillor-in-cavan-to-join-peadar-toibins-new-party-890685.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fianna Fáil councillor in Cavan to join Peadar Tóibín's new party&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Fianna Fáil councillor has announced she is defecting to join up with former Sinn Féin TD Peadar Tóibín's new political movement. Cavan County Councillor, Sarah O’Reilly, announced on Friday that she has resigned her membership of Fianna Fáil. She was co-opted onto the local authority in 2016 to fill the seat vacated by the election of Niamh Smith to Dáil Eireann. She said: "It's with great sadness that I announce my resignation today. I joined Fianna Fáil nearly 10 years ago as I sought to help make a difference for the people of County Cavan. "It has become clear to me that the Fianna F...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Cavan councillor quits Fianna Fáil to join Peadar Tóibín's new party - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/cavn-councillor-4381328-Dec2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAJJ35n9HGXbYXqmd0WnGiQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:31:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/cavn-councillor-4381328-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Cavan councillor quits Fianna Fáil to join Peadar Tóibín's new party&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A CAVAN FIANNA Fáil councillor has left the party to join former Sinn Féin TD Peader Tóibín’s planned new political party. Cavan councillor Sarah O’Reilly announced in a statement that she was leaving Fianna Fáil as the party she joined 10 years ago no longer exists. “Its with great sadness that I announce my resignation today. I joined Fianna Fáil nearly 10 years ago as I sought to help make a difference for the people of County Cavan. Cavan has long been neglected in terms of infrastructure, jobs and investment,” O’Reilly said in her statement. “It has become clear to me that the Fianna F...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Leo Varadkar will be on The Late Late Show this week - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/movies-tv/leo-varadkar-late-late-show-650759</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAT4yvnlzwr0uVLupx3ykZwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8woL6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:10:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/movies-tv/leo-varadkar-late-late-show-650759" target="_blank"&gt;Leo Varadkar will be on The Late Late Show this week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Taoiseach will reflect on his first 18 months in office. Leo Varadkartakes top billing on this week's Late Late Show as he looks back on the highs and lows of his run as Taoiseach thus far. The Fine Gael leader will join Ryan Tubridy on Friday night to talk about being Irelands youngest ever Taoiseach, navigating Brexit and the stability of the government as the Supply and Confidence agreement with Fianna Fil comes up for renewal. Varadkar will also address the speculation surrounding the prospect of an upcoming general election, in addition to the key issues that face the current gover...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin makes changes to Fianna Fáil frontbench - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/micheal-martin-makes-changes-to-fianna-fail-frontbench-890374.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENpN6cUpckoZLrott2AZIIgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/micheal-martin-makes-changes-to-fianna-fail-frontbench-890374.html" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin makes changes to Fianna Fáil frontbench&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin has made a number of changes to his party's frontbench. Deputy Leader Dara Calleary will become the party's spokesperson on Regional Development, Rural Affairs and the Gaeltacht, TD John Curran will join the frontbench as Spokesperson for National Drug Policy and Urban Affairs. A statement on the changes was been made by Mr Martin this evening. Deputy Martin says urban regeneration and drugs policy has been entirely neglected by this Government. He also says the appointment of the Deputy Leader to the rural affairs portfolio, demonstrates Fianna Fáil's dete...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Dara Calleary to replace Ó Cuív as Fianna Fail rural affairs spokesperson - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/dara-calleary-to-replace-cuv-as-fianna-fail-rural-affairs-spokesperson-37602381.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK5t0RFaazn6T0g4KCeutJoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:04:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/dara-calleary-to-replace-cuv-as-fianna-fail-rural-affairs-spokesperson-37602381.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dara Calleary to replace Ó Cuív as Fianna Fail rural affairs spokesperson&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil's deputy leader Dara Calleary is to become the party's rural affairs spokesman, replacing Éamon Ó Cuív. The move will pit him directly against his Mayo constituency colleague Michael Ring who is Minister for Regional Development and Rural Affairs. Mr Ó Cuív was demoted from the frontbench last month as punishment for taking part in an unofficial launch of party candidate for the local elections in Northern Ireland. Party leader Micheál Martin said: "The continued decline of rural Ireland and Fine Gael's failure to manage any sort of regional balance in terms of investment and jo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>'It's our job to question everyone': PAC says probe into president's spending was 'legitimate' - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/pac-presidents-spending-4377724-Dec2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtJ-LAOq2zzHoUofKWs2FoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:33:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/pac-presidents-spending-4377724-Dec2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'It's our job to question everyone': PAC says probe into president's spending was 'legitimate'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MEMBERS OF THE Oireachtas Public Accounts Committee have said they are very concerned about the Taoiseach and other political leaders questioning who and what they investigate. The committee got into hot water before the presidential election when it decided to review the spending of the Office of the President of Ireland. At the time, Taoiseach Leo Varadkar said he was concerned about the scrutinising of presidential spending in the midst of an election campaign, stating that it was “not advisable”. The hearing resulted in confusion surrounding an annual payment of €317,000 that’s been pai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheal Martin reveals why he changed his mind on Repeal - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/shows/micheal-martin-reveals-changed-mind-repeal-650675</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECfxJ2ZukAhZuK0m5dMrprIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8woL6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:40:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/shows/micheal-martin-reveals-changed-mind-repeal-650675" target="_blank"&gt;Micheal Martin reveals why he changed his mind on Repeal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If I get a chance again,Im going to change that aspect of it anyway." Michel Martin is our guest on a brand newIreland Unfilteredthis week and he spoke with host Dion Fanning about a wide range of subjects fromhis own childhood, to Brexit and his first trip to Northern Ireland. One subject that also arose was the subject of the Eighth Amendment and the historic referendum which took place in Ireland earlier this year. Martin shocked many people in January when he came out in support for the repeal of the Eighth Amendment, a move directly in contrast with his party's stance, who had voted a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Government called on to publish contingency plans for no-deal Brexit - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/government-called-on-to-publish-contingency-plans-for-no-deal-brexit-890116.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBpGxtykqjKKWfmrqVD16TgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/government-called-on-to-publish-contingency-plans-for-no-deal-brexit-890116.html" target="_blank"&gt;Government called on to publish contingency plans for no-deal Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A no-deal Brexit scenario would be “disastrous” for Ireland and the Government must publish its contingency plans, the Dail has heard. A British crash out in March will see accelerated recruitment and redeployment of staff to ensure Ireland's border is properly maintained, Taoiseach Leo Varadkar said. Under mounting pressure to publish its no-deal contingency planning, Mr Varadkar said Government agencies are “engaging in detailed preparedness and contingency planning”. However, the Government has repeatedly insisted it is not preparing for the return of a hard border, which a no deal would...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin says the DUP have "suspended their logic in terms of economics" over Brexit - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/shows/micheal-martin-says-dup-suspended-logic-terms-economics-brexit-650507</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGnDan_RrV9raDm-cwCR3hYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8woL6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:05:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/shows/micheal-martin-says-dup-suspended-logic-terms-economics-brexit-650507" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin says the DUP have "suspended their logic in terms of economics" over Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think there's a middle ground coming in the North." Michel Martin is our guest on a brand newIreland Unfilteredthis week and he spoke with host Dion Fanning in an in-depth interview about coping with unbearable tragedy, his journey as a nationalist and how Brexit can be stopped. He also spoke about his first trip to Northern Ireland when he was young and the impression it left on him. Talk eventually turned to Brexit, and Martin admitted that he thinks the DUP could gain a lot if they handled Brexit correctly. "The letter the late Martin McGuinness and Arlene Foster wrote in 2016 really ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin: his nationalist journey, how Brexit can be stopped &amp; coping with loss - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3JPSH343dj0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2CHUrqKKIkw1Iss4qnlZcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8wxYuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:24:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3JPSH343dj0" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin: his nationalist journey, how Brexit can be stopped &amp; coping with loss&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ireland Unfiltered with Dion Fanning, Ep7 Micheál Martin is our guest on Ireland Unfiltered this week. SUBSCRIBE to your new favourite show HERE: https://bit.ly/2D30D89 Hosted by Dion Fanning, Ireland Unfiltered will feature stripped-back, honest conversations with some of the biggest names in Irish entertainment, sport, politics and media. Fanning will also speak to notable international figures on some of the most important issues affecting Ireland today. Ireland Unfiltered will be available everywhere you get your podcasts - https://bit.ly/2D30D89 - and on YouTube every Tuesday. Use #Ire...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin explains how a meeting with Unionists changed his politics - JOE.ie</title><link>https://www.joe.ie/shows/micheal-martin-explains-meeting-unionists-changed-politics-650357</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO7DRCJICjs4szSBNXzhbJUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowud6fCTCrvm8woL6hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 07:59:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.joe.ie/shows/micheal-martin-explains-meeting-unionists-changed-politics-650357" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin explains how a meeting with Unionists changed his politics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;JOE.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's our kith and kin and it's our family that are being murdered." Michel Martin is our guest on a brand newIreland Unfiltered this week and he spoke with host Dion Fanning in an in-depth interview about coping with unbearable tragedy, his journey as a nationalist and how Brexit can be stopped. He spoke of how he and three others made a journey to Northern Ireland on a learning experience and explained how the whole thing was an "eye-opener" for him in terms of learning about the realities of the conflict. Martin: We met young Unionists in their homes. And I will never forget them really ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.joe.ie">JOE.ie</source></item><item><title>Kevin Doyle: 'TDs have one eye on Brexit and the other on Christmas' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/kevin-doyle-tds-have-one-eye-on-brexit-and-the-other-on-christmas-37587725.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOiZ4A9ljhH_JwzcdlQ9TgAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/kevin-doyle-tds-have-one-eye-on-brexit-and-the-other-on-christmas-37587725.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kevin Doyle: 'TDs have one eye on Brexit and the other on Christmas'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leinster House is in total wind down ahead of the Christmas break, which is still more than a fortnight away. The Dáil spent most of last week being filibustered on abortion while over in the Seanad there's a filibuster trying to prevent the Judicial Appointment Bill from progressing. Brexit is the burning issue, but we're in a holding pattern until at least December 11, when the House of Commons votes on the deal. To fill time and look busy, the Government has been going around launching 'funds' for rural folk, urbanites and even climate change. And in the background, the talks on a new co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin: Explanations of rural broadband plan meetings ‘do not stack up’ - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/micheal-martin-explanations-of-rural-broadband-plan-meetings-do-not-stack-up-888331.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECg7dXSWxs-XUK3WaU97a0MqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/micheal-martin-explanations-of-rural-broadband-plan-meetings-do-not-stack-up-888331.html" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin: Explanations of rural broadband plan meetings ‘do not stack up’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Explanations about meetings between former communications minister Denis Naughten and a lead bidder in the broadband plan do “not stack up” and more answers are needed on the stalled project, says Fianna Fáil. Taoiseach Leo Varadkar insisted that the process to supply broadband to half a million homes was “not tainted” after a review which concluded that Mr Naughten and David McCourt, a businessman leading the consortium bidding for the project, did not influence the plan, despite them meeting several times. However, the Peter Smyth review also concluded that it cannot be unequivocally stat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Leo Varadkar questions if Opposition is trying to 'scupper' broadband plan - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/leo-varadkar-questions-if-opposition-is-trying-to-scupper-broadband-plan-37575124.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOnybk41nbvwD1EHWhSWEV8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 17:02:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/leo-varadkar-questions-if-opposition-is-trying-to-scupper-broadband-plan-37575124.html" target="_blank"&gt;Leo Varadkar questions if Opposition is trying to 'scupper' broadband plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar questioned if the Opposition is trying to “scupper” the National Broadband Plan (NBP) when he was challenged on the controversial project in the Dáil. Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin quizzed the Taoiseach on when the NBP contact will be signed off on. He also raised concern over changes that have occurred within the consortium that’s the last remaining bidder. His questions came after the Irish Independent today reported that the NBP is to be fast-tracked in 2019 and a contract is expected to be signed in January. The plan was hit by controversy after it emerged tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Varadkar: Review shows broadband process 'is not tainted' - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/report-finds-broadband-tender-was-not-influenced-by-minister-and-david-mccourt-888218.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPC5Wlr7mfuXdbXq3R0TpUAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/report-finds-broadband-tender-was-not-influenced-by-minister-and-david-mccourt-888218.html" target="_blank"&gt;Varadkar: Review shows broadband process 'is not tainted'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latest: Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has declared that a review of the national broadband process and of meetings over the project shows that the “process is not tainted”, writes Juno McEnroe. Speaking in the Dáil this afternoon, Mr Varadkar faced questions about a report into meetings between former communications minister Denis Naughten and a consortium bidding for the plan. The Smyth review concluded the broadband plan process was “not influenced” by Mr Naughten or businessman David McCourt, who is leading the consortium bidding for the task to supply broadband to half a million people. The in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>FG pledge on taxes will be ditched after vote, says Martin - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/fg-pledge-on-taxes-will-be-ditched-after-vote-says-martin-37583693.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGjpqlqPlk8Pa-hpiP2OLxcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/fg-pledge-on-taxes-will-be-ditched-after-vote-says-martin-37583693.html" target="_blank"&gt;FG pledge on taxes will be ditched after vote, says Martin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar's promise for five years of tax cuts will be "abandoned within minutes of the election posters coming down", Fianna Fáil has said. The party's leader Micheál Martin last night took aim at the minority Government, saying it has promised a lot but not delivered. In particular, he said tax cuts announced at the Fine Gael Ard Fheis are "not prudent" and "not responsible". He was speaking at a Cork Chamber of Commerce event just hours after saying on radio that his party is election-ready. While Mr Martin renewed his offer not to do anything to spark an election during thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach questions how much 'senior republicans' dictate to Sinn Féin's elected politicians - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/taoiseach-questions-how-much-senior-republicans-dictate-to-sinn-fins-elected-politicians-37575200.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJYI0XlRs-D2Q_dER7_DmLoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 17:01:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/taoiseach-questions-how-much-senior-republicans-dictate-to-sinn-fins-elected-politicians-37575200.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach questions how much 'senior republicans' dictate to Sinn Féin's elected politicians&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has directly asked whether Mary Lou McDonald takes direction from “senior republicans” in her role as Sinn Féin leader. The comments came during terse Dáil exchanges which also saw Fianna Fáil leader, Micheál Martin, combine with the Taoiseach in criticising Sinn Féin for failing to provide a nationalist voice in the North in the Brexit crisis. The Taoiseach said he had followed proceedings of the Northern Ireland inquiry into the so-called “cash for ash scheme” which caused the collapse of the Belfast power-sharing government in January 2017. Mr Varadkar said he was ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Varadkar quizzes SF on 'senior republicans' influence - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/varadkar-quizzes-sf-on-senior-republicans-influence-37576606.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBiKt_BbhjQA7l73zrCYL4oqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/varadkar-quizzes-sf-on-senior-republicans-influence-37576606.html" target="_blank"&gt;Varadkar quizzes SF on 'senior republicans' influence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has directly asked whether Mary Lou McDonald takes direction from "senior republicans" in her role as Sinn Féin leader. The comments came in Dáil exchanges, with Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin combining with the Taoiseach to criticise Sinn Féin for failing to provide a nationalist voice in the Brexit crisis. The Taoiseach said he followed proceedings of the Northern Ireland public inquiry into the so-called "cash for ash scheme" which caused the collapse of the Belfast power-sharing government in January 2017. He was surprised to learn that Sinn Féin had a greater ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Ireland 'fully committed member of EU' regardless of what happens after Brexit - Varadkar - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/ireland-fully-committed-member-of-eu-regardless-of-what-happens-after-brexit-varadkar-37552960.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHaeEa9dRNyXpnH4jwEdAnEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wr8qiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 18:19:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/ireland-fully-committed-member-of-eu-regardless-of-what-happens-after-brexit-varadkar-37552960.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ireland 'fully committed member of EU' regardless of what happens after Brexit - Varadkar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IRELAND will remain a “fully committed member of the EU” regardless of anything that happens after Brexit, Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has said. Opening a four-hour debate on the UK Withdrawal Agreement, the Taoiseach said the negotiations which led to the deal showed the true value of EU membership. Mr Varadkar said while the importance of being in the EU is often measured in monetary terms, this country understands the other significance. He said: “We’ve had unwavering support throughout. There can be no better example of EU membership for a small country. The intangible benefits of solidarity...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Philip Ryan: 'Two party dinners, and two very different flavours on the menu' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/philip-ryan-two-party-dinners-and-two-very-different-flavours-on-the-menu-37562691.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBY9LGCTHJW6tQI__MPPkC8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 18:25:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/philip-ryan-two-party-dinners-and-two-very-different-flavours-on-the-menu-37562691.html" target="_blank"&gt;Philip Ryan: 'Two party dinners, and two very different flavours on the menu'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few days before the Fine Gael presidential dinner on October 6, two messages from the party's headquarters were sent to ministers. Firstly, the ministers were told they all had to wear something blue for the occasion - a dress, tie, shirt or even a rosette. Anything would do for the Fine Gael chiefs who seem to be proud of the origin of the party's ''blue shirts" nickname. Secondly, they were told to congregate outside Fitzwilliam Hall of what is now called the Clayton Hotel Burlington Road before entering the venue for the annual fundraising dinner. "For those of you attending the presid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheál Martin slams Fine Gael's ‘juvenile behaviour’ - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/micheal-martin-slams-fine-gaels-juvenile-behaviour-886216.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELsb2UKxT1aNND3Izy_Ux7MqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 05:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/micheal-martin-slams-fine-gaels-juvenile-behaviour-886216.html" target="_blank"&gt;Micheál Martin slams Fine Gael's ‘juvenile behaviour’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin hit out at “juvenile” comments from Fine Gael ministers who he accused of angling for an early general election. Speaking at his party’s Presidential Dinner in Dublin, Mr Martin was responding to a string of criticism from Cabinet members at the Fine Gael Árd Fheis. “I can’t explain the sort of juvenile behaviour by some ministers today,” he said. “They need to stand back and acknowledge the stability and the consensus across the Dáil on the Brexit issue.” Mr Martin was pressed about the slow pace of confidence and supply talks, which are heading into their...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach: 'Householders will have pay more to fill their cars, for electricity and gas under carbon tax hikes' - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/carbon-tax-hikes-4352539-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF54AlkYDUgMnEupbOo6C6oqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 15:53:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/carbon-tax-hikes-4352539-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach: 'Householders will have pay more to fill their cars, for electricity and gas under carbon tax hikes'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TAOISEACH LEO VARADKAR has said householders will have to pay more for electricity, gas and for petrol and diesel due to a hike in carbon taxes the government will roll out in the coming years. Varadkar said the increase in carbon taxes will be needed over the next number of years in order for Ireland to meet its international global warming targets. He told the Dáil that a new ESRI report, which suggests households may need to pay €3,000 a year in carbon taxes, in order for Ireland to avoid EU fines, is “way off the mark”. Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin raised the issue of carbon taxes ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Backing for 16-bed stepdown facility in Cork city - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/backing-for-16-bed-stepdown-facility-in-cork-city-886950.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBF4Xv-C_N1u_uYQyR3iut8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 04:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/backing-for-16-bed-stepdown-facility-in-cork-city-886950.html" target="_blank"&gt;Backing for 16-bed stepdown facility in Cork city&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The State must now provide funding to allow a rehab charity open a stepdown facility in Cork after a breakthrough in a stand-off which has seen the property lying idle for almost a decade. The call came after the HSE finally signalled its support for Cuan Mhuire’s proposal to open a 16-bed facility on the city’s Western Rd designed to break the cycle of homelessness. Colm Burke Fine Gael senator Colm Burke said it is essential that the estimated €300,000 annual running costs is sanctioned to ensure the facility can open by January 1. Fianna Fáil city councillor Fergal Dennehy said it is sca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Dáil in chaos as Varadkar and Martin argue 'like children' in carbon tax increase 'racket' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/dil-in-chaos-as-varadkar-and-martin-argue-like-children-in-carbon-tax-increase-racket-37551719.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOJtcqpv3WmiMLw0Om3TWP0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 13:10:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/dil-in-chaos-as-varadkar-and-martin-argue-like-children-in-carbon-tax-increase-racket-37551719.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dáil in chaos as Varadkar and Martin argue 'like children' in carbon tax increase 'racket'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Dáil was on the verge of being adjourned this afternoon as Taoiseach Leo Varadkar and Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin sparred over carbon tax increases. Ceann Comhairle Seán Ó Fearghaíl threatened to halt proceedings over the "racket" while People Before Profit’s Richard Boyd Barrett described the two men as "children". As ordered was restored Mr Martin was seen to approach the Ceann Comhairle for a private word before walking out of the chamber. He complained that Mr Varadkar was allowed to breach standing orders to accuse him of misleading the Dáil. It followed a debate on whether t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Dáil motion supporting Brexit deal passes without the need for a vote - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/dil-motion-supporting-brexit-deal-passes-without-the-need-for-a-vote-37553580.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDPbRHz3HzQEWOkRhP-IvGIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wr8qiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 22:30:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/dil-motion-supporting-brexit-deal-passes-without-the-need-for-a-vote-37553580.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dáil motion supporting Brexit deal passes without the need for a vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dáil has passed a motion supporting the Brexit deal without the need for a vote. As less than 10 TDs opposed the draft document agreed by the UK and EU, the Ceann Comhairle ruled that a formal vote was not necessary. Members of the Solidarity party did oppose the motion, along with Independent TD Mick Wallace. Cork representative Mick Barry said they objected to “the politics of neo-liberalism” which he claimed runs through the Withdrawal Agreement “like stitching in a jacket”. The vote was symbolical rather than legally binding. It was put forward by the Government and received support...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Varadkar: DUP does not want 'best of both worlds' for Northern Ireland in Brexit - Newstalk Newsfeed</title><link>https://www.newstalk.com/Varadkar:-DUP-does-not-want-best-of-both-worlds-for-Northern-Ireland-in-Brexit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECK-_5bfec7kniwY2obdElsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowmeSfCTCcwW8wmpuhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 07:05:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newstalk.com/Varadkar:-DUP-does-not-want-best-of-both-worlds-for-Northern-Ireland-in-Brexit" target="_blank"&gt;Varadkar: DUP does not want 'best of both worlds' for Northern Ireland in Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Newstalk Newsfeed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has said the DUP does not want the best of both worlds for Northern Ireland. He was speaking at a Dáil debate on the proposed Brexit text negotiated between the EU and UK. The Dáil is debating the draft agreement, which was backed by the British cabinet last week. It comes as British Prime Minister Theresa May held talks with European Commission President Jean-Claude Juncker in Brussels. At the start of the debate, Mr Varadkar hit out at the DUP - which is propping up British Prime Minister Theresa May's Westminster government. He said trying to argue with DUP lea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newstalk.com">Newstalk Newsfeed</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach admits carbon taxes will rise, but not by €3,000 per household - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/taoiseach-admits-carbon-taxes-will-rise-but-not-by-3000-per-household-886849.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGI7KIW-73l-g1MZ46hCf28qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 13:39:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/taoiseach-admits-carbon-taxes-will-rise-but-not-by-3000-per-household-886849.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach admits carbon taxes will rise, but not by €3,000 per household&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has said ESRI predictions that households will have to pay carbon taxes amounting to €3,000 in future years were "way off the mark", but that a regime to increase such levies was needed. Mr Varadkar said he favoured a Canada-type model and agreed with suggestions by the Greens of gradual increases over several years possibly quadrupling carbon charges to €80 a tonne. The debate comes after the Economic and Social Research Institute warned in a report that there needs to be a 15-fold increase in carbon taxes - up to €3,000 a home - by 2030 to help Ireland meet EU targe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach denies early election plan and accuses Fianna Fáil of dragging out agreement talks - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/taoiseach-early-election-4346101-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsZnXN80oeEAusaMcYF32wqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 16:29:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/taoiseach-early-election-4346101-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach denies early election plan and accuses Fianna Fáil of dragging out agreement talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TAOISEACH LEO VARADKAR said a new confidence and supply deal could be agreed between Fine Gael and Fianna Fáil, and accused Micheál Martin’s party of dragging out the agreement talks. Speaking to RTÉ’s This Week programme, Varadkar denied that he was planning for an early election, despite the poll numbers remaining in his party’s favour and a major tax pledge made yesterday if Fine Gael had its way over the next five Budgets. While Tánaiste Simon Coveney said the party was ready for an election at its Ard Fheis yesterday, Varadkar said today: “I am not planning for an early election.” With...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Ministers insist Fine Gael is ‘election-ready’ with posters waiting - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ministers-insist-fine-gael-is-election-ready-with-posters-waiting-886192.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP8lBbtqBsCGFNGFsYfqn5gqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ministers-insist-fine-gael-is-election-ready-with-posters-waiting-886192.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ministers insist Fine Gael is ‘election-ready’ with posters waiting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A chorus of Fine Gael ministers has insisted the party is “election-ready”, with posters set to be printed at any time. Several ministers speaking at the party’s ard fheis were bullish in their talk about an early election happening and were deeply critical of Fianna Fáil over its failure to agree to continue to support them. Tánaiste Simon Coveney, Health Minister Simon Harris, and Justice Minister Charlie Flanagan were among the members of Cabinet who said the party is fully prepared should a snap election be called. Tánaiste Simon Coveney and Housing Minister Eoghan Murphy chatting at th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>New Confidence and Supply deal could be wrapped up quickly 'if both sides wanted to' - Taoiseach - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/new-confidence-and-supply-deal-could-be-wrapped-up-quickly-if-both-sides-wanted-to-taoiseach-37540180.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGq8Y2njpzDJQvjSx1ELDp4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:06:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/new-confidence-and-supply-deal-could-be-wrapped-up-quickly-if-both-sides-wanted-to-taoiseach-37540180.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Confidence and Supply deal could be wrapped up quickly 'if both sides wanted to' - Taoiseach&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A NEW Confidence and Supply arrangement could be wrapped up very quickly 'if both parties wanted to' do a deal, Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has said. The Fine Gael leader was speaking after senior members of his party used the Fine Gael Ard Fhéis to ramp up pressure on Fianna Fáil to begin talks on a new deal. Currently there is a review underway of how the arrangement has worked to date. But various Fine Gael ministers have said the talks must move on to the next phase, something which has been rejected by Micheál Martin, who says the review has not concluded. Speaking on The Week in Politics o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Varadkar says he can give €3bn tax cut and spend too - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/varadkar-says-he-can-give-3bn-tax-cut-and-spend-too-37541429.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKjxBOnA76RIBEENh3Ln8awqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/varadkar-says-he-can-give-3bn-tax-cut-and-spend-too-37541429.html" target="_blank"&gt;Varadkar says he can give €3bn tax cut and spend too&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar is defending his new tax policy of promising a major giveaway for middle-income earners. In a move reminiscent of Celtic Tiger-era party conferences, the Fine Gael leader told his Ard Fheis that if re-elected he will cut tax bills by up to €3,000. By raising tax bands over five years, the Taoiseach pledged to bring the rate at which workers start paying the top rate to €50,000. At present, people can earn up €35,550 before being hit with the higher tax rate. The move would see an additional €3,000 in the pocket of someone earning €50,000 who would pay 20pc on their en...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Micheal Martin rubbishes Varadkar's tax promise, says it could cost up to €4bn - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/micheal-martin-rubbishes-varadkars-tax-promise-says-cost-could-be-up-to-4bn-886101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJjXr3Jku_ziXpaNi0k2kZEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 08:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/micheal-martin-rubbishes-varadkars-tax-promise-says-cost-could-be-up-to-4bn-886101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Micheal Martin rubbishes Varadkar's tax promise, says it could cost up to €4bn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latest: Fianna Fáil leader Micheal Martin has rubbished Taoiseach Leo Varadkar's big tax promise, saying it could cost up to €4bn to implement, writes By Daniel McConnell, Political Editor. . Mr Martin said he would not be getting into “matching” tax promises. On Mr Varadkar's plan, he said: “That could be anything from €1.6bn to €4bn of a pledge. Do you remember the last General Election, the big promise? US style taxes, the pledge of 'we will abolish the USC'. That was a €4bn promise abandoned as soon as they got into Government. So cool the jets, as someone said earlier.” “It was an elec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>McDonald accused of 'hypocrisy' after missing Presidential inauguration for fundraising dinner - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/mcdonald-accused-of-hypocrisy-after-missing-presidential-inauguration-for-us-fundraising-dinner-886615.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDd03brqQDJYlxSRgxjRkkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/mcdonald-accused-of-hypocrisy-after-missing-presidential-inauguration-for-us-fundraising-dinner-886615.html" target="_blank"&gt;McDonald accused of 'hypocrisy' after missing Presidential inauguration for fundraising dinner&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sinn Féin President Mary Lou McDonald has been accused of “rank hypocrisy” after missing the Presidential inauguration on November 11 to attend a $400 plate dinner in New York. During Leaders' Questions, Ms McDonald sought to highlight pending changes to how unvouched expenses are treated by the Revenue Commissioners, saying this would impact some of the lowest paid workers in the country. She compared the planned clamp down to the soft treatment given to the super wealthy by Fine Gael in office. Ms McDonald raised Mr Varadkar's Ard Fheis promise to deliver five years of income tax cuts if ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Laura Larkin: 'Everyone's ready for election - but UK chaos keeps it on back-burner' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/laura-larkin-everyones-ready-for-election-but-uk-chaos-keeps-it-on-backburner-37541420.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFlarUFLcxtR2bULZXjts_sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/laura-larkin-everyones-ready-for-election-but-uk-chaos-keeps-it-on-backburner-37541420.html" target="_blank"&gt;Laura Larkin: 'Everyone's ready for election - but UK chaos keeps it on back-burner'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were barely on the M50 and the pretence about not wanting an election was dropped - the message from the opening moments at the Fine Gael Ard Fheis was that it is election-ready. It was a threat, not a promise - but there were promises aplenty too. Tax cuts that would cause Charles Haughey to blush, a new focus on climate change, and even a review of history being an optional subject in schools. It was all good natured "banter"; the photos for the posters were taken, the printing machine was well-oiled, according to senior ministers. The Opposition could criticise "our Leo" all they li...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Latest: Govt hits out at 'Mystic Micheál' Martin's comments - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/fine-gaels-megaphone-diplomacy-does-not-work-with-fianna-fail-martin-says-886300.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED7DohT7Il9qrHPfmaoTB9sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 13:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.breakingnews.ie/ireland/fine-gaels-megaphone-diplomacy-does-not-work-with-fianna-fail-martin-says-886300.html" target="_blank"&gt;Latest: Govt hits out at 'Mystic Micheál' Martin's comments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Elaine Loughlin, Political Correspondent Update 1.38pm: The Government has attacked "mystic" Micheál Martin claiming he can read the minds of Fine Gael Ministers but refuses to provide any clarity on confidence and supply himself. Both Taoiseach Leo Varadkar and Health Minister Simon Harris hit out at the Fianna Fáil leader calling on him to "get on with it" and agree to a new deal to keep the Government in place until the summer of 2020. Their criticism came after Mr Martin took a swipe at Fine Gael, claiming that the Taoiseach is coming under pressure from some of his ministers to call...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.breakingnews.ie">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Ireland will miss EU emission targets for 2020, admits Taoiseach - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ireland-will-miss-eu-emission-targets-for-2020-admits-leo-886731.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMeObTsqIJtJFaEftr-Wfe0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 05:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ireland-will-miss-eu-emission-targets-for-2020-admits-leo-886731.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ireland will miss EU emission targets for 2020, admits Taoiseach&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has admitted Ireland will miss EU carbon emission reduction targets for 2020 and could face having to pay hundreds of millions of euro for credits. Mr Varadkar told the Dáil Ireland hopes to meet carbon reduction targets for 2030. “CO2 emissions are lower than they were, notwithstanding a significant increase in population, but we are nowhere near close to reaching our target of a 20% reduction by 2020,” he said. “With the reduction likely to be closer to 1%, it is evident that we will not reach our 2020 targets but I do think we will meet our 2030 targets. I am deter...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Harris says election likely unless Fianna Fáil extend Confidence and Supply deal - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/harris-says-election-likely-unless-fianna-fail-extend-confidence-and-supply-deal-886053.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENhPPHuc0qElEFY8H0nGv1EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 15:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/harris-says-election-likely-unless-fianna-fail-extend-confidence-and-supply-deal-886053.html" target="_blank"&gt;Harris says election likely unless Fianna Fáil extend Confidence and Supply deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health Minister Simon Harris has joined the chorus of Fine Gael ministers who have threatened a general election unless Fianna Fáil sign up to a deal to extend the life of the minority government. Simon Harris speaking at the Fine Gael conference today. Photo: Leah Farrell/RollingNews.ie He called on Fianna Fáil to stop delaying Confidence and Supply talks, warning the current deal has only days left to run. Mr Harris, speaking at the Fine Gael Ard Fheis in CityWest, said the “snails' pace” of the ongoing talks between the parties is no longer tolerable and a conclusion must be arrived at. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Govt's focus is on Brexit, not elections - Varadkar - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1117/1011525-fine-gael-ard-fheis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELsPeFDEAlyzDHxfAf0v_VQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 22:37:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1117/1011525-fine-gael-ard-fheis/" target="_blank"&gt;Govt's focus is on Brexit, not elections - Varadkar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Taoiseach has said that the focus of the Government must be on Brexit and not on elections. He said he is not planning a pre-Christmas election but it is not entirely in his hands. He also stated that Fine Gael has not set a deadline for the completion of the Confidence and Supply review talks, but he said he is interested in getting into "deliverables" very soon. Minister Regina Doherty, who is part of the Fine Gael delegation in the review talks, said it is time to move on to more substantive talks and they will come to a head in a few weeks' time. The Taoiseach reiterated that the Fi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach promises five years of tax cuts... Fianna Fáil hit back and say 'cool the jets' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/taoiseach-promises-five-years-of-tax-cuts-fianna-fil-hit-back-and-say-cool-the-jets-37538746.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPh29G7aHkeRmLe7h2oIJM8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 17:39:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/taoiseach-promises-five-years-of-tax-cuts-fianna-fil-hit-back-and-say-cool-the-jets-37538746.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach promises five years of tax cuts... Fianna Fáil hit back and say 'cool the jets'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has promised five years of income tax cuts if Fine Gael wins the next election. As talks on the extension of his minority government’s lifespan enter their fourth week, Mr Varadkar has massively upped the stakes. He used his televised Ard Fheis speech to turn on Fianna Fail, saying they are "not easy" to negotiate with. "We know what we inherited from Fianna Fáil – broke banks unable to lend, ghost estates, Pyrite, Mica, Priory Hall, hundreds of thousands of people in negative equity, mortgage arrears, and hundreds of thousands of construction workers on the dole," he...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach promises to raise top rate of tax to €50k over next five years - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/leo-varadkar-income-tax-fg-ard-fheis-4345216-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHbLJdMHqonB2SmTC0YZT-UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 17:30:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/leo-varadkar-income-tax-fg-ard-fheis-4345216-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach promises to raise top rate of tax to €50k over next five years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TAOISEACH LEO VARADKAR has committed to increase the point at which people pay the top rate of tax to €50,000 for a single person or €100,000 for a two income couple over the next five budgets. It’s being dubbed as an election promise, given the central message coming out of the Fine Gael Ard Fheis is that the party is election ready. The Taoiseach proposes to rise the threshold by €2,500 each year over the next five years. In October’s Budget, the government tinkered with the bands, increasing the entry point to the higher rate of income tax (40%) for all earners by €750, raising it from €...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Brexit breakthrough: cabinet to 'consider developments' as text on how to manage the Irish border 'agreed' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/brexit-breakthrough-cabinet-to-consider-developments-as-text-on-how-to-manage-the-irish-border-agreed-37524355.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6u9rErbbSUw4Y7MTZCIiUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 16:13:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/brexit-breakthrough-cabinet-to-consider-developments-as-text-on-how-to-manage-the-irish-border-agreed-37524355.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit breakthrough: cabinet to 'consider developments' as text on how to manage the Irish border 'agreed'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A MAJOR breakthrough on how to manage the Irish border after Brexit has been achieved. The EU Taskforce and British government representatives agreed to the ‘backstop’ late last night, it has emerged. While government sources in Dublin were this evening urging “calm”, it is understood the text is now under active consideration by UK Prime Minister Theresa May. She decided not to present any details of a deal to her Cabinet this morning. And in the Dáil, Taoiseach Leo Varadkar attempted to play down reports that an agreement on the Irish question has been reached. He repeatedly refused to an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>John Downing: 'Micheál Martin has shown some steel – but he still risks missing the big prize' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/john-downing-michel-martin-has-shown-some-steel-but-he-still-risks-missing-the-big-prize-37511975.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHE2DeFWibLdAIBL1x-rhoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:45:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/john-downing-michel-martin-has-shown-some-steel-but-he-still-risks-missing-the-big-prize-37511975.html" target="_blank"&gt;John Downing: 'Micheál Martin has shown some steel – but he still risks missing the big prize'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;To many people away from the Leinster House “political bubble” it looked like a storm in an eggcup. But sometimes the smaller dramas can reveal a lot. And there was a funny side to this little Fianna Fáil melodrama. Two political tearaways, Éamon Ó Cúiv, now aged 68, and Senator Mark Daly, aged 45, literally made a break for the border one night last month. The pair went to Omagh in Co Tyrone to launch the Fianna Fáil election campaign of Cllr Sorcha McAnespy for next year’s Northern Ireland local elections. On the plus side, the party has committed itself to organising in the North in time...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Kevin Doyle: 'No 'rabbit in the hat' but this buck stops with Leo' - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/kevin-doyle-no-rabbit-in-the-hat-but-this-buck-stops-with-leo-37517380.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPw_D6J5nVtK5vpqOMXWRJoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/opinion/comment/kevin-doyle-no-rabbit-in-the-hat-but-this-buck-stops-with-leo-37517380.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kevin Doyle: 'No 'rabbit in the hat' but this buck stops with Leo'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few reports have been as eagerly awaited as the one which lands on Taoiseach Leo Varadkar's desk this week. It is not the final Brexit deal, nor a bargaining plan for the confidence and supply arrangement - but the impact of Peter Smyth's assessment of the National Broadband Plan could be just as big for this Government. When it comes to health, Mr Varadkar is able to rightly point out that Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin had his opportunity to fix the problems and didn't. On housing, Fine Gael is quick to remind us that it was 13 years of Fianna Fáil relying on construction taxes which l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Éamon Ó Cuív sacked from Fianna Fáil frontbench for launching NI candidate without permission - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/eamon-ocuiv-sacked-4330260-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB-YWOkVQxoPlbnRcpFGAbgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 17:16:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/eamon-ocuiv-sacked-4330260-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Éamon Ó Cuív sacked from Fianna Fáil frontbench for launching NI candidate without permission&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIANNA FÁÍL LEADER Micheál Martin has sacked Eamon Ó Cuív from the Fianna Fáil frontbench after he went rogue and announced a local election candidate in Tyrone without Martin’s permission. A party statement issued this afternoon states that “Party Leader and Spokesperson on Northern Ireland Micheál Martin TD met last evening with Deputy Éamon Ó Cuív”. It adds: “During the course of that meeting Deputy Ó Cuív made it clear that he was aware in advance of plans to hold an unauthorised launch of a candidate and agreed to participate in the event. “In light of this information, regretfully, De...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Éamon Ó Cuív escapes demotion after Mark Daly sanctioned - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/eamon-o-cuiv-escapes-demotion-after-mark-daly-sanctioned-883946.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOOl4eXrkb3R3pAo5nelwqAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 05:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/eamon-o-cuiv-escapes-demotion-after-mark-daly-sanctioned-883946.html" target="_blank"&gt;Éamon Ó Cuív escapes demotion after Mark Daly sanctioned&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil Galway West TD Éamon Ó Cuív appears to have escaped sanction from party leader Micheál Martin after the pair met face to face last night. It had been expected that Mr Ó Cuív would be sacked as the party’s rural affairs spokesman after senator Mark Daly was relieved of his double position of deputy Seanad leader and foreign affairs spokesman. However, party sources said that Mr Ó Cuív was not likely to be demoted, despite being a persistent thorn in the side of Mr Martin. The decision comes after Mr Daly and Mr Ó Cuív participated in an apparent launch of a party candidate in Nor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Ó Cuív in firing line over unveiling of first Fianna Fáil candidate in the North - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/cuv-in-firing-line-over-unveiling-of-first-fianna-fil-candidate-in-the-north-37505141.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFe7ZcOLy9FvDSHc-AWSzTkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/cuv-in-firing-line-over-unveiling-of-first-fianna-fil-candidate-in-the-north-37505141.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ó Cuív in firing line over unveiling of first Fianna Fáil candidate in the North&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-serving Fianna Fáil TD Éamon Ó Cuív was in the firing line last night over his involvement in the apparent unveiling of the party's first candidate for a Northern Ireland election. Mr Ó Cuív was central to organising an event which claimed to be the unveiling of former Sinn Féin councillor Sorcha McAnespy as Fianna Fáil's first election candidate in the North. Fianna Fáil issued a statement soon after the announcement, saying it was not an official event and insisted the party had not made a decision on running candidates in the North. The party later issued disciplinary proceedings ag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Daly 'accepts' sacking over NI candidate - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1107/1009313-mark-daly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN-7DxXYTC8Fmc3jOndTD3YqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wm5uhAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 14:38:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/politics/2018/1107/1009313-mark-daly/" target="_blank"&gt;Daly 'accepts' sacking over NI candidate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil Senator Mark Daly has said that he accepts the decision of Micheál Martin to sack him as the party's deputy Seanad leader and spokesperson for Foreign Affairs. The move follows Senator Daly and TD Éamon Ó Cuív's role in appearing to launch a Fianna Fáil candidate in Northern Ireland recently. Party Headquarters would later clarity that it had not endorsed the election launch of Fermanagh Councillor Sorcha McAnespy. Senator Daly said today that he would continue to work hard on behalf of his constituents. "In my position as foreign affairs spokesperson, for the last number of yea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Fianna Fail Senator stripped of title over involvement in candidate 'launch' in Northern Ireland - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/fianna-fail-senator-stripped-of-title-over-involvement-in-candidate-launch-in-northern-ireland-37502916.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGkoXtQjgG1ZDTb_h8imAd0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 14:10:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/fianna-fail-senator-stripped-of-title-over-involvement-in-candidate-launch-in-northern-ireland-37502916.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fianna Fail Senator stripped of title over involvement in candidate 'launch' in Northern Ireland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senator Mark Daly has been stripped of his role as deputy leader of the Seanad over his involvement in an event which alleged to announce Fianna Fail’s first candidate in Northern Ireland election. Mr Daly has also been stripped of his title as Fianna Fail’s Seanad spokesperson for Foreign Affairs as part of disciplinary action taken ordered by party leader Micheal Martin. Mr Daly along with Fianna Fail TD Eamon O’Cuiv used an event in Fermanagh to unveil former Sinn Fein councillor Sorhca McAnespy as the party’s first election candidate in the North. Soon after the unveiling, Fianna Fail i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>'Undermining' of fall-back plan to avoid hard border of 'grave concern' - Fianna Fail - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/undermining-of-fallback-plan-to-avoid-hard-border-of-grave-concern-fianna-fail-37499106.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBCIK2fGyPiudbhryWE2JysqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8wr8qiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 18:49:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/undermining-of-fallback-plan-to-avoid-hard-border-of-grave-concern-fianna-fail-37499106.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Undermining' of fall-back plan to avoid hard border of 'grave concern' - Fianna Fail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIANNA Fáil has said any “undermining” of the fall-back plan to avoid hard border in Ireland after Brexit is of “grave concern”. And the party’s business spokesman Billy Kelleher claimed that if Fianna Fáil had been involved in talks it would have tried to prevent the issue becoming “isolated” in the negotiations. Mr Kelleher also called on Taoiseach Leo Varadkar to clarify his remarks where expressed an openness to consider proposals for a review of any backstop arrangements. The proposal has been put forward by British prime minister Theresa May who is today seeking approval from her own ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach under fire for 'green jersey' demands in Brexit talks - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/taoiseach-under-fire-for-green-jersey-demands-in-brexit-talks-37501414.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPDsDKU5SUZ0KI6PSl4byMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 07:13:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/business/brexit/taoiseach-under-fire-for-green-jersey-demands-in-brexit-talks-37501414.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach under fire for 'green jersey' demands in Brexit talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TAOISEACH Leo Varadkar has come under fire for suggesting the Opposition and media should put on the ‘green jersey’ and unquestioningly support his Brexit strategy. Opposition leaders rounded on him after he announced he was open to the introduction of a review mechanism of the Brexit agreement. Independent.ie reported on the alarm which surrounded the backtrack on the Brexit backstop that would ensure there will be no border on the island of Ireland. But the Taoiseach’s officials have been extremely critical of media coverage and Opposition TDs whenever they perceive their commentary is no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach warns all hospital workers must work 'full whack' over Christmas holidays - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/taoiseach-warns-all-hospital-workers-must-work-full-whack-over-christmas-holidays-37500434.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA5Ozpic3M5unnXqATwjB7wqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 21:28:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/taoiseach-warns-all-hospital-workers-must-work-full-whack-over-christmas-holidays-37500434.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach warns all hospital workers must work 'full whack' over Christmas holidays&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has warned all hospital workers - including consultants, nurses and back-up staff – that they must work "at full whack" over the Christmas holidays. Mr Varadkar also specifically warned hospital consultant doctors and nurses, especially those in hospital emergency departments, they must not take leave in the first fortnight of the new year. The Taoiseach said this was the kind of winter plan needed to confront upcoming problems in the hospital accident and emergency departments. He defended the lack of a formal "winter plan" which Fianna Fáil leader, Micheál Martin, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach's 'Christmas holiday' comments were 'flippant and insensitive' to heath service workers - FF - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/taoiseachs-christmas-holiday-comments-were-flippant-and-insensitive-to-heath-service-workers-ff-37503974.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENMeNl9k_n0uIA6wa1HLsn0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 18:52:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/taoiseachs-christmas-holiday-comments-were-flippant-and-insensitive-to-heath-service-workers-ff-37503974.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach's 'Christmas holiday' comments were 'flippant and insensitive' to heath service workers - FF&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil have launched a blistering attack on the Taoiseach over his Christmas health service comments, claiming he was acting like "a radio chat show panellist". Frontbench spokesperson Billy Kelleher described the Taoiseach’s comments as "flippant and insensitive" to health service workers "who go above and beyond the call of duty every Christmas". Just minutes before his comments seeking to blame staff, the Taoiseach confirmed that the HSE is not attempting to implement a Winter Initiative this year because of the failure of previous initiatives. "If I was cynical, I’d wonder whether ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>'Absence of compassion' - Micheál Martin calls for medicinal cannabis to be legalised - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/absence-of-compassion-michel-martin-calls-for-medicinal-cannabis-to-be-legalised-37502800.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEquMy0ZiRMSWFsxMA7fx0QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 13:41:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/absence-of-compassion-michel-martin-calls-for-medicinal-cannabis-to-be-legalised-37502800.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Absence of compassion' - Micheál Martin calls for medicinal cannabis to be legalised&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who need the drug cannabis to help cope with illness and pain are suffering needlessly, Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin, has said. Mr Martin said special legislation for medicinal cannabis, proposed by People Before Profit TD, Gino Kenny, was withdrawn almost two years ago. This was because an official review was promised leading to better supervised access to the drug in Ireland on grounds of special medical need. He said that almost two years later nothing had changed and people, such as Cork woman Vera Twomey and her daughter Ava Barry, were forced to go to the Netherlands every...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Taoiseach directly calls on HSE not to sanction additional holidays for health staff over Christmas - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/taoiseach-directly-calls-on-hse-not-to-sanction-additional-holidays-for-health-staff-over-christmas-37502518.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYDvqBOD8LjW1nnQzg2BE8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 12:19:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/taoiseach-directly-calls-on-hse-not-to-sanction-additional-holidays-for-health-staff-over-christmas-37502518.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taoiseach directly calls on HSE not to sanction additional holidays for health staff over Christmas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TAOISEACH Leo Varadkar has directly called on the HSE not to sanction additional holidays for doctors and nurses over Christmas. Despite criticism from medical unions, the Taoiseach has today gone further in his demands for changes to way hospital operate their Christmas rosters. And he said while people might “misrepresent” his comments, he “speaks the truth”. “The situation is as simple as this: Every business, every industry, every service has a peak period of demand. “If you’re working retail it’s the week running up to Christmas. If you’re in education, it’s the first week or two of Se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Nurses and doctors should not be on Christmas holidays in the first weeks of January - Taoiseach - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/nurses-doctors-christmas-holidays-4326597-Nov2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJmME7hNUZuD4JBrhLXMBuwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 21:00:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/nurses-doctors-christmas-holidays-4326597-Nov2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Nurses and doctors should not be on Christmas holidays in the first weeks of January - Taoiseach&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TAOISEACH LEO VARADKAR has said consultant doctors and nurses should not be allowed to take Christmas holidays in the first week of the year in order to allow the health service avoid crisis-mode this winter. However, it is understood that no such instruction or circular has been issued to health service managers or hospitals about the proposals to the Christmas rosters. During Leaders’ Questions today, Fianna Fáil’s Micheál Martin asked the Taoiseach when the HSE Winter Plan would be announced. “Too many people, particularly the elderly, are suffering far too much in our emergency departme...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Ó Cuív and Daly unlikely to face party sanctions - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/cuv-and-daly-unlikely-to-face-party-sanctions-37473327.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMaZl2AUqwPrhs_ReMBLhgkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/cuv-and-daly-unlikely-to-face-party-sanctions-37473327.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ó Cuív and Daly unlikely to face party sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin has sent a "finger-wagging" letter to Éamon Ó Cuív and Mark Daly, warning them off any repeat of their party endorsement of a council candidate in the North. But the 14-line letter sent by email to the Galway West TD and Co Kerry Senator makes no reference to disciplinary sanctions. Controversy erupted last Thursday when photographs of the two Oireachtas members alongside Cllr Sorcha McAnespy with the Fianna Fáil logo were issued. The party promptly said the announcement of Ms McAnespy as a Fianna Fáil candidate for next year's local elections in the North ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>‘Fianna Fáil needs somebody like Peter Casey to shake it up,’ election runner-up insists - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fianna-fail-needs-somebody-like-peter-casey-to-shake-it-up-election-runner-up-insists-881943.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMqJdiyV0CyWIQ9r1iaZyucqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 03:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/fianna-fail-needs-somebody-like-peter-casey-to-shake-it-up-election-runner-up-insists-881943.html" target="_blank"&gt;‘Fianna Fáil needs somebody like Peter Casey to shake it up,’ election runner-up insists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil TDs have outright rejected Peter Casey’s calls to allow him to join and make him party leader, saying he would be “eaten alive” in real politics and will never be welcomed because he is “scapegoating” minority groups. Presidential candidate Peter Casey with his wife Helen at their home in Greencastle in North Donegal. (North West Newspix) A dozen Fianna Fáil TDs backed the party hierarchy’s decision to ignore Mr Casey’s takeover overtures, despite one TD privately saying the businessman’s controversial remarks about Travellers are “the one thing most of us think”. Mr Casey finis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Peter Casey says he wants Micheál Martin's job because the FF leader is 'too nice' to take on Leo Varadkar - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/peter-casey-fianna-fail-2-4311478-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHvqHbb2ZkvQ6jQJeDPWJr0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 13:57:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/peter-casey-fianna-fail-2-4311478-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Peter Casey says he wants Micheál Martin's job because the FF leader is 'too nice' to take on Leo Varadkar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETER CASEY HAS said that he wants to replace Micheál Martin as Fianna Fáil leader, claiming that Martin is “too nice” to challenge Taoiseach Leo Varadkar. The runner-up in the presidential election spoke yesterday about his desire to run for the Dáil in Donegal, despite Fianna Fáil already having chosen their two candidates for the next general election. Casey’s courting of Fianna Fáil was rejected by party deputies Timmy Dooley and Niall Collins but speaking on RTÉ’s Today with Sean O’Rourke, Casey said that he has yet to speak to the either of them or to Martin. “I can certainly understa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Peter Casey offered Renua leadership after FF rejection - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/peter-casey-offered-renua-leadership-after-ff-rejection-881973.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBR49qtgp8GTt08ntp1DGfcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 06:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/peter-casey-offered-renua-leadership-after-ff-rejection-881973.html" target="_blank"&gt;Peter Casey offered Renua leadership after FF rejection&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Presidential election runner-up Peter Casey’s audacious threat to set up a “new Fianna Fáil” if Micheál Martin blocks him from joining the party has led to Renua Ireland’s leader saying he “will not stand in the way” of him taking over his party. Renua told the Irish Examiner of the offer to Mr Casey after the businessman’s demand to join Fianna Fáil was definitively rejected by TDs. Speaking on RTÉ radio, Mr Casey said Fianna Fáil needs “somebody like Peter Casey to shake it up”. He finished second in the presidential race after a series of divisive remarks about Travellers and people on w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Ministers pressure Fianna Fáil for quick confidence and supply deal - Irish Examiner</title><link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ministers-pressure-fianna-fail-for-quick-confidence-and-supply-deal-882425.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOSB3vaxOlXXhet1h_n19Q0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyNLTATDN-jUwjbOhAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 05:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ministers-pressure-fianna-fail-for-quick-confidence-and-supply-deal-882425.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ministers pressure Fianna Fáil for quick confidence and supply deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Irish Examiner&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Juno McEnroe and Elaine Loughlin Ministers are increasing the pressure on Fianna Fáil to wrap up negotiations on a fresh confidence and supply deal in just a matter of weeks to safeguard the “stability” of the country. Fine Gael remains adamant that any new agreement must guarantee that Fianna Fáil will help keep the minority government in power until 2020. The demands come as the parties resume private talks today, reviewing progress under the existing three-year government support pact and looking towards a new deal. While Fianna Fáil is ruling out any deadlines or a rushed review, Fin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.irishexaminer.com">Irish Examiner</source></item><item><title>Fianna Fáil is urged not to 'close the door' on Peter Casey - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/fianna-fil-is-urged-not-to-close-the-door-on-peter-casey-37473326.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJszAGO31dKtuf7XWpss09wqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/fianna-fil-is-urged-not-to-close-the-door-on-peter-casey-37473326.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fianna Fáil is urged not to 'close the door' on Peter Casey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil's leadership has been accused of "closing the door too early" on the prospect of party membership for presidential runner-up Peter Casey. Mr Casey, who attracted almost one in four of the votes cast in Friday's presidential election, has further stirred things up by saying Fianna Fáil needed his leadership. He also said if he could not join the party he may form his own party calling it "new Fianna Fáil". The latest comments by the businessman-turned-politician were dismissed out of hand by several leading Fianna Fáil TDs who said his campaign comments about Travellers and peopl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Fine Gael, Fianna Fáil not looking for Casey candidacy - RTÉ News</title><link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1029/1007370-casey/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIChu-IUZPgJmDkoIWgpmHAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowyOSfCTDbw28wrJ2hAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 22:42:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rte.ie/news/2018/1029/1007370-casey/" target="_blank"&gt;Fine Gael, Fianna Fáil not looking for Casey candidacy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RTÉ News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senior figures in both Fianna Fáil and Fine Gael have said there would be no place for Presidential candidate Peter Casey in their parties. The businessman, who finished second in the election, has said he would like to either join Fianna Fáil or else form his own political party, which he dubbed the "New Fianna Fáil". Speaking this afternoon, Mr Casey said he would "be more aligned to Fianna Fáil than any other party, so that would be a logical step in that direction." He added: "I heard in the papers today that they are full up and not taking membership ... I think what it actually is, is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rte.ie">RTÉ News</source></item><item><title>Ó Cuiv and Daly face sanction for launching Fianna Fáil in North - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/cuiv-and-daly-face-sanction-for-launching-fianna-fil-in-north-37464273.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPLOEkDv7x6cQuI7y0s8TZAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/cuiv-and-daly-face-sanction-for-launching-fianna-fil-in-north-37464273.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ó Cuiv and Daly face sanction for launching Fianna Fáil in North&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fianna Fáil bosses are considering whether to discipline former minister Éamon Ó Cuiv and Senator Mark Daly for "bringing the party into disrepute". Party leader Micheál Martin is said to be "fuming" over the decision by the pair to publicly present Sorcha McAnespy as Fianna Fáil's first ever candidate in the Northern Ireland council elections. Ms McAnespy ran for election in 2014 as a Sinn Féin councillor but subsequently left the party, alleging there was a culture of misogyny. Photos were issued on Thursday night of the trio posing with Fianna Fáil-branded election posters carrying Ms Mc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Fionnán Sheahan: Mary-Lou the biggest loser as contenders fail to ignite - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/presidential-election/fionnn-sheahan-marylou-the-biggest-loser-as-contenders-fail-to-ignite-37463983.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFvax_qGBFDZ0QbmY0e5NjMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 22:30:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/presidential-election/fionnn-sheahan-marylou-the-biggest-loser-as-contenders-fail-to-ignite-37463983.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fionnán Sheahan: Mary-Lou the biggest loser as contenders fail to ignite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUST because you think you’re God’s gift doesn’t mean the voting public are going to agree with you. No matter how gruelling these Presidential campaigns become, there seems to be no shortage of politico-masochists willing to subject themselves to the pain and anguish. The conspiracy theory was that the three ‘Dragons’ Den’ businessmen were running in an effort to create a voting pact and attack Michael D Higgins. Seán Gallagher was a household candidate from his previous run for the Presidency. Gavin Duffy was reasonably well-known from television. Gallagher spent half the campaign whining...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item><item><title>Eamon Ó Cuiv goes rogue to announce candidate for NI elections without party backing - TheJournal.ie</title><link>http://www.thejournal.ie/ff-northern-ireland-4306151-Oct2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHETfLQbkNniL6IXTjsU3ScqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowv-qfCTD6yG8wj86hAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 22:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thejournal.ie/ff-northern-ireland-4306151-Oct2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Eamon Ó Cuiv goes rogue to announce candidate for NI elections without party backing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TheJournal.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE WAS UTTER confusion within Fianna Fáil this evening as a candidate for the next local elections in the Northern Ireland was announced without the full backing of the party. At an event in Tyrone this evening, councillor Sorcha McAnespy, who is already a member of the party’s national executive, was announced as the party’s candidate in the local elections. The media, including TheJournal.ie, reported the story after senior party members made official, on-the-record statements about the announcement. Standing next to TD Éamon Ó Cuív, the spokesperson on Regional Development, Rural Affa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thejournal.ie">TheJournal.ie</source></item><item><title>Varadkar rebuffs FF's 'ill-conceived offer' for a Brexit truce - Independent.ie</title><link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/varadkar-rebuffs-ffs-illconceived-offer-for-a-brexit-truce-37460335.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhvJY4YaPHK8e2kC5xJznQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowseyfCTDMyG8w99CiAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/politics/varadkar-rebuffs-ffs-illconceived-offer-for-a-brexit-truce-37460335.html" target="_blank"&gt;Varadkar rebuffs FF's 'ill-conceived offer' for a Brexit truce&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent.ie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taoiseach Leo Varadkar has refused the offer of a Brexit truce from Fianna Fáil on the grounds it would hand Brexiteers control over the timing of the next election. Representatives from the two main parties met for the first time yesterday to see if they could agree an extension to the confidence and supply arrangement. In advance of the talks, Fianna Fáil leader Micheál Martin was warned by some TDs that he should stop propping up Fine Gael and contest a general election. At a Fianna Fáil parliamentary party meeting in Leinster House, Mr Martin was told the minority Government was a "fail...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.ie">Independent.ie</source></item></channel></rss>