<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Maritime boundary - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR1p3YUdKbWVCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:28:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Ghana-Togo maritime boundary negotiations fail | General News 2018-12-05 - GhanaWeb</title><link>https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/Ghana-Togo-maritime-boundary-negotiations-fail-706423</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780127150370</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:01:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/Ghana-Togo-maritime-boundary-negotiations-fail-706423" target="_blank"&gt;Ghana-Togo maritime boundary negotiations fail | General News 2018-12-05&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GhanaWeb&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/business/Ghana-Togo-maritime-boundary-negotiations-fail-706401" target="_blank"&gt;Ghana-Togo maritime boundary negotiations fail | Business News 2018-12-05&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GhanaWeb&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWlpd3V1bGpZQU1FZTBfQmQ4am95QktLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ghanaweb.com">GhanaWeb</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/-RCpoKfCnrg5tImN8oJaI-Uzrnx2aCU8VTxTyCNq6-saInbveYwoyqXMaJVpuJf0OYZBIqcS6ixNmTsSHrZc3RQ-Av2gLw=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Philippines wants less confrontation in favor of more trade with China - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/business/396077-philippines-china-trade-economy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH6NV5eNZz_rcxOaWXm_z14qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwroQo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 09:29:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/business/396077-philippines-china-trade-economy/" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines wants less confrontation in favor of more trade with China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manilla has chosen to set aside its maritime border dispute with Beijing in the South China Sea and focus on building economic links, according to the Philippines’ trade minister. “I credit it to the wisdom of our president [Rodrigo Duterte] to really be more realistic and practical, to consider the positive points of having a relationship with China renewed,” Philippine Secretary of Trade and Industry Ramon Lopez told the South China Morning Post. “He has mentioned in many of his statements that why fight China when we can set aside the differences and focus on areas of cooperation, focus ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Australia and Timor-Leste strike deal to end bitter maritime boundary row - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-02/timor-leste-maritime-boundary-with-australia-agreement/8866776</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDNHJEkOdREMyrKAIvoG8aEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 08:01:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-02/timor-leste-maritime-boundary-with-australia-agreement/8866776" target="_blank"&gt;Australia and Timor-Leste strike deal to end bitter maritime boundary row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia and Timor-Leste have resolved their bitter and long-running dispute over maritime boundaries in the Timor Sea, in what is being described as a "landmark day" in the relationship between the two nations. The Permanent Court of Arbitration in The Hague today announced the parties reached an agreement on Wednesday over the disputed territory, which contains large oil and gas deposits worth an estimated $40 billion. Foreign Minister Julie Bishop hailed the breakthrough as a "landmark day in the relationship" between Timor-Leste and Australia. "This agreement, which supports the nation...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Israel and Lebanon clash over maritime border amid oil interest - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0250eed4-1082-11e7-b030-768954394623</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjMTAM5Bdd6sHAhm6Z0UY8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 04:30:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0250eed4-1082-11e7-b030-768954394623" target="_blank"&gt;Israel and Lebanon clash over maritime border amid oil interest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Israeli attempt to establish sovereignty over a disputed area of the Mediterranean has angered Lebanon and put the two countries at odds when both are trying to attract foreign investors in oil and gas. The disagreement over the maritime border comes at a time of rising tensions between Israel and Hizbollah, the Lebanese militant group, and serves as a reminder of regional geopolitical risk as both Israel and Lebanon — two enemy states — want to secure multibillion-dollar energy investments. The dispute stretches back years, but has burst into the open in recent days after it was reveale...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Australia, East Timor reach agreement on maritime border - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-timor/australia-east-timor-reach-agreement-on-maritime-border-idUSKCN1BD085</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECnxIHpkS1nFFLttu-X1_KkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 07:24:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-timor/australia-east-timor-reach-agreement-on-maritime-border-idUSKCN1BD085" target="_blank"&gt;Australia, East Timor reach agreement on maritime border&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Joseph Hinchliffe and Anthony Deutsch MELBOURNE/THE HAGUE (Reuters) - Australia and East Timor have reached a breakthrough agreement on a maritime border, ending a decade-old row between the two nations that has stalled a $40 billion offshore gas project. The Permanent Court of Arbitration in The Hague announced on Saturday that the neighboring countries had reached an agreement "on the central elements of a maritime boundary delimitation between them in the Timor Sea" – but that details would remain confidential until the deal was finalised. Arbitration began last year and the talks, ho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Israeli bill redefining maritime border with Lebanon labelled a ‘declaration of war’ - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/israel-lebanon-maritime-border-bill-redefine-move-declaration-war-parliament-annex-860-square-km-a7648476.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDm8QBkQ_J316G15z4ePyzQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 15:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/israel-lebanon-maritime-border-bill-redefine-move-declaration-war-parliament-annex-860-square-km-a7648476.html" target="_blank"&gt;Israeli bill redefining maritime border with Lebanon labelled a ‘declaration of war’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lebanese politicians have reacted with anger over a proposed Israeli parliament bill which would redraw the current highly sensitive maritime border with Lebanon. Israel is seeking to annex a zone of 860 square kilometres (330 square miles) of disputed waters between the two neighbours which is believed to be rich in natural gas reserves, Israeli newspaper Yedioth Ahronoth reported on Monday. The move comes after Lebanon’s government - formed at the end of 2016 after two years of political deadlock - recently advertised commercial tenders for oil and gas exploration in the same stretch of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Indonesia renames part of S. China Sea, Beijing calls move ‘meaningless’ - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/396355-indonesia-south-china-sea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPoRw5dFP28RbR09MFptMSwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 15:39:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/396355-indonesia-south-china-sea/" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia renames part of S. China Sea, Beijing calls move ‘meaningless’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia has renamed part of the South China Sea, reaffirming its position that Beijing’s claims to the waterway infringe on its exclusive economic zone. China says the renaming is “totally meaningless.” The country renamed the northern reaches of its exclusive economic zone in the South China Sea on Friday, choosing instead to call it the North Natuna Sea. The Ministry of Maritime Affairs unveiled a map with the new name on Friday. “We want to update the naming of the sea we gave a new name in line with the usual practice: the North Natuna Sea,” the ministry's deputy of maritime sovereign...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Asserting sovereignty, Indonesia renames part of South China Sea - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-politics-map-idUSKBN19Z0YQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEe11E095pPtuK0B8V7Pq98qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 09:58:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-politics-map-idUSKBN19Z0YQ" target="_blank"&gt;Asserting sovereignty, Indonesia renames part of South China Sea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Tom Allard and Bernadette Christina Munthe JAKARTA (Reuters) - Indonesia renamed the northern reaches of its exclusive economic zone in the South China Sea as the North Natuna Sea on Friday, the latest act of resistance by Southeast Asian nations to China's territorial ambitions in the maritime region. Seen by analysts as an assertion of Indonesian sovereignty, part of the renamed sea is claimed by China under its contentious maritime boundary, known as the 'nine-dash line', that encompasses most of the resource-rich sea. Several Southeast Asian states dispute China's territorial claims ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>East Timorese president-elect to push for new boundary with Australia - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-05-11/east-timor-president-to-push-for-new-maritime-boundary/8514800</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKsfr088GdojO2mHBxNe350qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 23:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-05-11/east-timor-president-to-push-for-new-maritime-boundary/8514800" target="_blank"&gt;East Timorese president-elect to push for new boundary with Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;East Timor's relationship with Australia is too important to dramatically change under its new leader, according to former President Jose Ramos-Horta. However, he also said President-elect Francisco Guterres, also known as "Lu-Olo", will renew his country's push for a maritime boundary halfway between Timor and Australia Australia and East Timor are currently renegotiating their boundary, after a treaty was torn up when it emerged Australian spy agencies had bugged Timorese offices during the negotiations. That now-defunct treaty put 80 per cent of the Greater Sunrise oil and gas field, wor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>China hails 'golden period' in relations with Philippines - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-philippines-idUSKBN19K0T9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHTcqq-h94VBKB4up2C61NwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 07:58:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-philippines-idUSKBN19K0T9" target="_blank"&gt;China hails 'golden period' in relations with Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (Reuters) - Relations between China and the Philippines have entered a "golden period of fast development", Chinese Foreign Minister Wang Yi said on Thursday, touting growth in trade ties and bilateral efforts to settle disputes in the South China Sea. Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte has opted to court China for its business and investment and avoid the rows over maritime sovereignty that dogged his predecessors. Duterte has faced criticism at home for being what some people see as too soft on China over the long-running territorial dispute, but he considers his approach to be ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Oil interest heats up maritime dispute between Israel and Lebanon - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/business/382576-israel-lebanon-maritime-oil/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHy3zzE_02p6Nui8X18u2YkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwroQo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 14:32:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/business/382576-israel-lebanon-maritime-oil/" target="_blank"&gt;Oil interest heats up maritime dispute between Israel and Lebanon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A long-running dispute between Israel and Lebanon over a maritime border in the Mediterranean Sea has reached boiling point as both sides want to secure multibillion-dollar energy investments from the oil and gas rich area. Lebanese politicians have reacted with anger over a bill in the Israeli parliament that would seek to establish the country’s sovereignty over the territory. Israeli officials said they aim to resolve the dispute through dialogue and mediation but also need to assert their rights after Lebanon’s decision to put out tenders for the seabed exploration work. “The Lebanese g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>East Timor's Gas Dream Is Doomed, ConocoPhillips And Woodside Have Failed - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/damonevans/2016/12/12/east-timors-gas-dream-is-doomed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB-YwsA_zN2XTk8RDQRd_OEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 04:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/damonevans/2016/12/12/east-timors-gas-dream-is-doomed/" target="_blank"&gt;East Timor's Gas Dream Is Doomed, ConocoPhillips And Woodside Have Failed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;East Timor independence hero Xanana Gusmao remains the de facto powerbroker in government. (AP Photo/Kandhi Barnez) The government of East Timor and international oil companies, including ConocoPhillips and Woodside Energy, are responsible for failing to progress the development of the Greater Sunrise gas fields, in the Timor Sea. Greater Sunrise’s gas reserves are potentially worth more than $8 billion to the southeast Asian nation, which is almost entirely dependent on petroleum revenue from its only producing fields at the Bayu-Undan project in the Timor Sea. But as I wrote recently, wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Indonesia, Philippines jointly patrol Celebes Sea to cut off militants - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-indonesia-patrol-idUSKBN19N08U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH-KF9rP03Tw4mX0HMuLjNUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 08:43:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-indonesia-patrol-idUSKBN19N08U" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia, Philippines jointly patrol Celebes Sea to cut off militants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA (Reuters) - The Philippines and Indonesia will jointly patrol the Celebes Sea this week to stop Islamist militants reaching the Philippines' restive southern island of Mindanao, where rebels have seized a city, an army spokesman said on Sunday. The joint patrol is aimed at strengthening border security and improving interoperability, military spokesman Major Ezra Balagtey said in a statement. The two countries' warships will sail from the Philippines' Davao city on Thursday. "The coordinated patrol ... is intended to strengthen the security of the Davao Gulf and the common boundary o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Costa Rica sues Nicaragua over alleged territory violation - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-costa-rica-nicaragua-idUSKBN1502JC</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJkODjl0LRlZNvkcel_LiAEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 23:51:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-costa-rica-nicaragua-idUSKBN1502JC" target="_blank"&gt;Costa Rica sues Nicaragua over alleged territory violation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN JOSE (Reuters) - Costa Rica's government said on Monday it has filed a complaint against Nicaragua at the International Court of Justice for establishing a military post on its territory, heightening the risk of renewed tensions between the two nations. Costa Rican foreign minister Manuel Gonzalez said Nicaragua had occupied a beach on Isla Calero in northeastern Costa Rica in November 2016, a virtually uninhabited area where both countries have a historic border dispute. "(Nicaragua) has installed a military post in a small strip of that Costa Rican territory. We took diplomatic steps ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>East Timor drops spying case against Australia - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-01-24/east-timor-drops-its-spying-case-against-australia/8209400</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHpYO7fYPYUebbj0iPwOxwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 10:11:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-01-24/east-timor-drops-its-spying-case-against-australia/8209400" target="_blank"&gt;East Timor drops spying case against Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;East Timor has dropped its spying case against Australia as part of negotiations to resolve the long-running dispute over permanent maritime boundaries in the Timor Sea. After a week of conciliation talks in Singapore, both countries announced East Timor had agreed to drop the spying case as part of the "good faith" negotiations to resolve the underlying disagreement over maritime boundaries. In a joint statement, they also said they would aim to resolve permanent maritime boundaries by September this year. The talks are a result of East Timor's move last year to take Australia to the Unite...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Push to build Greater Sunrise gas plant in East Timor 'doomed to fail' - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-01-12/east-timor-gas-pipe-dream/8176482</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAhEUTSrCv403dV5gN9o6xkqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 05:53:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-01-12/east-timor-gas-pipe-dream/8176482" target="_blank"&gt;Push to build Greater Sunrise gas plant in East Timor 'doomed to fail'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Political and energy analysts have expressed serious doubts that East Timor will ever be able to benefit from a major gas project unless it changes its policy. East Timor and the Australian Government on Monday announced they would abandon a 10-year-old treaty on maritime borders. Audio: Gas and energy experts say processing Greater Sunrise gas in East Timor is not viable (ABC News) The 2006 treaty was an agreement that a freeze of 50 years be put on negotiations for a permanent maritime border in the Timor Sea. Within the area is the large and high quality Greater Sunrise gas field, which ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Turkey says it will not tolerate shift in Greek maritime border - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-greece-diplomacy/turkey-says-it-will-not-tolerate-shift-in-greek-maritime-border-idUSKCN1MX11W</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFc1DHZa8pw3lWS_Ro1cCDUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 11:47:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-greece-diplomacy/turkey-says-it-will-not-tolerate-shift-in-greek-maritime-border-idUSKCN1MX11W" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey says it will not tolerate shift in Greek maritime border&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey warned Greece on Tuesday it would not tolerate a shift in the Greek maritime border, a few days after Athens said it planned to extend its territorial waters to 12 miles to the west of the country. Territorial waters are a sensitive issue between the two neighbors, who are separated by the Aegean Sea. Turkey and Greece have been at odds over their respective continental shelves for decades. Turkey has previously warned it could not preclude military action to defend its interests. Former Greek Foreign Minister Nikos Kotzias, who resigned last week, said on Saturday that Athens planne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Bishop arrives in East Timor as diplomatic tensions ease - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-07-30/julie-bishop-arrives-in-east-timor-ending-diplomatic-drought/10049560</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOgElQdeheZeed-Zl4Tx0Y8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 19:02:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-07-30/julie-bishop-arrives-in-east-timor-ending-diplomatic-drought/10049560" target="_blank"&gt;Bishop arrives in East Timor as diplomatic tensions ease&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was little fanfare or pomp when Julie Bishop arrived in East Timor on Sunday. But when the Foreign Minister landed at the tiny Nicolau Lobato International Airport yesterday evening, she brought an astonishing diplomatic drought to an end. It had been almost five years since a Federal Government minister from Australia had visited East Timor. Five years is a long time. In foreign policy, that's an eternity. So what happened? What has soured our relationship with our tiny northern neighbour for half a decade? And why does Ms Bishop want to change course? The heart of the problem On the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item></channel></rss>