<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Sinohydro - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRFV4ZWpWamVCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:59:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>We'll ensure value for money audits on Sinohydro projects – Assibey-Yeboah - GhanaWeb</title><link>https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/We-ll-ensure-value-for-money-audits-on-Sinohydro-projects-Assibey-Yeboah-706763</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiggFodHRwczovL3d3dy5naGFuYXdlYi5jb20vR2hhbmFIb21lUGFnZS9OZXdzQXJjaGl2ZS9XZS1sbC1lbnN1cmUtdmFsdWUtZm9yLW1vbmV5LWF1ZGl0cy1vbi1TaW5vaHlkcm8tcHJvamVjdHMtQXNzaWJleS1ZZWJvYWgtNzA2NzYz0gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:02:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/We-ll-ensure-value-for-money-audits-on-Sinohydro-projects-Assibey-Yeboah-706763" target="_blank"&gt;We'll ensure value for money audits on Sinohydro projects – Assibey-Yeboah&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GhanaWeb&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chairman of Parliament's Finance Committee, Dr Mark Assibey Yeboah has assured that comprehensive value for money audits will be conducted on the ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpkMktHbWpZQU1FYWhFVENXVGNhM3pLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ghanaweb.com">GhanaWeb</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/DBSk8FTcmzHhM_rpo7eURNBnfOWYiB2Po4P9zrQyMu9dnKfeob4cbK6JQQ5IqhLAnJsTH5TS51EwiftN6dHOpvKQPB1piA=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Fast Asia Open: Japan unemployment, Vietnam trade data - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b7e7fed7-6c28-3369-ac72-a26c5e67c2b7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKXnjDTavGrdnh_GKR8kACMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 23:06:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b7e7fed7-6c28-3369-ac72-a26c5e67c2b7" target="_blank"&gt;Fast Asia Open: Japan unemployment, Vietnam trade data&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;North Korea has launched a ballistic missile that overflew Japan’s northern island of Hokkaido – an aggressive step the country has not taken in almost 20 years. The Japanese government issued an alert in Hokkaido to take cover, putting residents on alert and marking a significant escalation in tensions. NHK, Japan’s national news service, said the missile fell into the waters off Hokkaido, at about 6am on Tuesday. The Pentagon also confirmed the launch. The escalation is likely to undermine US efforts to bring the nuclear aspirant to the negotiating table. The yen pushed to as strong as ¥1...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Myanmar weighs infrastructure, strategic ties to China - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2117c98a-4559-11e7-8d27-59b4dd6296b8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM6lT1CwgEBfbG94mI73gokqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 11:28:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2117c98a-4559-11e7-8d27-59b4dd6296b8" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar weighs infrastructure, strategic ties to China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xi Jinping, China’s president, staged an impressive show for Asean leaders attending his summit in Beijing this month. The assembled politicians received the intended message loud and clear — that their countries stand to benefit from the One Belt One Road initiative every bit as much as China. Surprisingly, the state within the 10-member Association of Southeast Asian Nations that until recently had an ill-defined role in the One Belt script is Myanmar. Yet this is the country that could make some of the greatest gains from the infrastructure connectivity promised by the latter-day Silk Ro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Ghana relations with China raise the emotional heat - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/bdb7c066-c1ad-11e8-84cd-9e601db069b8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENIbkC_Q7sd08SDSlko687gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 03:31:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/bdb7c066-c1ad-11e8-84cd-9e601db069b8" target="_blank"&gt;Ghana relations with China raise the emotional heat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are an estimated 6,500 Ghanaians studying in China, making Ghana, with its population of 28m, Africa’s number one supplier of students to the country. China has surged from almost nowhere to become Ghana’s top trading partner, with bilateral trade rising from less than $100m in 2000 to $6.7bn in 2017. In describing the closeness of relations between the two countries, Chinese state newspaper the People’s Daily highlights China’s construction of the Bui hydropower station by Sinohydro Corporation and the 200MW Sunon Asogli thermal plant, which is operated by Shenzhen Energy Group. It a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>