<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Elon Musk - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRE51ZW1ZeEVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:52:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Mark Zuckerberg And Elon Musk Go At It In 'Epic Rap Battle’ - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/elon-musk-mark-zuckerberg-epic-rap-battle_us_5c0b9ebbe4b0ab8cf693bbd5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELzYFN3mEciJh2RDHtg4XzYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:26:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/elon-musk-mark-zuckerberg-epic-rap-battle_us_5c0b9ebbe4b0ab8cf693bbd5" target="_blank"&gt;Mark Zuckerberg And Elon Musk Go At It In 'Epic Rap Battle’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two modern-day titans of tech duke it out in the latest installment of “Epic Rap Battles of History.” Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg and billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk, who have previously feuded over the dangers posed by artificial intelligence, hilariously attempt to one-up each other in the spoof video shared online Friday. “Your site’s got so many Russian bots, they should call it the Social Nyet-work,” fake Musk taunts faux Zuckerberg, who fires back: “Set your self-driving truck to haul yourself home, because this battle’s like PayPal, you got owned!” Check out the battle here:&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Tesla stock jumps after Jefferies turns bullish, boosts price target - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-stock-jumps-after-jefferies-turns-bullish-boosts-price-target-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK60Vr12i_jXBjDpLvMfDPAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-stock-jumps-after-jefferies-turns-bullish-boosts-price-target-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla stock jumps after Jefferies turns bullish, boosts price target&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RATINGS GAME By Tomi Kilgore New price target to $450 is more than 20% above current levels Getty Shares of Tesla Inc. shot up toward a four-month high Friday, after Jefferies analyst Philipe Houchois turned bullish and targeted a more than 20% rally in the stock, citing the electric-vehicle maker’s profit and self-funding potential. Houchois raised his rating to buy, after upgrading it to hold from underperform in April. He raised his stock price target to $450, which is 21% above current levels, from $360. “The shares have done well since Q3, with Tesla having demonstrated its profit ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Technical glitch sees Elon Musk's SpaceX Falcon rocket crash land in sea - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/technical-glitch-sees-elon-musks-spacex-falcon-rocket-crash/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ0qMY2klE1W9CArLCXz_1kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:05:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/technical-glitch-sees-elon-musks-spacex-falcon-rocket-crash/" target="_blank"&gt;Technical glitch sees Elon Musk's SpaceX Falcon rocket crash land in sea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Christmas turkey rocketed toward the International Space Station on Wednesday, along with cranberry sauce, candied yams and the obligatory fruitcake. The SpaceX booster missed its landing zone on the ground after liftoff, however, and ended up in the sea just a couple of miles offshore. Groans filled SpaceX Mission Control in Hawthorne, California, as live video showed the first-stage rocket booster spinning out of control, still high above Cape Canaveral. It was the company's first missed ground landing, although it has overshot floating barges plenty of times in the past, a tougher feat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tesla Patent Application Mentions Augmented Reality Safety Glasses - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/sebastianblanco/2018/12/07/tesla-patent-augmented-reality-safety-glasses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH6NlS962zdM3Usazl0F4tYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sebastianblanco/2018/12/07/tesla-patent-augmented-reality-safety-glasses/" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla Patent Application Mentions Augmented Reality Safety Glasses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla Factory Aerial View A lot has been made of the fact that Tesla had to put some Model 3 production process into a giant tent. That may sound like an unusual place to build a car, but apparently it wasn’t as ramshackle as one might think on first blush. However Tesla got its mass-market electric vehicle up and running, the company has bigger, tech-ier plans for future EV production. Like, say, maybe some augmented reality safety glasses. That’s one item listed in a newly published U.S. patent application Tesla filed May 31, 2018. Titled “Augmented reality feature detection,” Tesla’s ide...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Musk's Falcon X rocket crashes in sea - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ewxM7_RqBaQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENH8UoLnGwizp50ChzRrCE0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTD8vxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:29:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ewxM7_RqBaQ" target="_blank"&gt;Musk's Falcon X rocket crashes in sea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk posts videos on Twitter of one of his SpaceX Falcon rockets crash landing in the sea Get the latest headlines: http://www.telegraph.co.uk/ Subscribe: http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=telegraphtv Like us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/telegraph.co.uk Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/telegraph Telegraph.co.uk and YouTube.com/TelegraphTV are websites of The Telegraph, the UK's best-selling quality daily newspaper providing news and analysis on UK and world events, business, sport, lifestyle and culture.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tesla hires Washington trial lawyer as new general counsel - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-counsel/tesla-hires-washington-trial-lawyer-as-new-general-counsel-idUSKBN1O60EW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDuGjT1Yyh59awNL0ouGGaQqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-counsel/tesla-hires-washington-trial-lawyer-as-new-general-counsel-idUSKBN1O60EW" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla hires Washington trial lawyer as new general counsel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla Inc has hired Dane Butswinkas, a Washington, D.C. trial lawyer, as its general counsel, the electric car manufacturer said late on Thursday. Tesla Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk had hired Butswinkas to help settle a case with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, Bloomberg had reported in October. Musk and Tesla paid $20 million each in fines to settle the case, which stemmed from the billionaire CEO's Twitter posts in August about taking the company private. Butswinkas, the chairman of major Washington law firm Williams &amp; Connolly, is replacing Todd Maron at Tesla. Maron, w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Key For Tesla's Future Is Batteries, NotCars - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/enriquedans/2018/12/07/the-key-for-teslas-future-is-batteries-not-cars/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKSBhNSqeIJhFPhm1fvIjTkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/enriquedans/2018/12/07/the-key-for-teslas-future-is-batteries-not-cars/" target="_blank"&gt;The Key For Tesla's Future Is Batteries, NotCars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An overall view of the new Tesla Gigafactory is seen during a media tour Tuesday, July 26, 2016, in Sparks, Nev. It’s Tesla Motors’ biggest bet yet: A massive, $5 billion factory in the Nevada desert that could almost double the world’s production of lithium-ion batteries by 2018. (AP Photo/Rich Pedroncelli) Tesla’s Gigafactory will soon be the largest covered building ever built and, with the permission of the Chinese company BYD, the largest battery factory in the world, in what has become the fight to control of one of the most important technologies for the future. Tesla’s joint venture...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>SpaceX's Falcon rocket ditches in water after sending cargo to ISS (VIDEO) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445688-spacex-rocket-landing-failed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFzJftx9whYjzxqU-LyoJoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445688-spacex-rocket-landing-failed/" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX's Falcon rocket ditches in water after sending cargo to ISS (VIDEO)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SpaceX’s Falcon 9 rocket failed to stick the landing after successfully launching a supply pod to the International Space Station. CEO Elon Musk says the livestream should not have cut away from the failure. The CRS-16 mission launched supplies to the ISS on Wednesday, but the booster headed for the landing pad missed and landed in the water instead, ending SpaceX’s perfect record of 12 previous successful landings. Tracking shot of Falcon water landing pic.twitter.com/6Hv2aZhLjM — Elon Musk (@elonmusk) December 5, 2018 Musk also tweeted a video from on board the booster, showing the rocket...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Christmas turkey, fruitcake rocketing toward space station - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/bf2c68dfde1b48a69a93a354a3754ed7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDC2rX3qwm5S0QEXNctvekUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:10:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/bf2c68dfde1b48a69a93a354a3754ed7" target="_blank"&gt;Christmas turkey, fruitcake rocketing toward space station&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — Christmas turkey rocketed toward the International Space Station on Wednesday, along with cranberry sauce, candied yams and the obligatory fruitcake. The SpaceX booster missed its landing zone on the ground after liftoff, however, and ended up in the sea just a couple of miles offshore. Groans filled SpaceX Mission Control in Hawthorne, California, as live video showed the first-stage rocket booster spinning out of control, still high above Cape Canaveral. It was the company's first missed ground landing, although it has overshot floating barges plenty of times i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The first use of a hyperloop will be incredibly boring - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90277130/the-first-use-of-a-hyperloop-will-be-incredibly-boring</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJJlrFuPxZnxeKuNyG_Jh4cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:00:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90277130/the-first-use-of-a-hyperloop-will-be-incredibly-boring" target="_blank"&gt;The first use of a hyperloop will be incredibly boring&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hyperloop Transportation Technologies, which has received far less fanfare then its similarly named competitor Virgin Hyperloop (née Hyperloop One), today announced a joint venture with a German logistics and transportation company that runs container terminals. Together the two companies will bring HTT’s technology to the Port of Hamburg. Which is to say, the first real use of a hyperloop will be to move freight around a shipyard. Not terribly sexy! Of course, this was always going to be the first use case for this still largely untested transportation method. While many hyperloop hopefuls...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Tesla, smarting from trade war, seeks bids for China Gigafactory construction - Reuters</title><link>https://in.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-china-exclusive/exclusive-tesla-smarting-from-trade-war-seeks-bids-for-china-gigafactory-construction-idINKBN1O50IY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJZB6K4-o9jRzov9lLI0XO8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:00:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://in.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-china-exclusive/exclusive-tesla-smarting-from-trade-war-seeks-bids-for-china-gigafactory-construction-idINKBN1O50IY" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Tesla, smarting from trade war, seeks bids for China Gigafactory construction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla Inc has opened a tender process to build its Shanghai Gigafactory and at least one contractor has started buying materials, according to sources and documents reviewed by Reuters, the clearest indication that construction is imminent. The details, previously unreported, reveal that state-owned Shanghai Construction Group Co Ltd is taking part in the bidding while a unit of China Minmetals Corp Ltd is preparing materials for the plant's foundations. The $2 billion factory, Tesla's first in China, is a major bet for the U.S. electric vehicle (EV) maker as it looks to bolster its presenc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://in.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Valuable Immigrant-Founded Startups Coming To U.S. Stock Market - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stuartanderson/2018/12/06/valuable-immigrant-founded-startups-coming-to-u-s-stock-market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOsHs6b0rj2SGefxwglwFX8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/stuartanderson/2018/12/06/valuable-immigrant-founded-startups-coming-to-u-s-stock-market/" target="_blank"&gt;Valuable Immigrant-Founded Startups Coming To U.S. Stock Market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Headquarters of big data analytics company Palantir, co-founded by German-born immigrant Peter Thiel, which is expected to have an initial public offering (IPO) in 2019. (Photo via Smith Collection/Gado/Getty Images) Immigrants have created some of America’s most valuable privately held companies. Several of these companies are soon to become publicly traded and available to any American who wants to invest in these billion-dollar startups. The news of potential initial public offerings (IPOs) for many immigrant-founded companies comes at a time when a study from the National Foundation for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>SpaceX launches biggest U.S. 'rideshare' mission with 64 satellites - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-spacex/spacex-launches-biggest-u-s-rideshare-mission-with-64-satellites-idUSKBN1O22JQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILNkrBjTI332rIJsH96M1gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:35:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-spacex/spacex-launches-biggest-u-s-rideshare-mission-with-64-satellites-idUSKBN1O22JQ" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX launches biggest U.S. 'rideshare' mission with 64 satellites&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk's SpaceX launched a Falcon 9 rocket from California on Monday carrying 64 small satellites into low orbit around the Earth, which the company called the largest-ever "rideshare" mission by a U.S.-based rocket. The mission, dubbed SSO-A, also marked the third voyage to space for the same Falcon 9 rocket - another milestone for SpaceX's cost-cutting reusable rocket technology. The Falcon 9 blasted off from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California at 10:34 a.m. local time (18:34 GMT) carrying satellites from 34 different companies, government agencies and universities. SpaceX said the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Book That Explains Elon Musk's Paranoia - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-book-that-explains-elon-musks-paranoia</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1kigq9QG8-Z23XB0izS3cqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMI6imAI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 02:36:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-book-that-explains-elon-musks-paranoia" target="_blank"&gt;The Book That Explains Elon Musk's Paranoia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joshua Lott/Getty If you can imagine Elon Musk as some sort of wartime business leader, then you can understand the pressures the Tesla CEO has to deal with. “The wartime CEO is someone who is constantly paranoid, worried how his company might fail, and be vulnerable to attack,” says Hamish McKenzie, author of the new book Insane Mode: How Elon Musk’s Tesla Sparked an Electric Revolution to end the Age of Oil. Any possible Muskian paranoia is probably justified, adds McKenzie, because Tesla is coming up “against established industries like auto and oil, and you have to have this mindset tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Tesla to start production from Shanghai factory in 2019 - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/219795fa-f90a-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE9VxbUKwT4klTVxbdQcBEMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:59:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/219795fa-f90a-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla to start production from Shanghai factory in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla will begin partial production at its new Shanghai factory in the second half of next year, according to a post on a Shanghai municipal WeChat account. On Wednesday, Shanghai’s mayor Ying Yong paid a visit to the city’s Lingang area, where Tesla has secured a 200-acre site for its first Chinese production plant. “We will carefully observe the great demand for Tesla’s vehicles, encourage the company to ensure the safety and quality of engineering and encourage the acceleration of factory construction,” Mr Ying said. In July, Tesla chief executive Elon Musk signed an agreement in Shangha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Reused rocket takes off carrying 64 satellites - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/b5adaacf957f49efba481aef2ef55914</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOXkO6cFTZRQc3R0fcVJCukqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgw3utQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:52:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/b5adaacf957f49efba481aef2ef55914" target="_blank"&gt;Reused rocket takes off carrying 64 satellites&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VANDENBERG AIR FORCE BASE, Calif. (AP) — A SpaceX rocket carrying 64 small satellites lifted off from California on Monday, marking the first time the same Falcon 9 rocket has been used in three space missions. The rocket blasted off from Vandenberg Air Force Base, arcing over the Pacific Ocean west of Los Angeles as it headed toward space. Minutes later, the rocket's first stage performed a so-called boost back maneuver and landed on an unmanned ship in the Pacific. The landing marked the first time SpaceX had flown a first stage three times. The first stage was previously launched and rec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Nasa chief criticses Elon Musk's weed-smoking podcast appearance - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/30/nasa-chief-criticses-elon-musks-weed-smoking-podcast-appearance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKc6mUdZtEHReJE6_Z43IpcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:29:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/30/nasa-chief-criticses-elon-musks-weed-smoking-podcast-appearance/" target="_blank"&gt;Nasa chief criticses Elon Musk's weed-smoking podcast appearance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk has been warned by Nasa’s most senior figure not to repeat his weed-smoking, whisky-drinking antics on a recent podcast if he wants to continue working with the space agency. Jim Bridenstein, the Nasa administrator, suggested that Mr Musk, an entrepreneur who is financing commercial space exploration, had acted inappropriately given his role with the company. Mr Musk’s SpaceX is one of two firms contracted to build a shuttle that will fly US astronauts to the International Space Station from American territory – something that was ended in 2011. Recent behavior by Mr Musk, who co-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>SpaceX launched 64 satellites in record-breaking mission - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/spacex-record-sso-a-mission/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEp3hVzUGKXL06egEV-s_EcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:50:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/spacex-record-sso-a-mission/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX launched 64 satellites in record-breaking mission&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SpaceX delivered 64 satellites into orbit in one fell swoop for a record-setting mission. Elon Musk's company launched a rocket from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California on Monday after a series of delays triggered by bad weather and last-minute inspections for the rocket. It marked one of the largest satellite ride-sharing missions ever launched and the most crowded single mission in US history, according to Spaceflight, SpaceX's customer for the launch. The mission illustrated the growing demand to launch small satellites, modern devices that some companies hope will empower an array o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Five planned missions to Mars - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/02/five-planned-missions-to-mars-nasa-esa-china-russia-uae-spacex-elon-musk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOk6R6nvr6JRNDrLT5GGX00qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 07:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/02/five-planned-missions-to-mars-nasa-esa-china-russia-uae-spacex-elon-musk" target="_blank"&gt;Five planned missions to Mars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nasa’s InSight Lander Last week, Nasa successfully landed its InSight probe on Mars, as part of a two-year mission to study the planet’s deep interior. Nasa is also planning a rover mission for 2020, to investigate signs of life and collect data for future expeditions. An artist’s impression of the ExoMars 2020 rover. Photograph: M Thiebaut/ESA ExoMars 2020 The European Space Agency and its Russian counterpart, Roscosmos, have joined forces on this mission, planned for summer 2020. Using a European rover and a Russian surface platform, the project aims to study the planet’s atmospheric gase...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>NASA chief says Elon Musk’s pot smoking ‘did not inspire confidence’ - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nasa-chief-says-elon-musks-pot-smoking-did-not-inspire-confidence-2018-11-29</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE-xuoS5QpzxnYLAqOwS1LYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nasa-chief-says-elon-musks-pot-smoking-did-not-inspire-confidence-2018-11-29" target="_blank"&gt;NASA chief says Elon Musk’s pot smoking ‘did not inspire confidence’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KEY WORDS By Mike Murphy SpaceX founder reportedly says he’ll behave better Elon Musk lit up on Joe Rogan’s podcast earlier this year. YouTube NASA’s administrator said Thursday that it was inappropriate for SpaceX founder Elon Musk to smoke marijuana on a podcast earlier this year, and that the incident “did not inspire confidence.” The pot-smoking incident in September reportedly irked NASA officials, and earlier this month the space agency ordered a safety review of SpaceX and Boeing Co. (BA) to evaluate the companies’ workplace cultures, “including the adherence to a drug-free environ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk drops plans for west LA tunnel, instead focuses on Dodger fans - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/elon-musk-drops-out-of-la-tunnel-to-build-another/10570208</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJh_PnCBm-NmGkyJmtRKSQUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:40:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/elon-musk-drops-out-of-la-tunnel-to-build-another/10570208" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk drops plans for west LA tunnel, instead focuses on Dodger fans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk has scrapped plans for a high-speed passenger tunnel under the West side of Los Angeles but is moving ahead with a similar proposal across town designed to whisk baseball fans to and from Dodger Stadium in Chicago. Mr Musk's underground transit venture, the Boring Company, gave up on its development of a 4.4-kilometre tunnel in West LA to settle litigation brought by community groups opposed to the project, the two sides said in a joint statement. The move came six months after Mr Musk, the high-tech baron better known as founder of electric car company Te...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Brands To Watch In 2019 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/deniselyohn/2018/12/04/brands-to-watch-in-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI-U5x5jXN49g1s_8qObmTsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 10:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/deniselyohn/2018/12/04/brands-to-watch-in-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;Brands To Watch In 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Chinese zodiac, 2019 is the year of the pig — which usually means a spirit of relaxation and enjoyment. It’s unlikely, though, that all brands will enjoy a happy, prosperous 2019. Many will undergo significant changes – others will face challenges from category disruption and stiff competition. And all will have to figure out how to navigate an economy that will likely end up slowing down in the back half of the year. Here’s the list of brands I’ll be keeping my eye on, in my annual tradition of one brand for each letter of the alphabet — my list of Brands to Watch in 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Latest: SpaceX lands rocket's first stage on ship - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/888cc6224c424f75a49eaa8732682c62</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK3EDVh9aLMXoESXwaR4QggqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgw3utQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:15:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/888cc6224c424f75a49eaa8732682c62" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: SpaceX lands rocket's first stage on ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VANDENBERG AIR FORCE BASE, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on a SpaceX rocket launch from California (all times local): 11:10 a.m. For the third time, SpaceX has successfully launched and landed the same first stage of a Falcon 9 rocket. The spacecraft carrying dozens of small satellites lifted off Monday from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California. Minutes later, the first stage landed on an unmanned ship in the Pacific. The same first stage was previously launched and recovered on missions in May and August. Reusability is a major goal of SpaceX founder Elon Musk's rocket program. ___ 10:45 a.m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk will not smoke cannabis on a podcast again, says Nasa boss amid concern over billionaire's behaviour - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/elon-musk-nasa-cannabis-joe-rogan-joint-bridenstine-astronaut-safety-a8661201.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO_g1dL-dFW-KUL40X1k_YMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 10:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/elon-musk-nasa-cannabis-joe-rogan-joint-bridenstine-astronaut-safety-a8661201.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk will not smoke cannabis on a podcast again, says Nasa boss amid concern over billionaire's behaviour&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk will not be smoking cannabis in public again, the boss of Nasa has assured the public, amid concern about the SpaceX boss's behaviour. Nasa administrator Jim Bridenstine has said that Mr Musk has promised not to repeat a moment where he smoked a joint and drank whisky on a comedian's podcast. That incident caused consternation across the space industry, because Mr Musk's rocket company SpaceX is expected to soon begin carrying US astronauts on its rockets. His behaviour had led to worries about whether he was responsible enough to lead an organisation that will take US astronauts ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>SpaceX launch: Rocket containing ashes of 100 people sent into space - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/spacex-launch-ashes-remains-rocket-falcon-9-shooting-star-memorial-elon-musk-a8665106.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAdyAgZ_bAunwwyFvsxVw0wqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/spacex-launch-ashes-remains-rocket-falcon-9-shooting-star-memorial-elon-musk-a8665106.html" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX launch: Rocket containing ashes of 100 people sent into space&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a unique application of commercial space flight, people are launching the cremated remains of their loved ones into a satellite that will orbit the earth. Companies including Elysium Space and Celestis offer their customers the poetic opportunity to send the ashes of dead people (and at least one dog) to travel among the stars. In 2012, the Falcon 9, a rocket from Elon Musk’s company SpaceX, carried a secondary payload of 308 sets of ashes while delivering supplies to a space station. Families had each sent a gram of ashes to the company Celestis and reserved a space in a capsule in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk scraps plans for Los Angeles tunnel after lawsuit settlement - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/28/elon-musk-underground-tunnel-los-angeles-lawsuit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3oUltpuDM-iyyo1JQbufQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 01:01:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/28/elon-musk-underground-tunnel-los-angeles-lawsuit" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk scraps plans for Los Angeles tunnel after lawsuit settlement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk has scrapped his plans to dig through an affluent section of west Los Angeles after his tunneling company reached a settlement in an environmental review lawsuit. The Boring Company “is no longer seeking the development of the Sepulveda test tunnel and instead seeks to construct an operational tunnel at Dodger Stadium”, the firm announced in a statement to NBC News on Tuesday. The tunnels are Musk’s solution to “soul-destroying traffic”, a way to make roads “go 3D”, according to the company’s website. Work began last year on a test tunnel in Hawthorne, California, across the stree...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk shares his terrifying vision of ‘assassin drones’ - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musk-shares-his-terrifying-vision-of-assassin-drones-2018-11-26</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFbPS0U5NQI1dIPm7zRvYYkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 19:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musk-shares-his-terrifying-vision-of-assassin-drones-2018-11-26" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk shares his terrifying vision of ‘assassin drones’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KEY WORDS By Shawn Langlois MarketWatch photo illustration/Getty Images, iStockphoto Elon Musk, in a ranging interview aired on Sunday night on “Axios on HBO,” talked about how Tesla (TSLA) was “bleeding money like crazy” and almost went under earlier this year. But the chat took a darker turn when he started talking about the scary future — and present — of artificial intelligence: ‘You could make a swarm of assassin drones for very little money. By just taking the face I.D. chip that’s used in cell phones, and having a small explosive charge and a standard drone, and just have it do a gr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Owner of Elon Musk's big SA battery escaped fine for missed deadline - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-28/owner-of-elon-musks-big-sa-battery-escapes-taxpayer-fine/10560386</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_aDNJ613ulp2UvgksEhvsqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 23:41:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-28/owner-of-elon-musks-big-sa-battery-escapes-taxpayer-fine/10560386" target="_blank"&gt;Owner of Elon Musk's big SA battery escaped fine for missed deadline&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Nick Harmsen Tesla boss Elon Musk famously delivered on a promise to build it within 100 days or do it for free, but a new report has revealed the owner of South Australia's giant battery escaped a government fine for missing a key testing deadline. The 100-megawatt lithium-ion Tesla battery, the most powerful of its kind in the world, has been operating alongside French company Neoen's Hornsdale Wind Farm near Jamestown in South Australia's north since the beginning of last summer. The battery was a key element of the former Weatherill government's $550 million energy plan, aimed at red...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk says he’ll turn you into a cyborg in the next decade - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90272087/elon-musk-says-hell-turn-you-into-a-cyborg-in-the-next-decade</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPdOcpkl-29Y4LGndy6Ell4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 07:16:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90272087/elon-musk-says-hell-turn-you-into-a-cyborg-in-the-next-decade" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk says he’ll turn you into a cyborg in the next decade&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Musk told Axios that his neuroscience company, Neuralink, will have the technology “probably” within the next decade to fuse humans with artificial intelligence. In order to do this, Musk says Neuralink will produce an “electrode-to-neuron interface at a micro level,” basically “a chip and a bunch of tiny wires” that will be implanted into your skull. So why does Musk want to turn us into cyborgs? He says it’s humanity’s only hope to survive the upcoming glut of super-intelligent machines powered by artificial intelligence that will take over the world and would otherwise push humanity to e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Tesla was weeks from dying earlier this year, Elon Musk says - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-was-weeks-from-dying-earlier-this-year-elon-musk-says-2018-11-25</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOXNKG5Jvg3_vKh3MzEtI8gqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 11:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-was-weeks-from-dying-earlier-this-year-elon-musk-says-2018-11-25" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla was weeks from dying earlier this year, Elon Musk says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KEY WORDS By Mike Murphy Tesla CEO admits company was ‘bleeding money’ and ‘faced a severe threat of death’ Elon Musk speaks in Chicago in June. Getty Images Tesla Inc. was “bleeding money like crazy” during its Model 3 production ramp-up and almost went under earlier this year, Elon Musk said Sunday. In an interview aired Sunday night on “Axios on HBO,” Tesla’s chief executive said the electric-car company was “within single-digit weeks” of dying. ‘Tesla really faced a severe threat of death due to the Model 3 production ramp.’ — Elon Musk “Essentially, the company was bleeding money like ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk Pulls Plug on Boring Company Tunnel Project in Los Angeles - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/elon-musk-pulls-plug-on-boring-company-tunnel-project-in-los-angeles</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELgJTPg0mM6-WFa8cxjIzL8qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 07:13:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/elon-musk-pulls-plug-on-boring-company-tunnel-project-in-los-angeles" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk Pulls Plug on Boring Company Tunnel Project in Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kyle Grillot/Reuters, Elon Musk’s plan to build a high-tech tunnel in Los Angeles has reportedly gone belly up. Musk’s Boring Company announced Tuesday that it has nixed a project to construct a subterranean passageway below the 405 freeway along L.A.’s Westside. The decision came after several community groups sued the city over its move to exempt the project from an environmental review process, resulting in a settlement. "The parties (The Boring Company, Brentwood Residents Coalition, Sunset Coalition, and Wendy-Sue Rosen) have amicably settled the matter of Brentwood Residents Coalition...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk: Workers should put in 100 hours a week to change the world - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/27/elon-musk-workers-should-put-80-hours-week-change-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENE5OFl2JBa2l69s1MgyZg8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:54:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/27/elon-musk-workers-should-put-80-hours-week-change-world/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk: Workers should put in 100 hours a week to change the world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla and SpaceX workers should put in 80 to 100 hours a week to "change the world", Elon Musk has said. The technology entrepreneur admitted that there were "way easier places to work" than his companies, adding: "Nobody ever changed the world on 40 hours a week." Asked how many hours a week were necessary, Mr Musk said: "Varies per person, but about 80 sustained, peaking above 100 at times. Pain level increases exponentially above 80." Mr Musk's comments attracted criticism from commentators who suggested that overwork could lead to decreased productivity. He is the founder and chief exec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk is talking about moving to Mars. But how close are we to that, really? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/elon-musk-says-he-could-make-it-to-mars-in-five-years/10553914</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJC9V-mVUInvJ1NTYNMXucqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 18:45:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/elon-musk-says-he-could-make-it-to-mars-in-five-years/10553914" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk is talking about moving to Mars. But how close are we to that, really?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk is so confident he'll get to Mars within his lifetime, he's already talking about moving there. "I know exactly what to do … we've recently made a number of breakthroughs that I am just really fired up about," he told Axios on HBO in an interview yesterday. But at the age of 47, time is ticking. He told Axios there was a 70 per cent chance he would personally ride to Mars on one of his SpaceX rockets. But with some scientists predicting it could take another 30 years for humans to get to the Red Planet, how feasible is his timeline? Let's — like NASA's InSight lander — delve a lit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk says he is probably going to go and live on Mars - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-mars-spacex-tesla-live-red-planet-earth-rocket-a8652101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEETeCs-sw3hIjOesOPLvv-oqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 11:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-mars-spacex-tesla-live-red-planet-earth-rocket-a8652101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk says he is probably going to go and live on Mars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk is probably going to live on Mars. That is, if he doesn't die first: something that is highly likely, given how risky the journey will be. And if he doesn't die on his way to the red planet, he could easily die once he get there. If he and his fellow travellers do manage to get to Mars and survive, life will be a difficult prospect, he has said. It is going to be lots of work and very little leisure time, he said, with the high chance that you might die from Mars's harsh environment before you get to enjoy it. Nasa's most stunning pictures of space - + show all Nasa's most stunnin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Billionaires Love Energy Storage But Can Energy Storage Make Its Own Billionaire - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnparnell/2018/11/30/billionaires-love-energy-storage-but-can-energy-storage-make-its-own-billionaire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKNO_3WcG6nG3hSXXXEw7gMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnparnell/2018/11/30/billionaires-love-energy-storage-but-can-energy-storage-make-its-own-billionaire/" target="_blank"&gt;Billionaires Love Energy Storage But Can Energy Storage Make Its Own Billionaire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year, yet another billionaire took a big bet on energy storage – twice. First, Patrick Soon-Shiong’s company NantEnergy bought zinc-air battery manufacturer Fluidic and earlier this month, he added in Sharp’s SmartStorage division in the US. Soon-Shiong is treading a well-worn path. Wang Chuanfu, the head of Chinese firm BYD, has seen his company become a major electric vehicle and stationary energy storage manufacturer. Elon Musk, of course, segued Tesla into stationary storage as well. And one of the solar industry’s self-made billionaires, Jifan Gao, has also moved into energy stora...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Robo-taxis or high-tech tunnels? The race for traffic utopia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/f8177bb6-ecaf-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJT1Y0pxhu1TBzxXDk8-YFkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 05:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f8177bb6-ecaf-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Robo-taxis or high-tech tunnels? The race for traffic utopia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On my first day as a reporter in Silicon Valley, I witnessed what I thought was the greatest product unveiling I had ever seen. It was a sunny morning, late June 2012. From an airship hovering over downtown San Francisco, a team of stuntmen wearing Google Glass headsets started to leap out into the Californian sky. Inside the Moscone Center, where Google’s annual developer conference was being held, we in the audience watched in awe as they plunged to Earth, the Glass cameras beaming a live video feed of their descent. After landing on the roof and abseiling to the ground, the stuntmen then...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk renames 'BFR' rocket to 'Starship' ahead of planned SpaceX trips to the Moon and Mars - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-bfr-name-starship-big-falcon-rocket-moon-mars-mission-a8643846.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH9CvTLuX1hEQ88IVt2vsr8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 19:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-bfr-name-starship-big-falcon-rocket-moon-mars-mission-a8643846.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk renames 'BFR' rocket to 'Starship' ahead of planned SpaceX trips to the Moon and Mars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk has renamed the BFR, the spaceship that he hopes will carry humans to Mars. It will now be known as Starship, he said, though the bottom part will have a separate name. The BFR name had always been slightly controversial and strange: while SpaceX officially insisted it was short for "Big Falcon Rocket", the F really seemed to stand for something a little more explicit. Nasa's most stunning pictures of space - + show all Nasa's most stunning pictures of space - 1/30 Earth from the ISS From the International Space Station, Expedition 42 Flight Engineer Terry W. Virts took this photo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk Said Tesla Was 'Single-Digit Weeks' From Death - Where's The Disclosures? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/christopherhelman/2018/11/28/elon-musk-said-tesla-was-single-digit-weeks-from-deathwheres-the-disclosures/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-iP5tq0HKXnioodHqHZT8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 18:32:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/christopherhelman/2018/11/28/elon-musk-said-tesla-was-single-digit-weeks-from-deathwheres-the-disclosures/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk Said Tesla Was 'Single-Digit Weeks' From Death - Where's The Disclosures?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=2] With reporting by Alan Ohnsman The past year has been tough on Elon Musk, but we hadn’t known the depths of his peril at Tesla until he opened up to Axios in an interview. Though we’ve grown to expect mendacity out of Musk, he sounded heartfelt when he shared the following: “Tesla really faced this severe threat of death due to the Model 3 production round. Essentially the company was bleeding money like crazy, and, just, if we didn’t solve these problems in a very short period of time, we would die, and it was extremely difficult to solve them.” How close to death did Tesla come? “W...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk says he is thinking of moving to Mars - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/25/elon-musk-says-thinking-moving-mars/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFApxhfJ0w7NLjm0cvBt6sQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 22:29:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/25/elon-musk-says-thinking-moving-mars/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk says he is thinking of moving to Mars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon musk has declared that there is a "70 per cent chance" he will personally visit Mars within his lifetime despite a "good chance" of death. The SpaceX founder told reporters that travel to Mars might be possible within seven years for a few hundred thousand dollars per ticket, saying: "I'm thinking about moving there." Mr Musk, who endured multiple scandals this year over his drug use, and stewardship of his electric car company, Tesla, has been working towards colonising the red planet since 2001, believing it to be essential insurance against a global disaster on Earth. Asked by the A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk believes he has a 70% likelihood of flying to Mars despite 'good chance of death' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/elon-musk-mars-70-spacex-axios-space-travel-a8651356.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM_-ptE1veOHfv_GTsjkiC8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 18:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/elon-musk-mars-70-spacex-axios-space-travel-a8651356.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk believes he has a 70% likelihood of flying to Mars despite 'good chance of death'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tech entrepreneur Elon Musk has claimed there is a 70 per cent likelihood he will make it to Mars on one of his spacecraft – despite there being “a good chance of death”. The 47-year-old founder of Tesla, who is among several businessmen seeking to find a way to reach the red planet, said while some consider his vision a fantasy, he thinks making the journey could be possible in as little as seven years from now, with the price of a ticket as low as “a couple of hundred thousand dollars”. “I know exactly what to do,” Mr Musk told Axios on HBO. “I’m talking about moving there.” - Read more S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>U.S. SEC chairman says Tesla case is 'settled' despite CEO's tweet - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-sec-clayton/sec-chairman-says-tesla-case-is-settled-despite-ceos-tweet-idUSKCN1NV2RO</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2s0EfwZ53fRhZVfRD4tBIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 15:02:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-sec-clayton/sec-chairman-says-tesla-case-is-settled-despite-ceos-tweet-idUSKCN1NV2RO" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. SEC chairman says Tesla case is 'settled' despite CEO's tweet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission chairman said on Monday that the agency would not revisit its securities fraud settlement with Tesla Inc despite Chief Executive Elon Musk's tweet mocking the regulator. Jay Clayton appeared to be unaware of the Oct. 4 tweet describing the SEC as the "Shortseller Enrichment Commission," when CNBC anchors read it to him on Monday. "He said that?" Clayton asked, declining to comment further. "As far as I'm concerned, that matter is settled." Tesla and Musk agreed in September to pay $20 million each to settle SEC charges over Musk's tweets on Aug. 7...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk considers move to Mars despite 'good chance of death' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/25/elon-musk-move-mars-chance-of-death</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFrn6JWJg73iVNbb4LQHzVEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 15:44:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/25/elon-musk-move-mars-chance-of-death" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk considers move to Mars despite 'good chance of death'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk is considering moving to Mars, and gives himself a 70% chance of doing so. Related: Mars is lovely at this time of year: futurists imagine life in 2050 “I know exactly what to do,” the billionaire Tesla founder told Axios on HBO, in an interview to be broadcast on Sunday night. “I’m talking about moving there.” He also implied that such a move might be permanent, saying: “We think you can come back but we’re not sure.” The Axios website trailed the interview a day before the scheduled Mars landing of the Insight spacecraft. According to the Associated Press, the Nasa vehicle will ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How Mate Rimac is supercharging electric cars - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/26441146-de02-11e8-b173-ebef6ab1374a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGFg8Uvq2ohEutAduQQCLpAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/26441146-de02-11e8-b173-ebef6ab1374a" target="_blank"&gt;How Mate Rimac is supercharging electric cars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not for nothing is Mate Rimac sometimes called “Europe’s Elon Musk”. Both run groundbreaking electric carmakers that have claimed speed records and won plaudits. Both have unconventional manufacturing locations — Tesla in California, Rimac Automobili on the outskirts of Zagreb in Croatia. When Tesla launched its first car, the Roadster, in 2008, Elon Musk was 37. Rimac today is just 30, with only the faintest hints of grey flecking his jet black hair. He is not keen, however, on the comparison with Musk. Tesla made 100,000 cars last year, and will hit close to triple that this year. Rimac’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tesla's head of global security exits after just 11 months - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/28/teslas-head-global-security-exits-just-11-months/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ1sdMd7QO4Cw1VQ2_OOH7kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:47:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/28/teslas-head-global-security-exits-just-11-months/" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla's head of global security exits after just 11 months&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla's head of global security and former Uber executive Jeff Jones has left the company after just 11 months in the job. Mr Jones, who left Uber for this role in January 2018, has joined a growing number of executives exiting the embattled electric car maker, which is under fire from US regulators over chief executive Elon Musk's plans to take the company private and accusations from investors over "misleading" production figures. Since the start of September Tesla has lost seven senior employees, including senior director of production and quality Antoin Abou-Haydar, vice president of su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tesla cuts China car prices to absorb hit from trade war tariffs - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-china-idUSKCN1NR0A6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP36w8e-HO3CfViku1myx4kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 13:17:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-china-idUSKCN1NR0A6" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla cuts China car prices to absorb hit from trade war tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla Inc (TSLA.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) is cutting the price of its Model X and Model S cars in China, the U.S. firm said on Thursday, in a shift in strategy that will see it take more of a hit from tariffs linked to a biting trade war between China and the United States. The electric carmaker, led by billionaire CEO Elon Musk, said it will cut prices of the two models by 12-26 percent to make the cars more "affordable" in the world's top auto market, where sales of so-called new-energy vehicles are rising fast. The move comes amid severe trade tensions between China and th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Musk opens up about Tesla's near 'death' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/11/26/musk-tesla-death.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECikXcVNSs4J9iJyZXueowoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 23:49:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/11/26/musk-tesla-death.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;Musk opens up about Tesla's near 'death'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an interview with Axios on HBO, Tesla CEO Elon Musk reflected on the electronic car giant's recent near "death" experience. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Musk renames Mars rocket 'Starship' and says 'later versions' will travel to new star systems - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/20/musk-renames-mars-rocket-starship-says-later-versions-will-travel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHmYSh6HJDlgDF5fLvNt2oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 11:12:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/20/musk-renames-mars-rocket-starship-says-later-versions-will-travel/" target="_blank"&gt;Musk renames Mars rocket 'Starship' and says 'later versions' will travel to new star systems&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk has renamed his Mars rocket for the third time, calling it Starship, and revealed that it will travel to other star systems. The SpaceX founder said on Monday night that his space tourism company plans to rebrand its largest ship, that has not been built yet, as later versions plan to reach locations outside the orbit of the Sun. Mr Musk had previously named his Mars spaceship the Mars Colonial Transporter (MCT), then the Interplanetary Transport System (ITS), then the Big Falcon Rocket (BFR), and is now calling it simply Starship. The rocket is expected t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tesla cuts China car prices to absorb trade war impact - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/847a4e02-ee19-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN02ON9JzyhUhZeiigOKWg4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 07:06:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/847a4e02-ee19-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla cuts China car prices to absorb trade war impact&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla has reduced prices of its cars in China by as much as a quarter to absorb the impact of tariffs from the US-China trade war on customers. The California-based electric carmaker said on Thursday that had cut the prices of its Model S and Model X in China by 12 to 26 per cent. “We are absorbing a significant part of the tariff to help make our cars more affordable for customers in China”, Tesla said in a statement. China imposed 25 per cent tariffs on $34bn of US goods, including cars, in July in response to Washington’s move to slap tariffs on $34bn of Chinese imports, one of a serie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Mexico's Tequila Regulatory Council Not Sold On Elon Musk's 'Teslaquila' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/teresafinney/2018/11/16/mexicos-tequila-regulatory-council-not-sold-on-elon-musks-teslaquila/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECxT2WuYQIrb9o-Wlrfeh3MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/teresafinney/2018/11/16/mexicos-tequila-regulatory-council-not-sold-on-elon-musks-teslaquila/" target="_blank"&gt;Mexico's Tequila Regulatory Council Not Sold On Elon Musk's 'Teslaquila'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla co-founder and CEO, and billionaire Elon Musk tweeted on Wednesday that he will “fight Big Tequila”, if necessary. The tweet comes after Mexico’s Consejo Regulador del Tequila, the Tequila Regulatory Council, said it would be pushing back against Musk’s latest project, Teslaquila, which is exactly what it sounds like: a Tesla-branded tequila. The Tequila Regulatory Council, also known in the industry as the CRT, argues that ‘Teslaquila’ is a bit too similar to the word ‘tequila’—a problem considering “tequila is a protected word,” the CRT said in a statement, adding that the Tesla-bra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ghosn Isn't Alone: Other Automotive Industry Executives Who Have Recently Run Afoul Of The Law - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccalindland/2018/11/21/ghosn-isnt-alone-other-automotive-industry-executives-who-have-recently-run-afoul-of-the-law/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANW169V2BquY6yXqGVkFooqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccalindland/2018/11/21/ghosn-isnt-alone-other-automotive-industry-executives-who-have-recently-run-afoul-of-the-law/" target="_blank"&gt;Ghosn Isn't Alone: Other Automotive Industry Executives Who Have Recently Run Afoul Of The Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carlos Ghosn is only the latest auto exec to be accused–or found guilty–of a crime in recent years. Automotive industry executive Carlos Ghosn, head of the Nissan-Renault-Mitsubishi Alliance and, was arrested in Japan on Monday, charged with several counts of financial impropriety, including underreporting his compensation, using company assets for personal gain, and falsifying financial statements. One of the industry’s most admired leaders, Ghosn is credited with breathing life back into Nissan and Renault by cutting costs and expanding their leadership role in the high-tech transition fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk's 'Teslaquila' drink faces clash with Mexican tequila industry - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-mexico-tequila/elon-musks-teslaquila-drink-faces-clash-with-mexican-tequila-industry-idUSKCN1NJ023</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGk17C5rAhq9ychKhTMmtt0qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 14:46:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-mexico-tequila/elon-musks-teslaquila-drink-faces-clash-with-mexican-tequila-industry-idUSKCN1NJ023" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk's 'Teslaquila' drink faces clash with Mexican tequila industry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla Inc co-founder Elon Musk and Mexico's tequila producers could be headed for a collision after the agave-based drink's industry group opposed the flamboyant billionaire's efforts to trademark an alcoholic drink dubbed "Teslaquila." One of the world's richest people and chief executive of Tesla (TSLA.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), Musk is known for ambitious and cutting-edge projects ranging from auto electrification and rocket-building to high-speed transit tunnels. Now it seems that Musk could be setting his sights on disrupting the multibillion-dollar tequila industry. On ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>A Tesla Owner Complains To Customer Service, Gets More Than He Bargained For - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/lianeyvkoff/2018/11/16/a-tesla-owner-complains-to-customer-service-gets-more-than-he-bargained-for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSHrGrOZElN38GD3lSLzw4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/lianeyvkoff/2018/11/16/a-tesla-owner-complains-to-customer-service-gets-more-than-he-bargained-for/" target="_blank"&gt;A Tesla Owner Complains To Customer Service, Gets More Than He Bargained For&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(credit: Getty) Tesla is known for quickly resolving a wide range of customer complaints, with many of the responses and fixes coming directly from its CEO, Elon Musk. But this isn’t a story about its good customer service. Rather, it’s a story of a chaotic communication process that led to a security breach for Tesla. Dan, who only uses his first name on the forums and the Web site he runs, recently picked up his much anticipated Model 3 after two previous false starts, and before he even got a chance to sit in it, the chaos began. Delivery logistics hell is just the beginning His sales ag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>SpaceX, TeleSat Canada bids get U.S. nod to expand satellite internet - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-fcc-satellite/spacex-telesat-canada-bids-get-u-s-nod-to-expand-satellite-internet-idUSKCN1NK2ET</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPLG-6e6YViap8yFy6_78WQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 21:40:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-fcc-satellite/spacex-telesat-canada-bids-get-u-s-nod-to-expand-satellite-internet-idUSKCN1NK2ET" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX, TeleSat Canada bids get U.S. nod to expand satellite internet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By David Shepardson WASHINGTON (Reuters - The U.S. Federal Communications Commission voted unanimously on Thursday to allow Tesla Inc (TSLA.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Chief Executive Elon Musk's Space X, Telesat Canada [PSPENC.UL] and two other companies to roll out new satellite-based broadband services. The FCC voted to grant "market access" requests to Telesat, Kepler Communications Inc and LeoSat MA, Inc to offer high-speed internet service and connectivity for sensors and other intelligence devices. The FCC, which had approved SpaceX's initial plans in March, further appr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tesla to deliver new Model 3 orders by year end - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-model3-delivery/tesla-to-deliver-new-model-3-orders-by-year-end-idUSKCN1NK2JP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMURztdk5m1XvYkz6eCbbL0qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 18:41:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-model3-delivery/tesla-to-deliver-new-model-3-orders-by-year-end-idUSKCN1NK2JP" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla to deliver new Model 3 orders by year end&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla Inc (TSLA.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk said on Thursday that Model 3s ordered in the United States by the end of this month will be delivered by Dec. 31, as the electric carmaker tries to take advantage of tax breaks. "Tesla just acquired trucking capacity to ensure Model 3 can be delivered in U.S. by Dec 31 if ordered by Nov 30," Musk tweeted here "Skipping rail saves over a month for East Coast deliveries. All things considered, it's better to use trucks. Single load/unload &amp; direct to owner location." Tesla did not immediately respond t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tesla's Board Chair Change: Its Broader Relevance - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelperegrine/2018/11/13/teslas-board-chair-change-its-broader-relevance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPGTDhT4lwUxGcGSonJOqIkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 18:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelperegrine/2018/11/13/teslas-board-chair-change-its-broader-relevance/" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla's Board Chair Change: Its Broader Relevance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Red Tesla Model S full-sized electric five-door hatchback. Tesla’s SEC-mandated change in its board chairmanship has governance relevance beyond the company, its shareholders and those who remain fascinated by the innovative but unpredictable Elon Musk. Indeed, Robyn Denholm’s appointment serves as a highly-visible prompt for boards to revisit the role and function of the board chair. This is especially the case when dealing with a flamboyant CEO, one whose vision and assertiveness is offset by volatile, eccentric or inconsistent tendencies. Ms. Denholm, an independent Tesla director, was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>FCC approves request for SpaceX to send over 7,000 satellites into space - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fcc-approves-request-for-spacex-to-send-over-7000-satellites-into-space-2018-11-15</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG53W4doYRwrugmsuUvthnkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fcc-approves-request-for-spacex-to-send-over-7000-satellites-into-space-2018-11-15" target="_blank"&gt;FCC approves request for SpaceX to send over 7,000 satellites into space&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Elisabeth Buchwald A mock up of the Crew Dragon spacecraft is displayed during a media tour of SpaceX headquarters and rocket factory on August 13, 2018 in Hawthorne, California. Getty Images In an effort to expand global connectivity, on Thursday the Federal Communications Commission approved the requests of Elon Musk’s SpaceX to deploy over 7,000 orbiting satellites into space. With more orbiting satellites in space, it is expected that more Americans, especially those living in rural areas as well as people in developing countries, will be able to access high-speed inte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Tesla starts taking Model 3 orders in China - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-model-3-china/tesla-starts-taking-model-3-orders-in-china-idUSKCN1NL1W0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDmAlB90NyFtTtdyztzPJaYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 16:59:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-model-3-china/tesla-starts-taking-model-3-orders-in-china-idUSKCN1NL1W0" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla starts taking Model 3 orders in China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla Inc has started taking orders for its Model 3 sedan in China for a deposit of 8,000 yuan ($1,153.60), according to the electric carmaker's China website www.tesla.cn/model3/reserve. Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk said, "Probably some deliveries in March, but April is more certain", after a Twitter user asked when the deliveries in China would begin. Tesla declined to comment. The company has been banking on its Model 3 sedan, the performance of which is seen crucial to the carmaker's future. Shares of Tesla rose 1.6 pct at $353.93 in morning trading. China is the largest market for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tesla had a record third quarter, so why do doubts persist? - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-had-a-record-third-quarter-so-why-do-doubts-persist-2018-11-12</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM_OKBr3aY0sh9xQsWa_j5AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-had-a-record-third-quarter-so-why-do-doubts-persist-2018-11-12" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla had a record third quarter, so why do doubts persist?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Francine McKenna Not everyone is cheering Tesla’s great quarter, especially skeptical short sellers who doubt whether Tesla made all the deliveries to customers it reported Tesla’s Model 3. Bloomberg News/Landov Why isn’t everyone satisfied with what Tesla Inc. reported as its third-quarter results? Tesla (TSLA) delivered more cars to customers in the third quarter than it did in all of 2016, and delivered for investors $271 million in pretax operating profit, its first profitable quarter in two years, and only its third ever. But not everyone is cheering. Skeptics, especi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Tesla FireX? Musk ridiculed online for offering to help with California wildfires - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/443625-musk-california-help-backlash/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKt-Y_cC3amTE-79mISY9t0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/443625-musk-california-help-backlash/" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla FireX? Musk ridiculed online for offering to help with California wildfires&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twitter users have come up with names and even blueprints for something to “help” tackle the raging California wildfires after Elon Musk invited the public to ask Tesla for assistance. Enormous fires visible even from space have gripped the state of California in recent days, forcing tens of thousands to flee. The disaster has already resulted in at least nine fatalities. The incident did not escape Musk’s attention, and the billionaire offered to have his company help by transporting people in California or assisting in any other way. If Tesla can help people in California wildfire, please...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Australian Tesla chairwoman's role will mean reining in Elon Musk - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-09/elon-musk-can-an-australian-woman-reign-in-tesla-maverick-ceo/10480926</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKayk2Vt-6_EPVA8chFuIM0qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:40:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-09/elon-musk-can-an-australian-woman-reign-in-tesla-maverick-ceo/10480926" target="_blank"&gt;Australian Tesla chairwoman's role will mean reining in Elon Musk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australian Robyn Denholm brings much-needed financial and auto industry expertise to her new role as Tesla's board chair, but her biggest challenge is whether she can rein in a chief executive with a proclivity for misbehaviour. Ms Denholm, who has been a Tesla board member for nearly five years, was named as Elon Musk's replacement as part of a securities fraud settlement with US government regulators. Corporate governance experts said they would have preferred an outsider with manufacturing expertise be appointed to lead the board, now dominated by people with personal and financial ties ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Immigrant Tech Founders Create Thousands Of Jobs - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stuartanderson/2018/11/13/immigrant-tech-founders-create-thousands-of-jobs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHnZWoW8rQK7ywmNg_jUEyMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 05:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/stuartanderson/2018/11/13/immigrant-tech-founders-create-thousands-of-jobs/" target="_blank"&gt;Immigrant Tech Founders Create Thousands Of Jobs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket launched just before dawn in June 2018. SpaceX, founded by immigrant Elon Musk, employs 7,000 people. (Red Huber/Orlando Sentinel/TNS via Getty Images) The U.S. economy relies on startups for much of America’s net job creation, and immigrants start many of those companies. A recent study from the National Foundation for American Policy finds that 55%, or 50 of 91, of the country’s $1 billion startup companies had at least one immigrant founder. The research identified the number of jobs created in immigrant-founded billion-dollar companies, revealing an average of m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Tesla names director Denholm to replace Musk as board chair - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-chair/tesla-names-director-denholm-to-replace-musk-as-board-chair-idUSKCN1ND0PI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOW0E42t_7SQIHJsEVRJBB8qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 21:57:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-chair/tesla-names-director-denholm-to-replace-musk-as-board-chair-idUSKCN1ND0PI" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla names director Denholm to replace Musk as board chair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla Inc has named director Robyn Denholm as board chair, fulfilling a demand by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to strip the job from Elon Musk, the electric car maker's wayward chief executive who has dragged the company through months of turbulence. The appointment was required as part of a September deal Tesla struck with the securities regulator to settle fraud charges against Musk and Tesla. Legal experts said it was unclear if Denholm, who has been on Tesla's board for four years, was independent enough for Tesla to comply with the court-approved settlement. Denholm, 55,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tesla names new chair to replace Elon Musk - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/08/tesla-names-new-chair-robyn-denholm-to-replace-elon-musk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMeIraPBOqq25gvzsOkkywQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:09:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/08/tesla-names-new-chair-robyn-denholm-to-replace-elon-musk" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla names new chair to replace Elon Musk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla has appointed Robyn Denholm as chair of its board, replacing the electric carmaker’s billionaire founder Elon Musk. Denholm, one of two female directors on the nine-member board, assumes her new position immediately, Tesla said. It will become full-time once she leaves her role as chief financial officer and head of strategy at Telstra, Australia’s largest telecom company, after her six-month notice period. The 55-year-old Australian will temporarily step down as chair of Tesla’s audit committee until she quits Telstra. In late September, Musk, who remains chief executive and is also ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Tesla names Robyn Denholm as new chair to replace Elon Musk - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/tesla-elon-musk-chairman-replacement-robyn-denholm-board-electric-car-a8623646.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN2sMa8lAj0Qljhbf3r6sTAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/tesla-elon-musk-chairman-replacement-robyn-denholm-board-electric-car-a8623646.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla names Robyn Denholm as new chair to replace Elon Musk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla has named Robyn Denholm as its new chair to take the place of Elon Musk after he was forced to relinquish the position as part of a settlement with US regulators. Tesla was ordered to appoint an independent chair to its board under Mr Musk’s settlement with the Securities and Exchange Committee (SEC), after claims he committed fraud by tweeting that he had “funding secured” to take the company private. It is hoped a strong outside voice will rein in Mr Musk who remains chief executive and is hugely powerful at the electric car company. - Read more Tesla share price plummets after Elon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Samsung is working on a TV that you can control using your thoughts - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/13/samsung-working-tv-can-control-using-thoughts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM-b8IQ8D5gxwacBiJPnPEYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 13:01:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/13/samsung-working-tv-can-control-using-thoughts/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung is working on a TV that you can control using your thoughts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The days of hunting for the TV remote could be numbered. Samsung has announced that it is working on software that will allow viewers to control their television using the power of thought. The South Korean tech giant hopes it could someday be used by people with physical disabilities to easily control electronics without the help of others. The project, named Pontis, is being undertaken with the help the Center of Neuroprosthetics of the Ecole Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne (EPFL) in Switzerland. Samsung recently unveiled a prototype of the system during its developer conference in San...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Hyperloop train might be coming to India - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/hyperloop-india-mumbai-pune-train/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGnu_zfjGkleB5kx3IGpcbUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 04:16:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/hyperloop-india-mumbai-pune-train/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hyperloop train might be coming to India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mumbai to Pune in less than half an hour? That could be the case if a new train concept comes to India. Virgin Hyperloop One is a Los Angeles company originally based on an idea by Tesla founder Elon Musk. The company's goal is to transform public transportation by creating "hyperloops," or pods that whiz people through tunnels at high speeds in order to get from place to place more quickly. The company has just hired Jay Walder as their new CEO, and his plans for the business -- which has Virgin founder Richard Branson as its chairman -- are ambitious. Its first project will be a hyperloop...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Tesla chairwoman's biggest challenge is controlling Musk - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/2b4c621fde3f465e8772cef94078f973</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECRCWZrh5yd17W6U6UVboBMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 22:17:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/2b4c621fde3f465e8772cef94078f973" target="_blank"&gt;New Tesla chairwoman's biggest challenge is controlling Musk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Australian telecommunications executive Robyn Denholm brings much-needed financial and auto industry expertise to her new role as Tesla's board chairwoman, but her biggest challenge is whether she can rein in a CEO with a proclivity for misbehavior. Denholm, who has been a Tesla board member for nearly five years, was named to the post late Wednesday, replacing Elon Musk as part of a securities fraud settlement with U.S. government regulators. Corporate governance experts say they would have preferred an outsider with manufacturing expertise be appointed to lead the board, no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>NASA says humans could land on Mars in 25 years - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/443989-nasa-mars-25-years/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEuPo9MNgKLTQoYdL55r8jIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/443989-nasa-mars-25-years/" target="_blank"&gt;NASA says humans could land on Mars in 25 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NASA has said that the first human flights to Mars could take place in 25 years, as long as someone comes up with the technology to properly shield astronauts from deadly radiation. With Mars around 140 million miles from Earth, sending humans there poses difficulties far beyond anything faced by the Apollo missions to the moon. With current rocket technology, Mars is a nine month journey, during which astronauts would be at the mercy of solar radiation and muscle decay from prolonged exposure to zero gravity conditions. “The cost of solving those means that under current budgets, or slight...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk has a new boss at Tesla - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/08/tech/tesla-robyn-denholm-telstra/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZywy-yDcaRbmVpFwpraU8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 05:37:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/08/tech/tesla-robyn-denholm-telstra/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk has a new boss at Tesla&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla has chosen a new leader for its board of directors after Elon Musk was forced to step down. The electric car company said late Wednesday that Musk will be succeeded by Robyn Denholm, the chief financial officer of Australian telecommunications company Telstra. Denholm, who is already a member of Tesla's (TLSA) board, will begin working at the company full time after her six-month notice period with Telstra is over. "To ensure a smooth transition during the remainder of Robyn's time at Telstra (TLSYY), Elon will be a resource to Robyn and provide any support that she requests in her ro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Low-key Robyn Denholm takes on challenge of taming Elon Musk - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/32bb0428-e3cc-11e8-a6e5-792428919cee</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIe2-RIV6kDGrHDcYiaKO5kqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 07:34:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/32bb0428-e3cc-11e8-a6e5-792428919cee" target="_blank"&gt;Low-key Robyn Denholm takes on challenge of taming Elon Musk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robyn Denholm, a backroom finance operative with a firm but low-key manner, seems an unlikely choice to take on one of the toughest jobs in corporate America: taming the mercurial Elon Musk. But at least some people who have followed the career of the Australian-born accountant believe that taking on the chairmanship of electric carmaker Tesla — a title she was handed late on Wednesday — was not as unlikely as it might sound. “She has a proven record for dealing with very high-ego individuals,” said Pierre Ferragu, a Wall Street analyst who covered Juniper Networks, where Ms Denholm was emp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>