<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Airbnb - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV3Y1cxemVuQVNBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:09:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Airbnb rentals in London block sparks call for action - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/3aa0bd72-fa01-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDq3Vzwj4L2WBNyCv0jHps8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:06:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3aa0bd72-fa01-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb rentals in London block sparks call for action&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 100 apartments in a London block are under investigation for being let out illegally, in a dramatic illustration of the potential of Airbnb and other short-term rental platforms to disrupt city life. Westminster City Council says it has reason to believe that 106 of the 530 flats in Park West, a mansion block near Hyde Park in central London, are being used as short-term rentals rather than residential accommodation. Residents say they feel like they are living in a hotel, rather than an apartment building. “These people treat the place like a hotel because they have no interest, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Resort Security Guard Arrested After Florida Woman Found Dead Near Her Airbnb in Costa Rica - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/resort-security-guard-arrested-after-florida-woman-found-dead-near-her-airbnb-in-costa-rica</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP9dF0Pf1xaFmpm-2WEZUEcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:07:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/resort-security-guard-arrested-after-florida-woman-found-dead-near-her-airbnb-in-costa-rica" target="_blank"&gt;Resort Security Guard Arrested After Florida Woman Found Dead Near Her Airbnb in Costa Rica&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;via Facebook Carla Stefaniak flew to Costa Rica planning to celebrate her 36th birthday in style. She booked the tropical Villa Le Mas resort via Airbnb for her final night before the flight back home to Miami—but she never made it to the airport. In retrospect, perhaps the TripAdvisor reviews offered a clue. One review warned that the place was “scary” and another that it was like a prison. "This place is a nightmare," one reviewer wrote in part. "I fled before the end of my stay and contacted the police... The gates were closed at night and I felt like a prisoner." On Monday, sniffer dogs...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>10 reasons to explore Britain's wildest corner - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/united-kingdom/scotland/orkney/articles/britains-wildest-corner/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKRtIJYksdMaY5u68RkYXYAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:25:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/united-kingdom/scotland/orkney/articles/britains-wildest-corner/" target="_blank"&gt;10 reasons to explore Britain's wildest corner&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this week, Airbnb revealed their top 19 destinations to visit for 2019 and among far-flung destinations such as New Zealand’s Kaikoura and the USA’s Great Smoky Mountains, sits Scotland’s Outer Hebrides. "Based on a combination of Airbnb search, booking and wish list growth data, we’re forecasting growing interest in more off-the-beaten-path regions, cities and towns to explore," stated the peer-to-peer tech company behind the boom in the sharing economy. Airbnb isn't the only one predicting that next year will be a big year for Scotland’s north. The Highlands and islands also made ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Lyft Confidentially Files For IPO To Try To Beat Uber To The Public Market - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bizcarson/2018/12/06/lyft-confidentially-files-for-ipo-to-try-to-beat-uber-to-the-public-market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAswjVo403ufCS4Y19ULGR8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:45:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bizcarson/2018/12/06/lyft-confidentially-files-for-ipo-to-try-to-beat-uber-to-the-public-market/" target="_blank"&gt;Lyft Confidentially Files For IPO To Try To Beat Uber To The Public Market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=0] In a race between ride-hailing companies to go public, Lyft announced Thursday that it’s first to confidentially file a draft S-1 with the Securities and Exchange Commission. According to Lyft’s statement, the number of shares to be offered and price range has not yet been determined. Private investors most recently valued the company at $15.1 billion after a $600 million funding round in June 2018. Private funding hasn’t been scarce for ride-hailing companies, as Lyft and other rivals have raised billions to build out their businesses. However, going public will be the first test to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Will Airbnb move from home-sharing to home-building? - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/will-airbnb-move-from-home-sharing-to-home-building-2018-11-29</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDXgxrwx_WcK5BiRjSKj2ngqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 16:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/will-airbnb-move-from-home-sharing-to-home-building-2018-11-29" target="_blank"&gt;Will Airbnb move from home-sharing to home-building?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KEY WORDS By Andrea Riquier A founder of the company that disrupted hotels wants to do the same for housing . Getty Images ‘An endeavor to design and prototype new ways of building and sharing homes...’ — Joe Gebbia That’s how Airbnb Chief Product Officer Joe Gebbia describes a new initiative that will take the company from a platform on which homeowners can list rooms for rent to a developer of altogether new properties. Gebbia told Fast Company that his team is thinking about all types of housing, from the small in-law cottages that often sit in backyards to single-family houses and multi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>The Top Creative Cities and Countries of 2018 According to Airbnb - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/906924/the-top-creative-cities-and-countries-of-2018-according-to-airbnb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGnxlVlOyKeaz6Zj5MkAm4cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/906924/the-top-creative-cities-and-countries-of-2018-according-to-airbnb" target="_blank"&gt;The Top Creative Cities and Countries of 2018 According to Airbnb&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tianjin Binhai Library / MVRDV + Tianjin Urban Planning and Design Institute. Image © Ossip Van Duivenbode As 2018 draws to a close, accommodation website Airbnb has dived into their data to reveal the most creative cities and countries from the year. Based on the percentage of hosts who are in the creative industries, the list builds on a previous survey by Airbnb which found that one in 10 Airbnb hosts and one in three Experience hosts identify as members of the creative community. Read on below for the list of top creative countries and cities according to the new Airbnb study. For archi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Airbnb will start selling houses in 2019 - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90271599/exclusive-airbnb-will-start-selling-houses-in-2019</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP4e0So6XQpfmP1zrL5I4qkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90271599/exclusive-airbnb-will-start-selling-houses-in-2019" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Airbnb will start selling houses in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After launching a home-sharing revolution, Airbnb’s founders started asking themselves, “What’s next?” They successfully created a global network of more than 5 million homes, castles, and treehouses for rent, and their business is worth an estimated $38 billion. But what else could Airbnb become? It’s a question that led chief product officer and cofounder Joe Gebbia to start a futures division of Airbnb in 2016, meant to develop new products and services for the company. Gebbia’s answer to what Airbnb can be next: architect and urban planner. Not just the company that provides the housing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Airbnb hires Amazon veteran as CFO ahead of potential IPO - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-airbnb-moves-idUSKCN1NV1S0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBBUe9mwpK7lEUDqxkxWIwoqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 03:31:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-airbnb-moves-idUSKCN1NV1S0" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb hires Amazon veteran as CFO ahead of potential IPO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Home-renting company Airbnb Inc on Monday hired Amazon.com Inc (AMZN.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) veteran Dave Stephenson as chief financial officer (CFO), ahead of a widely anticipated initial public offering next year. Stephenson's departure was followed by the exit of another Amazon veteran, Jason Warnick, who is leaving the e-commerce giant to become CFO at online brokerage startup Robinhood. Stephenson will start in early January, Airbnb said in a statement here, and will replace Laurence Tosi, who left the company in February. Stephenson, a who has worked at Amazon for 17 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>30,000 empty homes and nowhere to live: inside Dublin’s housing crisis - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2018/nov/29/empty-dublin-housing-crisis-airbnb-homelessness-landlords</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMvyZdUnTWZTQO46Sug8VNUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 06:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2018/nov/29/empty-dublin-housing-crisis-airbnb-homelessness-landlords" target="_blank"&gt;30,000 empty homes and nowhere to live: inside Dublin’s housing crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The room Jenny Quinn shares with her 10-year-old son is about 10 sq metres, kitted out with the most basic furniture and dominated by what looks like a prison-issue metal bunkbed on which they both sleep. There is a small en suite bathroom; behind a heavy wooden shutter, the window looks out on to a bare expanse of concrete. “He’s in drama therapy in school, for anxiety,” she tells me. “He cries a lot. He doesn’t believe in Santy [Father Christmas] any more. He’s not an angry child, but he’s lonely: he’s so, so lonely. There’s no kids his age here: they’re all babies. The PlayStation’s his ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Airbnb hires Amazon finance chief as new CFO - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/airbnb-hires-amazon-finance-chief-as-new-cfo-2018-11-26</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA2eCks_IleA0SGfQDqmPmoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/airbnb-hires-amazon-finance-chief-as-new-cfo-2018-11-26" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb hires Amazon finance chief as new CFO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WALL STREET JOURNAL By Nina Trentmann Company ramping up for IPO in 2019 Airbnb was valued by investors at $31 billion as of a capital raise in March 2017. Getty Images Airbnb Inc. has hired another executive from Amazon.com Inc., this time naming Dave Stephenson as chief financial officer of the vacation-rental portal ahead of a potential initial public offering. Stephenson will join the San Francisco-based company in early January, according to a company blog post, and will report to Airbnb Chief Executive Brian Chesky. He joins Airbnb after 17 years at Amazon (AMZN) , where he was m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Jewish Americans sue Airbnb over West Bank listing ban - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-airbnb-lawsuit-israel/jewish-americans-sue-airbnb-over-west-bank-listing-ban-idUSKCN1NX2V1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELFQWdcU_V9NNyXMDkRcpD0qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 22:53:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-airbnb-lawsuit-israel/jewish-americans-sue-airbnb-over-west-bank-listing-ban-idUSKCN1NX2V1" target="_blank"&gt;Jewish Americans sue Airbnb over West Bank listing ban&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of Jewish Americans sued Airbnb Inc on Wednesday in U.S. federal court, accusing the home rental company of religious discrimination over its decision last week to remove listings for about 200 homes in the Israeli-occupied West Bank. The 18 plaintiffs, including Israeli-American families and individuals who said they own or wish to rent affected homes, accused Airbnb of "redlining" Jewish-owned properties while letting Muslims and Christians rent their homes. They said this effectively left Airbnb taking sides in the dispute over the West Bank, where Palestinians hope to establish ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>From Airbnb to city bikes, the ‘sharing economy’ has been seized by big money - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/27/airbnb-city-bikes-sharing-economy-big-money</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFQzMbYHOXPmW9IA6wmCcOAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 06:00:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/27/airbnb-city-bikes-sharing-economy-big-money" target="_blank"&gt;From Airbnb to city bikes, the ‘sharing economy’ has been seized by big money&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of all the ideologies spawned by Silicon Valley, that of techno-populism – the making of empty promises on the basis of seismic digital disruption – is the strangest. Promising a world of immediate and painless personal empowerment, techno-populism is ambiguous enough to unite big tech firms, startups, cryptocurrency aficionados and even some political parties. The history is murky, but we do know the date when it went mainstream. It can be traced to Time magazine’s selection, in 2006, of “You” – the millions of ordinary people behind the user-generated web of the 2000s – as its Person of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Airbnb taps veteran Amazon executive as new CFO - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0b087054-f183-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB6kW6iAFSQTV2IYbGXcoEsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 14:19:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0b087054-f183-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb taps veteran Amazon executive as new CFO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Airbnb has tapped a senior Amazon executive as its new chief financial officer following a 10 month search, in a move that could help put the home rental website back on track for a possible initial public offering in 2019. Dave Stephenson will start at Airbnb in January, the company said in a blog post on Monday. He was most recently vice-president and CFO of Amazon’s Worldwide Consumer Organization, which is responsible for all global website sales. “In this role, he oversaw gross merchandise sales in excess of $250 billion and helped the business achieve double digit revenue and operatin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>On A Rainforest Adventure Trip, A Treehouse Is The Only Way To Stay - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/lenakatz/2018/11/27/on-a-rainforest-adventure-trip-a-treehouse-is-the-only-way-to-stay/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPL6qdk0UQIwZNFWswqGIb8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/lenakatz/2018/11/27/on-a-rainforest-adventure-trip-a-treehouse-is-the-only-way-to-stay/" target="_blank"&gt;On A Rainforest Adventure Trip, A Treehouse Is The Only Way To Stay&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come to the rainforest; stay in a tree. According to bohemian-minded travelers from the United States and Europe, this is a time-honored way to live in tropical paradise. And a multitude of fancified treehouse vacation rentals have popped up in the past decade, catering to the authentic experience seeker who wants a bit more than bare bones — er, branches. But what destination is safe enough, more or less moderate climate, and possessed of near-endless rainforest? I’d first call out Costa Rica–a destination well positioned in the safe middleground between off-the-map getaway and tourism ce...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Déjà Vu: Online Travel Agents Face Up To Challenge Of Airbnb - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/paulnoelguely/2018/11/26/deja-vu-online-travel-agents-face-up-to-challenge-of-airbnb/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKPAY3q5BdGMgWtU3yGJJ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/paulnoelguely/2018/11/26/deja-vu-online-travel-agents-face-up-to-challenge-of-airbnb/" target="_blank"&gt;Déjà Vu: Online Travel Agents Face Up To Challenge Of Airbnb&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wrote recently on how M&amp;A within the travel industry has not only been the inevitable response of large incumbents to technological disruption in the sector; it has also provided a clear indicator of which new technologies are most likely to change how we take vacations in the future, such as the ability to create complex, tailored, multi-day tours on digital platforms. However, it would be remiss to think of the acquisitions made by large online travel agents (or “OTAs”) just in terms of a defensive move to stave off the challenge of the Internet giants. Consolidation in the metasearch m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Israel to turn to U.S. government over Airbnb removal of settlement listings - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-palestinians-airbnb/israel-to-turn-to-us-government-over-airbnb-removal-of-settlement-listings-idUSKCN1NP19W</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI3-76tyWODDkwvgSdpk_80qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 19:32:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-palestinians-airbnb/israel-to-turn-to-us-government-over-airbnb-removal-of-settlement-listings-idUSKCN1NP19W" target="_blank"&gt;Israel to turn to U.S. government over Airbnb removal of settlement listings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel plans to consult with the U.S. government over a decision by home-renting company to remove listings in Jewish settlements in the Israeli-occupied West Bank, a cabinet minister said on Tuesday. Palestinians who want to establish an independent state in territory including the West Bank that Israel captured in a 1967 war welcomed the San Francisco-based firm's move, announced on Monday and taking effect in the coming days. Israel called it a "wretched capitulation" to boycotters. "We will approach the U.S. government because 25 U.S. states have sanctions against American companies tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Israeli minister urges Airbnb boycott, talks up rival service - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/israel-palestinians-airbnb/israeli-minister-urges-airbnb-boycott-talks-up-rival-service-idUSL8N1XW2BM</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPczGfUYp2Oir1DhmTtybUIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 12:25:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/israel-palestinians-airbnb/israeli-minister-urges-airbnb-boycott-talks-up-rival-service-idUSL8N1XW2BM" target="_blank"&gt;Israeli minister urges Airbnb boycott, talks up rival service&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Israeli cabinet minister called on Wednesday for a boycott of Airbnb and promoted one of its rivals, escalating the government's response to the home-rental company's decision to delist Israel's settlements in the occupied West Bank. "I call today on all those who support Israel and oppose discriminatory boycotts: they should cease using Airbnb and turn to other services," Strategic Affairs Minister Gilad Erdan told a diplomatic conference hosted by the Jerusalem Post newspaper. "By the way, Booking.com is a great service," added Erdan, the point-man in Israeli government efforts to comb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>OMG I Want To Rent This House: Stellenbosch, South Africa (Photos) - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/omg-i-want-to-rent-this-house-stellenbosch-south-africa-photos</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEArNNKGiEkwjnLKb6xXezYAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 02:30:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/omg-i-want-to-rent-this-house-stellenbosch-south-africa-photos" target="_blank"&gt;OMG I Want To Rent This House: Stellenbosch, South Africa (Photos)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Daily Beast presents a look at one of the most insane houses in the world. With the blustery winds of winter beginning to blow across the U.S., it’s time to turn your attention to the southern shores. (Good rule of thumb: always pine after the weather you don’t currently have.) We have six words for you: flower farm, wine country, South Africa. That’s right, while your loved ones are shoveling snow, you can be having the most delightful getaway of your life courtesy of a charming farmhouse called Johannesdal. Rent on Airbnb Airbnb With a lovely farmhouse in an even more beautiful settin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Travel M&amp;A Will Provide Guidebook To The Vacations Of The Future - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/paulnoelguely/2018/11/23/travel-ma-will-provide-guidebook-to-the-vacations-of-the-future/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOnvsDCJiwtzW5XRMx-0DM4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/paulnoelguely/2018/11/23/travel-ma-will-provide-guidebook-to-the-vacations-of-the-future/" target="_blank"&gt;Travel M&amp;A Will Provide Guidebook To The Vacations Of The Future&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In few sectors has the transition to a digital economy been as conspicuous or as widely felt as travel. What was previously a quintessential bricks-and-mortar industry with a ubiquitous high-street presence has, in almost all developed markets, moved online. In the UK, 62% of all travel bookings were made via the Internet in 2016, according to Phocuswright data. The rise of a new generation of tech companies, such as Airbnb and Hong Kong-based Klook, has shaken up the last sleepy backwaters of the travel sector. And, reliable as clockwork, where a sector undergoes technological disruption, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Airbnb removes Israeli West Bank settlements listings - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/20/middleeast/airbnb-israel-west-bank-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMYwFDPIBFEk3sfl5WirTtMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 19:10:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/20/middleeast/airbnb-israel-west-bank-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb removes Israeli West Bank settlements listings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Airbnb has announced that it is removing listings of rentals in Israeli settlements in the West Bank, saying they are "at the core of the dispute between Israelis and Palestinians." In a press release issued Monday, the company said the decision would affect some 200 Airbnb listings. "We are most certainly not the experts when it comes to the historical disputes in this region. Our team has wrestled with this issue and we have struggled to come up with the right approach," the statement said. "We concluded that we should remove listings in Israeli settlements in the occupied West Bank that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Airbnb bags more than $1bn in quarterly revenue - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1d13d21c-e9c6-11e8-a34c-663b3f553b35</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDz1fFtkktyo-rRTrweCCWgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 18:18:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1d13d21c-e9c6-11e8-a34c-663b3f553b35" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb bags more than $1bn in quarterly revenue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Airbnb said Friday it booked more than $1bn in third-quarter revenue, driven by international growth in bookings. The home rental start-up is seen as a candidate to go public in 2019. Wall Street has speculated that Airbnb, along with Uber and Lyft, could launch initial public offerings next year. Airbnb is currently valued at $31bn. Revenue was “substantially more” than $1bn during the period, Airbnb said in a memo, adding that it was the “strongest quarter” in its 10-year history. The company did not disclose additional financial data. Airbnb said investments in its global footprint have ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Airbnb to take rentals in Israeli West Bank settlements off website - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/19/airbnb-removes-rentals-in-israeli-west-bank-settlements</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP_TH1hE3mu61IRKAQ513EIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 18:56:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/19/airbnb-removes-rentals-in-israeli-west-bank-settlements" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb to take rentals in Israeli West Bank settlements off website&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Airbnb has said it will remove from its website all properties in Israeli settlements built on the occupied Palestinian territories in the West Bank, after years of accusations that the company was benefitting from rentals in the illegal outposts. The accommodation bookings website announced on Monday that around 200 listings would be taken down in what will be seen as a victory for the Palestinian-led anti-occupation movement. “Many in the global community have stated that companies should not do business here because they believe companies should not profit on lands where people have been...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Israel steps up boycott fight after Airbnb settlement ban - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/03e75ec15f4844408771e5b762902a06</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK3l3HNer0pfpdDfJlb57dMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 19:27:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/03e75ec15f4844408771e5b762902a06" target="_blank"&gt;Israel steps up boycott fight after Airbnb settlement ban&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KFAR ADUMIM, West Bank (AP) — Israel said Tuesday it would slap high taxes on vacation rental company Airbnb and encourage legal steps against the site over its decision to ban listings from West Bank settlements. The threats of sanctions ramp up Israel's fight against a global movement advocating for boycotts over the country's treatment of the Palestinians. The Boycott, Divestment, Sanctions campaign, also known as BDS, has claimed a number of successes in recent years, leading Israel to identify it as a major threat. Israeli Tourism Minister Yariv Levin called on Airbnb to reverse what h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Airbnb takes on Boston in its latest legal tussle over short-term rental laws - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90267170/airbnb-takes-on-boston-in-its-latest-legal-tussle-over-short-term-rental-laws</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPKgE8hE2tIaIBtelTzoLKAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 07:00:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90267170/airbnb-takes-on-boston-in-its-latest-legal-tussle-over-short-term-rental-laws" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb takes on Boston in its latest legal tussle over short-term rental laws&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boston just became the latest city to be sued by Airbnb over legislation that forces the home-sharing platform to remove illegal listings or face fines. In addition to the lawsuit, filed Tuesday in U.S. District Court for the District of Massachusetts, Airbnb is seeking an injunction to pause new short-term rental laws that are supposed to take effect in January. The city ordinance says hosts must register with the city and requires Airbnb to take down listings that don’t comply with the law. Airbnb says its job is not to enforce the law, and therefore it shouldn’t be required to remove pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Airbnb to remove listings in Israel's West Bank settlements - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-palestinians-airbnb/airbnb-says-removing-listings-in-west-bank-settlements-idUSKCN1NO1WA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFjQ5S4OKNZBwfX4GnJfhQsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 14:32:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-palestinians-airbnb/airbnb-says-removing-listings-in-west-bank-settlements-idUSKCN1NO1WA" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb to remove listings in Israel's West Bank settlements&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Home-renting company Airbnb Inc said on Monday it would remove listings in Israeli settlements in the occupied West Bank, a move Israel called a "wretched capitulation" to boycotters and Palestinians hailed as a step towards peace. The decision, affecting some 200 listings, would take effect in the coming days, Airbnb said. Israel captured the West Bank in a 1967 war. Its settlements there are considered illegal by most world powers. Palestinians deem the settlements, and the military presence needed to protect them, to be obstacles to their goal of establishing a state. Israel disputes thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Seven Tips For Bringing Vacation Home Renters Back To Your Hotel - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesrealestatecouncil/2018/11/21/seven-tips-for-bringing-vacation-home-renters-back-to-your-hotel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENH4i28LjSis_VNqJISWNBoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesrealestatecouncil/2018/11/21/seven-tips-for-bringing-vacation-home-renters-back-to-your-hotel/" target="_blank"&gt;Seven Tips For Bringing Vacation Home Renters Back To Your Hotel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the rise of services like Airbnb that feature vacation homes rented by owners, travelers have more varied lodging options than ever before. This industry development has had a measurable effect on the profitability of hotels. While it may seem like bad news for traditional hospitality businesses, there’s plenty that hotels can do to keep filling their rooms. According to experts at Forbes Real Estate Council, attracting guests is all about differentiating yourself from owner-rented properties and adapting to what modern travelers want. Here’s how you can successfully market your hotel ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Israel threatens to slap high taxes on Airbnb after firm bans listings in illegal West Bank settlements - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/israel-airbnb-taxes-west-bank-settlements-palestine-bds-boycott-middle-east-a8644361.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMc64Y07lx1p4Nje1MKaOf8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 11:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/israel-airbnb-taxes-west-bank-settlements-palestine-bds-boycott-middle-east-a8644361.html" target="_blank"&gt;Israel threatens to slap high taxes on Airbnb after firm bans listings in illegal West Bank settlements&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel has threatened to slap high taxes on Airbnb and encourage legal cases against the accommodation website, over its decision to ban listings from West Bank settlements which are considered illegal by most world powers. Tourism minister, Yariv Levin, called on the firm to reverse what he called a “discriminatory decision” and “disgraceful surrender” to the boycott movement. He vowed that Israel would retaliate. “If you have a policy of discrimination against Israelis you cannot earn money in Israel,” he said. Read more - Airbnb to remove listings in Israel’s West Bank settlements - Isra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>How a new credit card spoiled my holiday – and cost me £1,400 - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/advice/card-details-up-to-date-online-booking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIANKaCv2cV7HkS98Ld_7TMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 12:03:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/advice/card-details-up-to-date-online-booking/" target="_blank"&gt;How a new credit card spoiled my holiday – and cost me £1,400&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frances Kirk writes On a recent family trip to Vancouver we discovered that our pre-booked Airbnb apartment was occupied when we let ourselves in using a key code given to us by the host. On contacting both Airbnb and the host, it transpired that Airbnb had cancelled our booking due to non-payment. The reason given was that it hadn’t been able to collect the second instalment from my credit card. The first, for £342, had been paid in January but I had forgotten to update my payment details when a new card was issued. I did not receive a single message regarding this prior to our arrival on ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Dueling boycotts? Airbnb pledges to remove occupied West Bank settlement listings, Israel hits back - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/444407-airbnb-boycott-west-bank/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPsAMrCtQUKp194q5tXX3ScqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 01:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/444407-airbnb-boycott-west-bank/" target="_blank"&gt;Dueling boycotts? Airbnb pledges to remove occupied West Bank settlement listings, Israel hits back&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global home-rental company Airbnb says it will remove listings of homes located in Israeli settlements in the occupied West Bank. Israeli officials have predictably called the move anti-Semitic and a surrender to terrorism. Human Rights Watch applauded Airbnb's move, which came a day before the group's publication of a (presumably damning) report on the human rights impact of tourist rental listings in settlements. Waleed Assraf, who runs an anti-settlement group for the Palestinian Liberation Organization, was hopeful other companies would follow Airbnb's example, noting "this will contrib...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Airbnb not significantly hurting rental affordability in Sydney and Melbourne, report reveals - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-08/airbnb-not-worsening-rental-affordability-sydney-melbourne/10474580</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFEwwMoqaxuwyiNZuttMg_MqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 13:06:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-08/airbnb-not-worsening-rental-affordability-sydney-melbourne/10474580" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb not significantly hurting rental affordability in Sydney and Melbourne, report reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Airbnb isn't making rental affordability "significantly" worse, but it is reducing the number of properties that are available for long-term renters in Sydney and Melbourne. Key points: - Highest concentration of Sydney's and Melbourne's Airbnb listings are in the inner-city and beachside suburbs - 9-15pc of rental properties in those 'high demand' areas are listed on Airbnb - Study shows this trend results in fewer options for long-term renters According to a new report, released today, that applies especially to the "high-demand" suburbs with "significant tourism appeal". The report by th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Apple, Uber and Airbnb in firing line of tech tax - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/03/apple-uber-airbnb-infiring-line-tech-tax/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI3mg0wgU4nVuXgIfMJ1ZA0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/03/apple-uber-airbnb-infiring-line-tech-tax/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple, Uber and Airbnb in firing line of tech tax&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple, Uber and Airbnb face being snared by Philip Hammond’s tech tax crackdown. The Treasury last week unveiled a “digital services tax” that will impose a levy on Silicon Valley giants’ revenues. The 2pc tax is being imposed on advertising revenues from search engines and social networks, as well as commissions from “online marketplaces” – apps and websites that connect sellers and buyers. Amazon and eBay appear the most likely victims of the marketplace tax, but the policy will also apply to online services as well as to goods, sources familiar with the matter said. The Treasury declined...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Airbnb landlords agree to pay San Francisco $2.25 million - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/6f72322a2d144dc6ae9fce50b5afd0e8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKq0PascGk651DG_9hxjNmsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 00:49:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/6f72322a2d144dc6ae9fce50b5afd0e8" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb landlords agree to pay San Francisco $2.25 million&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — A San Francisco couple has agreed to pay $2.25 million to the city for illegally renting out 14 apartments as Airbnb units. City Attorney Dennis Herrera announced the settlement Monday, calling the penalty an important deterrent to others seeking to illegally profit from the city's housing crisis. The San Francisco Chronicle reported that Darren and Valerie Lee agreed to pay the money as penalties and investigation costs. An attorney for the Lees, John C. Brown, did not immediately respond to a call seeking comment Monday. The Lees were also barred for at least seven ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Meet America's Most Expensive Airbnbs - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alyyale/2018/11/02/meet-americas-most-expensive-airbnbs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGhiJG9Pr94KfKkntUWYU2sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alyyale/2018/11/02/meet-americas-most-expensive-airbnbs/" target="_blank"&gt;Meet America's Most Expensive Airbnbs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;London, UK – July 31, 2018: The buttons of the travel app Airbnb, surrounded by Amazon, ebay, News and other apps on the screen of an iPhone. The nation’s most luxe Airbnbs aren’t in the busy, bustling metros you’d expect. In fact, according to a new analysis, the country’s single most expensive short-term rental is in the heart of Midwest: in a quaint small town just outside of St. Louis, Missouri. With 80 acres of rolling hills and accommodations for 16-plus guests, Missouri’s Red Rock Ranch is the nation’s costliest Airbnb. The digs are stocked with a full bar, and guests have access to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Airbnb not to blame for Tasmanian housing crisis, boss tells inquiry - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-02/airbnb-not-to-blame-for-tasmanian-housing-shortage-boss-says/10458972</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBYzbsOxSOYNflsUD1tjNdAqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 02:02:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-02/airbnb-not-to-blame-for-tasmanian-housing-shortage-boss-says/10458972" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb not to blame for Tasmanian housing crisis, boss tells inquiry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Airbnb does not want short-stay accommodation hosts to become scapegoats for Tasmania's housing shortage, a national boss has told a parliamentary inquiry. Australian head of public policy Brent Thomas has given evidence to a Legislative Council inquiry into short-stay accommodation in Hobart. He said the perception Airbnb is contributing to Tasmania's accommodation shortage is a myth and other factors are responsible for the rental market squeeze. "Massive amounts of people moving in here to Tasmania and not enough housing being built, more university places being opened up and not enough ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>OMG, I Want This House: Bali (Photos) - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/omg-i-want-this-house-bali-photos</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG465fn-2yrHZULDNuFMi6IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 01:23:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/omg-i-want-this-house-bali-photos" target="_blank"&gt;OMG, I Want This House: Bali (Photos)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast The Daily Beast presents a look at one of the most insane houses in the world. We know, we know, everyone is going to Bali these days. So it’s about time you join in the fun and one-up your jet-setting competitors—er, friends—by booking this gorgeous and serene villa near the city of Pererenan. The ideal mix of modern and traditional, of luxurious and…well, luxurious, The Palm House is the perfect spot to treat your 11 closest friends to a getaway to remember. Or, at just over $600 a night, be the gracious host that you are and let them treat you. Rent ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Court orders Paris tenant to pay all Airbnb earnings to landlord - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/28/court-orders-paris-tenant-pay-airbnb-earnings-landlord/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELz9wztBiOVUUALKIpaBhTEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 12:42:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/28/court-orders-paris-tenant-pay-airbnb-earnings-landlord/" target="_blank"&gt;Court orders Paris tenant to pay all Airbnb earnings to landlord&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A court has ordered a tenant who regularly sub-let her Paris flat on Airbnb to pay all her earnings to her landlady as France cracks down harder on holiday rentals. The tenant must pay her landlady nearly £42,000 earned from short-term rentals since 2011, in addition to £1,800 in damages and legal fees. She breached the law by failing to obtain written consent from the property owner. Like other cities around the world, Paris is restricting holiday rentals in an attempt to alleviate a growing housing crisis, but it is the first time a French court has handed out such a severe punishment to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Airbnb can’t go on unregulated – it does too much damage to cities - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/24/airbnb-unregulated-damage-cities-barcelona-law-locals</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDAgaaxGgGyZ5H8b4U0CH3EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 08:30:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/24/airbnb-unregulated-damage-cities-barcelona-law-locals" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb can’t go on unregulated – it does too much damage to cities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember the “sharing economy”? That rhetoric looks more comically disingenuous than ever in light of the news that a single Airbnb user in Barcelona is managing a portfolio of properties that brings in an eye-watering £33,000 a day in high season. Old neighbourhoods are being overrun with short-term tourists and shops selling souvenir tat. Rents for residents are being driven up, in Barcelona as well as Berlin, New York and elsewhere. Airbnb is a parasitic monster that squats over cities and hoovers up vast sums of money through its slimy proboscis. So what can be done? Airbnb, short for “...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How to monetise your home – the ugly message of Netflix’s new show - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/28/how-to-monetise-your-home-ugly-message-netflix-show-airbnb-arwa-mahdawi</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFaItwgWuDW9i5p1oY_O2CoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 15:00:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/28/how-to-monetise-your-home-ugly-message-netflix-show-airbnb-arwa-mahdawi" target="_blank"&gt;How to monetise your home – the ugly message of Netflix’s new show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking for a new Netflix show to watch? Something with a late-capitalist theme, perhaps? Something that leaves you feeling just a little bit empty inside? Well, I have just the series. I recently discovered Stay Here, a property programme with a modern twist. Instead of featuring hard-to-please couples searching for their dream home, Stay Here features a couple of extremely irritating real estate experts, who are helping people optimise their homes for Airbnb. The hosts traverse the US giving homeowners design and marketing tips so they can “succeed in the world of short-term rental”. A sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Bold Brand Storytelling: Lessons From Companies Who Take A Stance - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ekaterinawalter/2018/11/01/bold-brand-storytelling-lessons-from-companies-who-take-a-stance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECqzL6hqif-uzgvMTXijtm0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ekaterinawalter/2018/11/01/bold-brand-storytelling-lessons-from-companies-who-take-a-stance/" target="_blank"&gt;Bold Brand Storytelling: Lessons From Companies Who Take A Stance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s never been more important for companies to take a stance. Companies that take a stance and bring bold stories to life about the issues, values and causes that matter the most to them have a powerful opportunity to make a difference while attracting like-minded customers. Interestingly, while companies stand poised to reap the rewards of bold brand storytelling, it’s actually their consumers who are asking for this level of transparency. Research from Sprout Social uncovered that two-thirds of consumers believe it is important for brands to take a public stance on social and political i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Barcelona Airbnb host 'manages rentals worth £33,000 a day' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2018/oct/22/barcelona-airbnb-host-manages-rentals-worth-33000-a-day-report</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF7Ewfgx4J3aYz0T587-eW4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 14:52:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2018/oct/22/barcelona-airbnb-host-manages-rentals-worth-33000-a-day-report" target="_blank"&gt;Barcelona Airbnb host 'manages rentals worth £33,000 a day'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One Airbnb “host” manages a portfolio of 204 apartments in Barcelona worth €37,721 (£33,369) a day in rental income during the high season, a data organisation established to look into Spain’s tourist apartment industry has found. The 10 biggest hosts in the Spanish city manage 996 apartments between them, while a further 666 manage five or more, and 3,633 host between two and four, the report by DataHippo found. Altogether the rent for licensed holiday apartments let via Airbnb and other platforms comes to €1.5m a day. The findings appear to contradict the “shared economy” image projected ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Are Bleisure Trips Becoming More Common? This Study Says Yes. - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnnyjet/2018/10/25/are-bleisure-trips-becoming-more-common-this-study-says-yes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJPP-kI5uHXx3dPV1uIXoAYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnnyjet/2018/10/25/are-bleisure-trips-becoming-more-common-this-study-says-yes/" target="_blank"&gt;Are Bleisure Trips Becoming More Common? This Study Says Yes.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most work trips used to strictly be for business. However, an SAP Concur study shows otherwise. In fact, “bleisure trips” are becoming more common with business travelers tacking on an extra day or two to sightsee. And it’s not just millennials that are mixing business with leisure when they travel. Bleisure Trips are Up 20% How do we know more people are extending their business trips? SAP Concur – Hipmunk travel and expense data from 2017 show a 20% uptick in bleisure trips. For this study, a “bleisure trip” included a Saturday night stay. But, it’s not uncommon for bleisure trips to exte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Airbnb’s Chip Conley is doubling down on being a “modern elder” - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90255475/airbnbs-chip-conley-is-doubling-down-on-being-a-modern-elder</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECNzQ56OD7o_2il9zMksc3EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 12:15:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90255475/airbnbs-chip-conley-is-doubling-down-on-being-a-modern-elder" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb’s Chip Conley is doubling down on being a “modern elder”&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chip Conley found himself at a crossroads at age 52. He had already found success with the boutique hotel group Joie de Vivre that he ran as CEO for 24 years. At midlife he wasn’t sure what was next, until he got a call from the young founders of Airbnb, who asked him to join their startup and guide their growth into a hospitality behemoth. Conley was happy to join in, but quickly realized that he lacked the digital fluency he needed to make it in the tech world. He hadn’t heard of the sharing economy and didn’t have the Uber or Lyft apps on his phone, and was neck-deep in a venture that wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>How This Operator Leveraged Remote Work To Build Airbnb's Trust At Scale - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/emilyjoffrion/2018/10/18/how-this-operator-leveraged-remote-work-to-build-airbnbs-trust-at-scale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_KIcn9_nN-bqL-HqoXxPEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/emilyjoffrion/2018/10/18/how-this-operator-leveraged-remote-work-to-build-airbnbs-trust-at-scale/" target="_blank"&gt;How This Operator Leveraged Remote Work To Build Airbnb's Trust At Scale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talia Page In Airbnb’s early days, scams on sites like Craigslist and VRBO were prolific. So, to build trust, co-founders Brian Chesky and Joe Gebbia put their art school skills to work taking verified photos of Airbnb listings. This scrappy “do things that don’t scale” approach worked. But how do you take something that doesn’t scale and make it, well, scale? They looked to operator Talia Page who built a team of remote photographers that stretched around the world. And, by scaling verified photography, Page brought trust— and value—to Airbnb. We sat down with Page to learn how she built A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Vacasa proves the quiet power of vacation rentals with $64M in new funding - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90253005/vacasa-proves-the-quiet-power-of-vacation-rentals-with-64m-in-new-funding</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJbI9UZ8CbTILZsGRSLlWD8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 09:00:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90253005/vacasa-proves-the-quiet-power-of-vacation-rentals-with-64m-in-new-funding" target="_blank"&gt;Vacasa proves the quiet power of vacation rentals with $64M in new funding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vacation rentals have always been a sleepy business. Vacasa wants to shake it up. The property management company has announced a new $64 million round of funding, bringing its total capital raised to $207.5 million. Vacasa lists homes for rent on its platform much like Airbnb, but the company also manages property for homeowners, handling everything from marketing and bookings to decor and maintenance. Since the company distributes its listings on other booking platforms, it doesn’t see itself as competing with Airbnb or HomeAway. The company is keen to shift more of its business away from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Uber’s and Airbnb's Plans To Share Their Wealth Could Shake Up Capitalism - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/uber-airbnb-shareholders-sharing-economy_us_5bc4ba37e4b040bb4e84b5ec</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGYAYiZF0WQW7rIC5kNsZqkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMIiW7QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 09:45:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/uber-airbnb-shareholders-sharing-economy_us_5bc4ba37e4b040bb4e84b5ec" target="_blank"&gt;Uber’s and Airbnb's Plans To Share Their Wealth Could Shake Up Capitalism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Uber and Airbnb first appeared on the scene, they pitched themselves as part of the “sharing economy,” along with other platforms that let people lend out their tools, toys and even pets. These projects promised to share resources, reduce consumption and improve people’s lives. Then came stories of racial discrimination on Airbnb, of Uber drivers unable to make ends meet, of worsening traffic and mounting housing costs, and of these multibillion-dollar companies strong-arming and tricking regulators. Clearly, there was a gap ― between the talk of sharing and the behavior of corporate o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Japanese officials are no longer investigating Airbnb - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90249139/japanese-officials-are-no-longer-investigating-airbnb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHjMO-KUuVIVuTFGhBBbaQoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 06:49:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90249139/japanese-officials-are-no-longer-investigating-airbnb" target="_blank"&gt;Japanese officials are no longer investigating Airbnb&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Airbnb just got a big win in Japan. The company has been under investigation by an antitrust watchdog, which was looking into whether the company was stifling competition. Now, the Japanese agency is no longer looking into Airbnb’s practices, according to Reuters. The commission first began the investigation after receiving reports that Airbnb forced some users to not post listings on rival websites. Airbnb now says that’s no longer the case. This comes a few months after Japan enacted a new law that officially made the platform legal in the country. This change, however, caused many listin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Uber pushes for rule change to allow it to give drivers shares - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/12/uber-pushes-rule-change-allow-give-drivers-shares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAa3eEje3O2GKuhHk5-59sIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 12:25:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/12/uber-pushes-rule-change-allow-give-drivers-shares/" target="_blank"&gt;Uber pushes for rule change to allow it to give drivers shares&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Uber is seeking to give its drivers a share of its business, joining Airbnb in calls for US regulators to change rules about security ownership. The ride-hailing company has written to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to say it is the "proper role of public policy and key institutions as well as the private sector to explore avenues to give individuals greater economic security regardless of how they work". Uber has asked for a change to the SEC's "Rule 701", under which companies can issue shares to employees, to include so-called "gig economy" workers, who are not officially c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Someone's Trying To Kill Turo, Airbnb And Uber. Here's Why It Matters - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/christopherelliott/2018/10/06/someones-trying-to-kill-turo-airbnb-and-uber-heres-why-it-matters/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJBwbVzf4srw1eBQFlbSOzYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/christopherelliott/2018/10/06/someones-trying-to-kill-turo-airbnb-and-uber-heres-why-it-matters/" target="_blank"&gt;Someone's Trying To Kill Turo, Airbnb And Uber. Here's Why It Matters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Michelle Peacock caught wind of Illinois Senate Bill 2641, an amendment to the state’s Renter’s Financial Responsibility and Protection Act, she knew who was behind it and how to stop it. It was yet another effort by the car rental industry to kill her employer, peer-to-peer car sharing company Turo — and she had to divert. Quickly. The Illinois amendment, which would have added a “personal car facilitation company” as a legal car rental entity in the state, was already headed to a committee vote. The rental industry wants states to reclassify companies such as Turo as car rental compa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Airbnb faces questions from UK tax authorities - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/fe845b30-ca46-11e8-b276-b9069bde0956</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPwQRcb58AxyjIoWOt-5pY8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 03:00:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/fe845b30-ca46-11e8-b276-b9069bde0956" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb faces questions from UK tax authorities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Airbnb’s tax arrangements have come under scrutiny from UK authorities, intensifying pressure on the home-sharing app that has transformed the market for short-term holiday rentals since its launch in 2008. Airbnb, which has faced increasing criticism and legal pressure from international policymakers, said in a filing submitted to Companies House last week that it had been “contacted” by HM Revenue &amp; Customs “regarding the application of tax laws or regulations impacting the company’s business”. It is the first indication from Airbnb UK Limited, the entity that submitted the filing, that t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Airbnb bans host for telling hijab-wearing British PhD student she wouldn’t ‘fit’ into neighborhood - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/440377-airbnb-hijab-banned-host/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDd0fQrAuv6OsMjPch6B_d8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/440377-airbnb-hijab-banned-host/" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb bans host for telling hijab-wearing British PhD student she wouldn’t ‘fit’ into neighborhood&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Homestay website Airbnb has booted a host from its platform after the host declined to accept a Muslim guest, telling a British PhD student she would not “fit” into their neighborhood due to her veil. 25-year-old British neuroscience student Nurjahan Saleque is doing her PhD in Hamburg, Germany. Tired of her commute, she saw an apartment on Airbnb closer to the city that seemed perfect. She reached out to the host ‘Claudia’ –Airbnb only provides the first names of hosts– but her request was declined despite the room being available. According to screenshots of Saleque’s messages to Claudia,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Where Hurricane Michael Evacuees Can Ride Out The Storm -- For Cheap (Or Free) - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alyyale/2018/10/10/where-hurricane-michael-evacuees-can-ride-out-the-storm-for-cheap-or-free/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFF2C34jUAQ20M4BiWvBJTMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 15:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alyyale/2018/10/10/where-hurricane-michael-evacuees-can-ride-out-the-storm-for-cheap-or-free/" target="_blank"&gt;Where Hurricane Michael Evacuees Can Ride Out The Storm -- For Cheap (Or Free)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This satellite image from the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration shows Hurricane Michael inching closer to the Florida coast. As thousands flee the Florida Panhandle in anticipation of Hurricane Michael’s landfall, a major question looms: where will they all go? With prolonged rain and flooding expected throughout most of the coast, there’s no telling how long these evacuees will be gone — and many families don’t have the funds to cover extended hotel stays or vacation rentals. Fortunately, a few hotel chains, along with Airbnb, have stepped in to help. Here’s where Hurricane M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Uber's UK turnover hits £60m despite year of regulatory battles - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/06/ubers-uk-turnover-hits-60m-despite-year-regulatory-battles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDlL897DPqdDKXlhflmW038qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/06/ubers-uk-turnover-hits-60m-despite-year-regulatory-battles/" target="_blank"&gt;Uber's UK turnover hits £60m despite year of regulatory battles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Uber has driven up revenues for its UK business by 61pc despite spending the year battling regulators in London and across the country. Last year, the ride-hailing app was threatened with the loss of its London licence by the city's transport regulator and issued with suspensions in several towns and cities. Despite this, Uber increased its revenues to £59.5m for the year ending in December 2017, up from £36.9m the year before, according to its accounts. Profits at the ride-hailing firm grew by £1.6m to £4.6m. London has been one of Uber's most important international markets outside the US...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Rooms with new views: Hotels try their hand in home-sharing - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/172de877fe09451c99779bbd33572b19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPAWfaGr5PeR8uERS0kvNOYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 11:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/172de877fe09451c99779bbd33572b19" target="_blank"&gt;Rooms with new views: Hotels try their hand in home-sharing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Travelers sometimes want a cookie-cutter room in a downtown hotel, and they sometimes want a cozy Tuscan farmhouse to share with friends. Hotels have always been good at providing the first one. Now, they're trying to figure out how to provide the second — and blunt the growth of competitors like Airbnb. But they're having mixed success. Marriott said Tuesday it's expanding its six-month-old home-sharing pilot in London to three additional European cities. On the same day, Hyatt announced it was pulling out of a money-losing collaboration with luxury home-sharing company Oasis. Analysts say...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Here's how Airbnb went from air mattresses to rental empire - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/10/03/airbnb-orig.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKiOup1RdXt57vUG4Lp1SZcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 22:45:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/10/03/airbnb-orig.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;Here's how Airbnb went from air mattresses to rental empire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Airbnb operates in over 190 countries now. But it started with just a few air mattresses. Here's how the company went from a small startup to rivaling some of the largest hotel chains in the world. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Old Unicorn, New Tricks: Airbnb Has A Sky-High Valuation. Here's Its Audacious Plan To Earn It - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bizcarson/2018/10/03/old-unicorn-new-tricks-airbnb-has-a-sky-high-valuation-heres-its-audacious-plan-to-earn-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB40XlJykofOuxKW6BgCF8QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 10:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bizcarson/2018/10/03/old-unicorn-new-tricks-airbnb-has-a-sky-high-valuation-heres-its-audacious-plan-to-earn-it/" target="_blank"&gt;Old Unicorn, New Tricks: Airbnb Has A Sky-High Valuation. Here's Its Audacious Plan To Earn It&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=29] For a full 32 seconds, the notoriously fidgety Brian Chesky sits still. Planted under a fake tree in a bespoke conference room at Airbnb’s headquarters in San Francisco, the 37-year-old CEO is intently focused on the iPhone in his hands. It’s playing a marketing video showing goats mingling with guests during an Airbnb Experience at a Northern California animal sanctuary, offered as part of the company’s two-year old tour guide business. A sheltie named Osso (short for Ossobuco) sits under the conference table licking the billionaire’s black sneakers. As the sound of the last bleat ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Could Airbnb Point The Way To Fairer Distribution Of Profits? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/enriquedans/2018/09/30/could-airbnb-point-the-way-to-fairer-distribution-of-profits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQbeTvFBfJU2QArcVIplmQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/enriquedans/2018/09/30/could-airbnb-point-the-way-to-fairer-distribution-of-profits/" target="_blank"&gt;Could Airbnb Point The Way To Fairer Distribution Of Profits?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FILE- In this Feb. 22, 2018, photo, Airbnb co-founder and CEO Brian Chesky speaks during an event in San Francisco. People who use the vacation rental website Airbnb are coming to Albany, N.Y., on Tuesday, March 6, to encourage lawmakers to rescind, or at least revise, a law authorizing hefty fines for short-term apartment rentals in New York City. (AP Photo/Eric Risberg, File) Airbnb has written to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) requesting an end to the rule that currently prevents companies from giving shares to anyone other than employees or investors. The missive is in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why This "Apart-Hotel" Startup Is Betting $50 Million On Group Travel - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jennawang/2018/09/30/why-this-apart-hotel-startup-is-betting-50-million-on-group-travel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI6IAKGE6MxD7pFqTrpofhgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jennawang/2018/09/30/why-this-apart-hotel-startup-is-betting-50-million-on-group-travel/" target="_blank"&gt;Why This "Apart-Hotel" Startup Is Betting $50 Million On Group Travel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Domio’s new apart-hotel in New Orleans, set to open in November. They say good things come in groups of traveling millennials. Domio, the vacation rental company, announced last week a $50 million joint venture with private equity firm Upper90 to open a new line of apartment-hotel hybrids, or “apart-hotels.” Domio aims to be the “Airbnb of group travel” by renting out curated vacation apartments to group travelers. The company first got its start by using its automation-enabled platforms to host more than 60,000 “instant” online bookings across the country at its single unit properties. Now...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Airbnb says not property agent, French hoteliers say nonsense - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-airbnb-ahtop-court/airbnb-says-not-property-agent-french-hoteliers-say-nonsense-idUSKCN1M82OR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGt3c5sUpuSDj7C28xzxNI0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 20:37:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-airbnb-ahtop-court/airbnb-says-not-property-agent-french-hoteliers-say-nonsense-idUSKCN1M82OR" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb says not property agent, French hoteliers say nonsense&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online rental marketplace Airbnb rejected on Friday a contention by a leading French hoteliers' association that it is a real estate agent and should be subjected to property rules in a case which could affect other online services. Since its launch in San Francisco in 2008, Airbnb, which matches people wishing to rent out all or part of their homes to temporary guests via a website, has expanded rapidly. The company has, however, clashed with hoteliers and authorities in cities from New York to Amsterdam, Berlin and Paris amid accusations of it worsening housing shortages and pushing out l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Airbnb cancels Great Wall of China contest - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/gallery/china-great-wall-airbnb/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENz3a6pajtyj8nPSvfZ6zXEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 19:55:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/gallery/china-great-wall-airbnb/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Airbnb cancels Great Wall of China contest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Night at the Great Wall: Airbnb has canceled a contest that would have offered four people and their guests a chance to sleep in a custom-designed "home" set in one of the Great Wall of China's towers. Airbnb Open-air bedroom: Winners would have stayed in a one-of-a-kind modern bedroom, created within a centuries-old tower perched along the Wall with 360-degree views. airbnb Negative reaction: Amidst negative feedback, Airbnb made the decision to cancel the competition. Airbnb Canceled competition: "We deeply respect the feedback we have received," said the company in a statement. "We have ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Spend a Night on the Great Wall of China, Courtesy of Airbnb - ArchDaily</title><link>https://www.archdaily.com/899493/spend-a-night-on-the-great-wall-of-china-courtesy-of-airbnb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFh6mgtAEDGpNkSZk23bB6kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.archdaily.com/899493/spend-a-night-on-the-great-wall-of-china-courtesy-of-airbnb" target="_blank"&gt;Spend a Night on the Great Wall of China, Courtesy of Airbnb&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Courtesy of Airbnb Airbnb is giving four lucky winners the honor of being among “the first people in thousands of years to spend the night on the Great Wall of China.” The competition, open until August 11th, offers the prize of staying in a custom-designed home situated on one of the seven wonders of the modern world. The competition, run in collaboration with the Beijing Tourism Development Committee, is intended to “promote sustainable tourism to China by spotlighting wide-ranging efforts to preserve the Wall’s deep heritage and bring Chinese culture to life.” The four winners will have ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Meet The Designer Who Brought Airbnb, Headspace And SoundCloud's Offices To Life - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/emilyjoffrion/2018/08/02/airbnb-workplace-designer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAKL1eZ1DMr6k2PsdjO4NCUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/emilyjoffrion/2018/08/02/airbnb-workplace-designer/" target="_blank"&gt;Meet The Designer Who Brought Airbnb, Headspace And SoundCloud's Offices To Life&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Workplace Designer, Kelly Robinson Tech offices have long been the brunt of jokes about opulence in Silicon Valley. But when a product is written in code and stored on the cloud, the office space can often be the first (or only) physical encounter employees, customers and other stakeholders have with a brand. No one knows this better than Kelly Robinson, a workplace designer whose portfolio includes the breezy, livable offices of Airbnb, SoundCloud, Headspace, Branch, and many more. I sat down with her to learn more about the connection between online brands and physical space and how she s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Business leaders speak out against child separation policy - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/c8e873dbb1ea4d8482ce6cfee206027f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELZLWDlhK6gnv4DMCWATEH4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 19:10:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/c8e873dbb1ea4d8482ce6cfee206027f" target="_blank"&gt;Business leaders speak out against child separation policy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Business leaders are condemning the Trump administration's decision to separate children from parents who are accused of crossing the border illegally. The Business Roundtable, a lobbying group that includes the CEOs of Walmart Inc., General Motors Co., Boeing Co. and Mastercard Inc., released a statement Tuesday urging the immediate end to the policy. "This practice is cruel and contrary to American values," said Chuck Robbins, the chairman and CEO of Cisco Systems Inc. and the head of the Business Roundtable's immigration committee. The group called for comprehensive immigr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>How Tech Giants Design For Transgender Users–Or Don’t - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcodesign.com/90165071/how-tech-giants-design-for-transgender-users-or-dont</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN9G8vYzx90XFpRyuNQ5R1QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMIGcAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 07:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcodesign.com/90165071/how-tech-giants-design-for-transgender-users-or-dont" target="_blank"&gt;How Tech Giants Design For Transgender Users–Or Don’t&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Sophie Alpert began living as a woman, she grew out her hair, she changed her name, and she changed how she dressed. But her profile on Airbnb, where she had been a member since 2013, still referred to her with male pronouns and referenced her old name. At best, it was inconvenient to explain the situation to potential guests. At worst, potential guests might have suspected some kind of scheme. By design, Airbnb mines your history to build your profile, and that’s incredibly problematic for transgender people who’ve established a new life. In this sense, it’s a perfect example of what ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcodesign.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>These Are The Cities Where You Can Earn The Most On Airbnb - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/learnvest/2018/02/21/these-are-the-cities-where-you-can-earn-the-most-on-airbnb/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOXZ7-zOlc8D0fQ-weMbz94qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/learnvest/2018/02/21/these-are-the-cities-where-you-can-earn-the-most-on-airbnb/" target="_blank"&gt;These Are The Cities Where You Can Earn The Most On Airbnb&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty Images By Jennifer Liu This story originally appeared on LearnVest as “If You Live in One of These Cities, You Need to Airbnb Your Home.” Does it ever just feel like people in coastal towns get all the good things in life? Not only do they get day trips to the beach, they’re also in a prime spot to earn a quick buck from visitors hoping to do the same. According to average nightly Airbnb rates collected by Homes.com, East Coast hosts can stand to earn the most by renting out their spaces. Bridgeport, Connecticut takes the top spot, where hosts can expect to bring in about $246 per nig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item></channel></rss>