<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Narendra Modi - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREk1Tm5FeUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:00:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>As election nears, religious tensions surge in an Indian village - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-insight/as-election-nears-religious-tensions-surge-in-an-indian-village-idUSKBN1O70DE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELRA4tyBUgdxRTY6-mREOrMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:09:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-insight/as-election-nears-religious-tensions-surge-in-an-indian-village-idUSKBN1O70DE" target="_blank"&gt;As election nears, religious tensions surge in an Indian village&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nayabans isn't remarkable as northern Indian villages go. Sugar cane grows in surrounding fields, women carry animal feed in bullock carts through narrow lanes, people chatter outside a store, and cows loiter. But this week, the village in Uttar Pradesh state became a symbol of the deepening communal divide in India as some Hindu men from the area complained they had seen a group of Muslims slaughtering cows in a mango orchard a couple of miles away. That infuriated Hindus, who regard the cow as a sacred animal. Anger against Muslims turned into outrage that police had not stopped an illega...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India extradites UK businessman over bribery claims - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/59883936-f853-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECAPpOgH3by7xk2YxioSTnsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 08:52:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/59883936-f853-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;India extradites UK businessman over bribery claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A British businessman has been extradited to India to face prosecution for alleged bribery in connection with New Delhi’s $720m acquisition of 12 VIP helicopters in 2010 when the country’s previous Congress party was in power. Christian Michel James, 57, is alleged to have acted as an agent for AugustaWestland, which sold the helicopters. He was transported from Dubai to New Delhi on Tuesday night while Sushma Swaraj, India’s foreign minister, was in the United Arab Emirates for an official visit. Mr James, whose lawyers said during his extradition hearings in Dubai that he was not involved...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Three arrested in connection with police killing during 'cow vigilante' clashes in India - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/asia/india-cow-vigilante-killing-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGuodpJ1rA3v2HvnXIjEgLQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:49:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/asia/india-cow-vigilante-killing-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Three arrested in connection with police killing during 'cow vigilante' clashes in India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian authorities have arrested three people in connection with the fatal shooting of a police officer and a local man involved in clashes over the alleged killing of cows Monday. The shootings are the latest in a wave of mob violence branded as "cow vigilantism" that critics say is growing on Prime Minister Narendra Modi's watch. Clashes between villagers and police broke out in the northern Indian state of Uttar Pradesh after cow carcasses were allegedly discovered in a village near the city of Bulandshahr, about 46 miles from the capital, New Delhi. India's majority Hindu population con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Indian court remands British businessman accused in AgustaWestland 'copter deal - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-agustawestland/indian-court-remands-british-businessman-accused-in-agustawestland-copter-deal-idUSKBN1O41LG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA03Gm_E2MNOk1GvTPIA8nwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:57:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-agustawestland/indian-court-remands-british-businessman-accused-in-agustawestland-copter-deal-idUSKBN1O41LG" target="_blank"&gt;Indian court remands British businessman accused in AgustaWestland 'copter deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indian court on Wednesday remanded to custody a British businessman accused of paying bribes to Indian officials to win a helicopter deal for Anglo-Italian firm AgustaWestland, following a rare extradition. The case threatens strong repercussions for India's opposition Congress party, as Prime Minister Narendra Modi's ruling party called the extradition of Christian Michel a victory in its fight against graft. "Who knows what secrets will tumble out once he starts talking?" Modi said at a rally in western Rajasthan which is electing a new state assembly. Modi is seeking to embarrass Cong...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Modinomics has yet to deliver for many in India - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a1a6e8d4-f4bb-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPhPPgoTSPda0LWYvGFv0JwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 10:00:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a1a6e8d4-f4bb-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Modinomics has yet to deliver for many in India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India’s ruling Bharatiya Janata party is no stranger to changing history. In 2016, it omitted India’s first prime minister Jawaharlal Nehru from a state-level textbook. A few days ago, the central statistic offices revised down an estimate of annual Indian growth during the previous period when the rival Indian National Congress was in power, from 8.1 per cent to 6.3 per cent. That put it below the 7.3 per cent average for the first four years of BJP prime minister Narendra Modi’s term — and distracted from a slowdown to 7.1 per cent in the third quarter, from 8.2 per cent in the second. Wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Indian farmers march seeking better prices for produce - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/2b7c0dc344064aef89d2bad846066440</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDBZ-R6aKF8w4GcdmbsfFf0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:54:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/2b7c0dc344064aef89d2bad846066440" target="_blank"&gt;Indian farmers march seeking better prices for produce&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — Thousands of farmers marched to India's Parliament on Friday demanding higher prices for their produce and a government waiver on their farm loans to alleviate hardships. Waving red, yellow and green flags and banners representing their organizations, the protesters also called for lower prices for diesel fuel and fertilizer and blamed the Hindu nationalist government for hardships caused by years of declining earnings in the agriculture sector. Several farmers carried human skulls they said were of farmers who had killed themselves due to deep debt. Their widows also joine...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>India police arrest two over officer's killing in mob violence - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/india-arrests-police-officer-killed-mob-violence-181204060250033.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIquZ44WRdRDvkzVlbIad8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 09:49:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/india-arrests-police-officer-killed-mob-violence-181204060250033.html" target="_blank"&gt;India police arrest two over officer's killing in mob violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least two people have been arrested in connection with the killing of a police officer during a mob violence in India's Uttar Pradesh state, officials have said. A Special Investigation Team (SIT) has been constituted to probe the cause of the violence in Bulandshahr district, senior police officer Prashant Kumar told local ANI news agency. Police have filed cases against at least 27 people, including a Hindu far-right leader, in connection with the violence that saw a police station torched by the angry crowd. 170927084018325 Hundreds of paramilitary forces have been deployed in the are...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Argentine TV Welcomes Indian PM With Picture Of Apu From 'The Simpsons' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/argentina-apu-the-simpsons-g20_us_5c024577e4b0a173c0233305</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKjD9sRJWKVaQfvW8cs-Zs8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 09:32:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/argentina-apu-the-simpsons-g20_us_5c024577e4b0a173c0233305" target="_blank"&gt;Argentine TV Welcomes Indian PM With Picture Of Apu From 'The Simpsons'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A television news station in Argentina faced backlash after it announced the arrival of Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi in the country for the G20 summit with a picture of “The Simpsons” character Apu Nahasapeemapetilon. “Apu Arrives,” Cronica TV reportedly captioned the image, which was circulated on Twitter Thursday by business journalist Patrick Gillespie: Argentine TV outlet @CronicaTV displays this racist image with the headline “Apu Arrived” as India Prime Minister @narendramodi arrives in Buenos Aires for the #G20. pic.twitter.com/oNqZVpS4E5 — Patrick Gillespie (@Pat_Gillespie) N...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>'The last straw': Tens of thousands of Indian farmers protest against Modi - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/tens-of-thousands-of-indian-farmers-protest-against-modi/10573542</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHlXnc5A1pIuCPtETy6JPeYqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:46:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/tens-of-thousands-of-indian-farmers-protest-against-modi/10573542" target="_blank"&gt;'The last straw': Tens of thousands of Indian farmers protest against Modi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tens of thousands of Indian farmers and rural workers marched to the Indian Parliament in the capital, New Delhi, in a protest against soaring operating costs and plunging produce prices that have brought misery to many. Key points: - Low food prices, export curbs, and anti-inflation policies that keep rural incomes low have angered Indian farmers - The 263 million farmers make up an important voting bloc ahead of next year's May election - Agriculture contributes about 15 per cent to India's $2.6 trillion economy, but employs nearly half of its 1.3 billion people The protest is one of the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>India: Two killed in protests over alleged cow slaughter - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/india-killed-protests-alleged-cow-slaughter-181203134632573.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOpeYGP8cnm5tJ-543rBph4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 18:22:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/india-killed-protests-alleged-cow-slaughter-181203134632573.html" target="_blank"&gt;India: Two killed in protests over alleged cow slaughter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two people, including a police officer, have been killed in northern India during violent protests by villagers over suspicions of cow slaughter, officials said. Police said a crowd of about 400 people gathered after hearing about the carcasses of animals, including a cow, reportedly being found on a farm on Monday morning. Inspector Subodh Kumar Singh and a 20-year-old man died after clashes erupted in a village in Uttar Pradesh state's Bulandshahr district. The officer died from gunshot wounds, district magistrate Anuj Kumar Jha told Reuters news agency. Earlier, police had said the offic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>India’s economic statistics bureau drawn into political row - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a21fe0ca-f3d7-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECu0TlhXR_oX4P1vV1l8dvUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:15:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a21fe0ca-f3d7-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;India’s economic statistics bureau drawn into political row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India’s economic statistics bureau has been sucked into a political firestorm ahead of next year’s general election, after revising downwards its estimates of growth under the previous government. Arun Jaitley, finance minister, on Thursday hit out at what he said were efforts to “discredit” the Central Statistics Office after it made substantial downgrades to the official annual growth rates between 2005 and 2012. His statement came after the opposition Congress party, which led a coalition government during the period in question, accused Mr Jaitley and Prime Minister Narendra Modi of “re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Saudi crown prince meets India's Modi in Argentina, plans to ramp up investments - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-crownprince-india-idUSKCN1NZ08K</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDy2UgTqaTMMgzcgFzZ0JQ8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 05:40:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-crownprince-india-idUSKCN1NZ08K" target="_blank"&gt;Saudi crown prince meets India's Modi in Argentina, plans to ramp up investments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman met Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi and told him about plans to scale up investments in India's tech, farm and energy sectors, an Indian official and the Saudi news agency (SPA) said on Friday. The two leaders, who are in Argentina for the G20 summit, met in the prince's residence in Buenos Aires and discussed Saudi Arabia's readiness to supply India with oil and petroleum products. The G20 summit in Buenos Aires is the first major international event the Saudi prince has attended since the murder of journalist Jamal Khashoggi in the Saudi consulat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Indian Politicians Spar Over Dodgy Economic Data as Election Nears - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/indian-politicians-spar-over-dodgy-economic-data-as-election-nears/4681169.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMOw-ZMfB1e_BWaQ0ncx-k0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:08:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/indian-politicians-spar-over-dodgy-economic-data-as-election-nears/4681169.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian Politicians Spar Over Dodgy Economic Data as Election Nears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may be the world’s sixth largest, but most other things about India’s economy are up for debate. The ruling Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) is under fire for the release of new historical GDP figures that significantly downgraded growth during the years the opposition Congress party was in power, replacing old government estimates and those prepared by an independent committee. The figures, released by the government’s Central Statistics Office (CSO), showed growth in the 10 years of Congress rule to 2014 averaged 6.7 percent, below an average of 7.4 percent under the current government. A ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>India's Modi and China's Xi aim to build on thaw in ties at G20 meeting - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-g20-argentina-india-china/indias-modi-and-chinas-xi-aim-to-build-on-thaw-in-ties-at-g20-meeting-idUSKCN1NX0Q3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZWhYXjDFilzM1UUstI55sqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 08:32:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-g20-argentina-india-china/indias-modi-and-chinas-xi-aim-to-build-on-thaw-in-ties-at-g20-meeting-idUSKCN1NX0Q3" target="_blank"&gt;India's Modi and China's Xi aim to build on thaw in ties at G20 meeting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi and Chinese President Xi Jinping will meet on the sidelines of a G20 meeting this week, aiming to build on a thaw in ties after a military standoff on their disputed border last year, officials said. The 3,500 km (2,200-mile) border between the nuclear-armed neighbors has been calm since Modi and Xi held several hours of talks in the Chinese city of Wuhan in April, agreeing to prevent political disputes escalating into confrontation. Later this year, their two armies will hold joint exercises in a bid to build trust after their 73-day face-off in a remote...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Angry India farmers march on parliament to highlight farm crisis - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/angry-india-farmers-march-parliament-highlight-farm-crisis-181130102003286.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEK3qYyLQDQ0u_rdWvYdGRoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:27:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/angry-india-farmers-march-parliament-highlight-farm-crisis-181130102003286.html" target="_blank"&gt;Angry India farmers march on parliament to highlight farm crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tens of thousands of farmers and agricultural workers marched towards the Indian parliament on Friday demanding debt waivers and higher crop prices, putting pressure on Prime Minister Narendra Modi ahead of 2019 general elections. "We are demanding legal rights for farmers - especially for tenant farmers and women farmers with no rights," said Kavitha Kuruganti, with the advocacy group Alliance for Sustainable &amp; Holistic Agriculture. "Our farmers need secure rights over land and better prices for their crop to be free from debt," she told Reuters. Organisers said some 80,000 farmers and far...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>India's Electrification Push Raises Environmental Stakes - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andystone/2018/11/29/indias-electrification-push-raises-environmental-stakes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOBd5a0dL8HSa8_0lo6mhXUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 03:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andystone/2018/11/29/indias-electrification-push-raises-environmental-stakes/" target="_blank"&gt;India's Electrification Push Raises Environmental Stakes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian public electricity cables India is in the home stretch of today’s most ambitious electrification effort, one that is akin to the U.S. government’s push to bring power to rural America in the 1930s. Back in 1936, President Roosevelt put forth the Rural Electrification Act as part of his Depression-era New Deal. The policy aimed to create jobs in the near term and, more enduringly, build electric infrastructure that would underpin future economic development in the nation’s rural and agricultural regions, including those that had been economically devastated by a half decade of drought...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Hard-line Hindus pressure Modi over temple at disputed site - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/ea6edae93e014e01a08b6e04aa4d4ec2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEez64iSvnvYr-J7sycFw18qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 00:43:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/ea6edae93e014e01a08b6e04aa4d4ec2" target="_blank"&gt;Hard-line Hindus pressure Modi over temple at disputed site&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUCKNOW, India (AP) — Tens of thousands of hard-line Hindus rallied Sunday to demand a Hindu temple be built on a site in northern India where hard-liners in 1992 had attacked and demolished a 16th century mosque, sparking deadly Hindu-Muslim violence. The Hindu hard-liners are building pressure on Prime Minister Narendra Modi's government to move quickly on the issue. Modi had promised to build the temple in 2014 elections that brought him to power. The next national elections are due before May. Thousands of police and paramilitary forces were deployed in and around Ayodhya, 550 kilometer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Modi mania in short supply as uncertainty clouds Indian stocks - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e5def1ce-f21b-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMkzbjnG-f-JPr0j4yIkpwgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 04:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e5def1ce-f21b-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;Modi mania in short supply as uncertainty clouds Indian stocks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to miss the helicopters in the skies over Madhya Pradesh and Rajasthan. They are ferrying candidates to rallies in Indian state elections, a prelude to the general election the country’s prime minister, Narendra Modi, must hold by May. However, the aerial traffic is less a sign of economic progress than a measure of how the region’s infrastructure isn’t up to the job of quickly moving people across large local constituencies. They are also an unmistakable sign that investors need to add politics to the mix as they weigh India as an investment destination. More than four years ago,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Hindu temple site protest ends peacefully as 200,000 disperse - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-idUSKCN1NU04L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG8y0marFLhWOQffJCRdi8AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 15:20:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-idUSKCN1NU04L" target="_blank"&gt;Hindu temple site protest ends peacefully as 200,000 disperse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 200,000 Hindu activists and monks protesting near a disputed religious site in northern India dispersed peacefully on Sunday after demanding the government build a temple at the site of a 16th-century mosque. A similar rally in 1992 near Ayodhya led to a Hindu mob tearing down the mosque, sparking riots that killed about 2,000 people in one of the worst instances of communal violence in India since the 1947 partition. Tensions have again been running high ahead of the latest rally, with a heavy security presence at the site. Prime Minister Narendra Modi's Bharatiya Janata Party (B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Indian farmers back in Mumbai to demand land rights, loan waivers - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-farmers-protests/indian-farmers-back-in-mumbai-to-demand-land-rights-loan-waivers-idUSKCN1NR0I3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKaAIuSox0YkNuwZR8utezkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 09:00:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-farmers-protests/indian-farmers-back-in-mumbai-to-demand-land-rights-loan-waivers-idUSKCN1NR0I3" target="_blank"&gt;Indian farmers back in Mumbai to demand land rights, loan waivers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tens of thousands of farmers from India's western state of Maharashtra marched to the state capital Mumbai on Thursday to demand loan waivers and the transfer of forest lands to villagers who have farmed there for decades. It was the latest protest by farmers against a state government headed by Prime Minister Narendra Modi's Bharatiya Janata Party, which faces a general election in May and a handful of state polls in the coming weeks. Indian farmers voted overwhelmingly for Modi in 2014. But a fall in rural incomes risks damaging that support next year. The protesters chanted slogans deman...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Factbox: India's Ayodhya temple dispute - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-factbox/factbox-indias-ayodhya-temple-dispute-idUSKCN1NR03O</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJG2fRDahPAhBBl7BDLrgaQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 01:31:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-factbox/factbox-indias-ayodhya-temple-dispute-idUSKCN1NR03O" target="_blank"&gt;Factbox: India's Ayodhya temple dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The demolition of a centuries-old mosque by a Hindu mob in the Indian holy town of Ayodhya in late 1992 sparked deadly religious riots around the country, killing about 2,000 people. The minority Muslim community in the town feels under siege once again, with some saying tensions are running at their highest levels since the riots, as Hindu groups intensify demands for the construction of a Hindu temple on the same site. Here are key facts about the disputed site, sourced from court and government documents. WHAT'S THE DISPUTE ABOUT? The Hindu epic scripture Ramayana mentions Ayodhya, locat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India farmers rebel against Modi’s bullet train - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9e1b3f64-d803-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAUJ3mggob-EOFvi5iwsJ6IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9e1b3f64-d803-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8" target="_blank"&gt;India farmers rebel against Modi’s bullet train&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The route for India’s first bullet train, a $15bn flagship project in the government’s drive to upgrade national infrastructure, goes directly through Navinbhai Patel’s house. Outside the mango farmer’s modest home in Valsad, a village in western Gujarat state, authorities have left stone and chalk markers to indicate the path where trains will run on their 530km journey between Mumbai and Gujarat’s industrial hub of Ahmedabad. But Mr Patel, 40, is unwilling to surrender his home and four acres of farmland to the project, backed by Japanese capital and technology in one of India’s biggest ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Modi's backers step up holy site dispute as Indian election looms - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-insight/modis-backers-step-up-holy-site-dispute-as-indian-election-looms-idUSKCN1NR039</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIfPuofQvJYaZP8TxsIMibcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 03:10:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-insight/modis-backers-step-up-holy-site-dispute-as-indian-election-looms-idUSKCN1NR039" target="_blank"&gt;Modi's backers step up holy site dispute as Indian election looms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a Hindu mob tore down a centuries-old mosque in the northern Indian town of Ayodhya 26 years ago, Haji Mahboob Ahmad says he and his family had to flee to a Muslim religious school miles away to escape deadly rioting. In days of communal clashes that followed more than a dozen people were killed in Ayodhya and about 2,000 people across the country. Ahmad said when he returned to his house, about a mile south of the disputed site, it had been gutted by fire. Now leaders of Prime Minister Narendra Modi's Hindu nationalist Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) and its affiliates are stepping up ef...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan and India begin construction of 'corridor of peace' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/asia/india-pakistan-road-link-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIxOMNxWmLqZY3S2t9XvzAoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 11:01:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/asia/india-pakistan-road-link-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan and India begin construction of 'corridor of peace'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India and Pakistan are set to inaugurate the construction of a corridor to facilitate hassle free cross-border travel for religious devotees -- a rare step to improve ties between the two South Asian foes even as deep-seated divisions continue to obstruct progress in long-stalled peace talks. The Indian cabinet approved the building and development of the so called Kartarpur corridor last week, a five kilometer (3.1 miles) long passage to connect two Sikh temples on either side of the border between India and Pakistan due to open in 2019. The temple in Kartarpur in Pakistan is among the hol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Opposition seeks clarity on Norwegian 'mediation' in Kashmir - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/opposition-seeks-clarity-norwegian-mediation-kashmir-181127130555711.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMFLGHm1AuhLKVMnm9b3ww8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:56:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/opposition-seeks-clarity-norwegian-mediation-kashmir-181127130555711.html" target="_blank"&gt;Opposition seeks clarity on Norwegian 'mediation' in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent visit by former Norwegian prime minister to Indian-administered Kashmir, where he met separatist leaders, has sparked a controversy, with opposition parties questioning the government over the surprise trip. Omar Abdullah, the leader of the regional National Conference (NC) party, pointed fingers at the Hindu nationalist government of Prime Minister Narendra Modi to explain the closed-door meetings held in Srinagar, the main city in the region. "What are the Norwegians up to in Kashmir? Would either (External Affairs Minister) @SushmaSwaraj ji or (National Security Advisor Ajit) Do...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan’s shrine corridor raises prospect of thaw with India - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/470f8a84-f1fa-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJWY5gsx3IPz4t6eq2Nt8BUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/470f8a84-f1fa-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan’s shrine corridor raises prospect of thaw with India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imran Khan, Pakistan’s prime minister, has raised hopes of a thaw with New Delhi by breaking ground on facilities for Indian pilgrims to visit a Sikh shrine in the country. One of Sikhism’s most sacred sites, the Gurdwara Kartarpur Sahib is the final resting place of Guru Nanak, the faith’s founder. In the subcontinent’s traumatic 1947 partition , Kartarpur wound up in Pakistan, 4km from the border with India, where most Sikhs now live. Today, Indian devotees can only gaze at the shrine through binoculars. But in an unexpected diplomatic overture, Islamabad and New Delhi have taken steps to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>'Smash Brahminical patriarchy': Twitter chief accused of 'hate-mongering' - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-21/twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-accused-hate-mongering-india-trip-sign/10518038</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMe8i7tcmHxo0lCy0PfGzw0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 02:56:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-21/twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-accused-hate-mongering-india-trip-sign/10518038" target="_blank"&gt;'Smash Brahminical patriarchy': Twitter chief accused of 'hate-mongering'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey has kicked up a social media storm in India after a picture of him holding a poster saying "smash Brahminical patriarchy", referring to the highest Hindu caste, went viral. Key points: - Jack Dorsey was handed the sign by a woman who grew up in Hinduism's lowest caste - Twitter apologised both in a statement and through its executives on the social platform - Tensions between castes in India have escalated in recent years Twitter apologised and expressed regret over the incident, which some Indians have called "hate-mongering". The picture, posted on Twitter by a jou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Modi Should Not Bail Out China In Maldives - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2018/11/28/modi-should-not-bail-out-china-in-maldives/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG7gGAJ9Qe-yIMJrpKKYR2cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 02:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2018/11/28/modi-should-not-bail-out-china-in-maldives/" target="_blank"&gt;Modi Should Not Bail Out China In Maldives&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer Graham Crouch/Bloomberg *** Local Caption *** Narendra Modi; Xi Jinping India’ Prime Minister Narendra Modi shouldn’t help the Maldives pay its debts to China. It isn’t in India’s own economic and geopolitical interests, at this point. After Sri Lanka and Pakistan, the Maldives has fallen into China’s ‘debt trap.’ The small tropical nation in the Indian Ocean owes Beijing a lot of money—around $8,000 for every inhabitant of the archipelago! That’s according to a Reuters report, which claims that China has handed the Maldives government an invoice for $3.2 billion. The loan is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why the 2019 election may be the most crucial in India's history - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2019-election-crucial-india-history-181120160323155.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGhEY8RDoIyt9U_cYz_ywN0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 10:06:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2019-election-crucial-india-history-181120160323155.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why the 2019 election may be the most crucial in India's history&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In April-May next year an estimated 900 million Indians will be heading to the polls to elect their next parliament. In the 70-odd years since India's independence, this will likely be the first election that seriously challenges the country's inclusive political culture. If the current government led by the Hindu Nationalist Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) and Prime Minister Narendra Modi secures another emphatic mandate, the country will move dangerously close to becoming a majoritarian state. A decisive victory would give the BJP hegemonic control over all state institutions, as well as the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Narendra Modi should trust his central bank’s instincts - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a5afd54a-ecc2-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPe0wpEvwJrpb63iAeN7A-wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 05:00:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a5afd54a-ecc2-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57" target="_blank"&gt;Narendra Modi should trust his central bank’s instincts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The emblem of the Reserve Bank of India is a tiger standing under a palm tree. The central bank has been living up to its image lately, baring its teeth at an attempt by Narendra Modi’s government to threaten its independence over whether India’s banks are lending enough. The tiger sheathed its claws on Monday, reaching a truce with the finance ministry on its policies towards state banks and how much of its reserves to pay to the government. But this does not resolve the battle that has broken out over the rapid growth of India’s shadow banking system — its thousands of consumer credit, as...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Maldives's new President sworn in but facing difficult road ahead - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-18/ibrahim-mohamed-solih-sworn-in-as-maldives-president/10508088</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBxLK92YYeo0_I5YAiY7Jt4qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 13:56:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-18/ibrahim-mohamed-solih-sworn-in-as-maldives-president/10508088" target="_blank"&gt;Maldives's new President sworn in but facing difficult road ahead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ibrahim Mohamed Solih took over as President of the Maldives on Saturday following a fierce political discord caused by the autocratic rule of outgoing leader Yameen Abdul Gayoom. Mr Solih faces a challenging task of balancing ties with powerful India and China. Thousands of people cheered for Mr Solih, from the Maldivian Democratic Party, at a swearing-in ceremony in a soccer stadium chosen to accommodate a large number of his supporters. Chief Justice Abdulla Didi administered the oath of office to the 54-year-old politician. The Maldives, an Indian Ocean archipelago known for its luxury ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Maldives' new president warns state coffers 'looted' after China-led boom - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-maldives-politics/maldives-new-president-warns-state-coffers-looted-after-china-led-boom-idUSKCN1NM0K8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEO8HCVKIE9rFWFPHQAcixIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 16:27:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-maldives-politics/maldives-new-president-warns-state-coffers-looted-after-china-led-boom-idUSKCN1NM0K8" target="_blank"&gt;Maldives' new president warns state coffers 'looted' after China-led boom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new president of the Maldives took office on Saturday, declaring the state coffers to have been looted and warned that the country was in financial difficulty after racking up debt with Chinese lenders in an infrastructure boom. The Maldives, famous for its luxury resorts on palm-fringed islands, is the latest in a number of small countries where China has invested millions of dollars building highways and housing as part of its Belt and Road Initiative. But these projects have left the country of just over 400,000 people in debt and prompted calls for investigations into how contracts ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India's Modi embraces Maldives as new leader takes office, China out of favor - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-maldives-politics-analysis-idUSKCN1NL1E8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKaA4DFC0niwnMXcqiYFqzEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 15:41:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-maldives-politics-analysis-idUSKCN1NL1E8" target="_blank"&gt;India's Modi embraces Maldives as new leader takes office, China out of favor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maldives' President-elect Ibrahim Mohamed Solih takes office on Saturday, seeking help from India and the United States to climb out from under a mountain of Chinese debt that his predecessor racked up in a breakneck development of the coral islands. The surprise defeat of pro-China strongman Abdulla Yameen has opened a window for India, the strategic outpost's traditional political partner, to regain ground lost to Beijing in their tussle for regional dominance. Prime Minister Narendra Modi will be the highest ranking visitor at the inauguration at the national soccer stadium in the capita...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>As India eases citizenship path for Hindus, Rohingya Muslims fear expulsion - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-india-insight/as-india-eases-citizenship-path-for-hindus-rohingya-muslims-fear-expulsion-idUSKCN1NK0VH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECq_G_2cDfOWRTkY-cN9aLkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:51:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-india-insight/as-india-eases-citizenship-path-for-hindus-rohingya-muslims-fear-expulsion-idUSKCN1NK0VH" target="_blank"&gt;As India eases citizenship path for Hindus, Rohingya Muslims fear expulsion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nar Singh can vividly recall the day in 2014 when Narendra Modi promised to provide refuge to Hindus suffering around the world. The 39-year-old shop owner sat awestruck inside his two-bedroom house in Pakistan's eastern Mirpur Khas district, as Modi's voice boomed from the television during his successful campaign to become India's prime minister. "If there are atrocities on Hindus in Fiji, where will they go? Should they not come to India? If Hindus are persecuted in Mauritius, where should they go? Hindustan!" Modi declared to a roaring crowd. For Singh, whose grandfather had been born i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India's Modi to get a test in state votes as general election looms - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-idUSKCN1NH0PZ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED_oZ512mPY58X3mj81AzgwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 08:24:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-idUSKCN1NH0PZ" target="_blank"&gt;India's Modi to get a test in state votes as general election looms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India began on Monday the first of five state elections to be held in coming weeks, important tests for Prime Minister Narendra Modi as he plots a course that he hopes will ensure him victory in a general election due by May. Voters in the central state of Chhattisgarh went to the polls on Monday to elect representatives for 18 of the state assembly's 90 seats in a staggered poll complicated by logistical problems and left-wing guerrillas. The state of about 26 million people has been ruled by Modi's Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) since 2003, and he will be hoping to hold on to power. "Some u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India's Reserve Bank Tightens To A Tee - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stevehanke/2018/11/13/indias-reserve-bank-tightens-to-a-tee/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJOJAiSXNG4YG6noXj21EB8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/stevehanke/2018/11/13/indias-reserve-bank-tightens-to-a-tee/" target="_blank"&gt;India's Reserve Bank Tightens To A Tee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi addresses business leaders as he launches his “Make in India” initiative. (AP Photo/Saurabh Das, File) The age-old sport of political leaders bashing central banks has come out of the shadows of late. President Trump has taken the Fed to the woodshed, working it over with tweets. President Erdogan has morphed into Turkey’s most noteworthy monetary crank. Most recently, Prime Minister Modi and his henchmen have gone toe-to-toe with the Reserve Bank of India (RBI). Modi, backed by the Confederation of Industry and the Federation of Chambers of Commerce and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>India clears sale of 'enemy shares' held by people who moved to Pakistan - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-stocks-enemy-idUSKCN1NE0QF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIKVq1xNGL68OYEKSmppjGwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 08:27:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-stocks-enemy-idUSKCN1NE0QF" target="_blank"&gt;India clears sale of 'enemy shares' held by people who moved to Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's government said it will sell stocks worth millions of dollars seized from people who moved to Pakistan following partition in 1947 and the wars since, as a way to make up for a shortfall in revenues. The stocks worth at least 30 billion rupees ($412.26 million) are part of what India calls "enemy properties" that once belonged to people who went to Pakistan and China, with which India also fought a war. Once these Indian nationals became citizens of these two countries, they were treated as "enemies" and their assets in India including land and houses as well as shares were seized a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India's finance minister says Mastercard, Visa losing out to local players - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-mastercard-idUSKCN1ND1BV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECE9SAhCUTUV7C4VaLihhXkqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 10:37:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-mastercard-idUSKCN1ND1BV" target="_blank"&gt;India's finance minister says Mastercard, Visa losing out to local players&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's finance minister said on Thursday that Mastercard (MA.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) and Visa (V.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) were losing market share to domestic payments networks, months after Mastercard complained to the U.S. government that Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi was using nationalism to promote a local rival. Finance Minister Arun Jaitley spoke about the surging growth of RuPay and Unified Payment Interface (UPI), which allows swift inter-bank fund transfers, on the second anniversary of Modi's shock decision to replace high-value bank notes i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India's ruling BJP turns up Hindu nationalist heat with renamings, statue plan - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-idUSKBN1ND1YP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_GNLyOhMe9odd4VDzA3D0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 05:32:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-idUSKBN1ND1YP" target="_blank"&gt;India's ruling BJP turns up Hindu nationalist heat with renamings, statue plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;From getting rid of some Muslim names of places to promising a "grand" statue of the Hindu god Ram, Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi's ruling party is making passionate appeals to its hard-core Hindu nationalist base in the most politically important state ahead of a national election next year. A near clean-sweep in Uttar Pradesh, the northern state of 220 million people that sends the highest number of lawmakers to the lower house of parliament, helped Modi's Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) win its biggest mandate in three decades in 2014. Political strategists say keeping its mainly Hind...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India celebrates Diwali 2018: Narendra Modi visits troops as country shines in festival of lights - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/india-diwali-2018-narendra-modi-troops-soldiers-kedarnath-temple-festival-lights-a8621426.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKy0f6JXVEL_N21zQiajfLAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 08:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/india-diwali-2018-narendra-modi-troops-soldiers-kedarnath-temple-festival-lights-a8621426.html" target="_blank"&gt;India celebrates Diwali 2018: Narendra Modi visits troops as country shines in festival of lights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India was celebrating one of its biggest festivals of the year on Wednesday, as the country came to a colourful standstill for the Hindu festival of lights, Diwali. People shared images on social media of houses lit up with fairy lights, public installations and candles laid out to mark the occasion. Most Indians spend the day inside with family, exchanging gifts and sharing lavish feasts, but the real festivities will kick off with elaborate firework displays in the evening. - Read more Deadly smog hits Delhi ahead of feared Diwali pollution spike The prime minister, Narendra Modi, travell...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Modi Keeps On Lifting India Up - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2018/11/05/modi-keeps-on-lifting-india-up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMOIZXVsaH8zvYCAUO71szIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 01:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2018/11/05/modi-keeps-on-lifting-india-up/" target="_blank"&gt;Modi Keeps On Lifting India Up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Kiyoshi Ota/Bloomberg Prime Minister Narendra Modi keeps on lifting India in the global ranks. Last week, the Indian economy jumped 23 spots in the World Bank’s 2018 Ease of Doing Business ranking. It occupies the 77th position, up from 100th in 2017. And that comes on the top of another jump of 30 spots in the 2017 ranking from the previous year. That’s remarkable progress.It sets India apart from other countries in the region — like Pakistan and Bangladesh, which ranked 136 and 176, respectively. The Ease of Doing Business measures the impact of government regulations on sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Deadly political calculations: Why India isn't fixing its toxic smog problem - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-pollution-politics-insight-idUSKCN1NB215</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAAI9qaaHBTTSqMl2K4Y3wwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 12:50:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-pollution-politics-insight-idUSKCN1NB215" target="_blank"&gt;Deadly political calculations: Why India isn't fixing its toxic smog problem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As pollution levels surged to "severe" and "hazardous" levels in New Delhi this week, there was little sign that residents of India's teeming capital were doing much to protect themselves. The smog, which is expected to worsen in the next few days, exposed people to as much as 24 times the recommended limits for dangerous particles on Monday. But unlike in many Chinese cities, where face masks are a common sight when smog levels spike, it is still rare to see locals taking measures to reduce their exposure. Toddlers stand at school bus stops in crisply ironed uniforms, while security guards...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Gandhi scholar quits Indian university after nationalist pressure - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/05/gandhi-scholar-quits-university-india-labelled-anti-national</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOSxkfTxwFZyuwpydYiB7P0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 08:24:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/05/gandhi-scholar-quits-university-india-labelled-anti-national" target="_blank"&gt;Gandhi scholar quits Indian university after nationalist pressure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indian biographer of Mahatma Gandhi will no longer teach at a university in the independence leader’s home state after the institute came under pressure from critics including Hindu nationalist student groups complaining his work was “anti-national”. Ramachandra Guha, an Indian public intellectual whose works have covered cricket, the environment, contemporary Indian history and the life of Gandhi, had been announced in September as the newest faculty member at Ahmedabad University in Gujarat state. Last week, after a student union affiliated with India’s ruling Hindu nationalist Bharati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Former governor wades into Indian central bank row - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c5a3d95a-e1c3-11e8-a6e5-792428919cee</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECa_r7LJAPKMGhiI1WvYYOYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 16:33:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c5a3d95a-e1c3-11e8-a6e5-792428919cee" target="_blank"&gt;Former governor wades into Indian central bank row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raghuram Rajan, the high-profile former governor of the Reserve Bank of India, has waded into the growing row between the central bank and the Indian government, warning of the risks of eroding the RBI’s independence. “These are not good times to be labelled a country which doesn’t respect the autonomy of the central bank,” Mr Rajan told Indian news station CNBC TV18 on Tuesday. “The RBI is something like a seatbelt, the driver being the government. If you don't put on your seatbelt [and] get into an accident, the accident can be quite severe.” The tension between the institutions has burst...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>India unveils world’s tallest statue with monument to independence campaigner Sardar Patel - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/india-statue-unity-sadar-patel-height-location-worlds-tallest-cost-inauguration-a8610006.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGtBcmJe7iWeu4A0bhb1y_oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/india-statue-unity-sadar-patel-height-location-worlds-tallest-cost-inauguration-a8610006.html" target="_blank"&gt;India unveils world’s tallest statue with monument to independence campaigner Sardar Patel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India has unveiled the world’s tallest statue – a towering bronze tribute to one of the key figures of its independence movement. The “Statue of Unity”, a 597-foot monument to the country’s first home minister after the end of British rule, Sardar Vallabbhai Patel, was opened in Kevadiya, Gujarat, on Wednesday. Air force planes showered flower petals on the statue, thought to have cost in excess of $400m (£315m), during an elaborate ceremony attended by Indian prime minister Narendra Modi. Read more - Statue of Matilda standing defiantly in front of Donald Trump unveiled - We must fight to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>India says nuclear submarine makes first patrol, Modi warns against 'misadventure' - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-submarine/india-says-nuclear-submarine-makes-first-patrol-modi-warns-against-misadventure-idUSKCN1NA1HK</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcGxHXgHLCL78XxmeTdJoQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 12:36:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-submarine/india-says-nuclear-submarine-makes-first-patrol-modi-warns-against-misadventure-idUSKCN1NA1HK" target="_blank"&gt;India says nuclear submarine makes first patrol, Modi warns against 'misadventure'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India said on Monday its first domestically built nuclear-powered submarine had recently completed a "deterrence patrol", giving it the capability to fire nuclear weapons from land, air and sea in the event of any "misadventure" by enemies. With nuclear-armed China to its north and nuclear-armed Pakistan to its west - both of which India has fought wars with - India's nationalist prime minister, Narendra Modi, said the INS Arihant was a "fitting response to those who indulge in nuclear blackmail". He did not elaborate. "Amid an increase in the number of nuclear weapons in our surroundings, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Why India's Modi wants to increase control over the central bank - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-centralbank-government-explaine/why-indias-modi-wants-to-increase-control-over-the-central-bank-idUSKCN1N70A5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENqO4-_JepWV-i5AZpu1jUoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 06:59:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-centralbank-government-explaine/why-indias-modi-wants-to-increase-control-over-the-central-bank-idUSKCN1N70A5" target="_blank"&gt;Why India's Modi wants to increase control over the central bank&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An incendiary speech by a top Reserve Bank of India (RBI) official last Friday blew the lid off an increasingly toxic dispute between the central bank and the government of Prime Minister Narendra Modi over monetary policy and who controls the institution's reserves. While historically there have been differences between the RBI and the nation's governments, the extent of the rift and its public nature are unprecedented. By Wednesday morning, there were Indian media reports saying that RBI Governor Urjit Patel was about to resign. The RBI declined comment. This followed three letters to the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>World's tallest statue opens amid surge in Indian mega-monuments - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/india-world-tallest-statue-opens/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGM3eLzkZoLPQq86VSY6L7gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIbnyQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:55:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/style/article/india-world-tallest-statue-opens/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;World's tallest statue opens amid surge in Indian mega-monuments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea that large statues might act as political tools is hardly a novel one. Immortalized figures from the past often serve the interests and ideologies of the present, whether it's Lord Nelson riding proudly above Trafalgar Square or North Korea's former leaders looming over Kim Il Sung Square. Compared to such blatant projections of power, the new 597-foot-tall sculpture of Sardar Patel in Gujarat cuts an altogether gentler figure. The record-breaking monument, which opens today, depicts the Indian politician wearing humble clothing and a placid expression. His arms hang calmly beside ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>India inaugurates world's tallest statue to celebrate independence hero - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-statue/india-inaugurates-worlds-tallest-statue-to-celebrate-independence-hero-idUSKCN1N50Z2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHa24NmYwxnIojSSOnWYp1YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 08:51:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-statue/india-inaugurates-worlds-tallest-statue-to-celebrate-independence-hero-idUSKCN1N50Z2" target="_blank"&gt;India inaugurates world's tallest statue to celebrate independence hero&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India on Wednesday inaugurated the world's tallest statue, a $400-million effigy of independence hero Vallabhbhai Patel that towers nearly twice the height of New York's Statue of Liberty. The 182-metre (597-ft) steel and bronze "Statue of Unity", in the prime minister's western home state of Gujarat, is part of his Hindu nationalist party's efforts to re-brand what it calls "forgotten" leaders. "Patel wanted India to be a forceful, strong, sensitive, vigilant and accommodative nation, and we're working toward that," Prime Minister Narendra Modi said at Wednesday's ceremony. Modi, who order...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The precarious autonomy of India’s central bank - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9b3e22da-de97-11e8-8f50-cbae5495d92b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEa3QUiHcuWoaFxN7ypsa3YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 17:14:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9b3e22da-de97-11e8-8f50-cbae5495d92b" target="_blank"&gt;The precarious autonomy of India’s central bank&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Viral Acharya, deputy governor of the Reserve Bank of India, uses a cricketing analogy to describe differences between the goals of central banks and governments. Politicians are in the hard-hitting 20-over form of the game, wrapped up in less than a day. Central bankers play the long form — Test match cricket, which last five days. While governments want quick results, the approach of central bankers is to try to win each session “but also importantly to survive it so as to have a chance to win the next”. In a polemical speech, this was a genteel way of framing an increasingly acrimonious ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Modi unveils towering statue of India's independence leader - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/modi-unveils-towering-statue-india-independence-leader-181029095308704.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBulSa7bp5JwvtOnoZ5W1NAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 05:49:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/modi-unveils-towering-statue-india-independence-leader-181029095308704.html" target="_blank"&gt;Modi unveils towering statue of India's independence leader&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi has unveiled a 182-metre statue, the world's tallest, to honour Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel, one of the country’s founding fathers and its first home minister. The $430m Statue of Unity, built on an island in Narmada river, was inaugurated by Modi on Wednesday in the western Indian state of Gujarat, home to both Patel and Modi. Patel was deputy to Jawaharlal Nehru, India's first prime minister, also the great grandfather of current Congress party president, Rahul Gandhi. Patel's legacy has been frequently used by Modi to undermine his chief political rivals,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Indian politician says had consensual relations with journalist accusing him of rape - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-harassment/indian-politician-says-had-consensual-relations-with-journalist-accusing-him-of-rape-idUSKCN1N71BD</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECCFRyoAwbJ2VBpMkpDHCyEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 12:13:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-harassment/indian-politician-says-had-consensual-relations-with-journalist-accusing-him-of-rape-idUSKCN1N71BD" target="_blank"&gt;Indian politician says had consensual relations with journalist accusing him of rape&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indian politician who resigned from the government last month after more than a dozen women accused him of sexual harassment, said on Friday he had a consensual relationship with a New York-based journalist who has accused him of raping her. Pallavi Gogoi, chief business editor at National Public Radio, wrote in a Washington Post column on Thursday that the former junior foreign minister, M.J. Akbar, "ripped off my clothes and raped me" in a hotel room in India 23 years ago. At the time, she and Akbar worked for the same newspaper. She said after the attack, Akbar had continued to "defil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Abe and Modi to discuss trade, security in Japan summit - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/abe-modi-discuss-trade-security-japan-summit-181028171042753.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFMF0pZRFPSfaJA09JqKtasqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 19:47:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/abe-modi-discuss-trade-security-japan-summit-181028171042753.html" target="_blank"&gt;Abe and Modi to discuss trade, security in Japan summit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe has welcomed his Indian counterpart Narendra Modi to Japan, hosting a private dinner at the premier's villa near Mount Fuji, to kick-off two days of talks on trade and security in the Indo-Pacific region. The two leaders are scheduled to hold formal talks in Tokyo on Monday that will also likely touch on China's growing power in the region. Abe himself had just returned from China, where he held talks with President Xi Jinping. Abe and Modi are expected to issue a joint communique on strengthening security cooperation and measures aimed at pursuing a "fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Indian court seeks pricing of Rafale jet deal with France - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/dd221374cfea405c9805b86558b52a7f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN2-Osb37Rg2krtp_uQ3kAAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:05:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/dd221374cfea405c9805b86558b52a7f" target="_blank"&gt;Indian court seeks pricing of Rafale jet deal with France&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — India's top court on Wednesday ordered the government to provide pricing details of 36 Rafale fighter jets it is buying from France. The court said the government must bring details of the decision-making process of the deal into the public domain, except those that are confidential and have strategic importance. The court said those can be provided in a "sealed cover" within 10 days. The deal has become a major political issue with the leader of the main opposition Indian National Congress party, Rahul Gandhi, accusing Prime Minister Narendra Modi's government of buying th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Killings in India's northeast raise tension over citizenship survey - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-assam-killings/killings-in-indias-northeast-raise-tension-over-citizenship-survey-idUSKCN1N70PM</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHNCUlqRDQSpAOuJagKwBGEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 09:16:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-assam-killings/killings-in-indias-northeast-raise-tension-over-citizenship-survey-idUSKCN1N70PM" target="_blank"&gt;Killings in India's northeast raise tension over citizenship survey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suspected Indian militants shot dead five Bengali-speaking Hindu men in a sensitive border state late on Thursday, police said, as tension grows over a controversial citizenship test to identify illegal immigrants from neighboring Bangladesh. India's northeastern state of Assam, home to 33 million people, has suffered years of violence as residents, including tribal groups, have clashed with suspected Hindu and Muslim settlers they accuse of plundering resources and grabbing jobs. The state's draft National Register of Citizens (NRC) released in July excluded 4 million mostly Bengali-speaki...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Mastercard lodged U.S. protest over Modi's promotion of Indian card network - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-mastercard-exclusive/exclusive-mastercard-lodged-us-protest-over-modis-promotion-of-indian-card-network-idUSKCN1N65IU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMwm1WU7CY6mVz5juKd0kRsqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 15:56:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-mastercard-exclusive/exclusive-mastercard-lodged-us-protest-over-modis-promotion-of-indian-card-network-idUSKCN1N65IU" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Mastercard lodged U.S. protest over Modi's promotion of Indian card network&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mastercard (MA.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) told the United States government in June that Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi was using nationalism to promote the use of a domestic payments network, and New Delhi's protectionist policies were hurting foreign payment companies, a document seen by Reuters showed. Modi has in recent years backed India's homegrown payments network "RuPay", whose rise has broken the dominance of U.S. payment giants such as Mastercard and Visa (V.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz). More than half of India's 1 billion debit and credit cards now ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Battle of wills pits Modi against central bank chief - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a43d845a-de9e-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPe5hyY_X2sDBrkmHtky5N0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 04:38:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a43d845a-de9e-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c" target="_blank"&gt;Battle of wills pits Modi against central bank chief&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India is not the first country where the government has been at loggerheads with the central bank over economic policy. Nor will it be the last. But the confrontation between Narendra Modi’s government and the Reserve Bank of India is unusually severe. RBI governor Urjit Patel reportedly threatened to resign after New Delhi considered invoking a law allowing the central government to impose its will. A full-blown crisis would alarm foreign investors and shake financial markets. The stand-off burst into the public domain with a combative speech by Viral Acharya, RBI deputy governor, that ref...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Protests expected as India prepares to unveil world's largest statue - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/30/protests-expected-india-prepares-unveil-worlds-largest-statue</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECi9YAibHVgaMV38r-sr4pwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 20:15:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/30/protests-expected-india-prepares-unveil-worlds-largest-statue" target="_blank"&gt;Protests expected as India prepares to unveil world's largest statue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of police officers have been deployed to guard the world’s biggest statue, as Indian authorities anticipate protests at its inauguration by the Indian prime minister, Narendra Modi. Authorities have planned a spectacular opening ceremony on Wednesday for the 182-metre (600ft) tall tribute to the Indian independence hero Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel, with air-force jets and helicopters to shower flowers on the statue during a flypast. But officials in Gujarat state are worried that community groups could stage protests to demand compensation for land taken to erect the Statue of Unity,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>India unveils world's biggest statue amid protests - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/31/india-unveils-worlds-biggest-statue-sardar-patel-amid-protests</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4ZgkummO9BeW2-7IIkNooqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 07:55:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/31/india-unveils-worlds-biggest-statue-sardar-patel-amid-protests" target="_blank"&gt;India unveils world's biggest statue amid protests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India has unveiled the world’s tallest statute depicting one of its independence leaders in a lavish ceremony that featured fireworks, fighter jets and rose petals showered by helicopters. The 182-metre statue of Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel, dubbed the “statue of unity” to commemorate the leader’s efforts to corral hundreds of princely states into the Indian union after independence, was opened on Wednesday by prime minister Narendra Modi. Huge crowds and more than 5,000 police officers gathered in a remote corner of Gujarat state for the opening, which has also sparked protests from local com...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Gloves off: India's ruling party underlines Hindu ambitions as elections near - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-analysis/gloves-off-indias-ruling-party-underlines-hindu-ambitions-as-elections-near-idUSKCN1N40VT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKomc_OeoJkkeBFIzR6v_vQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 08:31:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-religion-analysis/gloves-off-indias-ruling-party-underlines-hindu-ambitions-as-elections-near-idUSKCN1N40VT" target="_blank"&gt;Gloves off: India's ruling party underlines Hindu ambitions as elections near&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi's ruling Hindu nationalist party has been turning up the heat on some controversial and potentially highly divisive religious issues in recent days, with crucial state elections only weeks away and a general election due by next May. Top officials from his Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) have sided with some Hindus defying a court order that scrapped a ban on women of menstruating age from visiting a famous temple in southern India. At the same time, they and leaders of the Rashtriya Swayamsevak Sangh (RSS), the Hindu-first group from which the BJP was born,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Japan, India Leaders Build Ties Amid Trade, Security Worries - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/japan-india-leaders-build-ties-amid-trade-security-worries/4632548.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDim1njQCzoYxHvbZXA5IxkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 16:44:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/japan-india-leaders-build-ties-amid-trade-security-worries/4632548.html" target="_blank"&gt;Japan, India Leaders Build Ties Amid Trade, Security Worries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The leaders of Japan and India are reaffirming their ties amid growing worries about trade and regional stability. Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi, who arrived Saturday, was meeting Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe at a resort area near Mount Fuji on Sunday. Modi is also visiting a nearby plant of major Japanese robot maker Fanuc. Relations with China are a major issue shared by Modi and Abe, as their cooperation may balance China's growing regional influence and military assertiveness. "The India-Japan partnership has been fundamentally transformed and it has been strengthened as a '...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Celebrations as India unveils world’s tallest statue – in pictures - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/gallery/2018/oct/31/celebrations-as-india-unveils-worlds-tallest-statue-in-pictures</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPKmd0Rmm2P1VHkcYSb34a8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:29:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/gallery/2018/oct/31/celebrations-as-india-unveils-worlds-tallest-statue-in-pictures" target="_blank"&gt;Celebrations as India unveils world’s tallest statue – in pictures&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Indian prime minister, Narendra Modi, attends the inauguration of the statue, which has been constructed near the Narmada dam in Gujarat Photograph: EPA The 182-metre (597ft) tall statue cost £314m to construct. Funding came from the federal government, state-run companies and other institutions. It took the construction company Larsen &amp; Toubro 33 months to build Photograph: Sam Panthaky/AFP/Getty Images Traditional folk dancers from the state of Madhya Pradesh take part in the ceremony Photograph: Sam Panthaky/AFP/Getty Images Helicopters shower flower petals on the monument. Depicting...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>India RBI governor rumoured to be on brink of exit - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/58f8d1d0-dce5-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHdCt0Xqx6cOTtdSWxkEX3gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:43:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/58f8d1d0-dce5-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c" target="_blank"&gt;India RBI governor rumoured to be on brink of exit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urjit Patel, India’s central bank governor, was rumoured on Wednesday to be on the brink of resigning amid a stand-off with Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s government over the administration’s efforts to influence central bank policies. The speculation comes days after Mr Patel’s deputy, Viral Acharya, delivered a hard-hitting public lecture in which he warned of “potentially catastrophic” consequences of the government’s intensifying efforts to influence central bank policies. In an unusual statement on Wednesday, India’s finance ministry acknowledged that central bank autonomy was “an esse...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Amnesty says tax raid at its Indian office is assault on civil society - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/26/amnesty-says-tax-raid-indian-office-assault-on-civil-society</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEvXFwj0FFhKcLVMAF4Q8EIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 09:32:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/26/amnesty-says-tax-raid-indian-office-assault-on-civil-society" target="_blank"&gt;Amnesty says tax raid at its Indian office is assault on civil society&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amnesty International has condemned what it described as an “assault on civil society” in India after its office in the south of the country was raided by tax authorities. Amnesty India’s bank accounts have been frozen after tax investigators spent more than 10 hours searching the Bangalore headquarters of the London-based organisation on Thursday. Staff were ordered to remain in the office, shut their laptops and not use their mobile phones during the search, an Amnesty statement said. India’s enforcement directorate said in a press release it believed Amnesty had received £3.8m in foreign...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Urjit Patel: the yes-man who finally said no to Indian PM Modi - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cff837a6-dd8c-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFxITZUMyUMrbJYMe6IjGZQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 09:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cff837a6-dd8c-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c" target="_blank"&gt;Urjit Patel: the yes-man who finally said no to Indian PM Modi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Prime Minister Narendra Modi abolished India’s previous set of high-value banknotes two years ago, Urjit Patel, the newly appointed central bank governor, seemed little more than a pliant yes-man, who publicly defended one of the most unorthodox monetary experiments in Indian history. But two years on, Mr Patel, a Yale-trained economist known for being both publicity-shy and strong-willed, is refusing to do New Delhi’s bidding ahead of next year’s general election. Eager to boost the economy before Indians go to the polls within the next six months, Mr Modi’s government is pushing the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>India prepares to inaugurate the world's tallest statue - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/india-world-tallest-statue-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECD2MTjiHApaeU_HnX7MhewqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 01:53:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/style/article/india-world-tallest-statue-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;India prepares to inaugurate the world's tallest statue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India is set to unveil the world's tallest statue next week, the towering figure of Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel, a popular political and social leader, who was part of the freedom struggle that resulted in India's independence from British colonial rule in 1947. Looming 182 meters (597 feet) above the Narmada River in the western Indian state of Gujarat, the statue is set to be unveiled on October 31, revealing a figure molded from approximately 1,850metric tons of bronze. "In the world, people talk about America's Statue of Liberty. We want to make a statue of Sardar Patel at twice the size o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Indian PM Modi hails forgotten heroes in dig at opposition party - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-politics-modi-speech/indian-pm-modi-hails-forgotten-heroes-in-dig-at-opposition-party-idUSKCN1MV0HE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL7skiGZ5Jm261DbUWMRU88qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 12:16:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-politics-modi-speech/indian-pm-modi-hails-forgotten-heroes-in-dig-at-opposition-party-idUSKCN1MV0HE" target="_blank"&gt;Indian PM Modi hails forgotten heroes in dig at opposition party&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's Prime Minister Narendra Modi said on Sunday that many of the country's heroes from World War Two had been deliberately ignored, with his comments interpreted by many as an attack on the opposition Congress Party. In a speech in front of Delhi's historic Red Fort, Modi said that Subhas Chandra Bose, one of the key figures in India's battle for independence from Britain, had been marginalized in modern India. "In an effort to highlight the role of one family, efforts were made to deliberately ignore and forget others in the independence struggle," Modi said in a thinly-veiled referenc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India will retaliate with ‘double the force’ against any attack on its sovereignty – Modi - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/441893-india-sovereignty-force-army-modi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOdctDnG9s2Wh5R1TCB8-vUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 01:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/441893-india-sovereignty-force-army-modi/" target="_blank"&gt;India will retaliate with ‘double the force’ against any attack on its sovereignty – Modi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India will respond against aggressors who challenge its sovereignty with “double the force,” Prime Minister Narendra Modi has stated, noting that his government is not shy of taking “bold” steps to defend the country’s interests. “The strength of our Army has always been for self-protection, and it will remain so in the future too,” the Prime Minister said during his speech at Police Commemoration Day, stressing that “the best technology is being made available to the Indian Army.” Noting that while his government is committed to taking “big and bold” decisions, India has “never been greedy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Pakistan v India: Conflict moves to outer space as countries race to put human in orbit - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/442343-pakistan-india-space-mission/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBa8qLPSqxJfiVFIqrRipLIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 11:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/442343-pakistan-india-space-mission/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan v India: Conflict moves to outer space as countries race to put human in orbit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan is moving its competition with India to a parallel pitch as it intends to send a human into space with the help of China… in the exact year that India promised to do the same in collaboration with Russia. The Information Ministry of Pakistan announced on Thursday that the country intends to carry out its first space mission in 2022, with Prime Minister Imran Khan having already approved the plan at a federal cabinet meeting. The proposed deadline is the same year that Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi hopes to launch the country’s first manned mission to space, which will take pl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>India's CBI chief removed, critics say 'misuse of power' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/india-cbi-chief-removed-critics-misuse-power-181024085438865.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYg_XZaBL5Kdy2vezpULfsqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 14:58:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/india-cbi-chief-removed-critics-misuse-power-181024085438865.html" target="_blank"&gt;India's CBI chief removed, critics say 'misuse of power'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India's government removed the head of the country's top investigating agency and his deputy in a pre-dawn raid on Wednesday - a move the opposition parties and constitutional experts said amounted to "misuse of power". Director of the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI), Alok Verma, and Special Director Rakesh Asthana were asked to go on leave after the premier agency filed a corruption case against Asthana. A feud between the two men has been simmering since before Asthana, who is allegedly close to Prime Minister Narendra Modi, was promoted to the agency's second-highest post last year...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item></channel></rss>