<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Central African Republic - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNREZ1ZVd3U0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:09:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Central African Republic extradites ex-militia leader 'Rambo' - Myjoyonline.com</title><link>https://www.myjoyonline.com/world/2018/November-18th/central-african-republic-extradites-ex-militia-leader-rambo.php</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMidGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm15am95b25saW5lLmNvbS93b3JsZC8yMDE4L05vdmVtYmVyLTE4dGgvY2VudHJhbC1hZnJpY2FuLXJlcHVibGljLWV4dHJhZGl0ZXMtZXgtbWlsaXRpYS1sZWFkZXItcmFtYm8ucGhw0gEA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.myjoyonline.com/world/2018/November-18th/central-african-republic-extradites-ex-militia-leader-rambo.php" target="_blank"&gt;Central African Republic extradites ex-militia leader 'Rambo'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Myjoyonline.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An MP and former militia leader in the Central African Republic (CAR) has been extradited to The Hague to face trial for crimes against humanity.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.myjoyonline.com">Myjoyonline.com</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/-Ep-ldHbBVSFU9Yzn2hd1mIAZtDDxTxPCFGm8cvzyQXC73q8aNwnMWKhiN3BBGTuK0icz6-FKkLUdXSXtDjOCeRQqbxXyzVInQ_7PsA8GaqtBw8iLIZxdWN8uJfbnbHp2uiH=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>UN rights office: Burundi's government has asked us to leave - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/a560b3ac68e84ca188568aeaecc003d8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPLSdPrJqACIOYCdM8pnfgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:25:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/a560b3ac68e84ca188568aeaecc003d8" target="_blank"&gt;UN rights office: Burundi's government has asked us to leave&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya (AP) — The United Nations human rights office on Thursday said Burundi's government has asked it to leave, months after the outgoing U.N. rights chief called the country one of the "most prolific slaughterhouses of humans in recent times." Spokeswoman Ravina Shamdasani in Geneva confirmed they received a letter on Wednesday "requesting us to close the office. We of course regret this decision and we would like to continue our cooperation with Burundi." She declined to comment further, calling the issue sensitive. Sources within the U.N. office in Burundi told The Associated P...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Burundi Orders Closure of UN Human Rights Office - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-rights-office-burundi-s-government-has-asked-us-to-leave/4689177.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMf61pXkYG1e41zm_Owov84qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:07:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-rights-office-burundi-s-government-has-asked-us-to-leave/4689177.html" target="_blank"&gt;Burundi Orders Closure of UN Human Rights Office&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burundi has ordered the U.N. Human Rights Council to close its office in the east African country. Geneva-based spokeswoman Ravina Shamdasani says the council received a letter Wednesday "requesting that we close the office in Burundi." Shamdasani told VOA's Central Africa service on Thursday, "We of course regret this as we are keen to continue our cooperation with Burundi on the promotion and protection of human rights." She added, "We will be communicating with [the] government in due course." Burundi's foreign ministry and U.N. sources said the council was given two months to leave the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Boris Becker drops claim for diplomatic immunity - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/boris-becker-drops-immunity-claim/10580086</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELkA6RmtF5k_uuhxqif9zR0qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:19:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/boris-becker-drops-immunity-claim/10580086" target="_blank"&gt;Boris Becker drops claim for diplomatic immunity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retired German tennis star Boris Becker has dropped his claim to have diplomatic immunity from bankruptcy proceedings in Britain. The three-time Wimbledon champion had been claiming his unpaid role as a sports attaché for Central African Republic gave him immunity from bankruptcy rulings.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Ex-Hong Kong politician faces jail after bribery conviction in US - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/asia/patrick-ho-bribery-conviction-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECJaAk-Kbr6K2LLl5yLAt90qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 01:31:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/asia/patrick-ho-bribery-conviction-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-Hong Kong politician faces jail after bribery conviction in US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former Hong Kong politician faces jail time in the US after being convicted of scheming to offer millions of dollars in bribes to African leaders, through contacts made at the United Nations. Patrick Ho Chi-ping, 69, was on Tuesday found guilty by a federal jury in New York on seven of eight counts of violating the Foreign Corrupt Practices Act and money laundering. He was acquitted on one count of international money laundering. The maximum penalty for each charge ranges from five to 20 years in jail. Ho, who pleaded not guilty, will be sentenced on March 15. The seven-day trial began a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>UN Hosts Meeting of Regional Envoys Over Western Sahara - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-hosts-meeting-of-regional-envoys-over-western-sahara/4687979.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEErgmybHV4dEBAq1xsntIxQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:32:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-hosts-meeting-of-regional-envoys-over-western-sahara/4687979.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Hosts Meeting of Regional Envoys Over Western Sahara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N. secretary-general's envoy for Western Sahara is meeting with foreign ministers from Algeria, Morocco and Mauritania plus leaders of the Polisario Front over the future of the Morocco-annexed territory. U.N. envoy Horst Koehler, a former German president, hosted a "round-table" discussion among the attendees at the first U.N.-hosted talks on the territory in six years, after meeting with them bilaterally earlier Wednesday. The U.N. says the two-day meeting is a first step toward a renewed negotiations process aiming to "provide for the self-determination of the people of Western Sah...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Yemen to face worst humanitarian crisis of 2019: UN - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/yemen-face-worst-humanitarian-crisis-2019-181204105615554.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENoQ1pwCSFKsQkQKzbHui8UqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:26:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/yemen-face-worst-humanitarian-crisis-2019-181204105615554.html" target="_blank"&gt;Yemen to face worst humanitarian crisis of 2019: UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some 132 million people in 42 countries will need humanitarian assistance and protection in 2019 with Yemen topping the list of most-desperate nations, the UN said on Tuesday. Funding requirements next year will amount to $21.9bn with Yemen facing the worst humanitarian emergency followed by Afghanistan, Cameroon and Central African Republic. Presenting the Global Humanitarian Overview for 2019, Emergency Relief Coordinator Mark Lowcock said the UN and its partner organisations aim to assist some 93.6 million of the most vulnerable with food, shelter, healthcare, emergency education, protec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pacific Island Hopper: The world's most scenic flight? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/pacific-island-hopper/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJzEiTC66D4pXFj5tFPgbCcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 09:39:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/pacific-island-hopper/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pacific Island Hopper: The world's most scenic flight?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spectacular scenic flight: Aviation geeks call it "the holy grail of flight routes" -- welcome on board United Airlines 154, the Island Hopper. Chris Dwyer Incredible experience: The Island Hopper flight connects seven islands in a 16-hour flight, four times weekly. Chris Dwyer 50 year anniversary: 2018 marks half a century since the route was first flown. Back in 1968 Continental Micronesia was the carrier. Chris Dwyer First stop: There are four pilots on board the plane to share the route. First stop? Marjuro, in the Marshall Islands. Courtesy Chris Dwyer Marjuro harbor: The Marshall Isla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>No major damage reported after magnitude-7.5 earthquake off New Caledonia's coast - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-05/new-caledonia-vanuatu-tsunami-warning/10586412</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHO5g52dtBR6q0rdZnwbZH0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:04:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-05/new-caledonia-vanuatu-tsunami-warning/10586412" target="_blank"&gt;No major damage reported after magnitude-7.5 earthquake off New Caledonia's coast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pacific Tsunami Warning Centre (PTWC) says the tsunami threat has passed after a strong, shallow earthquake hit off the coast of New Caledonia. Key points: - The earthquake struck about 310 kilometres from New Caledonia's capital - 1-3-metre waves were forecast, but Vanuatu is not expecting "destructive" waves - No threat alert was issued for Australia The US National Tsunami Centre said the magnitude-7.5 quake struck at a depth of around 10 kilometres just after 3:00pm (local time), about 168 kilometres east of the nearest population centre, Tadine, on New Caledonia's Loyalty Islands. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>The secret committee determining medical transfers from Nauru and Manus Island - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/secret-immigration-committee-medical-transfers-from-nauru-manus/10579072</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAHHhHjW9WSXPcSbQp9GuSgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 06:38:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/secret-immigration-committee-medical-transfers-from-nauru-manus/10579072" target="_blank"&gt;The secret committee determining medical transfers from Nauru and Manus Island&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A secret Australian government body tasked with making decisions on medical transfers from Nauru discussed eradicating a longstanding requirement that medical care in offshore facilities must meet "Australian standards", according to internal documents. 7.30 can reveal highly confidential details of the Transitory Persons Committee, a body comprised of senior public servants in the Department of Home Affairs. The committee serves as a crucial decision-making body for considering transfers of asylum seekers and refugees seeking urgent medical care, and has met roughly once a month over an 18...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Guinea-Bissau Naturalizes Senegalese Refugees - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/guinea-bissau-naturalizes-senegalese-refugees/4681514.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFDVWW4dDwEc8OdMz8assQ4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 04:45:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/guinea-bissau-naturalizes-senegalese-refugees/4681514.html" target="_blank"&gt;Guinea-Bissau Naturalizes Senegalese Refugees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senegalese refugees in Guinea-Bissau are getting identification cards after years — and, for some, decades — of living in a state of limbo. Ibrahima Ingo has lived in Pelundo, near Guinea-Bissau's border with Senegal, since 1992 when he fled southern Senegal due to unrest in the country's Casamance region. Today marks the first time he will register to receive his national identification card as a Guinea-Bissau citizen. Ibrahima Ingo, a refugee from Senegal now living in Guinea-Bissau, holds up his citizenship registration as he stands in his cashew field in Pelundo, Nov. 11, 2018. He says ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>UNICEF USA BrandVoice: A Malnourished Toddler's Recovery In Central African Republic - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2018/12/03/a-malnourished-toddlers-recovery-in-central-african-republic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMHskIKvG8bI6TjQ3tKy9G0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:17:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2018/12/03/a-malnourished-toddlers-recovery-in-central-african-republic/" target="_blank"&gt;UNICEF USA BrandVoice: A Malnourished Toddler's Recovery In Central African Republic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more than 70 years, UNICEF has been putting children first, protecting their rights and providing the assistance and services they need to survive and thrive. The day Prosper rushed his son Pierre to the health center, the frighteningly emaciated 3-year-old barely clung to life. During the 7-mile walk from their village to the nearest health center outside Bangui, the capital of Central African Republic (CAR), the desperate father prayed: “I didn’t know if I was going to get to the hospital with Pierre alive. Even if I made it, I didn’t know if he would make it. I wondered if God’s pla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Australia's climate change inaction nulls 'Pacific pivot': Tuvalu PM - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/tuvalu-pm-says-australian-pacific-pivot-undermined-by-emissions/10579424</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBhg6fGrUkJH5bx4dHNxTgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:39:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/tuvalu-pm-says-australian-pacific-pivot-undermined-by-emissions/10579424" target="_blank"&gt;Australia's climate change inaction nulls 'Pacific pivot': Tuvalu PM&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Prime Minister of Tuvalu Enele Sopoaga has warned Australia that its "Pacific pivot" risks being fatally undermined by its climate change policies ahead of crucial talks in Poland. Key points - Tuvalu's PM made the comments ahead of COP24, the most important climate talks since the Paris agreement - He says Australia's return to the Pacific undermined by climate change inaction - Tuvalu is particularly vulnerable to climate change, being made up of low-lying atolls Australia has unveiled an ambitious suite of policies to cement its position in the region and push back against China, inc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>UNICEF: More than 1.5 million children in CAR need emergency aid - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/unicef-15-million-children-car-emergency-aid-181130110305475.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELql9KYA5CMzPAGSeUqzaJUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:55:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/unicef-15-million-children-car-emergency-aid-181130110305475.html" target="_blank"&gt;UNICEF: More than 1.5 million children in CAR need emergency aid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around two-thirds of all children in the Central African Republic (CAR) need emergency aid, UNICEF has said, as it sounded alarm bells over the "neglected" crisis ravaging the country. In a report published on Friday, UNICEF said around 1.5 million children were in need of humanitarian assistance, with at least 43,000 children under the age of five "projected to face an extremely high risk of death due to severe acute malnutrition next year". "CAR has the world's second-highest newborn death rate and maternal mortality ratio, fewer than three out of five children make it through primary sch...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>UNICEF USA BrandVoice: An Escalating Crisis In Central African Republic - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2018/11/30/an-escalating-crisis-in-central-african-republic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENViEnz0BkC2BUBpCeUCsVgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:41:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2018/11/30/an-escalating-crisis-in-central-african-republic/" target="_blank"&gt;UNICEF USA BrandVoice: An Escalating Crisis In Central African Republic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more than 70 years, UNICEF has been putting children first, protecting their rights and providing the assistance and services they need to survive and thrive. PLEASE DONATE [id=0] In December 2012, armed groups began a campaign of sectarian violence in Bangui, the capital of the Central African Republic (CAR). The looting, raping and killing briefly made international headlines, amid speculation of a failed state and possible genocide. But then the story sank from view. A brutal bloodbath in 2013, and now a resurgence Now the few early signs of recovery and rebuilding in CAR have given...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nauru mental health situation akin to 'victims of torture', MSF says - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-03/msf-says-nauru-is-equivalent-to-torture-victims/10575818</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBgPFJTBaQtiOIQFqX1ZpgsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 23:36:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-03/msf-says-nauru-is-equivalent-to-torture-victims/10575818" target="_blank"&gt;Nauru mental health situation akin to 'victims of torture', MSF says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mental health situation on Nauru is equivalent to that of victims of torture, Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF) says, in what it describes as the first independent medical data on mental health conditions on the island. Key points: - MSF says offshore processing is to blame for the poor mental health on Nauru - Independent Kerryn Phelps plans to table a bill to bring asylum seekers to Australia for treatment - MSF said the bill does not go far enough and everyone should be removed from the island MSF treated 208 asylum seekers and refugees in the 11 months its medical staff were on Nauru, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>UNICEF: Children in CAR Face Lives of Desperation, Deprivation - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/unicef-children-in-car-face-lives-of-desperation-deprivation/4680986.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBwfSOdak9xw0bPbKxML0p0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 10:53:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/unicef-children-in-car-face-lives-of-desperation-deprivation/4680986.html" target="_blank"&gt;UNICEF: Children in CAR Face Lives of Desperation, Deprivation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new report presents a dire portrait of the lives of hundreds of thousands of children in the Central African Republic. They live in a state of permanent crisis brought on by years of conflict and international neglect, a report by the United Nations Children’s Fund on the “Crisis in the Central African Republic” found. The U.N. children’s fund considers the Central African Republic to be one of the most difficult and dangerous places in the world to be a child. And the statistics bear this out. The new UNICEF report finds that 2 out of 3 children, or 1.5 million children in the C.A.R., ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kremlin bank blames error for $12bn African ‘loan’ - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/29de9bf2-f331-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFOvoZMtwb7qLm2YKERDiEwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 18:36:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/29de9bf2-f331-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Kremlin bank blames error for $12bn African ‘loan’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Russian state bank appeared to give a $12bn loan to one of Africa’s poorest countries — then claimed the stated payment to the Central African Republic was an accounting error. VTB, the Kremlin’s second-largest bank, said on Wednesday that a software error had confused countries with obligations to it and awarded the CAR a nonexistent $12bn loan that was instead extended to Cyprus. “The accounting forms link the accounts to the countries. The links stopped working and the countries got moved all over the place,” said Dmitry Olyunin, VTB chief financial officer. VTB’s initial accounts for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Group of Manus Island refugees move to Nauru amid worsening health crisis - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/29/group-of-manus-island-refugees-move-to-nauru-amid-worsening-health-crisis</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELII4K9nGx4ZPBl937e515IqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:59:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/29/group-of-manus-island-refugees-move-to-nauru-amid-worsening-health-crisis" target="_blank"&gt;Group of Manus Island refugees move to Nauru amid worsening health crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of refugees have left Manus Island and are moving to Nauru while they wait for resettlement in a third country. Guardian Australia has confirmed at least eight men were told they could transfer from the immigration facility on the Papua New Guinea island to its equivalent in Nauru. It is understood they departed on Thursday morning amid a worsening health crisis on Manus. The group will arrive in Nauru on Thursday afternoon and will spend the night in the RPC1 section of the detention centre, before moving into the community accomodation units. Related: ‘Sam could have been saved’: ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UN warns of famine in violence-hit Central African Republic - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/warns-famine-violence-hit-central-african-republic-181121170805260.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHIW-4u_EC8TzdsZhHUYx8sqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 18:55:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/warns-famine-violence-hit-central-african-republic-181121170805260.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN warns of famine in violence-hit Central African Republic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Famine would hit the Central African Republic is nothing is done to reverse the humanitarian situation in the country which is deteriorating at an "alarming rate", the United Nations has warned. The growing unrest in the country of 4.5m people is forcing many to flee their homes and abandon their fields, causing spiralling food insecurity, the UN humanitarian coordinator in the country, Najat Rochdi, told reporters in Geneva on Wednesday. If the situation remains the same, and people do not return to their fields, "it means that in very few years, we'll have a famine in the Central African ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>'Rambo' CAR militia leader charged with war crimes and crimes against humanity - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/africa/yekatom-car-icc-war-crimes-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBQrpXKCwguOD1VPuUdxHnkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 16:18:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/africa/yekatom-car-icc-war-crimes-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Rambo' CAR militia leader charged with war crimes and crimes against humanity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Central African Republic (CAR) militia leader widely known as "Rambo" has been charged with a number of war crimes and crimes against humanity, including murder, torture and the use of child soldiers, at the International Criminal Court in The Hague. Alfred Yekatom is the former commander of a group of 3,000 members of the anti-balaka movement, a group consisting mainly of Christians that opposed a largely Muslim rebel alliance known as Seleka, the ICC said. His crimes allegedly took place "in various locations within the Central African Republic, including the capital Bangui and Lobaye p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Central African Republic Militia Leader Appears at ICC - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/central-african-republic-militia-leader-appears-at-icc/4671258.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKqViDEjDAlR5BjYavl-REqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:35:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/central-african-republic-militia-leader-appears-at-icc/4671258.html" target="_blank"&gt;Central African Republic Militia Leader Appears at ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Central African Republic militia leader and lawmaker who goes by the nickname Rambo told the International Criminal Court on Friday he was beaten and tortured after his arrest late last month in parliament. Prosecutors at the global court allege that 43-year-old Alfred Yekatom is responsible for crimes including murder, torture and using child soldiers during his country's bitter conflict. He allegedly commanded some 3,000 fighters in a predominantly Christian militia that killed Muslims in attacks between December 2013 and August 2014 in and around the capital, Bangui. At his first appea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Netanyahu to formally establish ties with Chad in upcoming visit - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/netanyahu-formally-establish-ties-chad-upcoming-visit-181127120212140.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPdyzhzFLNRtG2YfjwEVBugqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 12:26:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/netanyahu-formally-establish-ties-chad-upcoming-visit-181127120212140.html" target="_blank"&gt;Netanyahu to formally establish ties with Chad in upcoming visit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu will visit Chad in the near future to formally establish diplomatic relations between the two countries, the prime minister's office said. The announcement on Tuesday came hours after the Israeli leader met with Chad President Idriss Deby in Jerusalem, Israeli daily Haaretz reported. "The two discussed shared threats and the struggle against terrorism, increased cooperation between the nations in the areas of agriculture, counter terrorism, border security, technology, solar energy, water, health and more," the statement said. Deby had arrived in Is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Central African war crimes suspect 'Rambo' handed to global court - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-war-crimes-central-african-republic/central-african-war-crimes-suspect-rambo-handed-to-global-court-idUSKCN1NM0M4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMObrTlKZtczRvMAD86mQ0YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 18:20:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-war-crimes-central-african-republic/central-african-war-crimes-suspect-rambo-handed-to-global-court-idUSKCN1NM0M4" target="_blank"&gt;Central African war crimes suspect 'Rambo' handed to global court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A war crimes suspect wanted for alleged murder, deportation and torture of Muslims in the Central African Republic has been handed over to the International Criminal Court in the Hague, the tribunal said. CAR officials transferred Alfred Yekatom on Saturday to officials from the global court, which is investigating six years of violence that has destabilised a region at the heart of the continent. Yekatom, a sitting MP once nicknamed "Rambo", had been under arrest in Central African Republic since Oct. 29, when during a parliamentary session he first pointed a gun at a fellow lawmaker and t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Russian Bank: We Assigned $12B ‘Loan’ to Poor African State by Mistake - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/russian-bank-we-assigned-12-billion-loan-to-poor-african-state-by-mistake-/4677038.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJpFQLe8p4JrNXWYk7m1E0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:46:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/russian-bank-we-assigned-12-billion-loan-to-poor-african-state-by-mistake-/4677038.html" target="_blank"&gt;Russian Bank: We Assigned $12B ‘Loan’ to Poor African State by Mistake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The impoverished state of Central African Republic landed a windfall on Tuesday, at least on paper, when Russian state bank VTB reported it had lent the country $12 billion — but the bank then said it was a clerical error and there was no such loan. The loan was mentioned in a quarterly VTB financial report published by the Russian central bank. The report included a table listing the outstanding financial claims that VTB group had on dozens of countries as of Oct. 1 this year. In the table next to Central African Republic was the sum of $12 billion — more than six times the country's annua...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Central African Republic MP nicknamed 'Rambo' arrested over alleged war crimes against Muslims - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/war-crimes-alfred-yekatom-rambo-central-african-republic-muslims-hague-a8639816.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBr814KYHfqC4mShzYN0mgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 16:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/war-crimes-alfred-yekatom-rambo-central-african-republic-muslims-hague-a8639816.html" target="_blank"&gt;Central African Republic MP nicknamed 'Rambo' arrested over alleged war crimes against Muslims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A war crimes suspect wanted for alleged murder, deportation and torture of Muslims in the Central African Republic has been handed over to the International Criminal Court in The Hague, the tribunal said. CAR officials transferred Alfred Yekatom on Saturday to officials from the global court, which is looking into more than six years of violence that has destabilised a fragile region at the heart of the continent. Mr Yekatom, a sitting MP once nicknamed "Rambo", was flown out of the country and arrived in the court's detention centre in The Hague in the early hours of Sunday, officials ther...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Analysis: What's in the secret documents signed by China and Vanuatu at APEC? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/the-secret-documents-china-and-vanuatu-signed-at-apec/10557438</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHj6aslaT48Cngy696VtV-cqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 01:29:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/the-secret-documents-china-and-vanuatu-signed-at-apec/10557438" target="_blank"&gt;Analysis: What's in the secret documents signed by China and Vanuatu at APEC?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Pacific affairs reporter Stephen Dziedzic The ABC and the Vanuatu Daily Post newspaper have obtained seven agreements signed by China and the nation of Vanuatu just before the APEC meeting. They reveal just how much time, money and energy China is throwing into the Pacific as it continues to assert its presence in the region. You can see the benefits that this intensifying competition brings Pacific Island nations like Vanuatu. But you can also see the geopolitical tripwires and risks these countries face as they navigate increasingly turbulent waters and try to keep a firm grip on their...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Chad's Idriss Deby in first-ever visit to Israel - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/chad-idriss-deby-visit-israel-181125135735540.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBvG6qtuNilE03SFJIRc2rgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 15:43:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/chad-idriss-deby-visit-israel-181125135735540.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chad's Idriss Deby in first-ever visit to Israel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chadian President Idriss Deby is in Israel for talks with Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, the first such visit by a leader of the northcentral African nation which severed bilateral ties in 1972. Deby landed on Sunday in Tel Aviv, where he was received by Tzachi Hanegbi, minister for regional cooperation. "It was my honor to welcome the President of Chad, Idriss Deby, to Israel. This historic visit is yet another diplomatic breakthrough between Israel and Africa," Hanegbi posted on Twitter. Ofir Gendelman, a spokesperson for Netanyahu, quoted the Israeli prime minister as saying he will ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Dozens of bodies found after attack on CAR refugee mission - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/car-dozens-killed-attack-catholic-mission-hosting-refugees-181117150925230.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE5Nz293864QXkejrDUMv54qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 08:01:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/car-dozens-killed-attack-catholic-mission-hosting-refugees-181117150925230.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dozens of bodies found after attack on CAR refugee mission&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 40 people have been killed and dozens wounded in Central African Republic (CAR), in an attack on a Catholic mission sheltering 20,000 refugees, according to a regional legislator. The violence in the town of Alindao, some 300km east of the capital, Bangui, began on Thursday when Christian militiamen known as "Anti-balaka" killed Muslims, prompting revenge attacks. A church was burned, forcing "thousands" of people to flee, the United Nations' peacekeeping mission in the CAR (MINUSCA) said. "We have counted 42 bodies so far, but we are still searching for others. The camp has been ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Israel: Visit by Chad's leader Is 'Diplomatic Breakthrough' - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/israel-visit-by-chad-s-leader-is-diplomatic-breakthrough-/4672916.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbvbIbu1Vn_FIz-y22fcgoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 12:51:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/israel-visit-by-chad-s-leader-is-diplomatic-breakthrough-/4672916.html" target="_blank"&gt;Israel: Visit by Chad's leader Is 'Diplomatic Breakthrough'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel's prime minister says the leader of the African nation of Chad is arriving for a historic visit. Benjamin Netanyahu says he will host President Idriss Deby on Sunday in Jerusalem. He says they'll meet privately and then give a joint press statement before dining together. It's the first ever visit of a president of Chad, which broke off relations with Israel in 1972. Netanyahu calls the visit “another diplomatic breakthrough.” Netanyahu has made great efforts to extend Israeli diplomacy to Africa and has visited the continent several times in recent years. It's part of an overall pol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>At least 42 killed in attack on refugee base in Central African Republic - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/attack-refugee-camp-militia-central-african-republic-alindao-seleka-anti-balaka-a8639206.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN99XUlCwadA7tU_6MdrcUMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 22:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/attack-refugee-camp-militia-central-african-republic-alindao-seleka-anti-balaka-a8639206.html" target="_blank"&gt;At least 42 killed in attack on refugee base in Central African Republic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 42 people were killed in an attack on a Catholic mission sheltering 20,000 refugees in the Central African Republic, according to officials. The camp in the town of Alindao, around 300km east of the capital Bangui, was set on fire on Thursday following clashes between two rival armed groups. Thousands were forced to flee their homes during the violence and dozens were left injured. A priest is among the dead. “We have counted 42 bodies so far, but we are still searching for others,” said Etienne Godenaha, a politician from Alindao. Read more - London pupils share rap message with c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Vanuatu says it may sue fossil fuel companies and other countries over climate change - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/22/vanuatu-says-it-may-sue-fossil-fuel-companies-and-other-countries-over-climate-change</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB5Vd9xAu0hM0iZmFgaTCyIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 07:00:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/22/vanuatu-says-it-may-sue-fossil-fuel-companies-and-other-countries-over-climate-change" target="_blank"&gt;Vanuatu says it may sue fossil fuel companies and other countries over climate change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Republic of Vanuatu says it will explore whether it can take legal action against fossil fuel companies and countries for their role in causing climate change. The Pacific nation says it is growing desperate for financial assistance to deal with the loss and damage it is increasingly experiencing due to extreme weather and global warming. In a statement on Thursday to the Climate Vulnerable Forum, an international summit focused on those most at risk to the effects of climate change, Vanuatu’s foreign minister, Ralph Regenvanu, said he was putting the fossil fuel industry “and the state...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>New US Ambassador to Somalia Sees Path to Peace, Prosperity - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/new-us-ambassador-to-somalia-sees-path-to-peace-prosperity/4672810.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGVaC_jSBOUxWruoIgtRZPkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 02:02:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/new-us-ambassador-to-somalia-sees-path-to-peace-prosperity/4672810.html" target="_blank"&gt;New US Ambassador to Somalia Sees Path to Peace, Prosperity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A week before Donald Yamamoto arrived in Mogadishu, three car bombs exploded in the heart of the city, just outside the Sahafi Hotel. Dozens of nearby motorists and pedestrians were killed or maimed. A fourth bomb went off when first responders arrived, bringing the death toll to at least 52, with more than 100 casualties. It was the latest in a string of attacks by the Islamist terror group al-Shabab, which for more than a decade has sought to dismantle the Somali federal government. A Somali helps an injured civilian who was wounded in a bomb blast near the Sahafi hotel in the capital Mog...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>'Killing, abuse, sexual violence beyond belief': fears grow of all-out war in CAR - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/nov/16/killing-abuse-sexual-violence-beyond-belief-fears-grow-of-all-out-war-in-central-african-republic</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAEmwSWpFsA7aOo-1BfXNPQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 07:00:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/nov/16/killing-abuse-sexual-violence-beyond-belief-fears-grow-of-all-out-war-in-central-african-republic" target="_blank"&gt;'Killing, abuse, sexual violence beyond belief': fears grow of all-out war in CAR&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UN security council has failed to agree terms for extending a peacekeeping mission in Central African Republic just days after a top aid official warned the country is at risk of sliding into full-scale war. Jan Egeland, secretary general of the Norwegian Refugee Council, who warned the UN peacekeeping mission is overstretched, said wider efforts to end the conflict were also failing. “The UN effort is not succeeding, the donor effort is not succeeding and the government is in no way steering the country toward good governance,” said Egeland. “Nor are CAR’s neighbours playing the role o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Kiribati founding father accuses Government of covering up fatal ferry disaster - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-21/kiribati-government-accused-of-cover-up-of-ferry-disaster/10510446</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECjEAAu7NvuBntMfm55QmqIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 03:01:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-21/kiribati-government-accused-of-cover-up-of-ferry-disaster/10510446" target="_blank"&gt;Kiribati founding father accuses Government of covering up fatal ferry disaster&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kiribati's first president has accused the country's current leader of withholding a report into a ferry disaster in January that killed at least 80 people, because he says they are "trying to hide the fact they're responsible". Key points: - Many of the victims were the "best and brightest" students of Nonouti island - ABC understands a final report into the ferry disaster has been completed - A report into the tragedy has not been made public The MV Butiraoi sank in January when making the journey from the island of Nonouti to the Pacific island nation's capital of South Tarawa with about...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>C. African Republic militia leader turned over to tribunal - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/abe734ab2e3f430da0109d1a46b88d2f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJPSWffoJ5lHxyGirexAIgkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 20:09:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/abe734ab2e3f430da0109d1a46b88d2f" target="_blank"&gt;C. African Republic militia leader turned over to tribunal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — A commander in a Central African Republic militia has been arrested and turned over to the International Criminal Court to face charges that include murder and torture, the court announced Saturday. The court, established to prosecute atrocities such as war crimes, said Central African Republic authorities surrendered Alfred Yekatom on Saturday. Court spokesman Fadi El Abdallah would not say if Yekatom already had been sent to the court's headquarters in The Hague. The Central African Republic has been plagued by interreligious and intercommunal fighting since ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>CAR suspect wanted for war crimes against Muslims handed to ICC - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/car-suspect-wanted-war-crimes-muslims-handed-icc-181117180402662.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEeX2ND_L26ugFK8STB860oqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 19:10:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/car-suspect-wanted-war-crimes-muslims-handed-icc-181117180402662.html" target="_blank"&gt;CAR suspect wanted for war crimes against Muslims handed to ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alfred Yekatom, a war crimes suspect wanted for alleged atrocities against Muslims in the Central African Republic (CAR), has been extradited to The Hague to stand trial at the International Criminal Court (ICC). The announcement by the tribunal on Saturday came days after issuing a warrant against Yekatom - a sitting member of parliament once nicknamed "Rambo" - for his alleged criminal responsibility for war crimes and crimes against humanity The ICC launched an investigation in September 2014 into crimes committed in the resource-rich but poor country since 2012. A former army officer, Y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>China gives Tonga five years' grace on loan repayments - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-19/china-defers-tongas-loan-payments-as-nation-signs-up-to-bri/10509140</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIHv-uGak7umSQtRaZk-1pcqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:47:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-19/china-defers-tongas-loan-payments-as-nation-signs-up-to-bri/10509140" target="_blank"&gt;China gives Tonga five years' grace on loan repayments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tonga has signed up to China's Belt and Road initiative and received a reprieve from Beijing on the timing of debt payments shortly before an onerous schedule to repay loans was due to start. Lopeti Senituli, political adviser to Tongan Prime Minister Akilisi Pohiva, said Tonga had signed a Belt and Road memorandum of understanding, and the concessional loan had been deferred for five years. Tonga is one of eight island nations in the South Pacific that owe a significant debt to China. The deferment came just as Tonga was set to commence principal repayments on its debt, which is expected t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Central African Republic: A crisis forgotten by everyone, except Russia - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/blogs/africa/2018/11/central-african-republic-crisis-forgotten-russia-181114135617254.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENcKibGSjp40K0S4MEvXWVQqEwgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwgRI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:06:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/blogs/africa/2018/11/central-african-republic-crisis-forgotten-russia-181114135617254.html" target="_blank"&gt;Central African Republic: A crisis forgotten by everyone, except Russia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is something deeply unsettling about seeing a white man posing for pictures, surrounded by young African children calling for help, in the 21st century. Last year, I covered the visit of United Nations Secretary General Antonio Guterres to the Central African Republic (CAR). This year, we followed Jan Egeland from the Norwegian Refugee Council. One called the CAR a forgotten conflict the other a neglected one. Both visits were about pretty much the same thing: drawing attention to a country largely ignored by the international community spiralling into sectarian violence and on the ve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Brisbane construction firm Canstruct made $43m profit running Nauru detention centre last year - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/15/brisbane-construction-firm-made-43m-profit-running-nauru-detention-centre-last-year</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH7fNrscgZGj_p6eg5-dOOYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 01:02:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/15/brisbane-construction-firm-made-43m-profit-running-nauru-detention-centre-last-year" target="_blank"&gt;Brisbane construction firm Canstruct made $43m profit running Nauru detention centre last year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Brisbane construction firm made a profit of more than $43m for running Australia’s immigration detention centre on Nauru last financial year. Canstruct International’s sole contract is with the Australian government to provide garrison and welfare services at the regional processing centre on Nauru, which it has done since October 2017. In its first reporting period as a company, Canstruct International has disclosed it made an after tax profit of $43.16m, with a turnover of almost $212m. Almost $140m was spent on suppliers and employees, and it paid $8.6m in tax. Canstruct International ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>U.N. Security Council removes Eritrea sanctions after years - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eritrea-sanctions-un-idUSKCN1NJ28P</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFCapBNhMHtU-itB78lw7UgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:32:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eritrea-sanctions-un-idUSKCN1NJ28P" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. Security Council removes Eritrea sanctions after years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N. Security Council unanimously voted on Wednesday to lift a nearly decade-old arms embargo and targeted sanctions on Eritrea after a rapprochement with Ethiopia and thawing of relations with Djibouti. The British-drafted resolution also urged Eritrea and Djibouti to work toward normalizing ties and settling a border dispute. It asks Secretary-General Antonio Guterres to report to the council on progress by Feb. 15 and then every six months. The measures against Eritrea - which include a travel ban and asset freeze on certain people and entities - were imposed in 2009 after U.N. exper...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>UN lifts nearly decade-old sanctions on Eritrea - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/africa/un-lifts-eritrea-sanctions/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELvhXJyRTSMi5lIPuDA7P9oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:18:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/africa/un-lifts-eritrea-sanctions/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN lifts nearly decade-old sanctions on Eritrea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UN Security Council unanimously voted on Wednesday to lift 9-year-old sanctions against Eritrea that imposed travel bans, asset freezes and an arms embargo. The East African country was hit with targeted sanctions in 2009 after being accused of having ties to Al-Shabaab militants in Somalia and refusing to withdraw from border disputes with Djibouti. Eritrea denied the accusations of involvement with Al-Shabaab. The resolution, which was drafted by the United Kingdom and backed by allies, marks a new chapter for peace and cooperation in Eritrea after years of regional conflict. In July,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>UN lifts sanctions on Eritrea after nine years - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/lifts-sanctions-eritrea-years-181114170026561.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB1jbLCYBgBeCO8Ez28yk4UqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 18:31:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/lifts-sanctions-eritrea-years-181114170026561.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN lifts sanctions on Eritrea after nine years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations has lifted its sanctions on Eritrea, nine years after they were imposed by the international organisation. Wednesday's decision made during a meeting of the UN Security Council follows a rapprochement between Eritrea and neighbouring Ethiopia in recent months. The Security Council welcomed the improved relationship between the two countries, but added that Eritrea needs strive for closer ties with its other neighbour, Djibouti. Eritrea and Djibouti have been at odds over a border dispute since June 2008 that led to military clashes that killed a dozen Djiboutian troops. R...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>U.N. bemoans lack of funding for African anti-jihadist force - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-security/u-n-bemoans-lack-of-funding-for-african-anti-jihadist-force-idUSKCN1NJ2MB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPMuyROxS1SwVHl_Zf3tdtoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:15:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-security/u-n-bemoans-lack-of-funding-for-african-anti-jihadist-force-idUSKCN1NJ2MB" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. bemoans lack of funding for African anti-jihadist force&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;International donors have disbursed less than half of what they had pledged for a regional force fighting to contain West African jihadists, hampering its efforts as insecurity spreads across the region, a United Nations report said. A February conference of about 50 countries including the United States, Japan and Norway pledged 415 million euros ($470 million) for the G5 Sahel force, made up of troops from Mali, Niger, Chad, Burkina Faso and Mauritania. But the force has struggled to get off the ground and in his Nov. 12 report to the Security Council, U.N. Secretary General Antonio Guter...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>From the CAR to Eritrea, Russia’s African Ambitions Unfold - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/russia-in-africa/4653190.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA2prFG-taRvANDlyL1JZOkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 22:49:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/russia-in-africa/4653190.html" target="_blank"&gt;From the CAR to Eritrea, Russia’s African Ambitions Unfold&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Central African Republic might seem like an unusual venue for Russia’s evolving strategy in Africa. The CAR doesn’t boast Ethiopia’s booming economy or Angola’s deep oil reserves. It lacks a developed mining industry like Zambia or a strategic location like Djibouti. But the landlocked country of fewer than 5 million people, most of whom survive on subsistence farming, has something else of interest to Moscow: conflict. Since 2013, the CAR has grappled with a protracted civil war. Mass displacements, political instability, and competing factions of rebels and militia groups have weakene...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Prospect of Chinese Control of Djibouti Port Concerns Senators - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/prospect-of-chinese-control-of-djibouti-port-concerns-senators/4657768.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKY6L8dNNpw3Ag_FK32KvIgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 02:59:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/prospect-of-chinese-control-of-djibouti-port-concerns-senators/4657768.html" target="_blank"&gt;Prospect of Chinese Control of Djibouti Port Concerns Senators&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two prominent U.S. senators expressed alarm Tuesday about the military and political consequences if China gains control of a port terminal in Djibouti, saying it could further boost Beijing's influence in East Africa. In a letter to Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and Secretary of Defense Jim Mattis, Republican Sen. Marco Rubio of Florida and Democratic Sen. Chris Coons of Delaware said they were concerned about Djibouti's termination of a contract for the Doraleh Container Terminal with United Arab Emirates-based DP World in February and the nationalization of the port in September. Report...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Charity: Thousands Hiding in Central African Republic Hospital Risk Attack - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/charity-thousands-hiding-in-central-african-republic-hospital-risk-attack/4647832.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFJVJm6U3RQRuLR52wEXsGYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 01:02:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/charity-thousands-hiding-in-central-african-republic-hospital-risk-attack/4647832.html" target="_blank"&gt;Charity: Thousands Hiding in Central African Republic Hospital Risk Attack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some 5,000 people seeking refuge in a hospital in Central African Republic (CAR) risk being attacked by armed groups, a medical charity said Tuesday, amid ongoing clashes. About 10,000 people ran to the hospital in Batangafo, some 400 km (250 miles) north of the capital Bangui, last week, after armed groups looted and burned thousands of homes, three camps hosting 27,000 displaced and a market in the city. Half of those camped out in the hospital grounds have since joined others hiding in the bush or other villages, Omar Ahmed Abenza, head of mission for Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF) in CA...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Marshall Islands' president accuses Chinese interests of backing opponents - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/09/marshall-islands-president-accuses-chinese-interests-of-backing-opponents</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM1JIm8FXiA4G-CDDuzhDNAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 01:21:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/09/marshall-islands-president-accuses-chinese-interests-of-backing-opponents" target="_blank"&gt;Marshall Islands' president accuses Chinese interests of backing opponents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Marshall Islands’ president, Hilda Heine, says accusations that she is destroying the country’s financial reputation by adopting a cryptocurrency are “baseless” and her opponents are being unduly influenced by pressure from China. Earlier this week eight senators moved to pass a vote of no confidence in Heine, the first female leader of any Pacific Island. The vote is scheduled to take place next week. Heine’s opponents said she had bought the country’s financial reputation into disrepute by pushing ahead with the adoption of the cryptocurrency Sovereign as the country’s second legal te...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>France grants help to Gambia and Central Africa; pushes regional clout - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-gambia/france-grants-help-to-gambia-and-central-africa-pushes-regional-clout-idUSKCN1NA1PD?il=0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPNw7bU9qcExlOatA72ud1kqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 00:04:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-gambia/france-grants-help-to-gambia-and-central-africa-pushes-regional-clout-idUSKCN1NA1PD?il=0" target="_blank"&gt;France grants help to Gambia and Central Africa; pushes regional clout&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France flexed its muscles in West Africa on Monday granting millions of euros in aid to Gambia to support its democratic transition amid fears of regional instability and took aim at Russia over its "opportunist" role in Central African Republic. Born of British and French colonial rivalry in the 19th century and surrounded by francophone Senegal, Gambia - a tourist haven and groundnut producer - won independence from Britain in 1965. President Adama Barrow won the December 2016 election by beating exiled authoritarian former leader Yahya Jammeh, who fled Gambia after regional militaries la...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>U.N. Security Council considers lifting Eritrea sanctions next week - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eritrea-sanctions-un/u-n-security-council-considers-lifting-eritrea-sanctions-next-week-idUSKCN1NA2RG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHa3328PG6vl1OWKMoFq1LgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 23:12:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eritrea-sanctions-un/u-n-security-council-considers-lifting-eritrea-sanctions-next-week-idUSKCN1NA2RG" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. Security Council considers lifting Eritrea sanctions next week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N. Security Council is considering lifting sanctions on Eritrea next week after a rapprochement with Ethiopia, although some members want to maintain some diplomatic pressure to ensure a dispute with Djibouti is resolved, diplomats said on Monday. A British-drafted resolution, seen by Reuters, proposes the immediate removal of an arms embargo and targeted sanctions - a travel ban and asset freeze - imposed on Eritrea. It also strongly encourages Eritrea and Djibouti to work toward normalizing ties and settling a decade-old border dispute. However, diplomats, speaking on condition of a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Fact check: Have the asylum seekers on Nauru not proven themselves to be genuine refugees? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-02/fact-check-pauline-hanson-refugees-nauru/10456650</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJtahbIEPfHzdqjKal-Pa-kqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 18:40:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-02/fact-check-pauline-hanson-refugees-nauru/10456650" target="_blank"&gt;Fact check: Have the asylum seekers on Nauru not proven themselves to be genuine refugees?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former senate adversaries Sam Dastyari and Pauline Hanson have engaged in a fiery exchange on Sky News over the status of asylum seekers on Nauru. The heated argument broke out when Senator Hanson said the asylum seekers remaining on Nauru had not been judged to be refugees by the Australian Government, a claim Mr Dastyari strongly rejected. "These ones that are there have not proven themselves to be genuine refugees to warrant them coming to Australia," Senator Hanson said. Is she correct? RMIT ABC Fact Check investigates. The overwhelming majority of asylum seekers currently on Nauru have...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>UK can now use foreign aid budget to help richer overseas territories hit by natural disasters - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/foreign-aid-budget-caribbean-overseas-territories-british-virgin-islands-anguilla-penny-mordaunt-a8612021.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFAfS4QGTeweVlF_tFtap50qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 09:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/foreign-aid-budget-caribbean-overseas-territories-british-virgin-islands-anguilla-penny-mordaunt-a8612021.html" target="_blank"&gt;UK can now use foreign aid budget to help richer overseas territories hit by natural disasters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wealthy UK overseas territories will be allowed to receive foreign aid after the government secured a “significant” change to international rules. The Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) will now include richer countries that have been affected by natural disasters on a list of nations deserving of aid. It comes after the UK government urged other developed nations to change the rules, pointing out that Caribbean countries damaged by hurricanes last year had not received official assistance because they were deemed too wealthy. - Read more Government warned over ‘u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Asylum-seeker children likely to be off Nauru by year's end: Brandis - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-01/asylum-seeker-children-to-be-removed-from-nauru/10453588</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMlNDcUdxWZJf_IXHgciaBEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 20:45:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-01/asylum-seeker-children-to-be-removed-from-nauru/10453588" target="_blank"&gt;Asylum-seeker children likely to be off Nauru by year's end: Brandis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By political reporter Henry Belot The children of refugees and asylum seekers on Nauru are likely to be transferred off the island by the end of the year, according to former attorney-general George Brandis. Prime Minister Scott Morrison and Home Affairs Minister Peter Dutton have not disputed that timeline, instead saying they are working quietly without "showboating". More children have been transferred for treatment, with Government sources confirming there are now 40 on the Pacific Island — down from 52 last week. Political pressure has been mounting on the Coalition to transfer all chi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Russia not helping to stabilize Central African Republic: France - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-russia-france/russia-not-helping-to-stabilize-central-african-republic-france-idUSKCN1N20I7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELPSrxeDZv_sPGM07sKlzWwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 15:15:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-russia-france/russia-not-helping-to-stabilize-central-african-republic-france-idUSKCN1N20I7" target="_blank"&gt;Russia not helping to stabilize Central African Republic: France&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia's expanding influence in Central African Republic (CAR), a former French colony, over the past months is not likely to stabilize the country, French Defense Minister Florence Parly told weekly Jeune Afrique. In December 2017, Russia obtained the go-ahead from the United Nations' Security Council to deliver arms to CAR, facing near-constant armed conflict since 2013, when a mostly Muslim Seleka rebel coalition overthrew then-president Francois Bozize, prompting reprisals from Christian 'anti-balaka' militias. Depite electing a new leader in 2016, the country has been mired in tit-for-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Children will be brought to Australia from Nauru, but they won't be allowed to stay - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/01/australia/nauru-children-australia-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJPaNxGf7YooQTcVcikpSlwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 10:16:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/01/australia/nauru-children-australia-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Children will be brought to Australia from Nauru, but they won't be allowed to stay&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dozens of refugee children and their families set to be transferred from the tiny island of Nauru won't be allowed to permanently settle in Australia, the country's Home Minister Peter Dutton said Thursday. Dutton's comments came after Prime Minister Scott Morrison confirmed that his government is working "quietly" to remove the remaining children on Nauru, where they were sent as part of Australia's strict immigration policies. Australia reintroduced offshore detention centers in 2012 after a surge in the number of asylum seekers trying to reach the country by boat. "Our policy hasn't chan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Australia to move child refugees from island camps - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1039e0c6-dd7e-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE1u2k1w9IXzbJhLlSSyGBYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 04:09:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1039e0c6-dd7e-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c" target="_blank"&gt;Australia to move child refugees from island camps&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia is to move children in its offshore refugee processing camps on to its territory by the end of the year in response to a medical crisis that has prompted a political backlash against the conservative government. George Brandis, Australia’s high commissioner to the UK, said on Thursday the problem of children living on the tiny Pacific islands of Nauru and Manus island in Papua New Guinea had “largely gone away” following recent transfers to Australia. His comments follow a report in The Australian, a newspaper, which said Canberra had decided to move the remaining 40 children from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tony Abbott describes conditions on Nauru as 'very, very pleasant' - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-29/tony-abbott-describes-conditions-on-nauru-as-pleasant/10442694</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFH257087NX7SZ9LWT3Cm-oqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 07:11:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-29/tony-abbott-describes-conditions-on-nauru-as-pleasant/10442694" target="_blank"&gt;Tony Abbott describes conditions on Nauru as 'very, very pleasant'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By political reporter Nick Dole Former prime minister Tony Abbott says Nauru is being unfairly portrayed as a "hell-hole" when it is in fact a "very pleasant" place. Mr Abbott was responding to growing calls to remove asylum seeker children from the Pacific island. "Nauru is no hell-hole by any means. I've been there," Mr Abbott told radio station 2GB. "If you like living in the tropics, it's a very, very pleasant island." Medical groups including the Australian Medical Association and Medicin Sans Frontieres (Doctors Without Borders) have called for the immediate removal of children from t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>The Cook Islands: 'Everyone’s happy. If you’re not happy, you’re in the wrong place' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2018/oct/30/the-cook-islands-everyones-happy-if-youre-not-happy-youre-in-the-wrong-place</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKv-oV0CLeTb0tfUb7JsZ6sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCw3Gc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 17:00:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2018/oct/30/the-cook-islands-everyones-happy-if-youre-not-happy-youre-in-the-wrong-place" target="_blank"&gt;The Cook Islands: 'Everyone’s happy. If you’re not happy, you’re in the wrong place'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re just over the last crest of Maunga Pu when we see it. Here, at Aitutaki’s highest point, the true glory of the island’s sprawling lagoon reveals itself. Its outer edge encircles the tiny island, splitting crystal clear waters from the heaving dark blue of the Pacific beyond. It lends the atoll – the second most populous of the 15 Cook Islands – an air of stillness. “Pretty amazing view, hey?,” I say to a rare group of American tourists we find at the top of the hillside. “Yeah, incredible,” one responds, smiling. Related: Australia's top eight Indigenous travel destinations | Marcia L...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Inflight hiccup as Harry and Meghan's plane aborts Sydney landing - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-royals-tonga/inflight-hiccup-as-harry-and-meghans-plane-aborts-sydney-landing-idUSKCN1N00K1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENQQknehnQ5w-1WlCn6djjEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 10:13:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-royals-tonga/inflight-hiccup-as-harry-and-meghans-plane-aborts-sydney-landing-idUSKCN1N00K1" target="_blank"&gt;Inflight hiccup as Harry and Meghan's plane aborts Sydney landing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prince Harry and his wife Meghan returned to Australia on Friday from a tour of Pacific islands after their plane was forced to abort a first landing because another aircraft was in the way. Their Qantas plane charter flight QF6031, approaching Sydney, dropped to 125 feet before performing a "go-around", according to FlightRadar24. In aviation terminology, a go-around is a when a pilot pulls out of a landing and makes another attempt after circling the airport. According to the Civil Aviation Safety Authority a go-around is a "common and very safe practice". A Reuters witness on the plane s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Plane carrying Harry and Meghan aborts landing, flies around - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/efbd65ec39ea4015ba971d73d95c5c18</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKo66ytOq5TtMjvwGM-55yAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 08:59:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/efbd65ec39ea4015ba971d73d95c5c18" target="_blank"&gt;Plane carrying Harry and Meghan aborts landing, flies around&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NUKU'ALOFA, Tonga (AP) — A plane carrying the Duke and Duchess of Sussex had to abort its landing at Sydney airport on Friday evening and flew around because there was another aircraft on the runway. Prince Harry and wife Meghan were returning from a visit to Tonga back to Australia, where they began their 16-day tour of four nations, when a message from the flight deck announced: "There was an aircraft on the runway a little slow to roll so the decision was taken to abort the landing." The flight landed safely a few minutes later. Earlier Friday, the couple dedicated two forest reserves in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Laughing Meghan serenaded by mosquito choir in Tonga - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-26/meghan-serenaded-by-mosquito-choir-in-tonga/10435054</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEClbF9nylDqKNWkM3WyimWEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 07:01:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-26/meghan-serenaded-by-mosquito-choir-in-tonga/10435054" target="_blank"&gt;Laughing Meghan serenaded by mosquito choir in Tonga&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Tongan choir had Meghan, the Duchess of Sussex, in tears of laughter as she and Prince Harry wrapped up their tour of Tonga and hopped on a plane to return to Australia for the end of the Invictus Games. The pair, who are expecting a child of their own in the Spring, were serenaded by students at Tupou College. They laughed when boys from the college sang about mosquitoes, complete with dance moves, at a ceremony to dedicate two forest reserves on the campus. But mosquito-born diseases have been raised before on this tour — the World Health Organisation identified recent cases of the zika...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, seen with tag dangling from dress in Tonga - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/royal-tour-tonga-meghan-dress-label-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH_zMkAmhw5OkT6J0OhePIsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIbnyQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 11:54:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/style/article/royal-tour-tonga-meghan-dress-label-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, seen with tag dangling from dress in Tonga&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The British Royal family isn't known for scrimping on its wardrobe budget, but Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, has left some wondering whether she hopes to return her latest outfit for a refund. As the newly wed royal stepped off a Qantas charter flight in Tonga, a tag could be seen flapping from the hem of her dress as she walked down the red carpet. It was spotted by Sophie Walsh, a reporter for Australian CNN affiliate Channel 9 News, who tweeted, "With so many outfit changes I think the Duchess can be forgiven for this." The Duchess was wearing a green Jason Wu crepe sheath dress -- listed a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Prince Harry and Meghan arrive in Tonga after unveiling statue of SAS hero - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-25/prince-harry-and-meghan-unveil-statue-in-fiji-head-to-tonga/10428918</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENjxJ0do5ygAx4mhdefSgpAqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 06:40:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-25/prince-harry-and-meghan-unveil-statue-in-fiji-head-to-tonga/10428918" target="_blank"&gt;Prince Harry and Meghan arrive in Tonga after unveiling statue of SAS hero&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Duke and Duchess of Sussex have arrived in the tiny Pacific kingdom of Tonga after taking a short flight from Fiji, where they spent the morning unveiling a statue of a British-Fijian SAS sergeant. Prince Harry and wife Meghan were greeted at the airport in Tonga by Princess Angelika Latufuipeka. People gathered wearing traditional outfits, playing guitars and singing at the airport to welcome the Royal couple. Harry and Meghan were scheduled to meet with Tonga's King and Queen and to attend a reception and dinner with traditional Tongan entertainment. Prior to their arrival in Tonga, P...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Africa's aging leaders - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/25/africa/gallery/africa-aging-leaders-av/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPwmOF5LjvjfqWGiL28QDaQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:09:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/25/africa/gallery/africa-aging-leaders-av/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Africa's aging leaders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yoweri Museveni, President of Uganda, has been in power since 1986. He is 74 years old. Andrew Burton/Getty Images North America/Getty Images Tunisian President Beji Caid Essebsi is 91. His presidency follows a term as Prime Minister, a role he took following the revolution in the country which sparked the Arab Uprising across the Middle East. AFP/Getty Images Eighty-five year old Paul Biya has been Cameroon's president since 1982. He is seen as a particularly entrenched African leader, having survived a number of coup attempts. AFP/Getty Images Algeria's President Abdelaziz Bouteflika is 8...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Protestors rally in Australian cities to end offshore refugee detention - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-immigration/protestors-rally-in-australian-cities-to-end-offshore-refugee-detention-idUSKCN1N105F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH605fgsttPCQW3-jJ-S9B4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 06:02:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-immigration/protestors-rally-in-australian-cities-to-end-offshore-refugee-detention-idUSKCN1N105F" target="_blank"&gt;Protestors rally in Australian cities to end offshore refugee detention&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protesters rallied in Australia's two largest cities, Sydney and Melbourne, on Saturday calling for an end to the country's controversial South Pacific detention centers which house refugees who try to reach Australia by boat. Particular focus was directed toward the wellbeing of children on the tiny island nation of Nauru, though refugee advocates said all refugees should be out of detention. "It's kids off, everyone off and bring them here," Ian Rintoul, from the Refugee Action Coalition told Reuters on Saturday. More than 1,400 people are being held on the Australian-run detention center...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>UN rights chief outraged by Burundi's "slave trade" slur - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-burundi-un/un-rights-chief-outraged-by-burundis-slave-trade-slur-idUSKCN1MZ2FX</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO9cx74XFipRhqGeiOR7FdcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 16:13:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-burundi-un/un-rights-chief-outraged-by-burundis-slave-trade-slur-idUSKCN1MZ2FX" target="_blank"&gt;UN rights chief outraged by Burundi's "slave trade" slur&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.N. human rights chief Michelle Bachelet expressed outrage on Thursday at comments by Burundi's ambassador in New York comparing the chairman of a U.N. inquiry into the country to a participant in the slave trade. Burundi's Ambassador to the United Nations Albert Shingiro, speaking at the U.N. General Assembly on Wednesday, rubbished a report by the Commission of Inquiry into human rights in Burundi. His government has already criticized the report several times and refused to cooperate with the investigators. According to a transcript posted on the Burundian mission's website, tweeted by ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>A 10-minute flight? World's shortest airline routes - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/world-shortest-air-routes/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA2kxWcUNoXBcslZ3aR1WsQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 09:59:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/world-shortest-air-routes/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;A 10-minute flight? World's shortest airline routes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;World's shortest airline routes: Anguilla Airlines runs an 10-minute international flight between Sint Maarten (pictured) and Anguilla. The distance covered is 12 miles. Courtesy of PrivateFly Shortest international flight: Another 10 minutes will take you by road from Anguilla's Clayton J. Lloyd International Airport to Little Bay beach (pictured). Courtesy Anguilla Tourist Board World's shortest airline routes: May saw the launch of another quickie international flight -- the 15-minute trip between the Caribbean island of Aruba (pictured) and Venezuela's Punto Fijo. LUIS ACOSTA/AFP/Getty ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item></channel></rss>