<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Monk - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREkyTm5Kb0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:36:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Be celibate or leave the priesthood, pope tells gay priests - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-homosexuals-book/be-celibate-or-leave-the-priesthood-pope-tells-gay-priests-idUSKBN1O10K7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPC-D-hxGmhUbbEJfh08hNoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 11:19:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-homosexuals-book/be-celibate-or-leave-the-priesthood-pope-tells-gay-priests-idUSKBN1O10K7" target="_blank"&gt;Be celibate or leave the priesthood, pope tells gay priests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men with deep-rooted homosexual tendencies should not be admitted to the Catholic clergy, and it would be better for priests who are actively gay to leave rather than lead a double life, Pope Francis says in a new book. While he has previously spoken of the need for better screening of candidates for the religious life, his comments suggesting that priests who cannot keep their vows of celibacy should leave are some of his clearest to date. Francis made the comments in a book-length interview with Spanish priest Fernando Prado called "The Strength of Vocation", in which he discusses the cha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Police Hunting for Monk Increase Pressure on Thai Temple - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/police-hunting-for-monk-increase-pressure-on-thai-temple/3730880.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMuiQ5-RlUZIrthEN5vQ_LsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 14:56:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/police-hunting-for-monk-increase-pressure-on-thai-temple/3730880.html" target="_blank"&gt;Police Hunting for Monk Increase Pressure on Thai Temple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police in Thailand who spent three days in an orderly but unsuccessful search of a vast Buddhist temple for a prominent monk accused of financial wrongdoing kept up the pressure Sunday, sending fresh forces to confront devotees and monks at the compound's gates. Around 3,000 police had surrounded the Dhammakaya sect temple north of Bangkok from Thursday through Saturday, while smaller squads searched for its chief, Phra Dhammajayo, who is accused of accepting $40 million in embezzled money. Both security forces and Dhammajayo's followers gathered in growing numbers at the temple on Sunday a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Novice monk - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/178757029/novice-monk-by-visoot-uthairam</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHb62bPznOvIxDNO1OOZ7ykqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 22:11:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/178757029/novice-monk-by-visoot-uthairam" target="_blank"&gt;Novice monk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Novice monk at the door in temple .&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Learning about science to understand Buddhism - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/health/2017/02/20/vital-signs-dalai-lama-b.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECe3swNxFqC2ijHKQQWmP-IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 14:21:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/health/2017/02/20/vital-signs-dalai-lama-b.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Learning about science to understand Buddhism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emory University in Atlanta, US, hosts science classes for Buddhist monks. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Wirathu silenced by Myanmar's top Buddhist body - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/03/wirathu-silenced-myanmar-top-buddhist-body-170311141258664.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECuXA67cI0xpwSAt_T7nq4oqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 05:29:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/03/wirathu-silenced-myanmar-top-buddhist-body-170311141258664.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wirathu silenced by Myanmar's top Buddhist body&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Myanmar monk infamous for his bilious anti-Muslim tirades has been banned from giving sermons for a year by the country's top Buddhist body, an unprecedented slapdown on a man whose hate speech has galvanised religious tensions. Wirathu, a monk once dubbed the "face of Buddhist terror", has led calls for restrictions on Myanmar's Muslim population, penning hyperbolic speeches warning of an Islamic takeover of the overwhelmingly Buddhist country. Myanmar is gripped by deepening religious tensions that have repeatedly spilled into violence. The unrest has been partially attributed to anti-M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Myanmar Silences Radical Monk, but Legacy of Hatred Speaks for Itself - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/myanmar-silences-radical-monk-/3784751.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEMpFIz5E2_je3MEAB64n8UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 08:38:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/myanmar-silences-radical-monk-/3784751.html" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar Silences Radical Monk, but Legacy of Hatred Speaks for Itself&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Myanmar nationalist monk Wirathu has long used vile language to make a point. In January 2015, he called Yanghee Lee, the United Nations special rapporteur for human rights in Myanmar, a "whore." In an interview with 60 Minutes that aired in October the same year, he said that Muslims, who make up less than 5 percent of the population here, were defecating on the country. Government attitude changes Under the previous military-backed administration of President Thein Sein, Wirathu received little pushback for his remarks, often delivered in public sermons or broadcast on his popular Fac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Thousands of Thais obstruct search for wanted monk - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/thousands-thais-obstruct-search-wanted-monk-170219123011943.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGb14q8iPYtBFVRp5KODmkcqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 19:28:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/thousands-thais-obstruct-search-wanted-monk-170219123011943.html" target="_blank"&gt;Thousands of Thais obstruct search for wanted monk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of followers of Thailand's largest Buddhist temple have defied police orders to evacuate the 1,000 acre facility, hindering the search for the monastery's former head monk who is wanted for allegedly accepting $40m of embezzled money and money-laundering. Followers of the Dhammakaya Temple, north of the capital Bangkok, held posters on Sunday calling for police to retaliate and appealed for international attention and assistance. "We have cooperated with the government every step of the way but this is one step too far," Phra Pasura Dantamano, a temple spokesman and senior monk, t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Buddhist monk in critical condition of setting fire to himself - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/01/08/buddhist-monk-critical-condition-setting-fire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEFMca_NdkzfmKnKENyRGf0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 03:47:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/01/08/buddhist-monk-critical-condition-setting-fire/" target="_blank"&gt;Buddhist monk in critical condition of setting fire to himself&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A South Korean Buddhist monk is in critical condition after setting himself on fire to protest the country's settlement with Japan on compensation for wartime sex slaves, officials said Sunday. The 64-year-old monk suffered third-degree burns across his body and serious damage to vital organs. He's unconscious and unable to breathe on his own, said an official from the Seoul National University Hospital, who didn't want to be named citing office rules. The man set himself ablaze late Saturday during a large rally in Seoul calling for the dismissal of impeached President Park Geun-hye, poli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Thai junta replaces director of Buddhism department with policeman - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-buddhism-idUSKBN1640E8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDA4JqsOV6eLaitiLQrjE38qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 13:04:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-buddhism-idUSKBN1640E8" target="_blank"&gt;Thai junta replaces director of Buddhism department with policeman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BANGKOK (Reuters) - Thailand's military junta removed the chief of the department responsible for overseeing Buddhist affairs and replaced him with a police officer on Saturday, amid a stand-off between officials and monks at the country's largest temple. Thousands of followers of the Dhammakaya Temple have defied orders to leave temple grounds for over a week, blocking attempts by police to seek out their former abbot, who is accused of money laundering. The standoff at the scandal-hit temple represents one of the biggest challenges to the authority of Thailand's junta since it took power ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Novice monk Walking in nature. - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/227425491/novice-monk-walking-in-nature-by-visoot-uthairam</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBp-IM75UpMH85wUFeRmkB8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 02:54:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/227425491/novice-monk-walking-in-nature-by-visoot-uthairam" target="_blank"&gt;Novice monk Walking in nature.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dramatic moment of a little boy monk.Walking in nature in Asia,Novice monk at Luang Prabang,Laos.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Thai police search of Buddhist temple fails to turn up wanted monk - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-buddhism-idUSKBN15U2KB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKEnsajudfWD9EqZpJ29dS8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 11:38:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-buddhism-idUSKBN15U2KB" target="_blank"&gt;Thai police search of Buddhist temple fails to turn up wanted monk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Aukkarapon Niyomyat BANGKOK (Reuters) - Thai security forces filed past chanting monks on Thursday to search the country's biggest Buddhist temple for an influential former abbot accused of money laundering, but failed to find him. With political parties and many activists silenced since a coup in 2014, the scandal-hit Dhammakaya Temple is a rare institution in defying the junta, which until now trod warily in confronting a group that claims millions of followers. Police went in hours after Prime Minister Prayuth Chan-ocha used a security measure that critics dub "the dictator's law" to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Weather traps monks, takes away livelihood - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/03/01/us/big-sur-trapped-monks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHalH8pSd2njo4HuXjRCGVYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 04:00:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/03/01/us/big-sur-trapped-monks/" target="_blank"&gt;Weather traps monks, takes away livelihood&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big Sur is gorgeous country where people go to take in nature's beauty and be away from the trappings of the world. Many people pay good money for the isolation of the retreats along this picturesque stretch of California coast. While the remoteness is a gift, when bad weather hits, it can further isolate people there and create quite the test. The Camaldolese Benedictine monks at the New Camaldoli Hermitage are being tested after weeks of rain have pushed damaging rocks onto roads and buckled a vital bridge. They are cut off, trapped in their monastery, getting low on heating fuel and cons...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Scuffles at Thai Temple As Police Hunt for Monk - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/scuffles-at-thai-temple-as-police-hunt-for-monk/3732109.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECZoHlZditbRlc5wfBp967EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 16:40:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/scuffles-at-thai-temple-as-police-hunt-for-monk/3732109.html" target="_blank"&gt;Scuffles at Thai Temple As Police Hunt for Monk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monks and police scuffled on Monday at a Buddhist temple in Thailand where security forces are trying to arrest an influential former abbot on money-laundering charges. The standoff at the scandal-hit Dhammakaya Temple represents one of the biggest challenges to the authority of Thailand's junta since it took power in 2014. Police said they would try to avoid violence while threatening arrest for followers of the sprawling temple who have defied orders to leave and instead flocked there, hampering the search for 72-year-old Phra Dhammachayo. With tension rising four days after the military ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Montpellier attack: At least one killed after gunman attacks retirement home for Catholic monks - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/montpellier-attack-gunman-monks-retirement-home-montferrier-sur-lez-hostages-latest-police-terror-a7437696.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM8yELSOfbgf6aI7Ah9DvKAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 22:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/montpellier-attack-gunman-monks-retirement-home-montferrier-sur-lez-hostages-latest-police-terror-a7437696.html" target="_blank"&gt;Montpellier attack: At least one killed after gunman attacks retirement home for Catholic monks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least one person has been killed after a gunman launched an attack on a retirement home for Catholic monks near the French city of Montpellier. Armed police were deployed to the Maison de Retraite des Missions Africaines (African Missions Retirement Home) in Montferrier-sur-Lez on Thursday night. "An individual, who was masked and armed with a knife and a sawn-off shotgun came into the retirement home where 70 monks live," a source told the AFP news agency, adding that the man's motivations were unknown. Local media reported that at least one person had been found dead, with the e-Metrop...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Evictions, trials as Russian Church claims property - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/08/evictions-trials-russian-church-claims-property-170822103042061.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOyRu1CrCw09mnM2f16z1IYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 10:26:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/08/evictions-trials-russian-church-claims-property-170822103042061.html" target="_blank"&gt;Evictions, trials as Russian Church claims property&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Valaam, Russia - Varvara Sergeeva's great-grandfather was among the tens of thousands of clerics, monks, nuns and believers executed by Communist iconoclasts in 1937. Pavel Orleansky had served as a deacon in the revered Orthodox Christian monastery on Valaam, the lake island just south of Finland. Sergeeva learned about his fate from declassified KGB archives in 1988, when during the Perestroika reforms the USSR celebrated a millennium of Christianity in Russia. Soon after graduating from high school, Sergeeva decided to get baptised and leave her native St Petersburg for Valaam to help re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>In Meteora, monasteries reach toward the heavens - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/travel/article/meteora-greece/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP9P-1uZNkLaJ6nE6sA6o-oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 00:30:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/travel/article/meteora-greece/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;In Meteora, monasteries reach toward the heavens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meteora: This celebrated view of Meteora has become one of the most photographed spots in Greece. Alesha Bradford The Great Meteoron Monastery: The region's largest and oldest monastery is the Great Meteoron. Meteora means "suspended in the air" and this place of worship gave its name to the entire region. Abseiling the Great Saint: The sandstone peaks have become a hot destination for rock climbers and hikers. A popular excursion is the Via Ferrata up Meteora's highest mountain, the Great Saint. Alesha Bradford Fancy a walk on this cliff?: Years ago the only access to the monasteries was b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sri Lanka port protesters doused by water cannon - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-01-07/sri-lankans-protest-china-port-deal/8168110</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIMsifaIN2ATRMyHlBzMxVUqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 11:15:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-01-07/sri-lankans-protest-china-port-deal/8168110" target="_blank"&gt;Sri Lanka port protesters doused by water cannon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sri Lankan police used water cannons to try to break up violent clashes between government supporters and villagers marching against what they say is a plan to take over private land for an industrial zone in which China will have a major stake. Key points: - Clash takes place as Prime Minister attends opening ceremony for industrial zone - Several people are taken away in ambulances - Lease agreement enables 80pc Chinese ownership The clashes took place as Prime Minister Ranil Wickremesinghe was attending an opening ceremony for the industrial zone near the port city of Hambantota. Governm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Robot monk dispenses Buddhist wisdom at Beijing temple - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2016/05/30/travel/china-buddhism-robot-monk/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECkpFHJP3K0JJmr1ueuWEjUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 02:33:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2016/05/30/travel/china-buddhism-robot-monk/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Robot monk dispenses Buddhist wisdom at Beijing temple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This funny-looking, chubby robot might well be the most popular Buddhist monk in China. Standing two-feet (60 centimeters) tall, Xian'er is based on a cartoon character created by a Buddhist master at Beijing's Longquan Temple. He's already attracted a steady stream of admirers to the 1,700-year-old place of worship after first shooting to fame on Chinese social media. Master Xianfan says the robot is intelligent enough to chant Buddhist mantras and even interact with people. Master Xianfan carries Xian'er the robot monk at the 1,700-year-old entrance gate of the Longquan Temple in Beijing....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Spaniard Who Spent 50 Years Building a Cathedral With His Own Hands - ArchDaily</title><link>http://www.archdaily.com/802476/the-spaniard-who-spent-50-years-building-a-cathedral-with-his-own-hands</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJv9NJpQBMRyybmolPr-rssqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkLQGMJBaMK-8Ag</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.archdaily.com/802476/the-spaniard-who-spent-50-years-building-a-cathedral-with-his-own-hands" target="_blank"&gt;The Spaniard Who Spent 50 Years Building a Cathedral With His Own Hands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ArchDaily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;© Flickr user: santiago lopez-pastor, licensed under CC BY-ND 2.0 A huge cathedral with tall towers and a magnificent dome rises slowly in the municipality of Mejorada del Campo, 20 kilometers from Madrid. It seems like a common occurrence, but it is not. The building has been under construction for 50 years - brick by brick - by one man: Justo Gallego Martínez, farmer, ex-monk and a self-taught architect of 91 years of age. Learn about his life's work (literally) after the break. Without any previous knowledge of architecture or any experience in the construction industry, Martínez has spe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.archdaily.com">ArchDaily</source></item><item><title>Buddhist religious beliefs that elephants have given to monks. - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/207111371/buddhist-religious-beliefs-that-elephants-have-given-to-monks-by-visoot-uthairam</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEwQ-x5WiQozgFf9ZluGVmIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 12:46:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/207111371/buddhist-religious-beliefs-that-elephants-have-given-to-monks-by-visoot-uthairam" target="_blank"&gt;Buddhist religious beliefs that elephants have given to monks.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buddhist religious beliefs that elephants have given to monks.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Buddhist monk found with drugs, grenade in monastery - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-02-07/buddhist-monk-arrested-in-myanmar-with-drugs-grenade/8249474</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEywxtw1HSdvTZJ2UdXkdbwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 09:19:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-02-07/buddhist-monk-arrested-in-myanmar-with-drugs-grenade/8249474" target="_blank"&gt;Buddhist monk found with drugs, grenade in monastery&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Buddhist monk has been arrested in Myanmar after a grenade, ammunition and more than four million methamphetamine pills were found in his car and in his monastery. Police officer Maung Maung Yin said the monk was stopped Sunday (local time) as he drove in northern Rakhine state, which borders Bangladesh. Authorities had been tipped off that the monk was carrying an illegal haul. An anti-drug task force then found 400,000 pills in the monk's car, Maung Maung Yin said. A subsequent search of his monastery turned up 4.2 million pills along with a grenade and ammunition. A statement from the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Buckfast locals back monks after criticism of drink's links to violence - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2016/dec/16/buckfast-locals-back-monks-after-criticism-of-tonic-wine-links-to-violence</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIUzQXQT8syXPGhgkYlVNIMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 13:36:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2016/dec/16/buckfast-locals-back-monks-after-criticism-of-tonic-wine-links-to-violence" target="_blank"&gt;Buckfast locals back monks after criticism of drink's links to violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The routine for the Benedictine monks of Buckfast Abbey in Devon is plain and strict: a bell rings at 5.25am to wake them and thereafter the day is divided into periods of prayer, work and study. Meals are simple and, except on very special occasions, taken in silence. Yet there is nothing austere about the finances of the Buckfast Abbey trust, which supports the community. New figures from the Charity Commission reveal that – in large part thanks to the success of the abbey’s tonic wine – the trust’s annual income totalled a cool £8.8m. The success is not without controversy. Buckfast toni...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Novice monks,Mrauk-u Myanmar - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/205743307/novice-monks-mrauk-u-myanmar-by-saravut-whanset</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-VXvoN2-JsLYRhi5dAfJEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 02:51:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/205743307/novice-monks-mrauk-u-myanmar-by-saravut-whanset" target="_blank"&gt;Novice monks,Mrauk-u Myanmar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Novice monks on the plain of mrauk-u Ratanabon Paya ,Mrauk-u Myanmar&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>sacred rocks of Meteora - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/197714077/sacred-rocks-of-meteora-by-dimitris-koskinas</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELwy3kaJIr518btZAp2dbWMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:12:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/197714077/sacred-rocks-of-meteora-by-dimitris-koskinas" target="_blank"&gt;sacred rocks of Meteora&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In view of the sacred rock, the visitor is stunned by the impressive majesty of this gigantic stone complex. The ascetic huts on the rocks witness the undeniable presence of the first monks devoted body and soul to God. Serving Christ recorded their ascetic path in monastic life, walking the paths that lead from earth to heaven. The first monasteries were built with great care and craftsmanship in the 14th century. Over the years some of them were reconstructed and others suffered major repairs to be completed, and thereby provide the final architectural shape. Since then standing up in the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Novice Monk in Thailand - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/190790593/novice-monk-in-thailand-by-sasin-tipchai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPn1SUgM1jWStR8l-L_2YP0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 11:00:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/190790593/novice-monk-in-thailand-by-sasin-tipchai" target="_blank"&gt;Novice Monk in Thailand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Novice Monk in Thailand&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Buddhist monk arrested in Burma 'for stashing 4.6 million meth pills' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/buddhist-monk-burma-meth-pills-car-monastery-rakhine-state-a7567416.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDNl3KDbfdXctgst3udcSzIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 14:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/buddhist-monk-burma-meth-pills-car-monastery-rakhine-state-a7567416.html" target="_blank"&gt;Buddhist monk arrested in Burma 'for stashing 4.6 million meth pills'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Buddhist monk has been arrested in Burma after authorities said they found more than four million methamphetamine pills in his car and his monastery. The monk was stopped as he drove in northern Rakhine state, which borders Bangladesh, said police officer Maung Maung Yin. Authorities had been tipped off that the monk was carrying an illegal haul. - Read more Buddhist monks buy 600lbs of lobster to release them back into ocean ​Maung Maung Yin said an anti-drug task force found 400,000 pills in the monk's car. A subsequent search of his monastery turned up 4.2 million pills along with a gr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Monastery of St. Theoktistis, Ikaria_9, Greece... - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/215290933/monastery-of-st-theoktistis-ikaria-9-greece-by-dimitrios-tsakiris</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB_qqoqvuiJMHZl4XokM_0cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 21:55:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/215290933/monastery-of-st-theoktistis-ikaria-9-greece-by-dimitrios-tsakiris" target="_blank"&gt;Monastery of St. Theoktistis, Ikaria_9, Greece...&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This monastery was build before 1688 and contains the main church with interesting frescos, an old a modern house for the monks and later for the nuns and an impressive chapel build between two huge rocks. The last nun served the monastery for 52 years and slept in 1975. Since then the place has been looked after by local volunteers, and recently by a lovely Mrs Maria, aged 74. She received us with smiles and offered us coffee, fried eggs of the day form her chickens and fresh goat milk with tasty honey. She argued to be paid, so we compromised and bought some local herbs she has been gathe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>In Myanmar - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/220902555/in-myanmar-by-sutipond-somnam</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSKpvhDaT5s3Jr4Fv5Fix0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 00:27:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/220902555/in-myanmar-by-sutipond-somnam" target="_blank"&gt;In Myanmar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two novice monks in the pagoda Bagan Mandalay Myanmar&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>The Battle For Myanmar’s Buddhist spirit - video - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/video/2017/sep/08/the-battle-for-myanmar-buddhist-spirit-video</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENk2pofXCrxngFOUn2yOelwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 11:20:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/video/2017/sep/08/the-battle-for-myanmar-buddhist-spirit-video" target="_blank"&gt;The Battle For Myanmar’s Buddhist spirit - video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Myanmar different groups of Buddhist monks are battling with how to deal with the country's minority Muslim population. While some advocate peace, others such as the extremist Ma Ba Tha, are stoking up hatred and violence. The Guardian visited Myanmar to investigate how the monks' actions are threatening to destabilise the country's newly established democracy&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Silence, serenity and sparkling wine at Finland's Valamo Monastery - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/jun/16/finland-valamo-monastery-silence-serenity-simple-life</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECtGFIMete0pC8N-an1vtFIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCw3Gc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 09:36:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/jun/16/finland-valamo-monastery-silence-serenity-simple-life" target="_blank"&gt;Silence, serenity and sparkling wine at Finland's Valamo Monastery&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Finland’s North Karelia region, the eastern province that borders Russia, the Valamo Monastery and its Orthodox brotherhood, receives more than 160,000 visitors every year who come to experience an alternative way of life. The monastery is in Heinävesi, a haven for wildlife including moose, where visitors seeking solitude can walk around the vast lake or through the dense forest with no other people in sight. Those of all faiths are encouraged to join church services, browse the monastery’s collection of rare, handmade Orthodox artefacts (many from Soviet Russia), and take out books from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Radical Burmese Buddhist Monk Is Subject of Documentary at Cannes Film Festival - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/radical-burmese-buddhist-monk-is-subject-of-documentary-at-cannes-film-festival/3854047.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELUlAy5fb-7uKTJfbvsVXy0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 12:34:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/radical-burmese-buddhist-monk-is-subject-of-documentary-at-cannes-film-festival/3854047.html" target="_blank"&gt;Radical Burmese Buddhist Monk Is Subject of Documentary at Cannes Film Festival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ashin Wirathu, the Burmese Buddhist monk known for whipping up anti-Muslim sentiment in Myanmar, is the subject of a new documentary airing at France’s renowned Cannes Film Festival, which starts Wednesday. By filmmaker Barbet Schroeder, “The Venerable W” will appear in a special screening at one of the most prestigious cultural events in the world, marking the culmination of Wirathu’s journey from an obscure rabble-rouser to international infamy. But his path to notoriety abroad points to questions back home about how much of a role the media have played in fueling his rise. Some believe h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Thai police fail to find fugitive monk in temple search - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-buddhism-idUSKBN15W08E</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEObGeFxzTCOGBeomCWuR54oqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 12:00:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-buddhism-idUSKBN15W08E" target="_blank"&gt;Thai police fail to find fugitive monk in temple search&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Aukkaraporn Niyomyat BANGKOK (Reuters) - Thai police failed to find a fugitive Buddhist monk wanted on money-laundering charges in a two-day search through the country's biggest monastery, but will not stop the hunt, a spokesman said on Friday. The military government used an emergency law on Thursday to let police explore the scandal-hit Dhammakaya Temple after months of failing to get it to hand over its former abbot, Phra Dhammachayo, in a politicised money-laundering case. The Dhammakaya Temple has said the monk, 72, is too sick to face questioning and has not been seen for months. "...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Sutton United 0 Arsenal 2: Theo Walcott brings up his century to set up quarter-final against Lincoln City - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/02/20/sutton-united-vs-arsenal-fa-cup-live-score/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEClBtevAmrWX4FpSN3cxEWQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 22:30:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/02/20/sutton-united-vs-arsenal-fa-cup-live-score/" target="_blank"&gt;Sutton United 0 Arsenal 2: Theo Walcott brings up his century to set up quarter-final against Lincoln City&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was the beleaguered against the non-Leaguers. Arsenal squeezed unconvincingly into the quarter- finals of the FA Cup but how they were pushed by Sutton United. For one night only this quiet commuter suburb of South London was turned into the centre of the football universe in a season when Arsène Wenger’s world has been turned upside down. Wenger is not expected to survive as Arsenal manager beyond this campaign but he survived here even if Sutton had their chances and even struck the crossbar. The prize for Wenger is another non-League side, Lincoln City, but that is back at the Emir...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Desmond Tutu condemns Aung San Suu Kyi: 'Silence is too high a price' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/sep/08/desmond-tutu-condemns-aung-san-suu-kyi-price-of-your-silence-is-too-steep</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIz6vx_g_DeclalfLB7j-wUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 01:45:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/sep/08/desmond-tutu-condemns-aung-san-suu-kyi-price-of-your-silence-is-too-steep" target="_blank"&gt;Desmond Tutu condemns Aung San Suu Kyi: 'Silence is too high a price'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nobel laureate Desmond Tutu has called on Aung San Suu Kyi to end military-led operations against Myanmar’s Rohingya minoritythat have driven 270,000 refugees from the country in the past fortnight. The 85-year old archbishop said the “unfolding horror” and “ethnic cleansing” in the country’s Rahkine region had forced him to speak out against the woman he admired and considered “a dearly beloved sister”. Related: Massacre at Tula Toli: Rohingya recall horror of Myanmar army attack Despite Aung San Suu Kyi defending her government’s handling of the growing crisis, Tutu urged his fellow N...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Somerset skeletons are oldest evidence of monks found in UK - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2016/dec/05/somerset-skeletons-are-oldest-evidence-of-monks-found-in-uk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLkIvHpYHG-nZGqphabV1QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 12:23:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2016/dec/05/somerset-skeletons-are-oldest-evidence-of-monks-found-in-uk" target="_blank"&gt;Somerset skeletons are oldest evidence of monks found in UK&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skeletons excavated at a site near Glastonbury are the oldest examples of monks ever found in the UK, carbon dating has proved. The remains, unearthed at the medieval Beckery chapel in Somerset, said to have been visited by legendary figures such as King Arthur and St Bridget, indicate a monastic cemetery dating back to the fifth or early sixth centuries AD, before Somerset was conquered by the Saxon kings of Wessex in the seventh century. Archaeologists first located an extensive cemetery of between 50 and 60 bodies during an excavation in the 1960s. The fact all were male – apart from one...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Jet-set' monk arrives in Thailand after extradition from U.S. - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-monk-idUSKBN1A423M</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKlBDlZLBrgqGwKyXGZr3bwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 17:58:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-monk-idUSKBN1A423M" target="_blank"&gt;'Jet-set' monk arrives in Thailand after extradition from U.S.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BANGKOK (Reuters) - A former Buddhist monk wanted on child sex charges arrived in Thailand's capital Bangkok late on Wednesday after being extradited from the United States where he had fled. Wirapol Sukphol came to public attention in 2013 when a YouTube video appeared showing the then-monk on a private jet with a Louis Vuitton bag and wearing aviator sunglasses, behavior deemed contrary to Buddhist teachings and a monk's vow to shun material goods. Later that year, he was expelled from the monkhood after being accused of having sexual intercourse - a grave offence for monks - with an unde...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>S Korean monk critical after sex slavery deal protest - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/01/korean-monk-critical-sex-slavery-deal-protest-170108202458643.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPX0HFvP6fMBo73sE0W3WHwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 21:32:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/01/korean-monk-critical-sex-slavery-deal-protest-170108202458643.html" target="_blank"&gt;S Korean monk critical after sex slavery deal protest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A South Korean monk is in critical condition after setting himself ablaze to protest against the country's deal with Japan on compensation for wartime sex slaves. The 64-year-old Buddhist monk suffered third-degree burns across his body and serious damage to vital organs following his self-immolation during a rally late on Saturday in the capital, Seoul, calling for the ouster of impeached President Park Geun-hye, police said. He is unconscious and unable to breathe on his own, an official from the Seoul National University Hospital told The Associated Press news agency on Sunday on conditi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Buddhist monk sets himself on fire in row over wartime sex slaves - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/buddhist-monk-sets-himself-on-fire-in-row-over-wartime-sex-slaves-a7515536.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECqL9kUEQps7E-WKxFik9bIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 08:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/buddhist-monk-sets-himself-on-fire-in-row-over-wartime-sex-slaves-a7515536.html" target="_blank"&gt;Buddhist monk sets himself on fire in row over wartime sex slaves&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A South Korean Buddhist monk is in critical condition after setting himself on fire to protest the country's settlement with Japan on compensation for wartime sex slaves. The 64-year-old monk suffered third-degree burns across his body and serious damage to vital organs. He's unconscious and unable to breathe on his own, said an official from the Seoul National University Hospital, who didn't want to be named citing office rules. The man set himself ablaze late on Saturday during a large rally in Seoul calling for the ouster of impeached President Park Geun-hye, police said. In his notebook...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Keep walking - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/202090509/keep-walking-by-saravut-whanset</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO41G4RfXDqg5cbN9Zi182wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 05:15:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/202090509/keep-walking-by-saravut-whanset" target="_blank"&gt;Keep walking&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buddhist monks are walking on green field in mist sunrise,Monks Thailand,Budha Monks,Thailand&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Burmaese Three novice monks walking - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/193395443/burmaese-three-novice-monks-walking-by-sutipond-somnam</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDGRwbKWuVeOT2nkPM0KbKsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 02:22:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/193395443/burmaese-three-novice-monks-walking-by-sutipond-somnam" target="_blank"&gt;Burmaese Three novice monks walking&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burmaese Three novice monks walking holding red umbrella in the pagoda.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Vietnam Plans Talks With Catholic Officials Over Monastery Dispute - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/vietnam-plans-talks-catholic-officials-monastery-dispute/3938053.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM5Jdg7h4qsH7A6ve-Y9DNsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 23:00:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/vietnam-plans-talks-catholic-officials-monastery-dispute/3938053.html" target="_blank"&gt;Vietnam Plans Talks With Catholic Officials Over Monastery Dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vietnamese authorities plan to hold talks with a Catholic monastery and church officials to resolve a land dispute that prompted a violent scuffle last month, a provincial government body said. Land disputes are common in Communist-ruled Vietnam, where conflicts over property between Catholics and regional authorities have posed one of the key obstacles to a normalization of relations with the Vatican. The Thua Thien-Hue provincial people's committee said it would meet clerics of the Thien An Saint Benedict Monastery and church officials from Hue, about 700 km (435 miles) southeast of the c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Cannes day trips: Retreat to these special islands - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/travel/article/cannes-day-trips-iles-de-lerins-france/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELPJ5amQEa0KfNyUJi10Bs0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 14:42:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/travel/article/cannes-day-trips-iles-de-lerins-france/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cannes day trips: Retreat to these special islands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Îles de Lérins: Just 15 minutes from Cannes, the tranquil island retreats of Île Sainte-Marguerite and Île Saint-Honorat feel like a world away. Cannes Office de Tourisme/Kelagopian Île Sainte-Marguerite: The largest of the two main islands of Îles de Lérins, Ile Sainte-Marguerite harbors hidden coves, tidal pools and beaches and is crisscrossed by a network of well-marked walking trails. Cannes Office de Tourisme/Kelagopian Water sports: The pristine waters between and around the islands are perfect for a dive or kayaking, outrigger canoeing or stand-up paddleboating. courtesy Tahitian Adv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Disgraced Buddhist monk charged with child rape in Thai court after extradition from US - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/397013-disgraced-buddhist-monk-jet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA-345XAUel2VN_P4QFYegsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 21:40:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/397013-disgraced-buddhist-monk-jet/" target="_blank"&gt;Disgraced Buddhist monk charged with child rape in Thai court after extradition from US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former Buddhist monk has been charged with the rape of an underage girl, money laundering and fraud by a Thai court following his extradition from the US to Thailand. The so-called 'jet-set monk,' Wiraphon Sukphon, 37, faces a total of five charges including the rape of a minor under 15 years of age, which is punishable by up to 20 years in prison. He allegedly fathered a child with the girl almost a decade ago reports Channel News Asia. “The Attorney-General will indict Sukphon on Thursday and advise the court to oppose bail because he poses a flight risk,” Somuk Siengkong, the Attorney-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Scuffles at Thai temple as police hunt for monk - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-buddhism-idUSKBN15Z08I</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJbUnmoUrzdApFoDKGcqdrYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 05:51:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-buddhism-idUSKBN15Z08I" target="_blank"&gt;Scuffles at Thai temple as police hunt for monk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Cod Satrusayang and Aukkaraporn Niyomyat BANGKOK (Reuters) - Monks and police scuffled on Monday at a Buddhist temple in Thailand where security forces are trying to arrest an influential former abbot on money-laundering charges. The standoff at the scandal-hit Dhammakaya Temple represents one of the biggest challenges to the authority of Thailand's junta since it took power in 2014. Police said they would try to avoid violence while threatening arrest for followers of the sprawling temple who have defied orders to leave and instead flocked there, hampering the search for 72-year-old Phr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Myanmar monks held after four million meth pills found - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/myanmar-monks-held-million-meth-pills-170208145238914.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOD6HmUsFRynL5863xFgeQgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 19:13:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/myanmar-monks-held-million-meth-pills-170208145238914.html" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar monks held after four million meth pills found&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police in Myanmar say three Buddhist monks have been arrested after authorities found more than four million methamphetamine pills - worth about $6m - in a car and monastery. Arsara - also known as Min Naing - was stopped on Sunday as he drove in northern Rakhine state after authorities were tipped off that he was carrying an illegal haul, Maung Maung Yin, a police officer, said on Tuesday. Pyin Nyar Nanda - also known as Aye Lwin - and Khone Na La - also known as Thein Shwe - were the two other monks caught by police in the town of Maung Daw over links to the narcotics found. Maung Maung Y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Myanmar's highest Buddhist authority bars radical nationalist group - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-nationalists-idUSKBN18J2ID</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENva0uW_TnYu4FnFKeDgSagqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 17:06:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-nationalists-idUSKBN18J2ID" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar's highest Buddhist authority bars radical nationalist group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Wa Lone YANGON (Reuters) - Myanmar's top Buddhist authority banned a hardline monks' group on Tuesday, raising pressure on extremists after they barred a firebrand monk from public sermons and authorities arrested several Buddhist nationalists. The radical group known by its Burmese initials Ma Ba Tha was declared illegal and "no person or organization" is allowed to use its name, according to a statement issued by the Sangha Maha Nayaka Committee, the country's highest Buddhist authority. All signs with the group's name must be removed by July 15, the statement said, and anyone who does...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>What is Wat Dhammakaya, the Conflict Behind It - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/wat-dhammakaya-conflict-thailand-buddhism/3778313.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJSs95avIak2xRdOfX9BY9AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 02:04:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/wat-dhammakaya-conflict-thailand-buddhism/3778313.html" target="_blank"&gt;What is Wat Dhammakaya, the Conflict Behind It&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nearly a month, the temple was under siege by more than 3,000 troops and police officers It’s more than eight times bigger than Vatican City and twice the size of Cambodia’s ancient Angkor Wat, making it quite possibly the world’s biggest religious complex. Yet few non-Buddhists have heard of Wat Dhammakaya, a sprawling, extravagant temple compound north of Bangkok that has been at the center of a high-profile power struggle between monks and Thailand’s ruling military. A gilded golden dome glimmers at the compound’s center, appearing to hover UFO-like over meditation grounds large enou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Thai police end search of temple without finding monk - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-buddhism-idUSKBN16H18Q</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKieFolXIH5hyMH-q5oPa34qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:07:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-buddhism-idUSKBN16H18Q" target="_blank"&gt;Thai police end search of temple without finding monk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Aukkarapon Niyomyat and Patpicha Tanakasempipat BANGKOK (Reuters) - Thai police ended their search of Thailand's biggest temple on Friday after laying siege to it for more than three weeks without finding the former abbot, who is wanted for suspected money-laundering. The standoff at the Dhammakaya temple between thousands of police and saffron-robed monks has posed one of the greatest challenges to the military government since it took power in 2014 and largely neutralized opposition. The influential Phra Dhammachayo, 72, is wanted for questioning over suspected money-laundering and num...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The novice - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/184448131/the-novice-by-alfredo-oliva</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKcAVW_yBw8zUP5QKgXtfocqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 21:18:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/184448131/the-novice-by-alfredo-oliva" target="_blank"&gt;The novice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A young monk go out the monastery after the evening class&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Bagan in Myanmar .. - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/195047489/bagan-in-myanmar-by-smoothy-</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH-4Fqr3sv9PwNMDJsP04LcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 16:47:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/195047489/bagan-in-myanmar-by-smoothy-" target="_blank"&gt;Bagan in Myanmar ..&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prayer of the young monk in the temple !!&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Novice Monks walking on ancient temple, Ayutthaya Thailand - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/229837443/novice-monks-walking-on-ancient-temple-ayutthaya-thailand-by-sasin-tipchai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMvm6NE5vvZ2mZOfzRZv8tMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:15:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/229837443/novice-monks-walking-on-ancient-temple-ayutthaya-thailand-by-sasin-tipchai" target="_blank"&gt;Novice Monks walking on ancient temple, Ayutthaya Thailand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Novice Monks walking on ancient temple, Ayutthaya Thailand&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Thai police pursue Buddhist monk with new arrest warrant - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-monk-idUSKBN15A0VY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFf04DlgcMtr3Si0u_yZTagqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 08:59:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-monk-idUSKBN15A0VY" target="_blank"&gt;Thai police pursue Buddhist monk with new arrest warrant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BANGKOK (Reuters) - A new warrant has been issued for the arrest of an influential Thai Buddhist monk and Thailand's police chief said on Thursday they would do their best to bring him to justice despite previous failures. Police in the predominantly Buddhist country have tried several times to arrest Phra Dhammachayo, former abbot of the futuristic-looking Wat Phra Dhammakaya, the country's biggest and richest monastery. A fourth arrest warrant was issued against Dhammachayo on Wednesday - for encroaching on land in southern Thailand. He already faced accusations of money laundering and of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Myanmar detains another journalist amid press freedom concerns - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-journalist-idUSKBN1AG0VE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL5N_5p49aODQy-dp8ZJXvkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 08:47:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-journalist-idUSKBN1AG0VE" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar detains another journalist amid press freedom concerns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Shoon Naing YANGON (Reuters) - Police in Myanmar said on Monday they had detained one of the country's best known journalists, months after a social media clash with firebrand Buddhist monk Wirathu, as concerns rise over freedom of expression. Swe Win, chief editor of news agency Myanmar Now, was detained at Yangon's airport on Sunday evening at the request of police in the central city of Mandalay, said Lieutenant Colonel Myint Htwe of Yangon regional police. "The Mandalay police informed us that Swe Win was trying to run away and to detain him at the airport," said Myint Htwe. Swe Win ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Woljeongsa Temple: Spend the night in a South Korean landmark - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/woljeongsa-temple-south-korea/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAmyaiBiZ34x2kdEX5TTTBEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 02:11:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/woljeongsa-temple-south-korea/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Woljeongsa Temple: Spend the night in a South Korean landmark&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This month's PyeongChang 2018 Olympic Winter Games has thrust South Korea's quiet Gangwon Province, northeast of Seoul, into the limelight. Despite the current flurry of activity, the area is actually best known for its peaceful scenery, from snow-capped peaks to stunning waterfalls. Best embodying this slower-paced way of life is the famous Woljeongsa Temple. Located in a fir pine forest inside Odaesan National Park, the Goryeo Dynasty-era (918-1392 CE) Buddhist complex welcomes visitors from all over the world to join its temple stay programs. "(The temples) have a culture of healing, whe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>'Fake news, and now fake fighting': Chinese audiences outraged after African student paid to lose to Kung Fu monk - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-02/chinese-monk-kos-fake-world-renowned-african-boxer/10454844</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAp9Nv0n4vJUxLtyA_Fj-v0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 04:28:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-02/chinese-monk-kos-fake-world-renowned-african-boxer/10454844" target="_blank"&gt;'Fake news, and now fake fighting': Chinese audiences outraged after African student paid to lose to Kung Fu monk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An African man touted to be a "brave warrior of boxing" was knocked out by a Chinese monk in just 43 seconds at an international martials arts tournament in China. Key points: - The Tanzanian boxer is an international student and only ever fought in 10 matches - Organisers recruited foreign fighters to make the tournaments look "more international" - Chinese netizens felt ashamed by the farce and questioned if the mix-up was deliberate Chinese state media — who were quick to trumpet the news of the swift defeat and how it demonstrated the power of Chinese Kung Fu — later found out the Afric...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Israeli forces arrest monk &amp; forcibly remove others protesting in East Jerusalem (VIDEO) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/442149-israel-arrest-coptic-monks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHm7mDPJfLUrlVK08KF8OhAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 14:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/442149-israel-arrest-coptic-monks/" target="_blank"&gt;Israeli forces arrest monk &amp; forcibly remove others protesting in East Jerusalem (VIDEO)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Video footage has captured Israeli police manhandling a group of Coptic Orthodox monks who were protesting outside the Church of the Holy Sepulchre in East Jerusalem’s Old City. Israeli forces can be seen dragging Monk Macarius Orshalemy along the ground before forcibly handcuffing him. The monk is pinned down for several minutes before being yanked to his feet and carried away. The protest was organized by the Coptic Orthodox Church after it was denied permission to carry out renovation works that are needed within the monastery of Coptic Sultan. Instead, Israel said the Israel Antiquities...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Marvelous Sky at Chihuahua - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/279552427/marvelous-sky-at-chihuahua-by-alfredo-garciaferro-macchia</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPWGvnS1SbAjDl3gzrmw6FUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 01:20:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/279552427/marvelous-sky-at-chihuahua-by-alfredo-garciaferro-macchia" target="_blank"&gt;Marvelous Sky at Chihuahua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most simple places, are one of the beautiful ones. This Valley its called by the locals as Monk Valley, as the shapes that some rocks represents. When your above a couple of these you just can feel all the energy, flowing around the environment... something magical.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Jailed Thai ex-monk gets further 16 years for raping teen girl - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/jailed-thai-monk-16-years-raping-teen-girl-181017090217063.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENQHfnckY4JH1j_QWERliaMqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 11:18:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/jailed-thai-monk-16-years-raping-teen-girl-181017090217063.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jailed Thai ex-monk gets further 16 years for raping teen girl&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Thai court on Wednesday sentenced a former Buddhist monk known for his lavish lifestyle to 16 years in prison for raping a 13-year-old girl whom he also impregnated. Wirapol Sukphol, formerly known by his monastic name of Luang Pu Nenkham, was sentenced in August to 114 years in prison after a court found him guilty of fraud, money laundering and computer crimes. He will only serve 20 years on those charges because that is the maximum for someone found guilty of multiple counts of the same offence. He was seen in a YouTube video in 2013 holding wads of cash on a private jet. The same year...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Former Buddhist monk sentenced for raping 13-year-old girl he impregnated - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/buddhist-monk-rape-thailand-wirapol-sukphol-sentenced-lavish-lifestyle-bangkok-a8588146.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENINQqz14n-uHnVFJI9Uv9MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 13:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/buddhist-monk-rape-thailand-wirapol-sukphol-sentenced-lavish-lifestyle-bangkok-a8588146.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Buddhist monk sentenced for raping 13-year-old girl he impregnated&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Thai court has sentenced a former Buddhist monk known for his jet-set lifestyle to 16 years in prison for raping a 13-year-old girl who he also impregnated. Wirapol Sukphol became infamous when he appeared in a 2013 YouTube video in his monk's robe aboard a private jet, wearing aviator sunglasses with a Louis Vuitton bag by his side. He was defrocked amid accusations he had sexual relations with women – a major violation of the precepts guiding monks' behaviour – and had impregnated one. He fled to the US, where he was arrested in 2016 and extradited last year. - Read more Dalai Lama says...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Buddhist extremism: Meet the violent followers of a religion widely known for its pacifism - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-21/buddhist-extremism-meet-the-religions-violent-followers/10360288</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELMVx9Eh1QZP2a1OuyMgsQIqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 19:01:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-21/buddhist-extremism-meet-the-religions-violent-followers/10360288" target="_blank"&gt;Buddhist extremism: Meet the violent followers of a religion widely known for its pacifism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Holly Robertson Myanmar's "Buddhist Bin Laden" has made a return to public life, appearing at a rally in support of the military generals condemned globally for a brutal crackdown on the Muslim minority Rohingya. Wirathu, an infamous Buddhist nationalist monk, was sanctioned in March 2017 for religious hate speech that demonised the Rohingya Muslims. And last weekend, his rhetoric demonstrated that — at least in his mind — little had changed. As military flag-waving demonstrators carried portraits of Senior General Min Aung Hlaing, Wirathu lambasted the United Nations, saying the day Mya...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Jailed Thai ex-monk gets further 16 years for child rape, abduction - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-religion/jailed-thai-ex-monk-gets-further-16-years-for-child-rape-abduction-idUSKCN1MR0SA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEImOJ07uF5otZAFyhGY3Ee4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 07:16:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-religion/jailed-thai-ex-monk-gets-further-16-years-for-child-rape-abduction-idUSKCN1MR0SA" target="_blank"&gt;Jailed Thai ex-monk gets further 16 years for child rape, abduction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former Buddhist monk who sparked outrage in Thailand over his lavish lifestyle and is already serving time for fraud was sentenced to a further 16 years in prison on Wednesday for abducting and raping a child. Wirapol Sukphol, formerly known by his monastic name of Luang Pu Nenkham, was sentenced in August to 114 years in prison after a court found him guilty of fraud, money laundering and computer crimes. He will only serve 20 years on those charges because that is the maximum for someone found guilty of multiple counts of the same offense. He was seen in a YouTube video in 2013 holding ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Wheel Of Prayers - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/278340243/the-wheel-of-prayers-by-matteo-carta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHT2AZKstJi9YWDOh-9VUtYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 05:56:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/278340243/the-wheel-of-prayers-by-matteo-carta" target="_blank"&gt;The Wheel Of Prayers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A monk spins the prayer wheel in Boudhanath Stupa, Kathamandu, Nepal. These wheels are spinned clockwise to accumulate wisdom and merit and to purify the negativities.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>The (Medieval) Saints And Sinners Of NBC's "The Good Place" - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewgabriele/2018/10/04/medieval-saints-good-place/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJrB-otJMaeQBACcEY6h4tgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 02:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewgabriele/2018/10/04/medieval-saints-good-place/" target="_blank"&gt;The (Medieval) Saints And Sinners Of NBC's "The Good Place"&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does it mean to be “good?” That’s the central question of NBC’s The Good Place, a show that has consistently tackled (at the same time) both the here-and-now of life on earth as well as what might wait for us all after death. At times, it seems to be spiritual but not religious, religious but not spiritual, both, and neither. Much of what’s discussed, however, as the 4 main characters try to figure out what’s going on, seems framed around the question of “what we owe to each other,” referencing the book by Prof. T.M. Scanlon. But there’s another interesting sub-text too – one that we c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>A former Buddhist monk is trying to help the world relax with an app - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/28/business/headspace-meditation-app/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPAnjQI8eyZmkG75zbYUjbwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:21:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/28/business/headspace-meditation-app/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;A former Buddhist monk is trying to help the world relax with an app&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story was originally published September 6, 2018 After spending a decade training as a Buddhist monk, Andy Puddicombe decided he wanted to share what he'd learned with the world. He has achieved his goal: his app, Headspace, has attracted more than 31 million users in over 190 countries. The app allows people to listen to guided meditation sessions while on the go. Puddicombe, 45, attributes its success to the age of information overload. "There's a lot of stuff going on right now that is hard to make sense of," he told CNN. "Especially if you think about the digital chatter in our liv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Egypt probes death of monk from murdered bishop's monastery - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-egypt-religion/egypt-probes-death-of-monk-from-murdered-bishops-monastery-idUSKCN1M72GV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI87I9NX1gntIm2OAgnh910qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 19:28:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-egypt-religion/egypt-probes-death-of-monk-from-murdered-bishops-monastery-idUSKCN1M72GV" target="_blank"&gt;Egypt probes death of monk from murdered bishop's monastery&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Egyptian prosecutors are investigating the death of a monk who was from the monastery where a bishop was murdered in July, a case that has rattled the biggest church in the Middle East. Zenon al-Makari, 45, died while being rushed to hospital after suffering severe stomach pains. He had served as a confessional priest for one of two defrocked monks charged with the murder of the Bishop Epiphanius on July 29, fellow monks said. A Church spokesman said Zenon had suffered a "sudden health crisis" and prosecutors were investigating the cause of death. Zenon was one of six monks that Coptic Chur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Meet the Jains of Melbourne, who are doing no harm - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-22/meet-the-jains-of-melbourne/10290302</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOZ8JW3TVnBaWSLBRrQdr9cqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-22/meet-the-jains-of-melbourne/10290302" target="_blank"&gt;Meet the Jains of Melbourne, who are doing no harm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Siobhan Hegarty for The Spirit of Things "For me, it's not about losing weight or seeing how long I can go without food," says Nimita, a 28-year-old electrical engineer from Melbourne's south. "It's about spending that extra time that I would've been eating doing religious activities. "It will help me progress and move forward and be a better person, and have a better soul and better karma." Nimita is a follower of Jainism — an ancient Indian religion grounded in the principle of non-violence. Their 'do no harm' approach extends to humans, animals, plants and even bacteria. It's the reas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Young Buddhist Novice monk reading in Bagan Myanmar. - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/273609205/young-buddhist-novice-monk-reading-in-bagan-myanmar-by-pramote-polyamate</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ0Op20lBO5GJMvLYHEM0zMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 05:14:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/273609205/young-buddhist-novice-monk-reading-in-bagan-myanmar-by-pramote-polyamate" target="_blank"&gt;Young Buddhist Novice monk reading in Bagan Myanmar.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young Buddhist Novice monk reading in Bagan Myanmar.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Myanmar Novice monk walking together in ancient pagoda Bagan Man - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/273609469/myanmar-novice-monk-walking-together-in-ancient-pagoda-bagan-man-by-pramote-polyamate</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwGenNZxDTQ3ZXQqHr7qcMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 05:18:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/273609469/myanmar-novice-monk-walking-together-in-ancient-pagoda-bagan-man-by-pramote-polyamate" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar Novice monk walking together in ancient pagoda Bagan Man&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Myanmar Novice monk walking together in ancient pagoda Bagan Mandalay The Buddhism the best in Asia and a culture faith of people in Burma. And landmark of tourism in Asian.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item></channel></rss>