<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Petroleum industry - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRE40YlROdEVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:15:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>200 persons to benefit from upstream oil and gas capacity programme - Myjoyonline.com</title><link>https://www.myjoyonline.com/business/2018/december-5th/200-persons-to-benefit-from-upstream-oil-and-gas-capacity-programme.php</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMifmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm15am95b25saW5lLmNvbS9idXNpbmVzcy8yMDE4L2RlY2VtYmVyLTV0aC8yMDAtcGVyc29ucy10by1iZW5lZml0LWZyb20tdXBzdHJlYW0tb2lsLWFuZC1nYXMtY2FwYWNpdHktcHJvZ3JhbW1lLnBocNIBAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:37:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.myjoyonline.com/business/2018/december-5th/200-persons-to-benefit-from-upstream-oil-and-gas-capacity-programme.php" target="_blank"&gt;200 persons to benefit from upstream oil and gas capacity programme&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Myjoyonline.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Accelerated Oil and Gas Capacity program has secured a $4.5m program to push 200 Ghanaians into skilled upstream oil and Gas jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWk1by1LbGpZQU1FWHNpRTdsaFpGUUlLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.myjoyonline.com">Myjoyonline.com</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/5tJHHTbS-Om76NqoQe5D31lGYNT62jgO6bdo-Wedpxcuy_kB2s7HbYjAANmu8iOoW7AJvLjOF4C9g--4vKOPIQofJcPZtRUv8YcH1aDKHEfj5uum7uhOprhnBkmZ6VG-tkFU=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Oil and Gas Capacity Programme to offer 200 Ghanaians jobs - GhanaWeb</title><link>https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/Oil-and-Gas-Capacity-Programme-to-offer-200-Ghanaians-jobs-706527</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMidGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdoYW5hd2ViLmNvbS9HaGFuYUhvbWVQYWdlL05ld3NBcmNoaXZlL09pbC1hbmQtR2FzLUNhcGFjaXR5LVByb2dyYW1tZS10by1vZmZlci0yMDAtR2hhbmFpYW5zLWpvYnMtNzA2NTI30gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:55:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/Oil-and-Gas-Capacity-Programme-to-offer-200-Ghanaians-jobs-706527" target="_blank"&gt;Oil and Gas Capacity Programme to offer 200 Ghanaians jobs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GhanaWeb&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under the Accelerated Oil and Gas Capacity (AOGC) Programme $4.5 million has been secured from Aker Energy to push 200 Ghanaians into skilled upstream ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ghanaweb.com">GhanaWeb</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/Y7L6LS4ZsnhkZ2_wYIHLZBR_gw1oNc_uvD_0Xv6vrYSPL89J7YbUOJVlcrAEYOTZmLRmz1TZ7Uohy7r9VfHaB0X3v2QEEQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Oil prices recover as Opec and allies agree to cut output - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/07/oil-prices-recover-as-opec-and-allies-agree-to-cut-output</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGTOSU3foIBjVltGoyvQEPgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:01:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/07/oil-prices-recover-as-opec-and-allies-agree-to-cut-output" target="_blank"&gt;Oil prices recover as Opec and allies agree to cut output&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil prices have rallied as the world’s major producers agreed a deeper-than-expected cut in output on Friday, recovering the losses of the previous day, when oil-rich states failed to reach a deal. Opec and allies including Russia, which together account for half of the world’s oil production, have committed to reducing output by around 1.2mb/d a day. The price of international benchmark Brent crude has plunged by a third since the start of October to about $60 a barrel due to fears that the market is oversupplied. But prices bounced up nearly 3% on Friday to $62.92 a barrel after the oil c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Oil producers join forces and cut production again - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/f05040b98fc54784a2e69e2f2af90d89</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBBNXx-rCsGnyf_hpWDgYegqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:08:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/f05040b98fc54784a2e69e2f2af90d89" target="_blank"&gt;Oil producers join forces and cut production again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VIENNA (AP) — Oil prices spiked sharply higher Friday as major oil producers, including the OPEC cartel, agreed to cut global oil production by 1.2 million barrels a day to reduce oversupply. Following two days of meetings, the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries that includes the likes of Saudi Arabia and Iraq said they would cut 800,000 barrels per day for six months from January, though some countries such as Iran, which is facing wide-ranging sanctions from the United States, have been given an exemption. The balance will come from Russia and other non-OPEC countries. The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Atlantic Coral Reef Discovery Raises Questions About Looming Seismic Surveys - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/atlantic-coral-reef-seismic-surveys-oil-gas_us_5c09b43ce4b04046345a87ee</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPSmSWQUUQlgq7m4VkB6RAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:00:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/atlantic-coral-reef-seismic-surveys-oil-gas_us_5c09b43ce4b04046345a87ee" target="_blank"&gt;Atlantic Coral Reef Discovery Raises Questions About Looming Seismic Surveys&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In August, a team of researchers working some 160 miles off the South Carolina coast made a startling discovery that upended the scientific community’s understanding of where deep-sea corals thrive off the Eastern Seaboard. There, a half mile below the water’s surface, scientists aboard the famous deep-sea submersible Alvin encountered mountains of ghost-white Lophelia pertusa, a stony coral species. Using sonar mapping of the ocean floor, they estimated that this previously unknown reef spans at least 85 linear miles. “The possibilities for where Lophelia could be forming reefs are now big...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Opec strikes a deal, CO2 emissions rise but Shell targets cuts, historic US oil exports and the positives of electric scooters - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cde85f22-fa97-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKSwDHuI01c-6co7JhWevywqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 07:00:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cde85f22-fa97-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Opec strikes a deal, CO2 emissions rise but Shell targets cuts, historic US oil exports and the positives of electric scooters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When they come to make the drama-documentary series about energy in the 21st century, one of the pivotal episodes should be based on cross-cutting between events in Vienna and in Katowice this week. In the Austrian capital ministers from Opec members and their allies in what is often called the Opec+ group, including Russia and Kazakhstan, met to thrash out an agreement on how to maximise their revenues from the most-used fossil fuel, oil. In the Polish city, meanwhile, officials from about 195 countries, including the nations represented in Vienna, have been meeting to debate how the world...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Bull's eye on US' Permian Basin as oil prices rise - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/5073817becae41e48c689a5d88877266</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJD4hIF3Jjd9vUKA7sva75AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:33:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/5073817becae41e48c689a5d88877266" target="_blank"&gt;Bull's eye on US' Permian Basin as oil prices rise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — Some of the largest energy companies in the U.S. have already invested billions of dollars on claims up and down the Texas-New Mexico state line, tapping one of the nation's richest and most prolific oil and natural gas regions. Now the stakes just got higher, as the U.S. Geological Survey released a new assessment Thursday that shows portions of the Permian Basin could hold even more promise. With the potential to double the nation's onshore oil and gas resources, the agency estimates more than 46 billion barrels of oil and some 280 trillion cubic feet of gas are w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump targets pair of Obama-era green rules to boost oil, coal - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-energy-trump/trump-targets-pair-of-obama-era-green-rules-to-boost-oil-coal-idUSKBN1O52L7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELksT9A31uzqYGP4p3AkLRQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:56:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-energy-trump/trump-targets-pair-of-obama-era-green-rules-to-boost-oil-coal-idUSKBN1O52L7" target="_blank"&gt;Trump targets pair of Obama-era green rules to boost oil, coal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration took aim at two Obama-era environmental policies on Thursday to boost the oil and coal industries, proposing to open up a bird's wildlife habitat to drilling and mining and remove hurdles to new coal-fired power plant construction. The moves, part of a broader agenda by U.S. President Donald Trump to revive the ailing coal industry and ramp up domestic energy production, come amid increasingly urgent warnings from within his own government about climate change, and as world leaders gather at a United Nations conference to combat planetary warming. Announced separate...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Oil price jumps 5 per cent on reports Opec has agreed to cut production - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/oil-price-latest-opec-meeting-saudi-arabia-iran-qatar-brent-crude-production-a8672616.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGQHOCjzOwTDbeaKJKrhwqAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/oil-price-latest-opec-meeting-saudi-arabia-iran-qatar-brent-crude-production-a8672616.html" target="_blank"&gt;Oil price jumps 5 per cent on reports Opec has agreed to cut production&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The price of oil jumped by as much as 5.4 per cent on Friday after it emerged that the Organisation of Petroleum Exporting Countries had agreed to reduce output by 1.2 million barrels per day. The oil producing nations had been expected to agree to a reduction in production on Thursday at its meeting in Vienna. Reaching a deal proved difficult as sanctions-hit Iran refused to comply with the output cuts, despite the input of non-Opec member Russia. The stalemate led the oil price to fall - the commodity had previously dropped by 30 per cent from four-year highs of more than $86 per barrel i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Analyst View: OPEC, allied exporters to cut crude output by 1.2 million bpd - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-oil-opec-analysts/analyst-view-opec-allied-exporters-to-cut-crude-output-by-12-million-bpd-idUSKBN1O61W6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPoSK19hMY0xr2iExkn7ZkAqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:20:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-oil-opec-analysts/analyst-view-opec-allied-exporters-to-cut-crude-output-by-12-million-bpd-idUSKBN1O61W6" target="_blank"&gt;Analyst View: OPEC, allied exporters to cut crude output by 1.2 million bpd&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEC and its Russia-led allies moved closer on Friday to clinching a deal that would cut oil production by more than the market had expected despite pressure from U.S. President Donald Trump to reduce the price of crude. The producer club will curb output by 0.8 million barrels per day from January while non-OPEC allies contribute an additional 0.4 million bpd of cuts, Iraqi Oil Minister Thamer Ghadhban said after OPEC concluded two days of talks in Vienna. BACKGROUND: This OPEC meeting has been more contentious than other recent get-togethers. The group has broadened its reach after it was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>OPEC and Russia agree to slash oil production - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/investing/opec-oil-prices/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVPelIQA6OujA1Wo5-i4iQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:56:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/investing/opec-oil-prices/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;OPEC and Russia agree to slash oil production&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEC and its allies reached a deal to slash oil production on Friday despite pressure from President Donald Trump to keep pumping. The cuts will remove 1.2 million barrels a day from world markets, UAE energy minister and OPEC president Suhail Al Mazrouei told reporters. US crude prices spiked nearly 5% to $54 a barrel on the news. Members of OPEC pledged to reduce their production by 800,000 barrels per day for six months beginning in January. Russia, and other producers outside the cartel, promised to slash an additional 400,000 barrels per day. OPEC members Iran, Venezuela and Libya have...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Glencore, Vitol and Trafigura face bribery probe - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2456aff4-f88f-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJfelRMRU7sEzkQB5iu1744qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:49:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2456aff4-f88f-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Glencore, Vitol and Trafigura face bribery probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commodity traders Vitol, Trafigura, and Glencore are under investigation on suspicion of paying bribes to employees of state-controlled oil company Petrobras in exchange for contracts, in the latest twist to the sweeping corruption investigation that has rattled Latin America’s largest economy. Brazilian prosecutors said on Wednesday that “there are suspicions” that between 2011 and 2014 the three companies paid more than $15.3m related to over 160 operations “of purchase and sale of oil products and rental of storage tanks”. Other unnamed companies are also being investigated for paying a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Ryan Zinke To Oil Reps: 'We've Gotten A Lot Better As Industry' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ryan-zinke-national-petroleum-council-oil-gas-climate_us_5c06f277e4b0680a7ec9cdd0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIkxntQf5x-d9tM2fl2i2s0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 23:09:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ryan-zinke-national-petroleum-council-oil-gas-climate_us_5c06f277e4b0680a7ec9cdd0" target="_blank"&gt;Ryan Zinke To Oil Reps: 'We've Gotten A Lot Better As Industry'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was clear Interior Secretary Ryan Zinke felt at home Tuesday addressing representatives of the industry that was a top donor to his congressional campaigns. It’s the same industry that the Trump administration has worked so hard to prop up over the last two years, and that Zinke now regulates as chief steward of America’s natural resources. “I see a lot of familiar faces,” he told the National Petroleum Council during its meeting in Washington, D.C., before launching into a series of go-to talking points about the importance of producing domestic energy, namely fossil fuels, and downplay...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Despite Qatar's Exit, OPEC+ Still Holds The Oil Price Cards - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2018/12/06/despite-qatars-exit-opec-still-holds-the-oil-price-cards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOWbA4oHKFa8AaCeygyz1IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2018/12/06/despite-qatars-exit-opec-still-holds-the-oil-price-cards/" target="_blank"&gt;Despite Qatar's Exit, OPEC+ Still Holds The Oil Price Cards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Issam Almarzooq, Kuwait’s oil minister, appears on screen as he speaks during a news conference ahead of the 173rd Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) meeting in Vienna, Austria, on Wednesday, Nov. 29, 2017. Photographer: Akos Stiller/Bloomberg Monday’s announcement by Qatar that it is leaving OPEC does not spell the end of that organization, or really do it much harm. But, coming as it does on the heels of the recent 30% drop in global crude prices, the meeting of the OPEC nations that began in Vienna on Wednesday represents a crucial moment for the global oil industry. As...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Latest: OPEC output decision delayed until Russia talks - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/8b9692d0dadb4ac2878a18a346cf3dac</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIx3JjhsJy5GargzSevIO8IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:39:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/8b9692d0dadb4ac2878a18a346cf3dac" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: OPEC output decision delayed until Russia talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VIENNA (AP) — The Latest on OPEC's meeting on whether to cut oil production and support energy prices (all times local): 6:40 p.m. Saudi Arabia's energy minister says OPEC nations have not yet been able to decide upon a possible production cut and is expressing skepticism about when an agreement will be reached. Leaving a day-long meeting Thursday when an agreement was expected to have been reached, Khalid al-Falih told reporters "we're still deliberating." OPEC countries will on Friday meet with Russia to negotiate its contribution to the overall cuts. Going in to the day he said Saudi Ara...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Mexico's new president throws down gauntlet to oil majors - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-politics/mexican-president-says-oil-production-needed-before-considering-new-deep-water-auctions-idUSKBN1O41VH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEf5R75WZZfW6VMhChzw0J4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:50:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-politics/mexican-president-says-oil-production-needed-before-considering-new-deep-water-auctions-idUSKBN1O41VH" target="_blank"&gt;Mexico's new president throws down gauntlet to oil majors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mexico's new president, Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador, said on Wednesday he would not cancel contracts issued to foreign and national oil companies by his predecessor but challenged them to pump oil quickly or no further oil fields would be offered. Lopez Obrador took office on Saturday, promising to increase the government's role in the energy industry and roll back what he described as a 36-year neo-liberal era in which successive governments gradually opened up the economy. During the election campaign, he pledged to review the contracts issued under a landmark energy reform for any signs ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Lord Browne’s DEA to buy Sierra Oil and Gas - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/45ba8988-f7e3-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBJPldnn2T6Wb5YZHpzejLUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:00:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/45ba8988-f7e3-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Lord Browne’s DEA to buy Sierra Oil and Gas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEA, the German oil and gas producer chaired by former BP chief John Browne, will on Wednesday announce plans to buy Mexico’s Sierra Oil and Gas in the country’s largest upstream oil M&amp;A deal since the liberalisation of the sector. The transaction — which according to people familiar with it is valued at about $500m — will expand DEA’s foothold in the Mexico as it looks to high-growth regions ahead of a multibillion-euro merger with rival Wintershall next year, which is set to create Europe’s largest independent oil and gas producer. “This is in line with the bigger end of the deals we’ve d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Shale's growing profits at the mercy of OPEC cuts and Trump's tweets - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-oil-opec-shale-analysis/shales-growing-profits-at-the-mercy-of-opec-cuts-and-trumps-tweets-idUSKBN1O41IQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPHLPiDE3J8WBaq0EfUKQTwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:29:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-oil-opec-shale-analysis/shales-growing-profits-at-the-mercy-of-opec-cuts-and-trumps-tweets-idUSKBN1O41IQ" target="_blank"&gt;Shale's growing profits at the mercy of OPEC cuts and Trump's tweets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent nosedive in crude oil prices came just as shale producers had started delivering healthy returns after years of heavy spending to boost production and market share. The shift has pleased investors who had grown weary of waiting for a payoff while watching the frenetic west Texas shale boom make the United States the world's top oil producer and a major exporter. The 29 percent drop in U.S. crude oil prices CLc1 since October now threatens those improved margins, and sustained prices below $50 per barrel could dent the value of shale reserves, which banks use to determine borrowin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Exxon, Chevron seek to exit Azerbaijan's oil after 25 years - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-exxon-azerbaijan-exclusive/exclusive-exxon-chevron-seek-to-exit-azerbaijans-oil-after-25-years-idUSKBN1O315D</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFnzG2obWzKa5zixNPxH3LcqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 16:11:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-exxon-azerbaijan-exclusive/exclusive-exxon-chevron-seek-to-exit-azerbaijans-oil-after-25-years-idUSKBN1O315D" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Exxon, Chevron seek to exit Azerbaijan's oil after 25 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exxon Mobil (XOM.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) and Chevron (CVX.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) are seeking to sell their stakes in Azerbaijan's largest oilfield, marking the retreat of the U.S. majors from the former Soviet state after 25 years as they re-focus on domestic production. Exxon is hoping to raise up to $2 billion from the sale of its 6.8 percent in the Azeri-Chirag-Gunashli (ACG) field in the Caspian Sea, according to industry sources. Rival Chevron said in a statement to Reuters it had also decided to launch the sale of its 9.57 percent stake in ACG as wel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Oil prices plunge as Opec delays decision on cutting output - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/06/oil-prices-plunge-as-opec-delays-decision-on-cutting-output</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK48Rqbm8DnzprXPUYBmMlUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:53:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/06/oil-prices-plunge-as-opec-delays-decision-on-cutting-output" target="_blank"&gt;Oil prices plunge as Opec delays decision on cutting output&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Saudi energy minister has cast doubt on the prospect of Opec announcing a cut in output after admitting he was “not confident” a deal would be reached. At a crunch meeting in Vienna this week, the Opec cartel has tried to plot a course between protecting member countries’ revenues and not angering Donald Trump, who on Wednesday called for oil to keep flowing in order to hold down prices. Oil prices slipped 4% to below $60 (£47) on Thursday as Khalid al-Falih’s comments, reported by Bloomberg, placed question marks over a deal. Brent crude, the international benchmark, has plunged from $...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Why A New 'Rush To Gas' Could Happen In 2019 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2018/11/30/why-a-new-rush-to-gas-could-happen-in-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBnLJywIgHMFTCvMELxdmVMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 15:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2018/11/30/why-a-new-rush-to-gas-could-happen-in-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;Why A New 'Rush To Gas' Could Happen In 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Asia Vision LNG carrier ship sits docked at the Cheniere Energy Inc. terminal in this aerial photograph taken over Sabine Pass, Texas, U.S., on Wednesday, Feb. 24, 2016. Photographer: Lindsey Janies/Bloomberg The upstream segment of the oil and gas industry has historically been a largely reactive business. Producers over the years have made a practice of trying to weight their reserve portfolios toward being either liquids-heavy or gas-heavy, depending on a variety of market factors, the most important of which is the expected commodity price. The trouble with that business practice, o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Expect A Kindler, Gentler OPEC To Support Oil Prices At Its Meeting Tomorrow - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimcollins/2018/12/05/expect-a-kindler-gentler-opec-to-support-oil-prices-at-its-meeting-tomorrow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJerwhHUSjsaCzfcffEMhPMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimcollins/2018/12/05/expect-a-kindler-gentler-opec-to-support-oil-prices-at-its-meeting-tomorrow/" target="_blank"&gt;Expect A Kindler, Gentler OPEC To Support Oil Prices At Its Meeting Tomorrow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike the stock and bond markets the oil futures pits are open for trading today. A quick glance at the CME’s website shows an oil price of $53.28, a gain of 28 cents on the day. Volume is below normal and I believe this is the calm before the storm ahead of OPEC’s meeting in Geneva on Thursday. Longtime energy industry observer Tom Petrie once told me and a crowd of others gathered in an aromatic rodeo ring in Midland, Texas that “OPEC meetings are scripted in advance.” I believe that is the case here. OPEC’s economic advisory panel–the JMMC–last week recommended a production cut of 1....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Rise In Optimism Provides Boost For UK Oil And Gas Jobs - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markvenables/2018/11/30/rise-in-optimism-provides-boost-for-uk-oil-and-gas-jobs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJoDU6fhm9RF7jRq3na7p-EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 09:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/markvenables/2018/11/30/rise-in-optimism-provides-boost-for-uk-oil-and-gas-jobs/" target="_blank"&gt;Rise In Optimism Provides Boost For UK Oil And Gas Jobs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engineer closes gate valve on industrial pipeline. Technician works on gas and oil station The last few years have undoubtedly been tough for those working within the oil and gas sector. According to Oil and Gas UK (OGUK), the oil sector supported 300,000 jobs in the UK last year, down from 460,000 just three years ago. However, OGUK has said it is encouraged by the latest Oil and Gas Survey issued by Aberdeen and Grampian Chamber of Commerce that has revealed oil and gas recruitment is on the rise as 33% of firms look to increase their UK workforce by 10% or more in 2019. Positive mood “We...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Neptune Energy to look beyond North Sea for growth - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e210c5c0-f4c5-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKw5QiRowCrQVzkEKK3xPM8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 17:08:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e210c5c0-f4c5-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;Neptune Energy to look beyond North Sea for growth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neptune Energy, the private equity backed oil and gas producer led by former Centrica chief Sam Laidlaw, plans to ramp up organic growth and exploration alongside acquisitions as the group moves to increase output. The company, which is backed by the Carlyle Group, CVC Capital Partners and China Investment Corporation, became a full-scale producer and explorer early this year after the acquisition of Engie’s oil and gas production assets, giving it a footprint stretching from the North Sea through north Africa and south-east Asia. It has been linked with a string of potential assets in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>How One AI Learning Tool Helps Oil Companies Reduce Costs - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2018/12/03/how-one-ai-learning-tool-helps-oil-companies-reduce-costs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENbMiCUxGLoXkbQ0ojPlwpUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2018/12/03/how-one-ai-learning-tool-helps-oil-companies-reduce-costs/" target="_blank"&gt;How One AI Learning Tool Helps Oil Companies Reduce Costs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A pumpjack operates at an oil well in Williston, North Dakota, U.S., on Sunday, Feb. 15, 2015. Photographer: Daniel Acker/Bloomberg As oil and gas producers, pipeliners and refiners strive constantly to lower their cost structures, they increasingly rely on an array of advancing technologies to help them achieve their goals. From better and stronger drilling rigs, to advanced frac fluids, to downhole sensors, to remote monitoring systems, to advanced leak detection equipment, improved technology systems are constantly making the nation’s oil fields safer, smarter and less expensive. What I ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How Can Nigeria's Upstream Become Relevant Again? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/woodmackenzie/2018/11/30/how-can-nigerias-upstream-become-relevant-again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBzoX6llWq4D0XNgeFthYX8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 09:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/woodmackenzie/2018/11/30/how-can-nigerias-upstream-become-relevant-again/" target="_blank"&gt;How Can Nigeria's Upstream Become Relevant Again?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEC’s biggest producer outside the Gulf and a global heavyweight. Nigeria’s industry has been on the go since the 1950s and there’s a big prize still to be had in deepwater. We estimate 10 billion boe in undeveloped deepwater resource, perhaps the same again in yet-to-find. Geologists acknowledge the best reservoirs as world class. Yet Nigeria is losing its relevance for Big Oil. Ten years ago, it was the most valuable country position by NPV in Shell’s global upstream portfolio. Today it’s fifth, has slipped in the rankings for Chevron and Eni too, and barely scrapes into ExxonMobil’s top...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>OPEC, Russia Move Closer to Cutting Oil Output - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/opec-russia-move-closer-to-cutting-oil-output/4688156.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHuEalBQ1XpRi9JijULdU6EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:57:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/opec-russia-move-closer-to-cutting-oil-output/4688156.html" target="_blank"&gt;OPEC, Russia Move Closer to Cutting Oil Output&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEC and Russia moved closer on Wednesday to agreeing cuts in oil production from next year despite pressure from U.S. President Donald Trump to reduce the price of crude. OPEC meets on Thursday in Vienna, followed by talks with allies such as Russia on Friday. OPEC's de facto leader, Saudi Arabia, has indicated a need for steep output reductions from January, fearing a glut, but Russia has resisted a large cut. "All of us including Russia agreed there is a need for a reduction," Oman's Oil Minister Mohammed bin Hamad Al-Rumhy told reporters after a ministerial committee that groups Saudi A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Looking For Open Standards In Oil And Gas Automation - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markvenables/2018/11/30/looking-for-open-standards-in-oil-and-gas-automation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPw2DCCuqqPEl5Y9offHPxYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/markvenables/2018/11/30/looking-for-open-standards-in-oil-and-gas-automation/" target="_blank"&gt;Looking For Open Standards In Oil And Gas Automation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Industrial landscape. Oil pumps against the setting sun. As part of its drive to improve operational efficiency the oil and gas sector has been looking at standardization as a vital tool. There has been good progress in several areas, but one key segment of the industry is lagging, namely automation. The dependence of the oil and gas industry on automation has increased in the last decade, and this is expected further to double by 2020. As a result of project cancellation followed by the fall in crude oil prices from 2014 to 2016, multiple rounds of industry layoffs were announced that left...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Two key Canada-to-U.S. oil pipelines hit by disruptions - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-enbridge-inc-mainline-outages/two-key-canada-to-u-s-oil-pipelines-hit-by-disruptions-idUSKBN1O32TX?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=businessNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEEjsTuj5bUqU_dn5maHKB4qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 02:15:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-enbridge-inc-mainline-outages/two-key-canada-to-u-s-oil-pipelines-hit-by-disruptions-idUSKBN1O32TX?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=businessNews" target="_blank"&gt;Two key Canada-to-U.S. oil pipelines hit by disruptions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two major pipelines carrying oil from Canada to the United States were hit by weather-related disruptions on Tuesday, the latest hit to Canada's oil industry just days after the Alberta government announced forced cuts in crude production. A number of lines on the Enbridge Inc (ENB.TO: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Mainline system, which carries crude and other liquids, were hit by power outages in the Western Canadian province of Saskatchewan due to severe weather, the company said Tuesday. TransCanada Corp's (TRP.TO: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) 590,000 barrel-per-day cru...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Hapless Alberta takes action as oil prices crash - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/business/445391-alberta-oil-prices-crash/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_ZCnU0WsZGnuEkTPx7sigqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwroQo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 15:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/business/445391-alberta-oil-prices-crash/" target="_blank"&gt;Hapless Alberta takes action as oil prices crash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Faced with a crisis moving oil out of the country, the provincial government in Alberta is stepping in to purchase trains in order to ease the midstream bottleneck. Western Canada Select (WCS), the benchmark for heavy oil in Alberta, continues to trade below $15 per barrel, or roughly $40-per-barrel lower than WTI. That is a hefty discount, although slightly narrower than the $50 per barrel discount WCS traded for a few weeks ago. “It’s worth more in the ground than it is to produce it right now,” Athabasca Oil Corp. CEO Rob Broen said in an interview Wednesday with BNN Bloomberg Television...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Trump admin approves seismic surveys for Atlantic drilling - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/3bd02acc43aa4cecada19d87d20edd31</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKzg3t74USToGFUALEIMYJ4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:29:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/3bd02acc43aa4cecada19d87d20edd31" target="_blank"&gt;Trump admin approves seismic surveys for Atlantic drilling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration on Friday authorized use of seismic air guns to find oil and gas formations deep underneath the Atlantic Ocean floor, reversing Obama administration policies and drawing outrage from critics who say the practice can disturb or injure whales, sea turtles and other marine life. The National Marine Fisheries Service said it has authorized permits under the Marine Mammal Protection Act for five companies to use air guns for seismic surveys in the mid-Atlantic, from Delaware to central Florida. The surveys are part of President Donald Trump's bid to exp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>As Iran supply dries up, South Korea petrochemical firms find new, costly oil sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-southkorea-iran-oil-analysis/as-iran-supply-dries-up-south-korea-petrochemical-firms-find-new-costly-oil-sources-idUSKBN1O22PO</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL21h2fjGnVk4oo4hn45n5UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 02:03:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-southkorea-iran-oil-analysis/as-iran-supply-dries-up-south-korea-petrochemical-firms-find-new-costly-oil-sources-idUSKBN1O22PO" target="_blank"&gt;As Iran supply dries up, South Korea petrochemical firms find new, costly oil sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With supply from major producer Iran uncertain, big condensate user South Korea is scouring the world for alternative sources of this key ingredient in its large chemical industry to avert shortages - a process that is proving to be costly for buyers. Condensate, a type of ultra-light crude oil, is a feedstock for South Korea's petrochemical industry. A by-product of natural gas production, Iran and Qatar are major condensate suppliers. But Iran's exports have fallen sharply this year as production in its South Pars gas field struggles to keep up with rising domestic demand while renewed U....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Opec summit: cut expected to balance price fall and global slowdown - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/03/opec-oil-prices-cartel-price-global-growth</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFY8Ke75E-P1H9uBJK8wJWIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 07:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/03/opec-oil-prices-cartel-price-global-growth" target="_blank"&gt;Opec summit: cut expected to balance price fall and global slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opec meetings are never simply about turning on and off the taps of the stuff that greases the world’s economy. And when the Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries meets on 6 December there will be more to discuss than oil prices. Geopolitics also overhangs the Opec meeting. Donald Trump has consistently pushed for lower prices and cheered recent falls earlier this month. Oil prices getting lower. Great! Like a big Tax Cut for America and the World. Enjoy! $54, was just $82. Thank you to Saudi Arabia, but let’s go lower! — Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) November 21, 2018 Then the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>OPEC Expected To Curb Output, But By How Much? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/daneberhart/2018/12/05/opec-expected-to-curb-output-but-by-how-much/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECDcPrMdUxg1BrfEu2v258EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/daneberhart/2018/12/05/opec-expected-to-curb-output-but-by-how-much/" target="_blank"&gt;OPEC Expected To Curb Output, But By How Much?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia’s Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, left, and Russian President Vladimir Putin, shake hands prior their talks at the G20 summit in Buenos Aires, Argentina, Saturday, Dec. 1, 2018. (Mikhail Klimentyev, Sputnik, Kremlin Pool Photo via AP) Ministers from the Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) and non-OPEC partners like Russia descend on Vienna this week with the idea of taming an oil market whipsawed by extreme volatility. But any notion that the cartel can successfully “manage” the market should be put to rest. There are too many factors in play that preclude a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Oil And Gas Entrants Need New Funding Sources - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markvenables/2018/11/26/new-oil-and-gas-entrants-need-new-funding-sources/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIg-_4TJcheX_xlp6h0s-V4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 20:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/markvenables/2018/11/26/new-oil-and-gas-entrants-need-new-funding-sources/" target="_blank"&gt;New Oil And Gas Entrants Need New Funding Sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are large capital needs within the oil and gas sector going forward It is apparent to all that the oil and gas industry is undergoing a fundamental transformation and it looks to align its business models with the reduced fossil fuel futures. There are some visible changes, such as Statoil ditching the oil from its title and renaming itself as Equinor, but under the surface, things are changing as well. There is a recognition that to make themselves sustainable they need more than oil and gas in their portfolios. Whether it is renewable energy or low-carbon transportation, or energy s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What is OPEC? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/opec-181203112510476.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKVoQ8zTjEasBUUMH15wMgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:46:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/opec-181203112510476.html" target="_blank"&gt;What is OPEC?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar announced on Monday it was leaving the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC), the world's leading oil producing bloc. The Gulf nation, which has been a member of OPEC since 1961, said it wanted to focus more on the production of Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG). Qatar supplied about 2 percent of annual OPEC output. The decision comes days ahead of a scheduled meeting of the oil bloc in Vienna, Austria and amid tension with leading OPEC member Saudi Arabia, which has imposed a land and air blockade on Qatar since 2017. The Gulf nation's Energy Minister Saad Sherida al-Kaa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Britain commits £20m to carbon-capture push - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8fc38854-f26b-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPBVLAzx4Z4C-XPFLWxOe9UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 00:01:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8fc38854-f26b-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Britain commits £20m to carbon-capture push&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government has made a commitment to ensure that Britain’s first large-scale carbon-capture and storage facility is fully operational by the middle of the next decade, winning the backing of some of the world’s largest energy companies for a pilot project to inject carbon dioxide into old North Sea oil and gasfields. Claire Perry, the clean energy minister, is set to dedicate £20m of the UK’s industry innovation budget to carbon-capture technology at a joint conference with the International Energy Agency in Edinburgh on Wednesday, as the government tries to accelerate the development of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Qatar pulls out of Opec to focus on gas production - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/03/qatar-pulls-out-of-opec-to-focus-on-gas-production</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA1_KIWdC0mAoIBYzk2AtFUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 08:21:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/03/qatar-pulls-out-of-opec-to-focus-on-gas-production" target="_blank"&gt;Qatar pulls out of Opec to focus on gas production&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar is to pull out of Opec after nearly 60 years of membership of the oil cartel, but will attend a meeting this week that will discuss cutting output. Saad al-Kaabi, the country’s energy minister, told a news conference: “Qatar has decided to withdraw its membership from Opec effective January 2019 and this decision was communicated to Opec this morning.” He said the decision was not linked to a political and economic boycott of Qatar imposed in June 2017 by Saudi Arabia, Opec’s largest member and its de facto leader, and three other Arab states – the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain and Eg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Dismantling the oil industry: rough North Sea waters test new ideas - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-north-sea-oil-decommissioning-analysi/dismantling-the-oil-industry-rough-north-sea-waters-test-new-ideas-idUSKCN1NW0IL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIgH8FiM47LhqzuHAL77A8AqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 11:17:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-north-sea-oil-decommissioning-analysi/dismantling-the-oil-industry-rough-north-sea-waters-test-new-ideas-idUSKCN1NW0IL" target="_blank"&gt;Dismantling the oil industry: rough North Sea waters test new ideas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scottish marine salvage group Ardent is adapting the tanksit used to refloat the Costa Concordia, the cruise ship wrecked off the Italian coast in 2012, to decommission North Sea oil platforms. It is one of several companies trying new ideas to win business in the market for dismantling disused oil platforms. In Britain's aging oil fields alone, the opportunities could be worth up to 17 billion pounds ($21.85 billion) before 2025, according to industry body Oil and Gas UK. The ideas could then be deployed to other maturing fields such as in the Gulf of Mexico and southeast Asia.GRAPHIC: Off...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Renewable Energy Laggard ExxonMobil To Power Oil Exploration With Wind And Solar - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnparnell/2018/11/28/renewable-energy-laggard-exxonmobil-to-power-oil-exploration-with-wind-and-solar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFKEx-dw0DWV04IZtqPKkEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 23:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnparnell/2018/11/28/renewable-energy-laggard-exxonmobil-to-power-oil-exploration-with-wind-and-solar/" target="_blank"&gt;Renewable Energy Laggard ExxonMobil To Power Oil Exploration With Wind And Solar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil major ExxonMobil will power its operations at a Texas oil field with electricity from wind and solar projects. The firm has faced criticism for its response to climate change and has been slower than its peers to hedge their bets by becoming involved in the clean energy sector. The contracts for the Permian filed in West Texas will be fulfilled by Orsted, which itself was the Danish state-run oil and gas company before a rebrand and its divestment of fossil fuel assets in 2017. In a presentation at its capital markets day in Copenhagen on Wednesday, Orsted revealed the two 250MW power p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Deepwater Continues To Thrive But Must Meet The Threat Of Rising Costs - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markvenables/2018/11/30/deepwater-continues-to-thrive-but-must-meet-the-threat-of-rising-costs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEY4TwVG_htj5m7BSJGBixoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/markvenables/2018/11/30/deepwater-continues-to-thrive-but-must-meet-the-threat-of-rising-costs/" target="_blank"&gt;Deepwater Continues To Thrive But Must Meet The Threat Of Rising Costs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Employee pass in front of the finished Abkatun-A2 oil platform at the Mcdermott International Inc. fabrication facility in Altamira, Tamaulipas state, Mexico, on Friday, Nov. 2, 2018. Mcdermott International was awarded the $454 million contract for engineering, procurement, construction and installation for Abkatun-A2 from Petroleos Mexicanos (Pemex) in 2016. Pemex is expected to start operating the oil platform in April 2019. Photographer: Luis Antonio Rojas/Bloomberg Although the deepwater oil and gas sector would appear to be in excellent health with many projects, including some ambiti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Drilling in the Great Australian Bight is not worth the risk - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/24/drilling-in-the-great-australian-bight-is-not-worth-the-risk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPM5zFrlPesjTmeducAFeJoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:00:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/24/drilling-in-the-great-australian-bight-is-not-worth-the-risk" target="_blank"&gt;Drilling in the Great Australian Bight is not worth the risk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Great Australian Bight is one of the most unique and productive marine ecosystems in the world. An estimated 85% of its known species are found nowhere else; the region has exceptionally productive and sensitive pelagic, seabed, and shoreline habitats; hosts the greatest concentrations of marine mammals, seabirds, pelagic fishes, and sharks in Australia; and supports an annual multi-billion dollar fishery, aquaculture, and tourism economy. By any measure, the Bight is a national and global treasure, but this treasure is now at risk from proposed deepwater oil drilling. Related: More of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>South Africa to Invest $1B in South Sudan Oil Sector - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-to-invest-1b-in-south-sudan-oil-sector-/4671577.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKd8UbtpLlqoaf61J9K9PEIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 20:59:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-to-invest-1b-in-south-sudan-oil-sector-/4671577.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa to Invest $1B in South Sudan Oil Sector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Sudan's oil minister says South Africa will invest $1 billion in the war-torn country's oil sector in what would be the largest investment in the East African country's history. Ezekiel Lol Gatkuoth confirmed Friday's signing of the memorandum of understanding (MOU) with South Africa's energy minister, Jeff Radebe. Radebe told state broadcaster SABC that both countries would benefit. South Sudan has Africa's third-largest oil reserves, at 3.5 billion barrels, and it hopes increasing production will help the country recover in the wake of the signing of a peace deal two months ago. One...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Energy: ENI accord with Algeria's Sonatrach on renewable - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/economics/2018/11/26/energy-eni-accord-with-algerias-sonatrach-on-renewable_8112aa3b-b5af-4e95-8709-19e54c751952.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDB4_S7w_KMS60tZ9ZGg1ncqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 11:55:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/economics/2018/11/26/energy-eni-accord-with-algerias-sonatrach-on-renewable_8112aa3b-b5af-4e95-8709-19e54c751952.html" target="_blank"&gt;Energy: ENI accord with Algeria's Sonatrach on renewable&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROME - ENI and Algeria's Sonatrach are inaugurating the photovoltaic plant of Bir Rebaa North worth 10 MW and have signed agreements on the renewable energy sector, according to a statement. The statement said that the president director general of the State-run Algerian company Sonatrach, Abdelmoumem Ould Kaddour, and the CEO of ENI, Claudio Descalzi, have inaugurated a solar energy plant worth 10 MW in Bir Rebaa North (BRN) in Algeria. The plant, jointly operated by ENI and Sonatrach through GSA (Groupement Sonatrach-Agip), will provide green energy to the oil field, contributing to the d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: EPA refinery biofuel waiver program on hold pending review - sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biofuels-waivers-exclusive/exclusive-epa-refinery-biofuel-waiver-program-on-hold-pending-review-sources-idUSKCN1NX1D9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKWtRsRjmB7k276oSLwTElEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:41:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biofuels-waivers-exclusive/exclusive-epa-refinery-biofuel-waiver-program-on-hold-pending-review-sources-idUSKCN1NX1D9" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: EPA refinery biofuel waiver program on hold pending review - sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump Administration has temporarily frozen a program meant to exempt small oil refineries in financial distress from the U.S. biofuels law, as it reviews the scoring system to evaluate applications, according to two sources familiar with the matter. The review means changes are likely to the program, which has become a lightning rod of controversy between the rival oil and corn industries since the Environmental Protection Agency vastly increased the number of waivers for last year. Under the U.S. Renewable Fuel Standard, oil refiners must increasingly blend biofuels like corn-based et...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Government spending foreign aid money to promote fracking in China - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/fracking-china-foreign-aid-shale-gas-climate-change-environment-dfid-funding-promoting-a8637601.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL7Cb_67N-L5N4y2AaoWz-kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 23:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/fracking-china-foreign-aid-shale-gas-climate-change-environment-dfid-funding-promoting-a8637601.html" target="_blank"&gt;Government spending foreign aid money to promote fracking in China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taxpayers’ money earmarked to support overseas development has been spent on supporting China’s fracking industry, The Independent can reveal. The government is required to spend 0.7 per cent of its national income each year on foreign aid. But even with climate change threatening the developing world with droughts, flooding and heatwaves, millions have been spent on fossil fuel investment abroad over the past two years. This includes two schemes aiming to “export the UK’s expertise in shale gas regulation” to China, as controversy about new drilling sites rages back in Britain. - Read more...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Eni in talks to grow presence in the Gulf: source - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eni-gulf/eni-in-talks-to-grow-presence-in-the-gulf-source-idUSKCN1NZ226</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEII4NHzvgdD01FRsNDIF7rUqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:09:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eni-gulf/eni-in-talks-to-grow-presence-in-the-gulf-source-idUSKCN1NZ226" target="_blank"&gt;Eni in talks to grow presence in the Gulf: source&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Italian major Eni (ENI.MI: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) is in talks to grow its footprint in Oman and the United Arab Emirates as part of plans to build its asset base in the oil-rich Gulf and offset its reliance on Africa, a source close to the matter said. The international oil company has a limited presence in the Middle East, where some of the world's biggest oil and gas reserves lie, producing more than half its output in Africa. "Eni is in talks with Oman for various opportunities," the source told Reuters, adding recent geopolitical tensions in the area had not curbed its in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Looking Forward At US Energy Policy In 2019 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/daneberhart/2018/11/22/looking-forward-at-us-energy-policy-in-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDzmVO5Go1dKVWOw6P4UfF4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 05:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/daneberhart/2018/11/22/looking-forward-at-us-energy-policy-in-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;Looking Forward At US Energy Policy In 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this Aug. 6, 2017, file photo, demonstrators against the Keystone XL pipeline march in Lincoln, Neb. Opponents of the proposed oil pipeline from (AP Photo/Nati Harnik) As we gather with our families today and give thanks for the blessings of the past year, it is a good time to take stock of where energy policy and global oil markets are headed in 2019. With Democrats winning a majority in the House and the return of divided government, it’s unlikely that both chambers of Congress and the White House will agree on broad, far-reaching energy legislation during the 116th Congress. The new H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Yes, It Is Possible For Oil Prices To Be Too Low - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/daneberhart/2018/11/28/yes-it-is-possible-for-oil-prices-to-be-too-low/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJD7BJgafxFJU1Q59NrgnVcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/daneberhart/2018/11/28/yes-it-is-possible-for-oil-prices-to-be-too-low/" target="_blank"&gt;Yes, It Is Possible For Oil Prices To Be Too Low&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A pump jack works near Firestone, Colo. (AP Photo/David Zalubowski, File) How low does President Donald Trump want oil prices to go? It’s become a crucial question for global oil markets and the U.S. oil industry after the president cheered the recent plunge to $50 a barrel, the lowest level since 2015. Trump has taken credit for the 30% drop in prices over the past six weeks, referring to it as a “big tax cut” for Americans, and encouraged OPEC kingpin Saudi Arabia to push prices even lower. But it’s hardly a tax cut for the America’s oil producers, particularly oil service companies like ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>A slippery trade: oil slump proves bears right - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-markets-oilmajors-bears-graphic/a-slippery-trade-oil-slump-proves-bears-right-idUSKCN1NS1IU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPEW9P6FYk2RohyR6fnQp0gqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:03:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-markets-oilmajors-bears-graphic/a-slippery-trade-oil-slump-proves-bears-right-idUSKCN1NS1IU" target="_blank"&gt;A slippery trade: oil slump proves bears right&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest collapse in oil prices has proved some investors right in their lack of confidence in energy stocks this year. Crude prices surged to a four-year high early in 2018 as tensions with Iran and OPEC supply cuts raised concerns that global oil supply was dwindling. But the narrative has flipped since October as worries over a global trade war and rising U.S. shale oil production mounted, driving oil to a one-year low on Friday. Brent crude is down to $60 a barrel from a peak of $85 in early October. While oil majors have gone some way to cleaning up their balance sheets since the 201...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Massive 14-Year Oil Spill Ordered To Be Cleaned As Leaks Continue - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/oil-spill-ordered-to-be-cleaned_us_5bf557d5e4b0771fb6b47f5d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKfwmJlpNMSa5iKRH-osMFwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:48:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/oil-spill-ordered-to-be-cleaned_us_5bf557d5e4b0771fb6b47f5d" target="_blank"&gt;Massive 14-Year Oil Spill Ordered To Be Cleaned As Leaks Continue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A massive oil spill that’s feared to become the largest marine disaster of its kind in the nation’s history is receiving attention from the U.S. Coast Guard after steadily leaking off Louisiana’s coast for more than 14 years. The military branch has ordered Taylor Energy Company to “capture, contain or remove oil” from the toxic site located 13 miles from the mouth of Mississippi River or face a $40,000 per day fine, The Washington Post reported. Since the company’s oil platform was destroyed by Hurricane Ivan in 2004, the Justice Department estimates that it leaks up to 29,400 gallons, or ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Big Oil v the planet is the fight of our lives. Democrats must choose a side - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/15/climate-change-democrats-oil-gas</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPen_53r9QR8G33cWMqaL8YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 11:00:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/15/climate-change-democrats-oil-gas" target="_blank"&gt;Big Oil v the planet is the fight of our lives. Democrats must choose a side&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world’s leading scientists issued a report warning of total planetary dystopia unless we take immediate steps to seriously reduce carbon emissions. Then, oil and gas corporations dumped millions of dollars into the 2018 elections to defeat the major initiatives that could have slightly reduced fossil fuel use. Though you may not know it from the cable TV coverage, this was one of the most significant – and the most terrifying – stories of the midterms. For those who actually care about the survival of the human race, the key questions now should be obvious: is there any reason to hope t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Trump ramps up pressure on Saudi Arabia to lower oil prices - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2a2f1022-ed92-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC7fcrod-ZdV1EDind5DrGkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:58:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2a2f1022-ed92-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57" target="_blank"&gt;Trump ramps up pressure on Saudi Arabia to lower oil prices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US president Donald Trump praised Saudi Arabia for helping to reduce oil prices and ramped up pressure on the kingdom to maintain the decline, even as talks have gathered pace among producer nations to enact new production curbs. “Oil prices getting lower. Great! Like a big Tax Cut for America and the World,” Mr Trump tweeted on Wednesday, suggesting a recent drop in crude would help big consumer countries such as the US by lowering fuel prices. “Thank you to Saudi Arabia, but let’s go lower!,” he added. Energy sector analysts are questioning how the US’s show of support for the kingdom, as...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Oil rout sends US energy junk bond spreads to 15-month highs - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ea043acc-ed9b-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB-jfN7jmiUrMTlZrWBB3iYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 18:01:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ea043acc-ed9b-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57" target="_blank"&gt;Oil rout sends US energy junk bond spreads to 15-month highs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent slump in oil prices has pushed the risk premium investors demand to hold the debt of riskier US energy companies to its highest level in 15 months. Amid Wall Street’s energy sector-led sell-off on Tuesday, junk-rated borrowers in the oil and gas sector were paying 5.4 percentage points over investment grade US Treasuries, according to Bank of America Merrill Lynch data. That saw the spread — which gauges the difference in yield between corporate bonds and haven Treasuries of the same duration — match its highest level since August 21, 2017. Any higher takes it to the costliest le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>The romance of drilling for oil has peaked - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e633ea7a-f253-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEABVf2wPEAwA0lKUlOz_zk0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e633ea7a-f253-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;The romance of drilling for oil has peaked&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the price of crude oil goes through one of its periodic downturns, as it is doing now, it sends a shiver through the oil industry. History promises that higher prices will return. Until then, US shale companies are under severe pressure and big oil companies wonder about the viability of new projects. There is more to worry them this time: not just the 29 per cent fall in the price of Brent crude since the start of October as Russia and Saudi Arabia pump more oil, but the fear of this bear market enduring. The romance of oil exploration is fading at companies such as Royal Dutch Shell,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia pumps record amount of oil as Trump piles on pressure - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-crude-output/saudi-arabia-pumps-record-amount-of-oil-as-trump-piles-on-pressure-idUSKCN1NV12L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELIcaSdw2ATIHqX-lUvCXXAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 15:27:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-crude-output/saudi-arabia-pumps-record-amount-of-oil-as-trump-piles-on-pressure-idUSKCN1NV12L" target="_blank"&gt;Saudi Arabia pumps record amount of oil as Trump piles on pressure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia raised oil production to an all-time high in November, an industry source said on Monday, as U.S. President Donald Trump piled pressure on the kingdom to refrain from production cuts at an OPEC meeting next week. The meeting, at which OPEC members will consider how to arrest a decline in oil prices, comes days after leaders of top global oil producers - Russian President Vladimir Putin, Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman and Trump - travel to Argentina for a G20 summit this week. Saudi Arabia agreed to raise supply steeply in June, in response to calls from consumers, inclu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Egypt says U.S. oil firms showing appetite for offshore projects - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-egypt-energy/egypt-says-u-s-oil-firms-showing-appetite-for-offshore-projects-idUSKCN1NT0KY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPeomvxv9sZ2hWvk2g2Z5WoqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 14:30:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-egypt-energy/egypt-says-u-s-oil-firms-showing-appetite-for-offshore-projects-idUSKCN1NT0KY" target="_blank"&gt;Egypt says U.S. oil firms showing appetite for offshore projects&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Egypt sees increasing interest from U.S. energy companies in developing its offshore oil and natural gas resources and expects them to participate in two bidding rounds due before year-end, Petroleum Minister Tarek El Molla said. Egypt has emerged as an attractive destination for foreign energy firms following a string of major discoveries in recent years including the giant Zohr offshore field, which holds an estimated 30 trillion cubic feet of gas. Molla said Egypt wanted to become a regional trading gas hub now it had achieved its goal of self-sufficiency, but would focus on meeting its ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>'Greenwash': oil giant under fire over plan to protect tropical forests - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/nov/20/greenwash-oil-forests-norway-equinor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMpP-FgJtRy_30nl6yAw1CgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:19:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/nov/20/greenwash-oil-forests-norway-equinor" target="_blank"&gt;'Greenwash': oil giant under fire over plan to protect tropical forests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the world’s biggest oil companies is set to join the fight against deforestation in the tropics as part of its climate change efforts – but the the move has been branded a “greenwash” by campaigners. State-owned Norwegian firm Equinor has written to the UN’s climate chief to tell her it wants to invest in the protection of tropical forests. The letter, sent less than a fortnight before the UN climate summit in Poland, is the latest sign that big oil sees a major role in forestry as a way to preserve business models based on drilling for oil and gas for decades when scientists say the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Oil plunge could help US consumers, some emerging markets - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/1922976c9e2549cc9b23049eede69a41</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI49cfgoebZK3lpPQDUtHHMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:52:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/1922976c9e2549cc9b23049eede69a41" target="_blank"&gt;Oil plunge could help US consumers, some emerging markets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — Holiday shoppers should enjoy more spending power thanks to the recent sharp drop in oil prices, though cheaper energy could also weigh on the U.S. economy by dampening investment in shale oil production. While the fall in oil prices doesn't yet match the 2014-2016 slump to $26 per barrel, the current decline should soon make itself felt through the global economy. The international crude benchmark, Brent, has fallen under $65 per barrel from a four-year high in early October over $86, and U.S. crude has dropped below $55 a barrel. Retailers in the U.S., who depend...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Rosneft's Sechin flies to Venezuela, rebukes Maduro over oil shipments - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-venezuela-exclusive/exclusive-rosnefts-sechin-flies-to-venezuela-rebukes-maduro-over-oil-shipments-idUSKCN1NT0TJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIycINC3Kp75SqHISJBi4iQqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 19:44:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-venezuela-exclusive/exclusive-rosnefts-sechin-flies-to-venezuela-rebukes-maduro-over-oil-shipments-idUSKCN1NT0TJ" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Rosneft's Sechin flies to Venezuela, rebukes Maduro over oil shipments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The head of Russian oil company Rosneft (ROSN.MM: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), Igor Sechin, flew to Caracas this week to meet Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro and complain over delayed oil shipments designed to repay loans, two sources briefed on the conversation said on Saturday. The visit, which was not publicly disclosed, is one of the clearest signs of strain between crisis-stricken Venezuela and its key financier Russia. Over the last few years, Moscow has become Venezuela’s lender of last resort, with the Russian government and Rosneft handing Venezuela at least $17 billi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>'Not even the Chinese will bankroll it': Timor- Leste moves ahead with gas hub - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-22/timor-leste-buys-shells-greater-sunrise-oil-and-gas-stake/10534814</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO9joDAqIDwS69CbT3WTIZQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 05:17:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-22/timor-leste-buys-shells-greater-sunrise-oil-and-gas-stake/10534814" target="_blank"&gt;'Not even the Chinese will bankroll it': Timor- Leste moves ahead with gas hub&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Timor-Leste has bought Shell's stake in the rich Greater Sunrise oil and gas fields as it presses ahead with its contentious plan to pipe the natural resources to its south coast for processing. Key points: - Timor is spending millions to take control of oil and gas resources - It plans to build a pipeline to its coast, a new refinery, and an airport - Experts say project is doomed to fail It's another twist in a long saga as Timor-Leste, Australia, and energy companies tussle over how to exploit the reserves which are key to the small nation's economic future. Timor-Leste has pursued its v...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Russia’s Lukoil nearly doubles third-quarter profits - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b6917436-f30c-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC_yHXdtTZ5gamtRfsXuX4oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:05:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b6917436-f30c-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Russia’s Lukoil nearly doubles third-quarter profits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lukoil, Russia’s second-largest oil producer, has reported an 89 per cent leap in third-quarter net profit citing rising sales, higher oil and gas prices and a weaker rouble. Lukoil’s profit compared to the year ago period rise came amid a nearly 5 per cent increase in hydrocarbons production on the year, at prices approaching four-year highs in the third quarter, which together with the depreciation of the national currency contributed to a 55 per cent increase in the company’s rouble-based sales. Oil prices rising through the quarter to close to four-year highs, coupled with the rouble sl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Oil And Gas Industry Gradually Getting Comfortable With Storing Data Off Premise - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gauravsharma/2018/11/16/oil-and-gas-industry-gradually-getting-comfortable-with-storing-data-off-premise/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBni-eDDvBV7p4NS0xhFjXsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gauravsharma/2018/11/16/oil-and-gas-industry-gradually-getting-comfortable-with-storing-data-off-premise/" target="_blank"&gt;Oil And Gas Industry Gradually Getting Comfortable With Storing Data Off Premise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As cloud computing proliferates and digitization becomes the norm in the oil and gas sector, anxieties over cybersecurity that turned off industry players from allowing their data to be stored off site, are gradually easing, according to a senior industry executive. Nathalie Marcotte, Senior Vice President, Industry Services &amp; Cybersecurity at Schneider Electric, believes acceptance of the need and benefits of storing large volumes of data off site versus on premise, has risen exponentially in the last five years. Speaking to your correspondent, at the global management and automation compa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Venezuela rejected BP bid to buy Total's stake in gas block - sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-total-bp-exclusive-idUSKCN1NV2B9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO_xvKi2HNmDu_EzNjvhkS4qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 18:13:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-total-bp-exclusive-idUSKCN1NV2B9" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Venezuela rejected BP bid to buy Total's stake in gas block - sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Venezuela's oil ministry last month turned down a proposal by BP (BP.L: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) to buy Total's (TOTF.PA: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) stake in a promising but inactive natural gas project along the maritime border with Trinidad and Tobago, five people briefed on the matter said. BP owns the rights to the Trinidadian side of the gas play. It could have used the output from the neighboring area, the Deltana Platform's fourth block off Venezuela's eastern coast, to feed its growing operations on the island, said the people, who were not authorized to spea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Syria Refineries Raise Health Concerns - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/syria-makeshift-oil-refineries-health-environmental-concerns/4675321.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECrSCwV6nCzK74aoIovM8NEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 01:05:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/syria-makeshift-oil-refineries-health-environmental-concerns/4675321.html" target="_blank"&gt;Syria Refineries Raise Health Concerns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Syria's 7-year civil war has had an impact on nearly all aspects of life in the country, it also has provided many Syrians working in the oil sector with new job opportunities. In the northeastern corner of Syria, the large oil fields have one common theme: makeshift oil refineries. The refining process involves an ad hoc oil burner and large containers with crude oil. But many locals complain that such primitive ways to produce and refine oil are leaving a major impact on their health and the environment they live in. Oil workers recognize the risks that come with their profession, b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Russian oil groups hit sweet spot as profits surge - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/622e933a-e76b-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILV2oLUKZt85-OE0_zUTZ4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:01:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/622e933a-e76b-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3" target="_blank"&gt;Russian oil groups hit sweet spot as profits surge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian oil companies have rarely had it so good. Rising oil prices coupled with a weakening rouble have sent profits for exporters surging above forecasts. Some companies have already made investment decisions to capitalise on high earnings, but the moves came just as the oil price started to slide. It has dropped about $20 a barrel since its four-year peak of $86 in early October. The joy for the oil groups, therefore, may be shortlived. However, the weakness of the rouble, which plunged to a two-year low in September, is still propping up earnings for groups as they repatriate foreign cu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>President Trump's Blind Spot On Oil Prices - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/rrapier/2018/11/22/president-trumps-blind-spot-on-oil-prices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKx7B14a-GfcW7EfAzvYYKEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/rrapier/2018/11/22/president-trumps-blind-spot-on-oil-prices/" target="_blank"&gt;President Trump's Blind Spot On Oil Prices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S President Donald Trump speaks to members of the media before boarding Marine One on the South Lawn of the White House in Washington, D.C., U.S., on Tuesday, Nov. 20, 2018. Trump said he wouldn’t let the murder of U.S-based columnist Jamal Khashoggi jeopardize U.S. relations with Saudi Arabia, citing the potential impact on oil prices and Iranian influence in the Middle East. Photographer: Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg President Trump recently took credit for the plunge in oil prices since early October. As I noted in a recent article, it’s true that the President’s actions have contributed to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Uncertainty weighs on Nigerian crude projects - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/3d785448-c71f-11e8-86e6-19f5b7134d1c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFw4T1x2JSnhx3ldn4iMyT8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 03:00:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3d785448-c71f-11e8-86e6-19f5b7134d1c" target="_blank"&gt;Uncertainty weighs on Nigerian crude projects&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the end of this year, Nigeria’s oil production could jump by 200,000 barrels a day — about a 10th — if the offshore Egina project, led by French oil major Total, comes online as planned. It is a huge undertaking, coming at a crucial time for Africa’s largest crude producer as its economy recovers from a recession brought on by the 2014 oil price crash. But it is the first project of its size and scope in several years. Analysts say an opaque and archaic system of regulations is a major reason for the lack of investment in the country’s oil sector, the backbone of its economy. The sector ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Of the two big shifts in the energy market, one is a surprise - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/fbc69d7c-ebde-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF6yB6Bukyze-1Hvsd5kQVIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/fbc69d7c-ebde-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Of the two big shifts in the energy market, one is a surprise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key driver of change in the global market is not climate change or the political chaos affecting oil producers in the Middle East and elsewhere, or the fall in the cost of renewables. All those things matter, of course, but their impact is minimal compared with the shift in the geography of supply and demand that has transformed the market in the last decade and will continue to do so. That is the most interesting message from the new edition of the International Energy Agency’s annual World Energy Outlook published last week. To understand what has been happening it is instructive to c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Falling oil prices put new pressure on US energy sector - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/155224be-f0f3-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKWqna0MqfwH_IBuYsb5NlEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 04:00:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/155224be-f0f3-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Falling oil prices put new pressure on US energy sector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Throughout the US shale oil and gas boom of the past 15 years, one of investors’ greatest concerns has been that the exploration and production companies needed continual infusions of cash to finance their investment programmes. After the rise in crude prices this year, it looked as though those fears could be put to rest: in the third quarter of this year the US E&amp;P sector was able to cover its capital spending from its operating cash flows, if only barely. The plunge in oil prices over the past two months is bringing those concerns gushing to the surface again. In the third quarter, a sam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>