<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Education minister - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRFZ0ZVRFMWRCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:26:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Education Minister did not verbally abuse CETAG members - Graphic Online</title><link>https://www.graphic.com.gh/news/politics/ghana-news-education-minister-did-not-verbally-abuse-cetag-members.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMicGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdyYXBoaWMuY29tLmdoL25ld3MvcG9saXRpY3MvZ2hhbmEtbmV3cy1lZHVjYXRpb24tbWluaXN0ZXItZGlkLW5vdC12ZXJiYWxseS1hYnVzZS1jZXRhZy1tZW1iZXJzLmh0bWzSAQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:23:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.graphic.com.gh/news/politics/ghana-news-education-minister-did-not-verbally-abuse-cetag-members.html" target="_blank"&gt;Education Minister did not verbally abuse CETAG members&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Graphic Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Minister of Education, Dr. Mathew Opoku Prempeh, never met with the leadership of the Colleges of Education Teachers Association of Ghana (CETAG) ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.graphic.com.gh">Graphic Online</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/-rMhYBxjl0h5GdMkpXggCdFo9rFJ873Gl59W7sWXHgtV7pcHMpEJRjJ1dxz94PRm_DvDByR1DfNNH3FeFEEhgixqDO8d8W4govFlDVkCuTbGEO6jY9rpqpda6d8zdxw7PtFrYxlhbo3zlCm09Q=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Israeli education minister vows not to resign in reprieve for Netanyahu - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/19/israeli-education-minister-naftali-bennett-vows-not-to-resign-in-reprieve-for-netanyahu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKTTTzfGZn1CVyGB7M5AercqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:15:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/19/israeli-education-minister-naftali-bennett-vows-not-to-resign-in-reprieve-for-netanyahu" target="_blank"&gt;Israeli education minister vows not to resign in reprieve for Netanyahu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benjamin Netanyahu has won a reprieve from the threat of early elections in Israel after a senior member of his cabinet announced he would not resign and break up the coalition government. Naftali Bennett, the hardliner education minister, was widely expected to quit during a press conference on Monday morning but instead said in a surprise announcement that his Jewish Home party would give the prime minister another chance. Related: Israeli defence chief Avigdor Lieberman quits over Gaza truce Bennett, a security hawk, had considered following Netanyahu’s defence minister, Avigdor Lieberma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Commonwealth warned of fraudulent family day care claims, FOI documents show - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-03/commonwealth-warned-of-fraudulent-family-day-care-claims-foi/8411050</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGntWWWE1MYximNHXmhgeP4qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 08:13:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-03/commonwealth-warned-of-fraudulent-family-day-care-claims-foi/8411050" target="_blank"&gt;Commonwealth warned of fraudulent family day care claims, FOI documents show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New South Wales Education Department has been warning the Federal Government about "fraudulent and criminal behaviour" in the family day care (FDC) system for years, confidential documents show. Key points: - NSW Education Department warned Federal Government about family day care fraud for years - Amount of family day care centres in NSW grew 300 per cent between 2012 and 2016 - Federal Education Minister Simon Birmingham says Government is cracking down on fraud Departmental staff noted in August last year that despite the evidence and their concerns, the Commonwealth continued to "pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Peru's Kuczynski swears in new Cabinet, opposition signals support - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-peru-politics/perus-kuczynski-forms-cabinet-aims-to-placate-congress-sources-idUSKCN1BS0PA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGPMakoSnzdk72B6AkqBfQMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:28:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-peru-politics/perus-kuczynski-forms-cabinet-aims-to-placate-congress-sources-idUSKCN1BS0PA" target="_blank"&gt;Peru's Kuczynski swears in new Cabinet, opposition signals support&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Marco Aquino and Teresa Cespedes LIMA (Reuters) - Peruvian President Pedro Pablo Kuczynski made Vice President Mercedes Araoz his new prime minister in a Cabinet shuffle on Sunday that won praise from the opposition - a sign his year-old government will likely avoid a fresh standoff with Congress. Kuczynski also swore in Deputy Economy Minister Claudia Cooper as his new finance minister and replaced his justice, education, health and housing ministers. The new, more socially conservative Cabinet sparked criticism from Kuczynski's centrist and leftist supporters that he had caved into the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China admits political education for students is poor - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-parliament-education-idUSKBN16J07P</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJukDiINTgGDEKoZzw8au94qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 08:17:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-parliament-education-idUSKBN16J07P" target="_blank"&gt;China admits political education for students is poor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (Reuters) - China is doing a poor job at political education for university students because the classes are outdated and unfashionable, the education minister said on Sunday in a rare admission of the difficulties faced enforcing a key government policy. Beijing has campaigned against the spread of "Western values" at universities, and the ruling Communist Party's anti-corruption watchdog last year sent inspectors to monitor teachers for "improper" remarks in class. In December, President Xi Jinping called for allegiance to the party from colleges and universities, the latest effor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Commonwealth, states still at loggerheads over school funding - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-05-18/commonwealth-and-states-still-at-loggerheads-over-school-funding/8538496</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENjb099juvKvEnjjdVhDmZAqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 06:28:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-05-18/commonwealth-and-states-still-at-loggerheads-over-school-funding/8538496" target="_blank"&gt;Commonwealth, states still at loggerheads over school funding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;State and Territory Education ministers have accused the Federal Government of cutting them out of the decision making over school funding. Key points: - Senator Birmingham met with state education ministers to discuss a nationally consistent funding model - SA's Susan Close says "there was insufficient detail to make any decisions" from the meeting - Senator Birmingham maintains the Government's funding model is fair The ministers met their federal counterpart Simon Birmingham in Adelaide today to discuss the Commonwealth's new plan for a nationally-consistent funding model. The Commonweal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Turkey's new curriculum ditches Darwin, will teach jihad as ‘loving your nation’ - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/396714-turkey-curriculum-jihad-evolution/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDHc0cBICjnJOhyeBUnsLbMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 17:20:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/396714-turkey-curriculum-jihad-evolution/" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey's new curriculum ditches Darwin, will teach jihad as ‘loving your nation’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey's education minister has announced details of the country's new curriculum, stating that it will include the concept of jihad as being patriotic, rather than a "holy war." It will also lack any reference to Darwin's theory of evolution. “Jihad is an element in our religion; it is in our religion…the duty of the Education Ministry is to teach every concept deservedly, in a correct way. It is also our job to correct things that are wrongly perceived, seen or taught,” Education Minister Ismet Yilmaz said during a Tuesday press conference, as quoted by Hurriyet. "The real meaning of jiha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Japan ministry finds documents that may show PM link to school scandal - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-politics-scandal-idUSKBN19616B</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHh3_ytSVGKLkQQ6tNFT9wUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 10:33:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-politics-scandal-idUSKBN19616B" target="_blank"&gt;Japan ministry finds documents that may show PM link to school scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TOKYO (Reuters) - Japan's education ministry on Thursday it had found documents that could back up opposition parties' suspicion that Prime Minister Shinzo Abe used his influence to unfairly help a friend set up a business. Abe has repeatedly denied abusing his authority to benefit his friend and his grip on power is not in danger. But the affair has chipped away at Abe's support, according to opinion polls, and it looks unlikely to fade away. "I am taking this result seriously," Education Minister Hirokazu Matsuno told a news conference, referring to the unearthing of the documents during ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>‘Fired, you are’: Saudi official sacked over image of Yoda near King Faisal in textbook - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/404680-saudi-fired-yoda-textbook/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELigH0S71QQR8mBYfK0B-c8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 17:13:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/404680-saudi-fired-yoda-textbook/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Fired, you are’: Saudi official sacked over image of Yoda near King Faisal in textbook&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An image of the iconic Star Wars character, Yoda, which made it inside a textbook in Saudi Arabia, has led to the dismissal of a senior education official and the supervisors who approved the material. On Tuesday, several Saudi outlets, including Okaz and al-Madinah Arabic daily papers, reported that the education minister had fired the undersecretary of the Curriculum and Educational Programs Department, Mohammed bin Attiyah al-Harthi, as well as other officials who oversaw the review and approval of the textbooks. The move was prompted not only by the Yoda flop, but also other errors foun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Germany probes abuse of fatally injured Egyptian woman after car accident - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-egypt-crime-idUSKBN17T2WB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDc4d_Ft31Z1NUiFuzQB8WAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 19:22:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-egypt-crime-idUSKBN17T2WB" target="_blank"&gt;Germany probes abuse of fatally injured Egyptian woman after car accident&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BERLIN (Reuters) - Prosecutors investigating the driver of a car that ran over and fatally injured an Egyptian woman in eastern Germany say they are also now pursuing a man who witnesses say hurled racial abuse at the victim after the accident.The 22-year-old student, identified only as Shaden M., died in hospital on April 18, three days after the accident in the city of Cottbus, and the driver is being investigated for possibly causing death by negligence, Horst Nothbaum, spokesman for the prosecutor's office, said. Two witnesses came forward 10 days after the accident to say that they had...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Netanyahu takes on defense post amid call for early polls - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/5196c9cc03de4c03bf1e6c3f8d71a11b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDT2QEQk7jZzxbTGRCXWJpIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 19:00:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/5196c9cc03de4c03bf1e6c3f8d71a11b" target="_blank"&gt;Netanyahu takes on defense post amid call for early polls&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said Sunday he would take on the defense minister portfolio, rejecting calls to dissolve his government even as early elections appeared increasingly likely. Netanyahu said heading to elections now, amid repeated violent confrontations with Gaza militants, was "irresponsible" of his coalition partners, who have been pushing for early polls since the resignation last week of Defense Minister Avigdor Lieberman over a Gaza cease-fire. "Today, I take on for the first time the position of defense minister," said Netanyahu, speakin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Netanyahu heads into cabinet showdown as allies demand early Israeli elections - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/17/netanyahu-heads-cabinet-showdown-allies-demand-early-israeli/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBIDNN16xkZfiWDU0cS9T4MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 17:48:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/17/netanyahu-heads-cabinet-showdown-allies-demand-early-israeli/" target="_blank"&gt;Netanyahu heads into cabinet showdown as allies demand early Israeli elections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benjamin Netanyahu faces a showdown with his coalition government partners on Sunday as he tries to stop them from forcing early elections in the wake of his unpopular decision to agree to a ceasefire with Hamas. Three of the smaller parties in the Israeli prime minister’s coalition have demanded elections as soon as possible and want to use today’s cabinet meeting to formally agree on a date for the vote. However, Mr Netanyahu said he wants to keep the government together and is eager to push the date of the elections off for several more months. “Prime Minister Netanyahu stressed that it ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>UK lawmaker, aide to education ministers, resigns from role over Brexit - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu-trevelyan/uk-lawmaker-aide-to-education-ministers-resigns-from-role-over-brexit-idUSKCN1NK1AH?il=0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOli6OKNTNJXMyP5GdzaBcMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 10:32:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu-trevelyan/uk-lawmaker-aide-to-education-ministers-resigns-from-role-over-brexit-idUSKCN1NK1AH?il=0" target="_blank"&gt;UK lawmaker, aide to education ministers, resigns from role over Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lawmaker in British Prime Minister Theresa May's Conservative Party, Anne-Marie Trevelyan, resigned on Thursday from her position as an aide to education ministers, citing concerns over the government's Brexit deal. (Reporting by William James. Editing by Andrew MacAskill)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Israel heading for early elections after turbulent week for Netanyahu - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/middleeast/israel-elections-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBEWmv40_k-9b8GAt8OU-lMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 15:57:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/16/middleeast/israel-elections-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Israel heading for early elections after turbulent week for Netanyahu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel will pick a date for early elections on Sunday, a source close to a key minister told CNN, following a turbulent week for Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu that saw key government resignations and calls for an early vote. The decision to call early elections came after crunch talks between Netanyahu and the rightwing Education Minister Naftali Bennett broke down on Friday. Bennett had threatened to quit the government if he wasn't given the defense portfolio after the resignation of former Defense Minister Avigdor Liberman on Wednesday, but Netanyahu rejected Bennett's demands. After...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Israel set for early elections after cabinet breaks up, source says - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/16/israel-set-for-early-elections-after-cabinet-breaks-up-source-says</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKhqdsZJ2lBz_e49isS0k_UqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 13:51:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/16/israel-set-for-early-elections-after-cabinet-breaks-up-source-says" target="_blank"&gt;Israel set for early elections after cabinet breaks up, source says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel is due to hold elections early next year after the prime minister, Benjamin Netanyahu, lost his defence minister and talks broke down in his coalition government on Friday, a source close to the cabinet told the Guardian. Netanyahu had met the education minister, Naftali Bennett, who wanted the defence ministry post in the rightwing government, but the meeting ended with a decision by cabinet members to hold national polls, which were previously due in November 2019. During a frantic few hours, ministers rushed to make media statements before the country shut down for the Friday nigh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Hamas abides by cease-fire, restrains protests - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/0d5a369f97fa4070abab487cf720465e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE85qTFpW5RJDkJLLeTzdagqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:52:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/0d5a369f97fa4070abab487cf720465e" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Hamas abides by cease-fire, restrains protests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — The Latest on the political developments in Israel (all times local): 5:35 p.m. Gaza's Hamas rulers are sticking to cease-fire with Israel by keeping border protests widely restrained. Thousands of Palestinians participated Friday in a Hamas-organized rally along the perimeter fence dividing Gaza from Israel, with crowds staying at least 300 meters from the fence. However, Gaza's health ministry said 40 Palestinians were wounded by Israeli fire and tear gas, without giving a number breakdown. Witnesses said most of the injuries occurred in stone-throwing incidents at the us...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>First state signs up to national schools funding agreement - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-05/school-funding-agreement-sa-first-state-to-sign-up-to-deal/10464122</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGFdFQnd2LznD-s8eLsnDI8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 18:34:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-05/school-funding-agreement-sa-first-state-to-sign-up-to-deal/10464122" target="_blank"&gt;First state signs up to national schools funding agreement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Australia has become the first state to sign up to the Federal Government's new national agreement for schools funding. Key points: - The Commonwealth has been locked in a dispute with the states over the funding deal - Education Minister Dan Tehan hopes other states will follow SA in accepting the deal - The Government had been close to signing deals with the states before it announced it would pour billions into the private-school sector The Commonwealth has been locked in a dispute with the states over the deal, with several states complaining not enough money would go towards publ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>'Bad idea': Nobel Prize winner criticises national interest test on research funding - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-31/nobel-prize-winner-criticises-research-funding-overhaul/10450504</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOah30Bf-Gi6QhnstPUd-TUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 23:13:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-31/nobel-prize-winner-criticises-research-funding-overhaul/10450504" target="_blank"&gt;'Bad idea': Nobel Prize winner criticises national interest test on research funding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Nobel Prize winner has criticised the Federal Government's overhaul of university research grants, describing it as "a bad idea". Education Minister Dan Tehan said there needed to be transparency about how taxpayer money was spent, and for researchers to pass "a national interest test" before getting Government funds. That has prompted the Federal Opposition to accuse the Coalition of interfering in academic freedom. Mr Tehan's intervention comes after revelations his predecessor, Simon Birmingham, blocked funding for 11 research projects that had already been approved by the independent ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Correction: Spain-Politics story - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/b7a17d5121654bda8e504e195dfd351f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL96RcmwYXOmiu3CnzzLzH8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 10:21:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/b7a17d5121654bda8e504e195dfd351f" target="_blank"&gt;Correction: Spain-Politics story&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADRID (AP) — In a story on June 6 about the new Spanish Cabinet, The Associated Press reported erroneously that the number of male ministers in the new administration was five, instead of six. A corrected version of the story is below: Majority of women in charge of new Spanish government A women-dominated cabinet, the first in Spain's history, is taking shape as part of the new Socialist government, which has chosen a former astronaut as science minister and a European Union bureaucrat to oversee the country's economy By ARITZ PARRA Associated Press MADRID (AP) — Spain's new Socialist gov...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Japan’s education minister apologises for using ministry car to visit 'sexy yoga' studio - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/04/25/japans-education-minister-apologises-using-ministry-car-visit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECgtrw7rvOZt_d8h0sjK0AsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:40:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/04/25/japans-education-minister-apologises-using-ministry-car-visit/" target="_blank"&gt;Japan’s education minister apologises for using ministry car to visit 'sexy yoga' studio&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan’s education minister has been accused of using an official ministry car to attend a “sexy yoga” studio, the latest in a string of scandals to hit the government. Yoshimasa Hayashi, 57, a veteran politician and minister of education, culture, sports, science and technology, reportedly spent two hours at the Tokyo studio, according to the weekly magazine Shukan Bunshan. The publication said the studio’s female staff, many former hostesses, offered customers private yoga classes followed by oil massages and was run by a woman who was a former porn actress - claims which she later denied....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>NAPLAN testing faces scrutiny as education ministers push for changes - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-02-15/naplan-testing-faces-scrutiny-and-push-for-changes/9446842</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOXN56_cha77WDOSKtd-jU4qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 19:07:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-02-15/naplan-testing-faces-scrutiny-and-push-for-changes/9446842" target="_blank"&gt;NAPLAN testing faces scrutiny as education ministers push for changes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the nation's education ministers have united to push for changes to the controversial testing system in schools known as NAPLAN. Key points: - NSW Education Minister believes NAPLAN has become "major event" in school calendar - SA minister Susan Close says time to have another look at NAPLAN - Federal minister indicated he was not open to any significant changes They believe the testing has strayed from its original purpose of helping teachers improve student learning to become a "major event" in the school calendar. NSW Education Minister Rob Stokes does not believe NAPLAN is funct...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>France to impose total ban on mobile phones in schools - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/12/11/france-impose-total-ban-mobile-phones-schools/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED8PM4r-Gjt_ljJA9WpA0jUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 16:01:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/12/11/france-impose-total-ban-mobile-phones-schools/" target="_blank"&gt;France to impose total ban on mobile phones in schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France is to impose a total ban on pupils using mobile phones in primary and secondary schools starting in September 2018, its education minister has confirmed. Phones are already forbidden in French classrooms but starting next school year, pupils will be barred from taking them out at breaks, lunch times and between lessons. Teachers and parents are divided over a total ban, however, with some saying children must be able to "live in their time". In France, some 93 per cent of 12 to 17-year-olds own mobile phones. "These days the children don't play at break time anymore, they are just al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Pro-Christian lawmaker seeks ban on Halloween celebration in Russian schools - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/politics/407188-pro-christian-lawmaker-seeks-ban/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHnZxNlEzCnquzlaQLHF50MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwnoQo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 12:17:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/politics/407188-pro-christian-lawmaker-seeks-ban/" target="_blank"&gt;Pro-Christian lawmaker seeks ban on Halloween celebration in Russian schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Russian Lower House MP known for his pro-Christian and anti-gay stance has proposed an official ban on Halloween celebrations in schools and kindergartens. Vitaly Milonov addressed the proposal to the Education Ministry. In his letter to Education Minister Olga Vasilyeva, Milonov wrote that in his view celebrations of Halloween by kids were unacceptable “both from the point of view of studying and upbringing and the position of spirituality and morals.” He also wrote that the necessity to shield children from the “decaying and negative influence of Halloween” was long overdue. He conclud...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item></channel></rss>