<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Stunted growth - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRGxuTlRSaUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:11:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>One-third of world's stunted children live in India: Report - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/world-stunted-children-live-india-report-181128191651345.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENkLCNytnHQL8HlhoZjUFVoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 03:10:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/world-stunted-children-live-india-report-181128191651345.html" target="_blank"&gt;One-third of world's stunted children live in India: Report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A major study published on Thursday warned of a malnutrition crisis in almost every country in the world with India holding about one-third of the world's burden for stunting. Forty-six million children in India are stunted because of malnutrition and 25.5 million more are defined as "wasted" - meaning they do not weigh enough for their height, according to the Global Nutrition Report 2018. Worldwide, 150.8 million children are stunted and 50.5 million are "wasted", the report said. "The uncomfortable question is not so much 'why are things so bad?' but 'why are things not better when we kn...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>'Diabolical' diets: four in 10 children consume sugary drinks every day - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/nov/29/diabolical-diets-four-in-10-children-consume-sugary-drinks-every-day</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDiYLPLLOtThQUiaKmr4BNkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 06:00:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/nov/29/diabolical-diets-four-in-10-children-consume-sugary-drinks-every-day" target="_blank"&gt;'Diabolical' diets: four in 10 children consume sugary drinks every day&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than four in 10 children drink sugary drinks every day and one in three never eat fruit every day, according to a global report that warns most countries are unlikely to meet nutrition targets. Researchers warn the standard of diets around the world is “diabolical”, and that problems such as obesity, anaemia and micronutrient deficiency are being neglected. While progress has been made in tackling child stunting, the report provides the most comprehensive picture of diets globally to date, analysing statistics on exclusive breastfeeding, dietary diversity and the consumption of sugary ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Mothers' nutrition pivotal for healthy child growth: study - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-stunting-mothers-idUSKBN12X01K</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG0rV482JUtPVu6BvI27LYwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 00:30:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-stunting-mothers-idUSKBN12X01K" target="_blank"&gt;Mothers' nutrition pivotal for healthy child growth: study&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Umberto Bacchi LONDON (Thomson Reuters Foundation) - Improving mothers' nutrition before and during pregnancy is pivotal to reducing child stunting in developing countries, researchers said on Tuesday, as a new study showed poor child growth often starts in the womb. Defined as low height-for-age, stunting affects one in three children in the developing world and carries severe, irreversible consequences for both physical health and cognitive function. An analysis of data from 137 developing nations by a team of Harvard scientists found the leading cause of stunting is fetal growth restr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>World Hunger Swells as Conflict, Climate Change Grow - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/world-hunger-swella-as-conflict-climate-change-grow/4031744.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIolqAqlAIdf1m3gO6nR7N4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 14:55:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/world-hunger-swella-as-conflict-climate-change-grow/4031744.html" target="_blank"&gt;World Hunger Swells as Conflict, Climate Change Grow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations reports world hunger is rising because conflicts and problems related to climate change are multiplying. The report finds about 815 million people globally did not have enough to eat in 2016 — 38 million more than the previous year. The statistics in this report are particularly grim. They show that global hunger is on the rise again after more than a decade of steady decline. The report, a joint product by five leading U.N. agencies warns that malnutrition is threatening the health of and compromising the future of millions of people world-wide. The report says 155 milli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>How iCow Is Helping Kids In Africa Avoid Life-Damaging Nutritional Stunting - Forbes Now</title><link>//www.forbes.com/sites/tobyshapshak/2017/08/28/how-icow-is-helping-kids-in-africa-avoid-life-damaging-nutritional-stunting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPHwNr251oAoSjXnj3fUyvUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="//www.forbes.com/sites/tobyshapshak/2017/08/28/how-icow-is-helping-kids-in-africa-avoid-life-damaging-nutritional-stunting/" target="_blank"&gt;How iCow Is Helping Kids In Africa Avoid Life-Damaging Nutritional Stunting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;iCow uses simple SMS to upskill African farmers. Nearly 60-million children in Africa suffer from nutritional stunting caused by lack of access to proper nutrition. This key health epidemic is one of the things Kenyan start-up iCow hopes to help solve by upskilling animal farmers in East Africa using simple SMS messages. “59-million children struggle to reach their potential, their genetic potential, because they don’t get enough protein when they are growing up,” iCow founder Su Kahumbu Stephanou told TED Global in Arusha, Tanzania. Growing children need a range of essential amino acids to...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Could Big Data Help End Hunger in Africa? - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3877562.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBmTVc40eCPQeo-T7oxtFL8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwip0i</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:28:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3877562.html" target="_blank"&gt;Could Big Data Help End Hunger in Africa?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Computer algorithms power much of modern life from our Facebook feeds to international stock exchanges. Could they help end malnutrition and hunger in Africa? The International Center for Tropical Agriculture thinks so. The International Center for Tropical Agriculture has spent the past four years developing the Nutrition Early Warning System, or NEWS. The goal is to catch the subtle signs of a hunger crisis brewing in Africa as much as a year in advance. CIAT says the system uses machine learning. As more information is fed into the system, the algorithms will get better at identifying pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Dangerous levels of arsenic found in baby food could stunt growth - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/05/04/dangerous-levels-arsenic-found-baby-food-could-stunt-growth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI21tXqG4rDdXjRYQjzp7kMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 19:21:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/05/04/dangerous-levels-arsenic-found-baby-food-could-stunt-growth/" target="_blank"&gt;Dangerous levels of arsenic found in baby food could stunt growth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around half of baby rice sold in major UK supermarkets contains illegal levels of inorganic arsenic which could stunt children's growth and intelligence, a study has found. Despite new stricter rules on how much arsenic children's food can contain being introduced in January, researchers from Queen’s University Belfast found levels had actually risen. Babies are particularly vulnerable to the damaging effects of arsenic that can prevent the healthy development of a baby’s growth, IQ and immune systemProfessor Andy Meharg Some 50 per cent of baby rice food products contains an illegal level ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Bangladesh falls short in tackling childhood stunting - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-bangladesh-health-stunting-idUSKBN14V02Q</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIAb5nqUdqiZFIPpQn4189YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 01:03:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-bangladesh-health-stunting-idUSKBN14V02Q" target="_blank"&gt;Bangladesh falls short in tackling childhood stunting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By AZM Anas DHAKA (Thomson Reuters Foundation) - Scampering up the wall of his tin shack in Bangladesh's capital, three-year-old Rozzob Ali has the same combination of mischief, charm and boisterous energy as many other boys. But the fourth of five children, all born in a Dhaka slum, Ali shows one danger sign - at 80 centimeters tall, he is a good 10 cms shorter than the ideal height for a boy his age. Poverty and a diet of mostly boiled rice or mashed potato are partly to blame for his stunting, which is caused by a lack of nutrients, protein, vitamins and minerals found in meat, fruit and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Child malnutrition at ‘all-time high’ in Yemen, UNICEF claims in alarming report - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/370288-yemen-children-malnutrition-unicef/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSHRI0OtkdN7yvf7XUJ7ZEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 15:32:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/370288-yemen-children-malnutrition-unicef/" target="_blank"&gt;Child malnutrition at ‘all-time high’ in Yemen, UNICEF claims in alarming report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly 2.2 million Yemeni children are in need of urgent aid, as malnutrition is at an “all-time high,” a UNICEF report claims. The figures represent a 200 percent increase from 2014, with severe acute malnutrition affecting 462,000 children. Physically severe acute malnutrition (SAM) is manifested in grotesquely slim bodies and stunted growth, as is the case in Sa’ada governorate in the northwest, which has the world’s highest stunting rates, according to Monday’s document – eight out of 10 children. It is joined by four other governorates, all experiencing alarming rates of SAM. Another 1...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>The first 1,000 days: Jay Rayner explains their impact on a child's future – video - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/video/2017/sep/06/the-first-1000-days-jay-rayner-explains-their-impact-childs-future-first-fight-nutrition-healthcare-sanitation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENPaLNKPVALT81Fdgo_jtoMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 07:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/video/2017/sep/06/the-first-1000-days-jay-rayner-explains-their-impact-childs-future-first-fight-nutrition-healthcare-sanitation" target="_blank"&gt;The first 1,000 days: Jay Rayner explains their impact on a child's future – video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good nutrition, healthcare and sanitation are crucial to a child's early development. Without these, a child's brain won't develop properly. They will have a lower IQ and they will grow up shorter than they should, a condition known as stunting. The Observer's food critic, Jay Rayner, explains how a child's future is determined by the first years of life&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UN: Conditions in Afghanistan Deteriorating, Kids at Great Risk - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/afghanistan-humanitarian-situation-children/3775810.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPyw7bNM1naHHG5DGt8WfScqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 19:11:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/afghanistan-humanitarian-situation-children/3775810.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN: Conditions in Afghanistan Deteriorating, Kids at Great Risk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations reports humanitarian conditions in Afghanistan are deteriorating, with children at great risk of dying at an early age from lack of health care and proper nutrition. The United Nations reports 9.3 million people in Afghanistan will need humanitarian assistance this year. The world body has appealed for $550 million to support 5.6 million of the most vulnerable people. U.N. Office of the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs spokesman Jens Laerke says this is nearly one third of the Afghan population and 13 percent more than the number of U.N. beneficiaries in 2016. “We ex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Animal-sourced foods vital to combating malnutrition and stunting in the developing world - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/animal-sourced-foods-vital-combating-malnutrition-stunting-developing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELNa90j8HkxJCIyXrtZkepMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:41:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/animal-sourced-foods-vital-combating-malnutrition-stunting-developing/" target="_blank"&gt;Animal-sourced foods vital to combating malnutrition and stunting in the developing world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When poorly nourished children in developing countries fall behind in their physical growth and become stunted relative to their healthier peers, they tend to fall behind in a lot of other things too: their health, cognitive development, schooling, and eventually, their productivity and income as adults. The high social and economic costs mean that there are high returns to preventing stunting, provided these actions happen early. In poor countries most growth faltering takes place from six months of age until a child’s second birthday. This crucial turning point isn’t random: at roughly si...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>UN finds 486 million in Asia still hungry, progress stalled - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/b380a7d36ac04bbb8f1fff01478e6447</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIxXADSAAztk3bq5G_x7qOgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 04:01:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/b380a7d36ac04bbb8f1fff01478e6447" target="_blank"&gt;UN finds 486 million in Asia still hungry, progress stalled&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Despite rapid economic growth, the Asia-Pacific region has nearly a half billion people who go hungry as progress stalls in improving food security and basic living conditions, a United Nations report said Friday. Even in relatively well-to-do cities like Bangkok and the Malaysian capital Kuala Lumpur, poor families cannot afford enough good food for their children, often with devastating long-term consequences for their health and future productivity, says the report compiled by the Food and Agricultural Organization and three other U.N. agencies. In Bangkok, more than a thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>UN: Nearly Half-Billion People Undernourished in Asia-Pacific Region - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/nearly-half-billion-people-undernourished-in-asia-pacific-region-/4643242.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC8vasfbuGg33N7hD1QqIjgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 14:30:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/nearly-half-billion-people-undernourished-in-asia-pacific-region-/4643242.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN: Nearly Half-Billion People Undernourished in Asia-Pacific Region&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four U.N. specialized agencies warn that many parts of Asia and the Pacific suffer from alarmingly high levels of malnutrition and hunger. This is the first time the Food and Agriculture Organization, the U.N. Children’s Fund, the World Food Program and the World Health Organization have issued a joint report, which calls for urgent action to reverse the situation. The report finds efforts to reduce malnutrition and hunger have come to a virtual standstill in Asia and the Pacific. Unless greater effort is made to tackle this situation, it warns prospects for economic and social development ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Starving and stunted: the Filipino children wasted by malnutrition – photo dispatch - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/starving-stunted-filipino-children-wasted-malnutrition-photo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJuFOsJHRJ_3kNFV41q2lZIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/starving-stunted-filipino-children-wasted-malnutrition-photo/" target="_blank"&gt;Starving and stunted: the Filipino children wasted by malnutrition – photo dispatch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;22 Oct 2018 Starving and stunted: the Filipino children wasted by malnutrition – photo dispatch Previous slideNext slide1 of 21View AllSkip Ad Ashlie Arangues, 13, is severely malnourished and stunted. She is photographed alongside her neighbours Johnsen Malate, 11, and Caselyn Zisaya, five. Ashlie lives in Navotas City, Manila, in the Philippines – a country with high child malnutrition rates. One in three children in the country have stunted growth – and in some areas, it is one in two. Protect yourself and your family by learning more about Global Health Security Simon Townsley Back to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>WHO: Air Pollution a Health Risk for Children - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/who-air-pollution-a-health-risk-for-children/4633655.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE9vtvTWWmye8mmRlqQ30JMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 16:28:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/who-air-pollution-a-health-risk-for-children/4633655.html" target="_blank"&gt;WHO: Air Pollution a Health Risk for Children&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization says air pollution kills hundreds of thousands of children every year and puts the physical health and neurological development of hundreds of millions of other youngsters at serious risk. The WHO is issuing a report titled “Air pollution and child health: Prescribing clean air” on the eve of the U.N. agency's first-ever Global Conference on Air pollution and Health. The World Health Organization reports more than 90 percent, or nearly 2 billion children under the age of 15, breathe toxic air every day. The WHO says debilitating problems associated with air pol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>FT Health: Health for all or health for some? - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/46f2d448-d85f-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIt1-5dkTDN7tXV8zkKstwwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 13:14:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/46f2d448-d85f-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8" target="_blank"&gt;FT Health: Health for all or health for some?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sign up here to receive FT Health by email each Friday. No FT subscription needed. A lot has changed in the world since the 1978 Alma-Ata declaration called for “health for all”. Since then, the Soviet Union — which had convened that gathering of health ministers — has imploded, the Berlin Wall has fallen, China has risen, and the host Kazakhstan has moved its capital to Astana. But this week’s Astana declaration suggests the aspiration four decades ago remains unmet. Half the world’s population still lacks access to essential health services. As an article in the BMJ argued, the bold visio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Stunting: a silent emergency threatening millions of children's lives - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/stunting-a-silent-emergency/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPZr30sXpblVuGHG30MVY-4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 15:31:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/stunting-a-silent-emergency/" target="_blank"&gt;Stunting: a silent emergency threatening millions of children's lives&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stunting A silent emergency Stunting A silent emergency An estimated 151m children under five – one in four children worldwide – become ‘stunted’ through poor nutrition. It is not just a matter of height. It leaves them cognitively impaired for life. Words by Jennifer Rigby. Photographs by Simon Townsley The hair on her temples is damp with sweat, and her eyes are closed. Maryann Barrios is sick, again, and asleep in her mother’s arms in the shade of a tarpaulin outside their one-room shack in Manila, capital of the Philippines. Maryann is only two, but she has been in and out of hospital e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>France launches new investigation into babies born with stunted or missing arms - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/21/france-launches-investigation-babies-born-stunted-missing-arms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAtkvS7WRzaiGLYAyH5CbjMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 19:30:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/21/france-launches-investigation-babies-born-stunted-missing-arms/" target="_blank"&gt;France launches new investigation into babies born with stunted or missing arms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France's health minister has ordered a fresh investigation into why 14 babies in rural areas were born with missing limbs in recent years, saying it was "unacceptable" that previous probes had not got to the bottom of the mystery. The announcement came just two weeks after an inquiry by health authorities ended with doctors saying they had failed to find out what had caused the babies to be born with stunted or missing arms since 2007. “We cannot simply say that we didn’t find any causes, that is unacceptable,” Health Minister Agnes Buzyn told RTL radio. The cases were found in three differ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Why Indonesia’s Children Are Not Growing - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/why-indonesia-s-children-are-not-growing/4605741.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG9utv-wCMOz1XVAlQBMYVwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 15:24:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/why-indonesia-s-children-are-not-growing/4605741.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why Indonesia’s Children Are Not Growing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite its middle income status, Indonesia is dealing with what experts say are unexpectedly high rates of childhood stunting. Now, its government – starting with the the president - is declaring war on the issue and committing to boost its response to the challenge following a World Bank publication that says 37 percent of Indonesia’s children were stunted in 2013, a rate on par with some far more impoverished nations of Sub-Saharan Africa. Stunting is the medical condition that the World Health Organization defines as “impaired growth and development that children experience from poor n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Investing in human capital is an urgent task - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9f8c3f18-cbb2-11e8-8d0b-a6539b949662</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF1bkIETzGEVL8Dp8yGlAH0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 21:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9f8c3f18-cbb2-11e8-8d0b-a6539b949662" target="_blank"&gt;Investing in human capital is an urgent task&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, we launch the Human Capital Index, which ranks countries on how effectively they are preparing their citizens for the future. We did this knowing that countries find rankings uncomfortable, but we are certain that this is a discussion that cannot wait. An index puts crucial information squarely in front of leaders — especially heads of state and ministers of finance — and makes it hard to ignore. Investing in human capital is an urgent task. Over the years, countless development reports and academic studies have made the case for investing in people. We now know more than we ever hav...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Children go hungry as the Philippine economy grows - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/children-hungry-philippine-economy-grows-181010212219743.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFflyrdj2XgmoE8Eis1EDVIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 22:11:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/children-hungry-philippine-economy-grows-181010212219743.html" target="_blank"&gt;Children go hungry as the Philippine economy grows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manila, Philippines - In Tondo, Manila's largest slum, children root around in the rubbish, looking for old chicken to boil and eat. Life in Tondo, an area that more than 100,000 people call home, centres around a dump where families make what living they can by sorting through the rubbish to find anything to sell. Twice a week, a colourful truck approaches the children. On those two days, they know they're going to be able to enjoy a fresh, hot meal. As young as three, they run to gather around the staff from Bahay Tuluyan, a non-profit organisation that brings food to the slum and other i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>How to Tackle Malnutrition In Africa By Encouraging Private Sector Investment - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mfonobongnsehe/2018/10/01/how-to-tackle-malnutrition-in-africa-by-encouraging-private-sector-investment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEELBtV2Ts2L4m0zoURKF8w0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 11:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mfonobongnsehe/2018/10/01/how-to-tackle-malnutrition-in-africa-by-encouraging-private-sector-investment/" target="_blank"&gt;How to Tackle Malnutrition In Africa By Encouraging Private Sector Investment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lawrence Haddad Malnutrition is one of Africa’s biggest challenges today. The number of ‘undernourished’ or hungry people in Africa increased from about 182 million in the early 1990s to around 233 million in 2016 according to the FAO, and yet no African country is expected to reach the UN target of ending childhood malnutrition by 2030. Africa is also the only continent in the world where children are both fat and stunted. The lack of nutritious food has come at a huge cost to African nations, affecting not only their well-being but also economic progress. In fact, African nations lose be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>821 million people hungry worldwide -UN - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/general_news/2018/09/11/821-million-people-hungry-worldwide-un_28cd8322-6ef4-41ad-9283-cd561d36f6ed.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHWR_Cg5jMVvC9Hq24CXzxUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 11:48:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/general_news/2018/09/11/821-million-people-hungry-worldwide-un_28cd8322-6ef4-41ad-9283-cd561d36f6ed.html" target="_blank"&gt;821 million people hungry worldwide -UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, September 11 - Hunger affected around 821 million worldwide in 2017, meaning the level of people in conditions of severe food insecurity has risen back up to that of 10 years ago, according to a UN report released on Tuesday. Hunger has been on the rise over the past three years, said The State of Food Security and Nutrition in the World. The situation is worsening in South America and most regions of Africa, while the decreasing trend in undernourishment that characterized Asia seems to be slowing down significantly, according to the report prepared by the UN's three Rome...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>One in nine going hungry globally as climate change increases food insecurity - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/one-nine-going-hungry-globally-climate-change-increases-food/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENfmGQMTufu8DnUH3LEaXMwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:19:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/one-nine-going-hungry-globally-climate-change-increases-food/" target="_blank"&gt;One in nine going hungry globally as climate change increases food insecurity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of people going hungry has increased for the third consecutive year, a major report reveals. Figures show 821 million people – or one in nine – were undernourished in 2017, as climate extremes have contributed to global food insecurity. Women, babies and the elderly are particularly vulnerable to the worsening trend, which raises concerns that the goal of eradicating hunger by 2030 will not be met. The annual State of Food Insecurity and Nutrition report, published on Tuesday by five United Nations agencies, found that while conflict and economic downturns exacerbated problems in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Hunger rising with global temperatures, UN report says - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/11/health/un-hunger-report-2018-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENxkjA0ckqCTedC30JUZDN0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 09:02:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/11/health/un-hunger-report-2018-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hunger rising with global temperatures, UN report says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Climate change is having a negative effect on global agriculture and is driving up the number of hungry people around the world, according to the United Nations' 2018 State of Food Security and Nutrition in the World report, released Tuesday. It found that 821 million people -- one in every nine -- were malnourished in 2017, up from 815 million in 2016, putting at risk the UN's goal of eradicating hunger in the world by 2030. There was also limited progress in 2017 in addressing multiple forms of malnutrition, such as child stunting (in which children don't grow properly due to undernourish...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The best and worst US states for children - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/27/health/child-well-being-state-rankings-study/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQe3V-hzOtzzPl81a2zuvcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 16:28:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/27/health/child-well-being-state-rankings-study/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The best and worst US states for children&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2017 report by Save the Children ranked 172 countries from best to worst in an effort to explore the main reasons why childhood comes to an early end in certain places. Here are countries that ranked highest and lowest. Norway: A woman kisses her 4-month-old son in Oslo. Fewer than 0.3% of children die before the age of 5 in Norway. Helene Negaard/Save the Children Finland: A 2-year-old at her public day care in Helsinki. Only 2% of primary- and secondary-school-age children are out of school in Finland. Ilse Holm/Save the Children The Netherlands: A woman and her 2-hour-old baby in The H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>World Food Prize goes to an economist and a doctor - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/77d0dcadc7294f12afb62a43dd34a704</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBtfebKYYV0NjWoT-WjukWkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgw3utQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 14:42:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/77d0dcadc7294f12afb62a43dd34a704" target="_blank"&gt;World Food Prize goes to an economist and a doctor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — The World Food Prize will be awarded this year to two men who have dedicated their careers to improving the availability of nutritious food for pregnant women and children in an effort to reduce the effects of malnutrition in developing countries. Lawrence Haddad, who is a British economist and food policy researcher, and Dr. David Nabarro, who has worked with the World Health Organization and United Nations on health and hunger issues, were named the 2018 prize recipients in a ceremony Monday at the U.S. Department of Agriculture in Washington. The World Food Prize ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Malnourished California girl had arms of infant - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/52753f312dd441c989d7a68172c04e8e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO45-YYeVxIuRPi2sJg5lGcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 22:57:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/52753f312dd441c989d7a68172c04e8e" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Malnourished California girl had arms of infant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RIVERSIDE, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on a hearing for California parents accused of shackling their kids (all times local): 3:55 p.m. An investigator says the children of a California couple facing torture and abuse charges were so malnourished that their 11-year-old daughter had arms the size of an infant. Riverside County district attorney's investigator Patrick Morris testified Wednesday that some of the 13 children had severe malnutrition and muscle wasting. Morris was testifying at a hearing in Riverside Superior Court to determine if David and Louise Turpin are tried on charges of tort...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The best and worst countries to be a child - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/15/health/gallery/best-worst-countries-save-the-children/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEvdnAUvaINCdUZvr5Ok-dkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 21:06:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/15/health/gallery/best-worst-countries-save-the-children/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The best and worst countries to be a child&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2017 report by Save the Children ranked 172 countries from best to worst in an effort to explore the main reasons why childhood comes to an early end in certain places. Here are countries that ranked highest and lowest. Norway: A woman kisses her 4-month-old son in Oslo. Fewer than 0.3% of children die before the age of 5 in Norway. Helene Negaard/Save the Children Finland: A 2-year-old at her public day care in Helsinki. Only 2% of primary- and secondary-school-age children are out of school in Finland. Ilse Holm/Save the Children The Netherlands: A woman and her 2-hour-old baby in The H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Among 20 wealthy nations, US child mortality ranks worst, study finds - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2018/01/08/health/child-mortality-rates-by-country-study-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHsYGZBdyNVBI3kPgu-yJfwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 21:32:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2018/01/08/health/child-mortality-rates-by-country-study-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Among 20 wealthy nations, US child mortality ranks worst, study finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2017 report by Save the Children ranked 172 countries from best to worst in an effort to explore the main reasons why childhood comes to an early end in certain places. Here are countries that ranked highest and lowest. Norway: A woman kisses her 4-month-old son in Oslo. Fewer than 0.3% of children die before the age of 5 in Norway. Helene Negaard/Save the Children Finland: A 2-year-old at her public day care in Helsinki. Only 2% of primary- and secondary-school-age children are out of school in Finland. Ilse Holm/Save the Children The Netherlands: A woman and her 2-hour-old baby in The H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Deaths Mount as Syria Refuses Permit for Medical Evacuation - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/syria-death-toll-medical-evaluation/4173317.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK-mCa5eLLU_o8nJNfJRfokqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 15:15:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/syria-death-toll-medical-evaluation/4173317.html" target="_blank"&gt;Deaths Mount as Syria Refuses Permit for Medical Evacuation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior U.N. official says people are dying because the Syrian government will not give the green light for an urgent medical evacuation from eastern Ghouta, a suburb of Damascus. The United Nations has been asking the Syrian Government for permission to transport patients from eastern Ghouta to Damascus for urgent medical treatment since May to no avail. FILE - Civil defense members and civilians carry a wounded man in the town of Hamoria, Eastern Ghouta, near Damascus, Syria, Dec. 3, 2017. Special advisor to the U.N. Syrian Envoy, Jan Egeland, says 494 people were on the priority lists f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Child malnutrition soars in besieged Damascus enclave - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/12/21/middleeast/syria-eastern-ghouta-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAC5F14sAKhUWNKHwOT8vuQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 18:12:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/12/21/middleeast/syria-eastern-ghouta-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Child malnutrition soars in besieged Damascus enclave&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite many claims the war in Syria is ebbing, one besieged pocket of rebel-aligned civilians near the Syrian capital is at a "critical point," says the International Committee of the Red Cross (ICRC). They are experiencing the worst outbreak of child malnutrition yet in the savage six-year civil war, and in need of an emergency medical evacuation of more than 100 children, say UN officials. An estimated 400,000 civilians in the suburban enclave of Eastern Ghouta have suffered from both a lengthy siege and continued bombardment. This has come amid a climate of peace talks and a victory dec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Children Are Hungrier In Modi's India Than In Kim's North Korea - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/11/22/children-are-hungrier-in-modis-india-than-in-kims-north-korea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAlo0ZwJrKccGK-_e35_S94qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 01:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/11/22/children-are-hungrier-in-modis-india-than-in-kims-north-korea/" target="_blank"&gt;Children Are Hungrier In Modi's India Than In Kim's North Korea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;/ AFP PHOTO / JIM WATSON (Photo credit should read JIM WATSON/AFP/Getty Images) Children are hungrier in Narendra Modi’s India than in Kim Jong-un’s North Korea. That’s according to the recently published Global Hunger Index (GHI), which ranks India 100 out of the 119 countries surveyed. That’s seven notches below North Korea, and seven notches above the bottom of the list, which is occupied by Afghanistan. The index includes four components: undernourishment, child mortality, child wasting, and child stunting. The survey finds a “disturbing reality of the country’s stubbornly high proporti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item></channel></rss>