<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Mahathir Bin Mohamad - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZzZVdSb0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:24:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Malays celebrate after Malaysia refuses UN racial equality pledge - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/malays-rally-after-malaysia-refuses-un-racial-equality-pledge/10597618</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEACjItDShyiyVsfWfzy2oc0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:31:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/malays-rally-after-malaysia-refuses-un-racial-equality-pledge/10597618" target="_blank"&gt;Malays celebrate after Malaysia refuses UN racial equality pledge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tens of thousands of Malay Muslims have rallied in Kuala Lumpur to celebrate the Malaysian government's refusal to ratify a UN convention against racial discrimination. Key points: - At least 55,000 people joined the rally - Malays account for about 60 per cent of Malaysia's multiethnic population - Former Malaysian prime minister Najib Razak attended the rally After weeks of pressure by pro-Malay groups, Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad's multiethnic Government decided last month that it would not ratify the convention, without giving a reason why it was going back on an earlier commitment ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Jubilant Malays rally after Malaysia refuses U.N. racial equality pledge - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-rally/jubilant-malays-rally-after-malaysia-refuses-un-racial-equality-pledge-idUSKBN1O70AS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKlAR3E4VjWSFkqDSfgtMcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 08:55:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-rally/jubilant-malays-rally-after-malaysia-refuses-un-racial-equality-pledge-idUSKBN1O70AS" target="_blank"&gt;Jubilant Malays rally after Malaysia refuses U.N. racial equality pledge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tens of thousands of Malay Muslims rallied in Kuala Lumpur on Saturday to celebrate the Malaysian government's refusal to ratify a UN convention against racial discrimination. After weeks of pressure by pro-Malay groups, Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad's multi-ethnic government decided last month that it would not ratify the convention, without giving a reason why it was going back on an earlier commitment to sign. Groups representing Malays, who account for around 60 percent of Malaysia's multi-ethnic population, raised fears that signing the UN pledge could have undermined Malay privilege...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Malaysia: Malays rally amid worries over government 'weakness' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/malaysia-malays-rally-worries-government-weakness-181208093049636.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHkXRYzgoGJd3mXDrfZ3W2kqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:05:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/malaysia-malays-rally-worries-government-weakness-181208093049636.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia: Malays rally amid worries over government 'weakness'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia - Tens of thousands of ethnic Malays have taken to the streets of Malaysia's capital to "celebrate" a government decision not to ratify a key UN anti-discrimination treaty, amid growing concerns the seven-month administration of Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad is losing reform momentum. Malaysia is one of only 14 countries in the world that have yet to sign the International Convention on the Elimination of all forms of Racial Discrimination (ICERD). The treaty what constitutes racial discrimination and sets forth a series of principles and guidelines by which states ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Malaysian fugitive Jho Low, four others hit with fresh 1MDB charges - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb-financier/malaysian-fugitive-jho-low-four-others-hit-with-fresh-1mdb-charges-idUSKBN1O40AW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEECoGE2jt5mDFpLSYoahoz0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 06:08:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb-financier/malaysian-fugitive-jho-low-four-others-hit-with-fresh-1mdb-charges-idUSKBN1O40AW" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysian fugitive Jho Low, four others hit with fresh 1MDB charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian police filed fresh criminal charges and issued arrest warrants for fugitive financier Low Taek Jho and four others wanted in connection with a multi-billion-dollar scandal at state fund 1MDB, officials said on Wednesday. Low, popularly known as Jho Low, has been identified by Malaysian and U.S. investigators as a central figure in the alleged theft of about $4.5 billion from 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB). Low, whose whereabouts is not known, has denied any wrongdoing through a spokesman. Last month, U.S. prosecutors charged Low and two former Goldman Sachs bankers with consp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>In 'New Malaysia,' Race Continues to Cast a Long Shadow - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/in-new-malaysia-race-continues-to-cast-a-long-shadow/4685740.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDD1lc_CD4eUgzYKfVgk8dIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:30:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/in-new-malaysia-race-continues-to-cast-a-long-shadow/4685740.html" target="_blank"&gt;In 'New Malaysia,' Race Continues to Cast a Long Shadow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just months after a stunning election victory, Malaysia's prime minister has had to step in to mollify the country's majority Malay Muslims in recent weeks, underlining a weighty challenge confronting his multi-ethnic, reformist coalition: race. When riots erupted at a Hindu temple outside the capital, Kuala Lumpur, last week, 93-year-old Mahathir Mohamad spared no effort to scotch speculation that tensions with Malays were to blame. Just a few days earlier, his government reversed its pledge to ratify a U.N. convention against racial discrimination following a backlash from groups who argu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Lynas considers legal action after Malaysia imposes new conditions - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/bd255d62-f82a-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE5sat2npmAi6O-YnjmlA7UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 02:50:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/bd255d62-f82a-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Lynas considers legal action after Malaysia imposes new conditions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lynas Corp said on Wednesday it was considering taking legal action against the Malaysian government over its decision to impose tough new conditions on its licence to operate in the country. The stand-off between one of the world’s only rare earths’ suppliers outside China and the new government in Kuala Lumpur caused shares in ASX-listed Lynas to fall by a quarter when the market opened. “This appears to be policy based on politics, not policy based on science,” said Amanda Lacaze, the Australian-listed miner’s chief executive. “However, we are confident we are well placed to manage poten...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Malaysia seeks return of airspace control amid Singapore flight path dispute - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-singapore-airspace/malaysia-seeks-return-of-airspace-control-amid-singapore-flight-path-dispute-idUSKBN1O318Z</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN4YXeaUYNoHPzUG17HBvFkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:30:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-singapore-airspace/malaysia-seeks-return-of-airspace-control-amid-singapore-flight-path-dispute-idUSKBN1O318Z" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia seeks return of airspace control amid Singapore flight path dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia has told Singapore it intends to take back control of airspace that the city-state has managed since 1974 amid a dispute over a flight path to a secondary airport in Singapore, Malaysia's transport minister said on Tuesday. Singapore has put in place a new instrument landing system at its small Seletar airport to be used by turboprops and business jets that involves a flight path over Malaysian airspace without its permission, Malaysian Transport Minister Anthony Loke told parliament. He said the flight path would lead to height limits on building development and affect shipping op...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Wanted in India, fiery Islamic preacher says he has not broken any law - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-islam-preacher/wanted-in-india-fiery-islamic-preacher-says-he-has-not-broken-any-law-idUSKCN1O101E</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDCu3rKn0Xx13X6L60zH9qoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 02:13:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-islam-preacher/wanted-in-india-fiery-islamic-preacher-says-he-has-not-broken-any-law-idUSKCN1O101E" target="_blank"&gt;Wanted in India, fiery Islamic preacher says he has not broken any law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Controversial Islamic preacher Zakir Naik, wanted in his home country of India, said he has not broken any Indian law and was being targeted by the "enemies of Islam," in a rare public speech in Malaysia where he has sought refuge. Naik, 53, is facing charges of money laundering and hate speech in India, where authorities last year said he has been "promoting enmity and hatred between different religious groups in India through public speeches and lectures". The preacher has been living in Malaysia, where he has permanent residency, since India started investigating him, but he has kept a l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Mahathir’s honeymoon fades as old ways resurface - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8d95866c-f316-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOBox9Ia9SaPgwyzpMEQ4dAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 19:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8d95866c-f316-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Mahathir’s honeymoon fades as old ways resurface&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mahathir Mohamad remains popular with Malaysians after his stunning election upset in May. However, the euphoria that greeted his victory has quickly faded as cracks appear in the ruling coalition and as some of the prime minister’s actions bring uncomfortable echoes of the past. Mr Mahathir, who sensationally returned to the prime-ministership to head a four-party coalition, is making good on his vow to clean up corruption. Our third-quarter survey of 1,000 urban Malaysians showed that they like what his government is doing so far. Mr Mahathir has given independence to Malaysia’s anti-corr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Malaysia says former PM Najib's office ordered changes to 1MDB audit report - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb/malaysia-says-former-pm-najibs-office-ordered-changes-to-1mdb-audit-report-idUSKCN1NU06I</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDHtwmDiieg8j3Zb5A8SPAAqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 14:54:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb/malaysia-says-former-pm-najibs-office-ordered-changes-to-1mdb-audit-report-idUSKCN1NU06I" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia says former PM Najib's office ordered changes to 1MDB audit report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The office of former Malaysian premier Najib Razak ordered changes to a 2016 audit report of scandal-plagued state fund 1MDB, including removing mention of financier Low Taek Jho's presence at a board meeting, authorities said. Financier Low has been described as a central player in the alleged corruption and money laundering at 1MDB, according to Malaysian and U.S. authorities investigating the fund. He had no official role in 1MDB, but advised on investments and negotiated deals for the fund, the authorities have said. Najib, ousted in a May 9 election by Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Relatives of missing from Malaysia plane say they have found pieces of debris - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysiaairlines-mh370-idUSKCN1NX1J9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIzR70rwOS7SlIS6Q0skNToqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:07:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysiaairlines-mh370-idUSKCN1NX1J9" target="_blank"&gt;Relatives of missing from Malaysia plane say they have found pieces of debris&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Relatives of people who went missing on Malaysia Airlines flight MH370 in 2014 have retrieved what they believe are new pieces of debris from the aircraft and will present them to the Malaysian government this week. Flight MH370 was on its way from Kuala Lumpur to Beijing on March 8, 2014, with 239 people on board, when it disappeared and became one of the world's greatest aviation mysteries. Malaysian and international investigators believe the jet veered thousands of miles off course from its scheduled route before eventually plunging into the Indian Ocean. But no one knows why. In all, 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Malaysia backpedals on U.N. race measure in face of protests - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-un/malaysia-backpedals-on-u-n-race-measure-in-face-of-protests-idUSKCN1NS13S</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO6e5tiANlj7kDtc6B0g4HQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 10:58:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-un/malaysia-backpedals-on-u-n-race-measure-in-face-of-protests-idUSKCN1NS13S" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia backpedals on U.N. race measure in face of protests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia on Friday reversed a pledge to ratify a UN convention against racial discrimination, following backlash from groups who fear it could dilute privileges for majority ethnic Malays. Leaders of Islamist party PAS, former ruling party UMNO and conservative groups plan a rally next month against the convention, which they fear could strip away Malay privileges and threaten Islam's position as the official religion. The government will not ratify the International Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Racial Discrimination (ICERD), the office of Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Coalition’s Israel embassy move trashes Australia’s reputation as a serious country - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/commentisfree/2018/nov/17/the-coalitions-israel-embassy-move-trashes-australias-reputation-as-a-serious-country</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ16uEJsLOpKLb1pjatHpUoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 22:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/commentisfree/2018/nov/17/the-coalitions-israel-embassy-move-trashes-australias-reputation-as-a-serious-country" target="_blank"&gt;The Coalition’s Israel embassy move trashes Australia’s reputation as a serious country&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We don’t settle on an Israel policy to please our Asian neighbours. No one should even hint we should. Shifting the embassy is wrong in principle. It takes off the negotiating table the status of Jerusalem, which we always said needed to be settled by the two parties. It undercuts the promise of the Oslo accords and any number of UN resolutions. It positions Australia with Guatemala as the only nation to follow Donald Trump. It sends a message to the Palestinians of the West Bank that there is no hope. It sends a message to hardliners in Israel that they can continue on their ruinous course...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Australia, Malaysia in war of words over Israel embassy shift - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/australia-malaysia-war-words-israel-embassy-shift-181116060551480.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMdAMTtHvpFzLeUrrNvQorIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 06:41:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/australia-malaysia-war-words-israel-embassy-shift-181116060551480.html" target="_blank"&gt;Australia, Malaysia in war of words over Israel embassy shift&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia's treasurer on Friday said Malaysian Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad had a history of anti-Jewish statements in an escalating war of words over the possibility Australia might move its Israeli embassy to Jerusalem. Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison first proposed the move during a local election campaign last month, sparking concern from Indonesia and Malaysia. Mahathir, 93, raised the potential relocation in a meeting with Morrison in Singapore on Thursday, later telling reporters he feared it could increase the threat of attacks. "I pointed out that in dealing with terror...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs bankers 'cheated' Malaysia over 1MDB: PM Mahathir - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb-goldman/goldman-sachs-bankers-cheated-malaysia-over-1mdb-pm-mahathir-idUSKCN1NI0D1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECWAsLpxwO48z5YQjOKjZUMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 01:27:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb-goldman/goldman-sachs-bankers-cheated-malaysia-over-1mdb-pm-mahathir-idUSKCN1NI0D1" target="_blank"&gt;Goldman Sachs bankers 'cheated' Malaysia over 1MDB: PM Mahathir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad said bankers at Goldman Sachs Group Inc (GS.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) "cheated" the country in dealings with state fund 1MDB and that U.S. authorities have promised to help return the fees the Wall Street bank earned from the fund. The U.S. investment bank has been under scrutiny for its role in helping raise funds through bond offerings for 1Malaysia Development Bhd (1MDB) [TERRN.UL], which is the subject of corruption and money-laundering investigations in at least six countries. Goldman's stock fell to a near two-year low on Monday...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs’ Asia franchise suffers in 1MDB storm - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8f33b9a0-e671-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENlQhftjduYFxceR4iEG3JoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 04:00:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8f33b9a0-e671-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3" target="_blank"&gt;Goldman Sachs’ Asia franchise suffers in 1MDB storm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The action for one of the worst crises in Goldman Sachs’ history is now centred in the US, where prosecutors have charged two of the bank’s former executives with money laundering and bribing foreign officials. Back in Asia, the Malaysian corruption scandal is still unfolding. The question now is how deep the rot goes and how serious the damage will be to Goldman’s wider business in the region, which the bank has built over decades. ‘Sure, all of my clients are crooks . . .’ The impact of the 1MDB scandal has been swift. Tim Leissner, the former Goldman partner who has pleaded guilty to cri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Malaysia and Indonesia are bucking the global trend on democracy - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/malaysia-indonesia-bucking-global-trend-democracy-181115134301036.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEM14jfuscSa3MvqA_QQzTcqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 11:25:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/malaysia-indonesia-bucking-global-trend-democracy-181115134301036.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia and Indonesia are bucking the global trend on democracy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In October, Latin America's most populous nation, Brazil, elected as president Jair Bolsonaro, a former military man and historically fringe, far-right senator known for his pro-gun, pro-torture views. In 1999, he told Brazilian television, "Elections won't change anything in this country. It will only change on the day that we break out in civil war here and do the job that the military regime didn't do: killing 30,000. If some innocent people die, that's fine. In every war, innocent people die." Elsewhere in the world, Donald Trump, Xi Jinping, Vladimir Putin, Recep Erdogan, Viktor Orban ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>China’s Belt and Road hits problems but is still popular - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/814b39ea-e8cd-11e8-a34c-663b3f553b35</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIcbNVZ6wz_uI_uZjivt8gQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 18:52:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/814b39ea-e8cd-11e8-a34c-663b3f553b35" target="_blank"&gt;China’s Belt and Road hits problems but is still popular&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a narrative of pushback against the Belt and Road Initiative, China’s programme to finance and build infrastructure in about 88 countries around the world. Coming against the backdrop of US-China confrontation, this evidence of pushback is being read as a collective response to Chinese leader Xi Jinping’s overarching foreign policy concept. But this misses the detail of several deals in which the context is more one of renegotiation than cancellation. The fundamental logic of many of the BRI in developing countries neighbouring China remains intact. Such is the need for investment ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Malaysia's former first lady to face more charges: anti-graft agency - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-rosmah-idUSKCN1NJ1I2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8sdqNhkuWkyO79JH6MzR8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 11:23:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-rosmah-idUSKCN1NJ1I2" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia's former first lady to face more charges: anti-graft agency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia will file additional charges against the wife of former Prime Minister Najib Razak, the anti-graft agency said on Wednesday, as authorities step up investigations into the former first couple. Najib and his wife, Rosmah Mansor, who was for years criticized for her extravagant lifestyle, are at the center of a wide-ranging graft investigation launched after a stunning election victory and return to power as prime minister in May by veteran leader Mahathir Mohamad. Najib has been charged with 38 counts of graft since his election defeat, mostly to do with state fund 1Malaysian Develo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Malaysia's Mahathir refuses to rule out banning Goldman over 1MDB - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/46dab434-e6ed-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGFyWZr-IOoGj1mHkj97IgAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 03:33:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/46dab434-e6ed-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia's Mahathir refuses to rule out banning Goldman over 1MDB&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mahathir Mohamad, Malaysia’s prime minister, has refused to rule out banning Goldman Sachs from the country as a result of its role in the 1MDB scandal that unfolded under his predecessor, warning the investment bank “we are watching”. “Goldman Sachs has done things which are wrong that they shouldn’t have done”, Mr Mahathir said in a CNBC interview when asked if Goldman had become persona non grata in Malaysia. “But we want to see the results of all this investigation and the actions taken against [former senior executive Tim] Leissner, for example.” Goldman is grappling with an investiga...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>US, China rivalry challenging entwined Asia-Pacific region - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/a03a387179554cfab37d22187d09ce6a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOylIi_NfYQEj-gH1CeVzaEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 11:31:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/a03a387179554cfab37d22187d09ce6a" target="_blank"&gt;US, China rivalry challenging entwined Asia-Pacific region&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — The rivalry between the U.S. and China in the Asia-Pacific is proving "awkward" for Southeast Asian nations that do not want to have to choose between their friends, Singapore's prime minister said Thursday as he wrapped up a regional summit. "It's easiest not to take sides when everybody else is on the same side. But if you are friends with two countries which are on different sides, then sometimes it is possible to get along with both, sometimes it's more awkward if you try to get along with both," Lee Hsien Loong said when asked about the competition between the U.S. and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Warnings of a 'domino effect' of protectionism as Asian leaders meet - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-asean-summit-malaysia/warnings-of-a-domino-effect-of-protectionism-as-asian-leaders-meet-idUSKCN1NI0VQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMrCQnnpnjk3Z4saDNGJbe0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 02:35:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-asean-summit-malaysia/warnings-of-a-domino-effect-of-protectionism-as-asian-leaders-meet-idUSKCN1NI0VQ" target="_blank"&gt;Warnings of a 'domino effect' of protectionism as Asian leaders meet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asian leaders gathered for a summit on Tuesday amid warnings that the post-World War Two international order is in jeopardy and trade tensions between Washington and Beijing could trigger a "domino effect" of protectionist measures by other countries. Malaysian Prime Mahathir Mohamad told a business forum ahead of the summit in Singapore that other developed countries would take a cue from the United States and China if their tit-for-tat tariff war is allowed to spiral. "The trade tension between the two world powers is bound to create a domino effect that will affect trade reactions and wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Malaysia PM says U.S. DOJ will help return money Goldman Sachs charged for 1MDB dealings - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-asean-summit-malaysia-1mdb-idUSKCN1NI10B</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAYRtyVzaVPzP3XjQRynOi0qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 10:31:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-asean-summit-malaysia-1mdb-idUSKCN1NI10B" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia PM says U.S. DOJ will help return money Goldman Sachs charged for 1MDB dealings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad said on Tuesday U.S. prosecutors had promised to help return money that Goldman Sachs (GS.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) charged for its dealings with troubled Malaysian state fund 1MDB. The U.S. investment bank has been under scrutiny for its role in helping raise funds through bond offerings for 1Malaysia Development Bhd (1MDB) TERRN.UL, which is the subject of corruption and money-laundering investigations in at least six countries. The U.S. Department of Justice has said about $4.5 billion was misappropriated from 1MDB, including some m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>At Southeast Asian summit, pushback against going it alone - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/d50eb2726153439bb082887c609d91b7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC6243sWrvI8lSUHSHviuokqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:15:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/d50eb2726153439bb082887c609d91b7" target="_blank"&gt;At Southeast Asian summit, pushback against going it alone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — The annual gathering of Southeast Asian leaders began Tuesday with a warning from the host, Singapore Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong, about threats against international rules that underpin world stability and economic growth. "The international order is at a turning point," Lee said at the opening ceremony of the summit of the 10-nation Association of Southeast Asian Nations. "The existing free, open and rules-based multilateral system, which has underpinned ASEAN's growth and stability, has come under stress," Lee said. U.S. President Donald Trump's "America First" foreig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs CEO: I feel horrible ex-bankers broke law in 1MDB case - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-goldmansachs-1mdb-probe-idUSKCN1NC0SN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDVipntuyv1OmYadg5t6LmwqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 09:36:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-goldmansachs-1mdb-probe-idUSKCN1NC0SN" target="_blank"&gt;Goldman Sachs CEO: I feel horrible ex-bankers broke law in 1MDB case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs Chief Executive David Solomon said on Wednesday he felt "horrible" that two former employees "blatantly broke the law" in their dealings with Malaysian state fund 1Malaysia Development Berhad. U.S. prosecutors filed criminal charges against the two former Goldman bankers and a Malaysian financier linked to the alleged theft of billions of dollars from the fund. An investigation into where 1MDB's money went became the largest carried out by the Department of Justice under its anti-kleptocracy program, and the scandal was a major reason why Malaysian voters rejected Najib Razak,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Malaysian tycoon wanted by US in 1MDB scandal fights back - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/d27f22e2c41a40fa9bdec2eda55f923a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDRzPzQqlg-wq1SfGOvHoegqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 12:24:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/d27f22e2c41a40fa9bdec2eda55f923a" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysian tycoon wanted by US in 1MDB scandal fights back&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The young Malaysian tycoon wanted by the U.S. for his alleged role in ransacking a state investment fund says he's innocent, and he's been fighting back against the allegations while in hiding. For 36-year-old Taek Jho Low, or Jho Low, it's a far cry from earlier days of partying with jet-set celebrities like Paris Hilton in Las Vegas and Saint Tropez. On Thursday the Justice Department charged Low for alleged involvement in a money laundering and bribery scheme that pilfered billions of dollars from Malaysia's 1MDB investment fund. Prosecutors announced a three-count indictment against Low...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Malaysian authorities seek former prime minister's British 'PR guru' in fraud probe - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/01/malaysian-authorities-seek-former-prime-ministers-british-pr/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJCZU4YC734-d2sEuEfnf24qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 14:30:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/01/malaysian-authorities-seek-former-prime-ministers-british-pr/" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysian authorities seek former prime minister's British 'PR guru' in fraud probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia’s anti-corruption body is hunting for a British PR consultant in connection with a multi-billion-dollar financial scandal that helped bring down the previous government. The Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) appealed on Thursday for the public’s help in locating Paul Stadlen, 39, who reportedly handled press operations for Najib Razak, the former prime minister. Mr Najib is facing multiple charges of money-laundering and criminal breach of trust over the handling of the state-run 1Malaysia Development Berhad fund, which he created. If convicted, he could be jailed for dec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>US charges Malaysian financier in multibillion-dollar scheme - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/fe87f23d36494f2d80d8b122c6e5e020</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZRd_yVsk9fnyfBmUl3Rb0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 01:58:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/fe87f23d36494f2d80d8b122c6e5e020" target="_blank"&gt;US charges Malaysian financier in multibillion-dollar scheme&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department announced charges Thursday against a fugitive Malaysian financier and two former Goldman Sachs bankers accused in a money laundering and bribery scheme that pilfered billions of dollars from a Malaysian investment fund created to spur economic development projects in that country. A three-count indictment charges Low Taek Jho, also known as Jho Low, with misappropriating money from the state-owned fund and using it for bribes and kickbacks to foreign officials, to pay for luxury real estate, art and jewelry in the United States and to help finance Ho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Malaysia seeks payment relief by challenging 1MDB-IPIC settlement - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb-ipic/malaysia-seeks-payment-relief-by-challenging-1mdb-ipic-settlement-idUSKCN1N40ZY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBDwfOD9PsVcZCqHzHsF4WQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 09:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb-ipic/malaysia-seeks-payment-relief-by-challenging-1mdb-ipic-settlement-idUSKCN1N40ZY" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia seeks payment relief by challenging 1MDB-IPIC settlement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia will file a legal challenge to a settlement agreement between scandal-plagued state fund 1MDB and Abu Dhabi sovereign fund IPIC negotiated during the premiership of former leader Najib Razak, its attorney general said on Tuesday. International Petroleum Investment Co, known as IPIC, and 1MDB had reached an agreement last year in a payment dispute over 1MDB bonds that IPIC had guaranteed. The Malaysian fund had agreed to pay $1.2 billion to IPIC and assumed responsibility for future principal and interest payments for the bonds. Najib was prime minister then, but he lost an election...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>US charges Malaysian financier, Goldman Sachs bankers over 1MDB - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/charges-malaysian-financier-goldman-sachs-bankers-1mdb-181101144203517.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBWqofWb8lJ8WW2rK_YIqjAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 16:36:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/charges-malaysian-financier-goldman-sachs-bankers-1mdb-181101144203517.html" target="_blank"&gt;US charges Malaysian financier, Goldman Sachs bankers over 1MDB&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors in the United States have unveiled criminal charges against a Malaysian financier and two former Goldman Sachs bankers tied to the billion-dollar 1MDB sovereign wealth fund scandal. The three-count indictment on Thursday charges Low Taek Jho of misappropriating money from the state-owned fund and using it to bribe foreign officials and to pay for luxury real estate, art and jewelry in the US and to fund Hollywood film, including "The Wolf of Wall Street." Low, also known as Jho Low, remains at large, Also charged by the US Department of Justice was a Goldman Sachs banker, Tim Le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Malaysia's PM rejects same-sex marriage: 'The institution of family ... has been disregarded in West' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/26/malaysias-pm-rejects-same-sex-marriage-institution-family-has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELx6lzto0ibexFjy1LYLy2IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 05:21:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/26/malaysias-pm-rejects-same-sex-marriage-institution-family-has/" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia's PM rejects same-sex marriage: 'The institution of family ... has been disregarded in West'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia’s prime minister has said his country will not be forced to accept “western values” such as same-sex marriage. His blunt comments were made at a forum during a state visit to Thailand on Thursday, against a backdrop of what activists say is a growing intolerance towards Malaysia’s Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender (LGBT) community. "At this moment, we do not accept LGBT but if they (the West) want to accept, that is their business. Don't force it on us," Mr Mahathir, 93, told a packed audience at Bangkok’s Chulalongkorn University, according to AFP. "The institution of marriag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Former Malaysian PM Najib faces six more corruption charges over state funds - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-najib/former-malaysian-pm-najib-faces-six-more-corruption-charges-over-state-funds-idUSKCN1MZ06Z</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAFS3ZMzISmrzHKUuLGeXwkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 06:53:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-najib/former-malaysian-pm-najib-faces-six-more-corruption-charges-over-state-funds-idUSKCN1MZ06Z" target="_blank"&gt;Former Malaysian PM Najib faces six more corruption charges over state funds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Malaysian premier Najib Razak was charged with six counts of criminal breach of trust involving government funds worth more than $1.5 billion on Thursday, adding to the 32 charges he already faces for money laundering and graft. His former treasury chief, Irwan Serigar Abdullah, was also charged with criminal breach of trust, becoming the highest-ranking civil servant to be charged since Najib was unexpectedly ousted in a general election in May. The two pleaded not guilty to all the charges. Each charge carries a jail term of up to 20 years, a financial penalty and a whipping senten...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Former Malaysian PM, Officials, Face New Graft Charges - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/former-malaysian-pm-officials-face-new-graft-charges/4627162.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGujW_VecGTaOT04HS9zY9YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 14:09:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/former-malaysian-pm-officials-face-new-graft-charges/4627162.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Malaysian PM, Officials, Face New Graft Charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian's anti-graft agency said Wednesday that ex-Prime Minister Najib Razak, along with two former high-ranking officials, will face new charges of criminal breach of trust. The agency said Najib and former treasury chief Mohamad Irwan Serigar Abdullah will be charged together Thursday in "several cases of criminal breach of trust involving the use of Malaysian government funds." It didn't give details but media reports said the charges are linked to the multibillion-dollar looting of the 1MDB state investment fund. Separately, it said in a statement that Hasanah Abdul Hami, the former ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Former Malaysian PM Najib charged with criminal breach of trust - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/malaysia-pm-najib-treasury-chief-graft-charges-181025023647364.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3_hytcTbOIYc4hc-E40VQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 07:14:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/malaysia-pm-najib-treasury-chief-graft-charges-181025023647364.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Malaysian PM Najib charged with criminal breach of trust&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Prime Minister Najib Razak and his top civil servant at the treasury have been jointly charged with the misuse of some 6.6 billion ringgit ($1.58bn) in government money, as Malaysian prosecutors step up their crackdown on corruption. Najib and Mohd Irwan Serigar, who was the secretary-general of the treasury, appeared in court in Kuala Lumpur on Thursday to face six counts of criminal breach of trust. The two pleaded not guilty to all charges. Each carries a jail term of as many as 20 years, a fine, and whipping. Neither Najib or Irwan would be subject to caning because of their age....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Malaysia to charge former PM Najib, ex-Treasury head in graft probe - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-najib/malaysia-to-charge-former-pm-najib-ex-treasury-head-in-graft-probe-idUSKCN1MY14L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBhxYXK4zqy90UFWOHUAB04qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 10:42:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-najib/malaysia-to-charge-former-pm-najib-ex-treasury-head-in-graft-probe-idUSKCN1MY14L" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia to charge former PM Najib, ex-Treasury head in graft probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Malaysian Prime Minister Najib Razak and his ex-head of Treasury will be charged on Thursday in connection with the misuse of government funds, the anti-graft agency said, the latest charges in a widening crackdown on corruption. Najib and former Treasury secretary-general Mohamad Irwan Serigar Abdullah were questioned by anti-graft investigators on Wednesday to help conclude the probe, the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) said in a statement. The two will be brought to a Kuala Lumpur court on Thursday to be charged, the MACC said. "Both of them will be charged together in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Malaysia's Mahathir says Uighurs released because they did nothing wrong - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-uighurs/malaysias-mahathir-says-uighurs-released-because-they-did-nothing-wrong-idUSKCN1MP09J</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEb7DaTe2YpvMantznhNq8IqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 04:06:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-uighurs/malaysias-mahathir-says-uighurs-released-because-they-did-nothing-wrong-idUSKCN1MP09J" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia's Mahathir says Uighurs released because they did nothing wrong&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia freed 11 ethnic Uighur Muslims who fled to the Southeast Asian nation after a Thai jailbreak last year because they did nothing wrong there, Malaysian Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad said on Monday. Reuters, citing the men's lawyer, reported last week that Malaysia had released the 11 from detention and sent them to Turkey, disregarding China's request to hand them to Beijing. "They have done nothing wrong in this country, so they are released," Mahathir said in brief comments to reporters in parliament, the first from the Malaysian government since their release. Malaysia's move w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Feeling 'vindicated,' Malaysia's Anwar takes lawmaker oath - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/4b6968f874844863bee74538f1d522a2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBqFbsPiNwnACFdIwqx8LkcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 05:53:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/4b6968f874844863bee74538f1d522a2" target="_blank"&gt;Feeling 'vindicated,' Malaysia's Anwar takes lawmaker oath&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR, Malaysia (AP) — Malaysian Prime Minister-in-waiting Anwar Ibrahim said he felt "vindicated" after taking his oath as a lawmaker Monday, marking his return to active politics three years after he was imprisoned for sodomy in a charge that critics said was politically motivated. The swearing-in ceremony in parliament followed Anwar's landslide win in a by-election Saturday in the southern coastal town of Port Dickson in which he defeated six other candidates. The seat was vacated after a lawmaker from his party quit, paving the way for Anwar's political comeback. Anwar, 71, join...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Anwar Ibrahim returns to Malaysian politics with landslide byelection victory - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/13/anwar-ibrahim-returns-to-malaysian-politics</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEClNaMkxPVnFheOvLQeg_ZoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 17:55:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/13/anwar-ibrahim-returns-to-malaysian-politics" target="_blank"&gt;Anwar Ibrahim returns to Malaysian politics with landslide byelection victory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Malaysian deputy prime minister Anwar Ibrahim has won a byelection with a landslide victory in a grand political comeback that will help him prepare for his eventual takeover from the current prime minister, Mahathir Mohamad. Anwar was designated as Mahathir’s successor after the two men set aside a bitter feud and joined hands to capture a stunning victory in May’s general election. Anwar could not participate in the election due to a sodomy conviction, a charge that he alleged was politically motivated. He was freed and received a royal pardon days after the polls. Related: Malaysi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Malaysia's Anwar Ibrahim wins parliamentary by-election - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/malaysia-anwar-ibrahim-wins-parliamentary-election-181013134217279.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPwgzVU0JKBVmkN02IA5Zm4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:23:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/malaysia-anwar-ibrahim-wins-parliamentary-election-181013134217279.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia's Anwar Ibrahim wins parliamentary by-election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian politician Anwar Ibrahim has won a parliamentary seat in a by-election, setting the stage for his eventual takeover from Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad. The Election Commission said on Saturday that Anwar received 71 percent of the total votes cast, defeating six other candidates. He got 31,016 votes, while his closest rival secured only 7,456. "I'm, of course, extremely pleased and humbled by the results," Anwar said after the victory, which marks the charismatic politician's political comeback from prison to parliament. "This to my mind is an important milestone, a vote of conf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Malaysia's Anwar wins by-election, steps closer to premiership - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-anwar/malaysias-anwar-wins-by-election-steps-closer-to-premiership-idUSKCN1MN0OF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENEIi9HA1F6XBztw2UaWugoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 16:22:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-anwar/malaysias-anwar-wins-by-election-steps-closer-to-premiership-idUSKCN1MN0OF" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia's Anwar wins by-election, steps closer to premiership&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia's Anwar Ibrahim won a by-election engineered for his return to parliament by an overwhelming majority on Saturday, bringing him closer to the premiership that has been promised to him by former foe, Mahathir Mohamad. The victory marks Anwar's official return to political life just five months after he was freed from jail, and will also be the first time that both he and Mahathir are members of parliament under the same banner after a bitter feud lasting over 20 years. Anwar, who has been the face of Malaysia's Reformasi or Reform movement over the past twenty years, won the seat by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Malaysia politician Anwar Ibrahim returns to politics - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/13/asia/anwar-ibrahim-return-to-politics/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELa-gm4G2scYrtPx68bvkKwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 17:34:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/13/asia/anwar-ibrahim-return-to-politics/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia politician Anwar Ibrahim returns to politics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian politician Anwar Ibrahim won a parliamentary seat Saturday, returning to politics just months after receiving a royal pardon for sodomy. According to state news agency Bernama, 71-year-old Anwar won a special by-election in the town of Port Dickinson. He'll be sworn into office on Monday. His victory means Anwar, once a voice of reform in Malaysia and former Deputy Prime Minister, is one step away from succeeding Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad, Bernama reported. The seat Anwar won was up for grabs after the incumbent, 68-year-old Danyal Balagopal, vacated the seat on September 12...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Lynas seeks ’plan B’ as Malaysia rare earths plant faces threat - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/76e29afa-ccff-11e8-b276-b9069bde0956</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8pdWSClXWZXFYLJT8u3tUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 03:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/76e29afa-ccff-11e8-b276-b9069bde0956" target="_blank"&gt;Lynas seeks ’plan B’ as Malaysia rare earths plant faces threat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lynas, one of the world’s major suppliers of rare earths outside China, is searching for alternative locations in case it is forced to close the world’s largest processing plant of the material in Malaysia following a government review. Amanda Lacaze, chief executive of the Australian-listed company, said she was confident Lynas would pass the environmental review ordered by the ruling coalition, which came to power in Malaysia in May after the surprise electoral victory of Mahathir Mohamad. Ms Lacaze told the Financial Times in an interview that a negative review would alarm investors, c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Malaysia to End Death Penalty and Sedition Act - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/malaysia-to-end-death-penalty-and-sedition-act/4609612.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECK1oB3ioZ1QH1QcdZGCR2YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 18:52:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/malaysia-to-end-death-penalty-and-sedition-act/4609612.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia to End Death Penalty and Sedition Act&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia's government plans to abolish the death penalty and a colonial-era law used to suppress dissent, officials said this week. Law Minister Liew Vui Keong said Wednesday the Cabinet would end the death penalty and halt all scheduled executions until the law takes effect. More than 1,200 people are currently on death row. "All death penalty will be abolished. Full stop," he was reported saying by the New Straits Times. Communications and Multimedia Minister Gobind Singh Deo said Thursday that the Sedition Act, introduced by the British in 1948, will also be repealed. Both proposals are ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>'I love him': Malaysian PM and former rival publicly bury hatchet after 20 years - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/09/malaysian-pm-mahathir-anwar-bury-hatchet-after-20-years</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEfsY1r5z9aTZrW0j6BthUgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 04:22:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/09/malaysian-pm-mahathir-anwar-bury-hatchet-after-20-years" target="_blank"&gt;'I love him': Malaysian PM and former rival publicly bury hatchet after 20 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was almost as though two decades of mudslinging, false accusations and jail sentences had never happened. Appearing at a political rally together for the first time in 20 years, Malaysian prime minister Mahathir Mohamad and his former protege-turned rival Anwar Ibrahim demonstrated they had set aside their bitter political feud once and for all- and even declared their love for each other. “I love him as a father and as a leader,” said Anwar, gesturing to Mahathir who made a surprise appearance in Port Dickson on Monday to pledge his support for Anwar’s return to politics in a by-electio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Mahathir: Malaysia May Introduce New Taxes, Sell Assets to Pay Debt - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/mahathir-malaysia-may-introduce-new-taxes-sell-assets-to-pay-debt/4605469.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFJTY40Dq6lU8fogE532SScqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 03:55:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/mahathir-malaysia-may-introduce-new-taxes-sell-assets-to-pay-debt/4605469.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mahathir: Malaysia May Introduce New Taxes, Sell Assets to Pay Debt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia may introduce new taxes and sell assets such as land to pay down debt, Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad said on Tuesday, as his administration struggles with liabilities of around 1 trillion ringgit ($240.67 billion). Mahathir, who unexpectedly won a general election in May, has blamed the previous administration of Najib Razak for taking the country into such heavy debt, including that of the 1MDB state fund, which is the subject of corruption and money laundering investigations in Malaysia and other countries. The government is also looking for new sources of revenue to make up th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Malaysia ignores China request; frees 11 ethnic Uighurs - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/malaysia-ignores-china-request-frees-11-ethnic-uighurs-181012044948455.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHOeB7KKx5mRXMcJWiWbacIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 06:20:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/malaysia-ignores-china-request-frees-11-ethnic-uighurs-181012044948455.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia ignores China request; frees 11 ethnic Uighurs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia has freed 11 ethnic Uighurs detained last year after they broke out of prison in Thailand and crossed the border, despite a request from Beijing for the men to be returned to China. Prosecutors dropped immigration charges against the group on humanitarian grounds and they flew out of Kuala Lumpur to Turkey on Tuesday, according to their lawyer Fahmi Moin. "The charges were withdrawn because the attorney general's chambers agreed to the [appeal] from our side," Fahmi told Reuters news agency. The decision may further strain ties with China, which has been accused of cracking down on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Malaysia to abolish colonial-era Sedition Act, death penalty - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-deathpenalty/malaysia-to-abolish-colonial-era-sedition-act-death-penalty-idUSKCN1ML1EU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED6akxvhhNe6euC7QGm4Vp0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 13:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-deathpenalty/malaysia-to-abolish-colonial-era-sedition-act-death-penalty-idUSKCN1ML1EU" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia to abolish colonial-era Sedition Act, death penalty&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia's cabinet has ordered the suspension of the colonial-era Sedition Act, widely used to rein in dissent, and is working on doing the same for the death penalty as it prepares to repeal both laws possibly by the end of the year. Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad's coalition romped to a shock win in a May general election on the back of promises to clamp down on rampant corruption and repeal oppressive laws, some of which date back to British rule. Communications and Multimedia Minister Gobind Singh Deo said on Thursday that cabinet had decided to suspend use of the Sedition Act as they ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Downbeat Filipinos buck upbeat Asean mood - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/5dff84f0-d13a-11e8-a9f2-7574db66bcd5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGA1_CMlWOUCA9W3w-beWb8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 17:29:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5dff84f0-d13a-11e8-a9f2-7574db66bcd5" target="_blank"&gt;Downbeat Filipinos buck upbeat Asean mood&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Filipino consumers stood apart from their Asean 5 peers in the third quarter as they turned negative on their economy in the face of rising inflation and slowing growth. The FTCR Asean Economic Sentiment Index (ESI) showed tempered optimism among Malaysians, renewed optimism among Thais and continued bullishness among Indonesian and Vietnamese consumers in the third quarter. The index dipped 1.6 points to 64.3 from the second quarter, remaining well above the 50-mark separating improving from deteriorating sentiment. Philippines: Our ESI for the Philippines dropped 5.8 points to 43.1 in the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Malaysia says it will end death penalty for all crimes - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f881e2fa9b694d5abbaec2da858c513d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO6KezsVY0amgHsh0_nHLpEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 11:15:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f881e2fa9b694d5abbaec2da858c513d" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia says it will end death penalty for all crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR, Malaysia (AP) — Malaysia's new government said it will abolish the death penalty for all crimes and halt all pending executions, a rare move against capital punishment in Asia that human rights groups hailed Thursday as a major advance. More than 1,200 people are on death row in Malaysia, which mandates hanging as punishment for a wide range of crimes including murder, drug trafficking, treason, kidnapping and acts of terror. Law Minister Liew Vui Keong announced Wednesday that the Cabinet had agreed to abolish the death penalty and that amendments to laws with capital punishm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Malaysian prime minister calls Jews 'hook-nosed' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/oct/02/malaysian-prime-minister-mahathir-mohamad-calls-jews-hook-nosed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFzVv6urqyxM4UDqzBC5JuQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 14:55:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/oct/02/malaysian-prime-minister-mahathir-mohamad-calls-jews-hook-nosed" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysian prime minister calls Jews 'hook-nosed'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Malaysian prime minister has described Jews as “hook-nosed” and blamed them for creating the troubles in the Middle East – reigniting accusations of antisemitism against him. Mahathir Mohamad, who at 93 became the world’s oldest head of government after starting his second stint as prime minister in May, has for decades been accused of antisemitism for his attacks against Jews, whom he has accused of perpetrating a humanitarian crisis in the Palestinian territories. “If you are going to be truthful, the problem in the Middle East began with the creation of Israel. That is the truth. But...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Malaysia PM Accuses Gulf Governments Of "Protecting" Individuals Linked To 1MDB Scandal - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/10/03/malaysia-pm-accuses-gulf-governments-of-protecting-individuals-linked-to-1mdb-scandal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBbbn-zxkk9IwXyx8FljGwwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dominicdudley/2018/10/03/malaysia-pm-accuses-gulf-governments-of-protecting-individuals-linked-to-1mdb-scandal/" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia PM Accuses Gulf Governments Of "Protecting" Individuals Linked To 1MDB Scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia’s prime minister Dr Mahatir Mohamad has suggested his government may struggle to pursue individuals in Saudi Arabia and the UAE in connection with the multi-billion dollar corruption allegations at Malaysia’s sovereign wealth fund 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB). The names of several companies and individuals with links to Saudi Arabia and the UAE have cropped up in the course of investigations into 1MDB by authorities around the world. A court filing in 2017 from the U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) cited, among others, UAE-based International Petroleum Investment Company (IPI...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Wife of Malaysia's ex-PM Najib charged with money laundering - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb-rosmah/wife-of-malaysias-ex-pm-najib-charged-with-money-laundering-idUSKCN1ME05K</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHjJLGSRkEmNNQXxzGXArnwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 10:47:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb-rosmah/wife-of-malaysias-ex-pm-najib-charged-with-money-laundering-idUSKCN1ME05K" target="_blank"&gt;Wife of Malaysia's ex-PM Najib charged with money laundering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wife of former Malaysian prime minister Najib Razak was charged with 17 money laundering offences on Thursday, as anti-graft agents investigate billions of dollars missing from state coffers. Rosmah Mansor, criticized for her extravagant lifestyle as first lady of Malaysia, and Najib, are at the center of a wide-ranging graft probe launched after Prime Minster Mahathir Mohamad's stunning election victory in May. Najib faces 32 charges from money laundering to abuse of power and criminal breach of trust over billions of dollars that went missing from state fund 1Malaysia Development Berh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Malaysian PM doubles down on ‘hook-nosed Jews’ comments, blames Israel for ME woes - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/440171-malaysia-prime-minister-jews-comments/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELoVWj952ypnMhRKaYJUKJ8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/440171-malaysia-prime-minister-jews-comments/" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysian PM doubles down on ‘hook-nosed Jews’ comments, blames Israel for ME woes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia's nonagenarian prime minister has defended his controversial statements referring to Jews as “hook-nosed,” doubling down to assert that the creation of Israel has triggered most of the current troubles in the Middle East. Mahathir Mohamad’s comments came after being asked about alleged instances of being a “proud anti-Semite” during his long career in politics, by journalist Zeinab Badawi during an interview on BBC’s Hardtalk program on Tuesday. “If you are going to be truthful, the problem in the Middle East began with the creation of Israel. That is the truth. But I cannot say th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Malaysia ex-PM's wife pleads not guilty to money laundering - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f769ed693a224cc6bd733673664af68c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEjhU4zs6RrfotMlH8d1PEMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 05:46:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f769ed693a224cc6bd733673664af68c" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia ex-PM's wife pleads not guilty to money laundering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR, Malaysia (AP) — The wife of former Malaysian Prime Minister Najjib Razak pleaded not guilty Thursday to laundering illegal proceeds linked to the graft scandal at the 1MDB state investment fund that led to her husband's shocking electoral loss. Rosmah Mansor was charged with 12 counts of receiving proceeds from unlawful activities totaling nearly 7.1 million ringgit ($1.7 million) in her bank account between 2013 and 2017. Another five counts against her allege she failed to declare taxes on the money she received. The charges sheets didn't mention 1MDB or where the allegedly ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Former Malaysian Prime Minister's wife, Rosmah Mansor, arrested - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/03/asia/malaysia-1mdb-rosmah-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP4RU7vHbmhUqVI6rkTPUcUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 02:06:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/03/asia/malaysia-1mdb-rosmah-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Malaysian Prime Minister's wife, Rosmah Mansor, arrested&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian authorities arrested Datin Seri Rosmah Mansor, the wife of former Malaysian Prime Minister Najib Razak, on Wednesday, state media reported, citing the government's anti-corruption body. The Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission confirmed Rosmah's arrest in a statement posted on its social media accounts. Rosmah will face "several charges" under the Anti-Money Laundering, Prevention of Terrorism Financing and Proceeds of Unlawful Activities Act 2001, according to the anti-corruption agency's statement reported by state-run Bernama. Rosmah is expected to be charged Thursday morning i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Malaysia to investigate Australian rare earth miner Lynas - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/dccf3226-c636-11e8-ba8f-ee390057b8c9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDtPda8aeKcvTteeMcSvee8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 11:41:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/dccf3226-c636-11e8-ba8f-ee390057b8c9" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia to investigate Australian rare earth miner Lynas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia is investigating a rare earths processing plant run by Australia’s Lynas Corp, which could threaten one of the only sources of supply of the critical elements outside of China. Fuziah Salleh, a Malaysian MP and a deputy minister in the prime minister’s department, said the three-month review will focus on the plant’s radioactive waste management and impact on the environment, in line with the manifesto of the ruling coalition, which came into power after an astonishing electoral victory by Mahathir Mohamad in May. The review is the latest reassessment of projects launched under Naj...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Wife of Former Malaysian Leader Arrested in Graft Scandal - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/rosmah-mansor-arrested/4597605.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOsXfetUZm63Q_WBV98yZ74qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 09:33:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/rosmah-mansor-arrested/4597605.html" target="_blank"&gt;Wife of Former Malaysian Leader Arrested in Graft Scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wife of former Malaysian Prime Minister Najib Razak was arrested Wednesday by the anti-graft agency and is expected to be charged in a scandal involving the 1MDB state investment fund, a government official said. The official, who declined to be named due to the sensitivity of the matter, said Rosmah Mansor was arrested after she was questioned by the agency for a third time over alleged theft and money laundering at the fund. Rosmah's lawyer, K. Kumaraendran, confirmed her arrest but declined to give details. The agency was expected to issue a statement soon. Wearing a bright green tra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Malaysia's former first lady arrested in 1MDB anti-corruption probe - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-04/malaysias-former-first-lady-rosmah-mansor-arrested/10335482</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMIUp96m1wByGiW6Et0R9z0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 19:39:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-04/malaysias-former-first-lady-rosmah-mansor-arrested/10335482" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia's former first lady arrested in 1MDB anti-corruption probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anti-corruption authorities have arrested Malaysia's former first lady Rosmah Mansor, who will spend a night in detention before being taken to court to face money laundering charges. Key points: - Anti-corruption police say Rosmah Mansor will face several charges - Her husband Najib Razak is currently facing 32 charges over the 1MDB scandal - US authorities say more than US$4.5 billion was misappropriated from the fund The Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) said it arrested Ms Rosmah, 66, who will face charges in court on Thursday for allegedly infringing an anti-money laundering ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>ASEAN Talks Tough on Rohingya Crisis - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/asean-talks-tough-rohingya-crisis/4601349.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL77R819hzrSz1iJLQaa8VYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:19:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/asean-talks-tough-rohingya-crisis/4601349.html" target="_blank"&gt;ASEAN Talks Tough on Rohingya Crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A groundswell of international condemnation of Myanmar's civilian leader Aung San Suu Kyi and her government's refusal to take action on atrocities committed against Myanmar's Rohingya minority is spreading closer to home. Nearly 700,000 ethnic Rohingya Muslims from Myanmar's Rakhine state have fled a brutal military crackdown that has seen systematic rape, mass killings and the torching of entire villages in what the U.N. has called a "textbook example of ethnic cleansing." Member states of the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN), who usually stand by the block's mantra of non-i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Wife of ex-Malaysian prime minister charged with money laundering after luxury items seized - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/04/wife-ex-malaysian-prime-minister-charged-money-laundering-luxury/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDiqHy33RkMl4ksGsRXo-6kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 10:34:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/04/wife-ex-malaysian-prime-minister-charged-money-laundering-luxury/" target="_blank"&gt;Wife of ex-Malaysian prime minister charged with money laundering after luxury items seized&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The luxury-loving wife of Malaysia's former prime minister has been charged with money laundering and tax evasion linked to a multi-billion-dollar scandal that helped bring down the country's previous government. Rosmah Mansor, the 66-year-old wife of former prime minister Najib Razak, pleaded not guilty to 17 charges that could see her spend the rest of her life in prison. Reviled in Malaysia for her lavish overseas shopping sprees and fetish for Birkin handbags as well as dazzling jewellery, Rosmah was released on bail after spending the night in detention at the office of the country's a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Malaysia's Mahathir: A portrait of the premier as an old man - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/363a7fb5a7cc469d93b67b9285790b9f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG7ClQeZd4Hf8i5AedmGI9sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 12:14:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/363a7fb5a7cc469d93b67b9285790b9f" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia's Mahathir: A portrait of the premier as an old man&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For a few seconds Thursday, Mahathir Mohamad looked his age. The 93-year-old once and current prime minister of Malaysia wobbled a bit as he clasped the railing, cautiously mounted the four stairs leading to the stage in the bowels of the Asia Society and shuffled over to the podium. Then Mahathir, called a strongman by his critics so often that he has a joke ready about it, faced the packed auditorium. He smiled broadly and began talking. And the years, maybe even a decade or two, seemed to melt away. First came the speech: 20 minutes without a single note, relying on the w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Wife of former Malaysian PM charged with money laundering - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1b4912ee-c775-11e8-ba8f-ee390057b8c9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELm-dZhTr7bECT4KKYqZk-oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 05:30:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1b4912ee-c775-11e8-ba8f-ee390057b8c9" target="_blank"&gt;Wife of former Malaysian PM charged with money laundering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rosmah Mansor, the wife of former Malaysian prime minister Najib Razak, has pleaded not guilty to 17 counts of money laundering and tax evasion in a court hearing that marks an escalation in the south-east Asian country’s crackdown on corruption. The court hearing comes as the new government headed by Mahathir Mohamad intensifies an investigation into scandal-ridden 1Malaysia Development Berhad, the state investment fund set up by Mr Najib in 2009 from which an alleged $4.5bn has gone missing. Ms Rosmah has been accused of handling funds from unlawful activities and of tax evasion involving...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>U.N. rights expert urges Malaysia to end child marriage - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-un-children/un-rights-expert-urges-malaysia-to-end-child-marriage-idUSKCN1MB2B7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH7y023S1jHA853iDZ4xY0YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 11:12:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-un-children/un-rights-expert-urges-malaysia-to-end-child-marriage-idUSKCN1MB2B7" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. rights expert urges Malaysia to end child marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia should ban child marriage immediately, a United Nations human rights expert said on Monday, stepping into a controversy that has raged since reports in July that a 44-year-old Malaysian man had married an 11-year-old Thai girl. Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad's government, in power since May, has promised to raise the legal age of marriage to 18, provoking a backlash from some conservative Islamic leaders who argue that early marriage provides an answer to social ills like premarital sex and pregnancies out of wedlock. Maud de Boer-Buquicchio, the U.N. special rapporteur on the sal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Six Malaysian rescue divers drown in whirlpool trying to save stranded teenager from water - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/rescue-divers-drown-die-whirlpool-malaysia-puchong-kuala-lumpur-a8568396.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOBQv4TWkaFgISgT07jXNlEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 13:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/rescue-divers-drown-die-whirlpool-malaysia-puchong-kuala-lumpur-a8568396.html" target="_blank"&gt;Six Malaysian rescue divers drown in whirlpool trying to save stranded teenager from water&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six Malaysian divers have died after they were caught in a strong whirlpool while trying to save a teenager trapped in a disused mining pool. The team who were members of the country’s fire brigade rescue department were killed during an operation in the town of Puchong, near Kuala Lumpur, on Wednesday evening. Local authorities reported divers were dispatched to search for a 17-year-old, who was feared dead after slipping into the pool while fishing with friends. Police said the divers, who were all tied to a single rope, had then become trapped in a vortex that had formed in the water. Re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Asian victors may find anti-China campaign vows hard to keep - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/ee0de0e8342e4e33aaabf1ead1427aac</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA1smOkghyo35h2c4CxWpKcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 08:02:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/ee0de0e8342e4e33aaabf1ead1427aac" target="_blank"&gt;Asian victors may find anti-China campaign vows hard to keep&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — Three Muslim-majority Asian countries have elected leaders who campaigned on a promise to temper China's growing influence, but analysts say reducing the foothold of the world's second-largest economy won't be easy because of the billions of dollars in development projects that are already under way. The surprising elections in recent months of nonagenarian Mahathir Mohamad in Malaysia, cricketer Imran Khan in Pakistan and longtime opposition lawmaker Ibrahim Mohamed Solih in the Maldives buck a regional trend toward authoritarianism, and could present an obstacle for Chine...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Malaysian rethink on projects risks contagion in the region - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8fe2f122-9649-11e8-95f8-8640db9060a7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFVsRzZzNgoPvfFsGW9_SUgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 21:03:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8fe2f122-9649-11e8-95f8-8640db9060a7" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysian rethink on projects risks contagion in the region&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Mahathir Mohamad swept to power in a surprise election victory over his former protégé, Najib Razak, leaders of countries along China’s Belt and Road sat up and took notice. Mr Najib had been an advocate of the Belt and Road Initiative, and had promised to fast-track more than $30bn of Chinese port, rail and other infrastructure projects in the country. Mr Mahathir meanwhile had spent much of the time on the campaign trail speaking out against the poor potential returns and growing debt burden for countries that agreed to Chinese infrastructure investment. Since his return to power, Mr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Malaysia's ex-first lady questioned for 13 hours in 1MDB probe - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb-rosmah/malaysias-ex-first-lady-questioned-for-13-hours-in-1mdb-probe-idUSKCN1M606E</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELw3mreUT_ljsKD2FMDbiQwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 16:31:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-1mdb-rosmah/malaysias-ex-first-lady-questioned-for-13-hours-in-1mdb-probe-idUSKCN1M606E" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia's ex-first lady questioned for 13 hours in 1MDB probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian anti-graft investigators questioned Rosmah Mansor, the wife of former Prime Minister Najib Razak, for nearly 13 hours on Wednesday over a corruption investigation at state fund 1MDB. Najib has been charged with money laundering, abuse of power and criminal breach of trust in the investigation into how billions of dollars went missing from 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB). Najib, who has pleaded not guilty to the charges and consistently denied wrongdoing, lost a national election in May. Last week, Azam Baki, the deputy commissioner of operations at Malaysian Anti-Corruption Co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China, Russia take up globalism mantle as US sheds it at UN - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/484660ba788b4ca48d50a7a13a212870</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOeDXAB-0Oi8yn8B94tHaNYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 20:42:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/484660ba788b4ca48d50a7a13a212870" target="_blank"&gt;China, Russia take up globalism mantle as US sheds it at UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Days after U.S. President Donald Trump denounced globalism before world leaders at the United Nations, China and Russia positioned themselves Friday as defenders of internationalism that are keeping promises when Washington is backing away from them. Chinese Foreign Minister Wang Yi denied his country was trying to eclipse the U.S. as a world leader, but his speech at the U.N. General Assembly was a stark contrast to Trump's "America First" message. It came amid rising tensions between the U.S. and China, which Trump accused this week of interfering in the upcoming U.S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Former Malaysian PM Najib slapped with 25 more corruption charges - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/20/asia/najib-razak-1mdb-charges-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEor2sufhaZPSCvlTINo49kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 12:06:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/20/asia/najib-razak-1mdb-charges-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Malaysian PM Najib slapped with 25 more corruption charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Malaysian Prime Minister Najib Razak has been hit with 25 more corruption-related charges over allegations that he siphoned off $681 million from the public. Najib pleaded not guilty to each offense. They add to the list of charges he faces in relation to a multibillion-dollar scandal involving the state fund 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB) set up under his leadership. The former leader has steadfastly maintained his innocence. Of the new charges, nine relate to receiving illicit funds; five to the use of illicit funds; and seven charges are on transferring illicit funds to other...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Beijing insists BRI is no Marshall plan - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/48f21df8-9c9b-11e8-88de-49c908b1f264</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH-TGHxDVovd4daTlyQ8bxIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 21:03:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/48f21df8-9c9b-11e8-88de-49c908b1f264" target="_blank"&gt;Beijing insists BRI is no Marshall plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese officials are often hard-pressed to explain exactly what the Belt and Road Initiative is, but they are sure of one thing that it is not. It is not, they insist, a Chinese Marshall plan for the 21st century. For the Chinese Communist party, the US-led effort to rebuild western Europe was as much a political project as an economic one, aimed at containing the Soviet Union and its eastern allies. Such associations with President Xi Jinping’s signature foreign policy project are not welcome in Beijing. “[The BRI] is neither a Marshall plan nor a geostrategic concept,” Wang Yi, China’s f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>