<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Global Citizen Festival - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZpZDJSME9UZHROUklDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:09:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Sammy Gyamfi chides Akufo-Addo for 'secretly' attending Global Citizen Concert - GhanaWeb</title><link>https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/Sammy-Gyamfi-chides-Akufo-Addo-for-secretly-attending-Global-Citizen-Concert-706155</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMihgFodHRwczovL3d3dy5naGFuYXdlYi5jb20vR2hhbmFIb21lUGFnZS9OZXdzQXJjaGl2ZS9TYW1teS1HeWFtZmktY2hpZGVzLUFrdWZvLUFkZG8tZm9yLXNlY3JldGx5LWF0dGVuZGluZy1HbG9iYWwtQ2l0aXplbi1Db25jZXJ0LTcwNjE1NdIBAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:50:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/Sammy-Gyamfi-chides-Akufo-Addo-for-secretly-attending-Global-Citizen-Concert-706155" target="_blank"&gt;Sammy Gyamfi chides Akufo-Addo for 'secretly' attending Global Citizen Concert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GhanaWeb&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Communications Officer of the opposition National Democratic Congress (NDC), Sammy Gyamfi has taken a swipe at President Akufo-Addo for “secretly ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ghanaweb.com">GhanaWeb</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/CJOT7i3RbwV_HqJsHY1yzW5WnrxWqOI8BxMw2csG1x-y0Lx6dbrBnanpwhefLQmOi04aD3RylHJlfQbJmy1c_RT-tkYc3w=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Photos of Jackie Appiah, Dumas, KOD at Global Citizen Festival in SA - GhanaWeb</title><link>https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/entertainment/Photos-of-Jackie-Appiah-Dumas-KOD-at-Global-Citizen-Festival-In-SA-705798</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMifmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdoYW5hd2ViLmNvbS9HaGFuYUhvbWVQYWdlL2VudGVydGFpbm1lbnQvUGhvdG9zLW9mLUphY2tpZS1BcHBpYWgtRHVtYXMtS09ELWF0LUdsb2JhbC1DaXRpemVuLUZlc3RpdmFsLUluLVNBLTcwNTc5ONIBAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:02:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/entertainment/Photos-of-Jackie-Appiah-Dumas-KOD-at-Global-Citizen-Festival-In-SA-705798" target="_blank"&gt;Photos of Jackie Appiah, Dumas, KOD at Global Citizen Festival in SA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GhanaWeb&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the fact that Ghanaian artists presence were not felt on the Global Citizen Festival stage held in South Africa, several Ghanaian showbiz personalities ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ghanaweb.com">GhanaWeb</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/TbANQ0TzvWF0Fr239jPdmdLnUGnYun5kHWzmqsls3fNiKcQOEr9svD3SvCO-ElFbBMM5UDqHYMrstz9py9wwfkF8Ba9cog=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Ed Sheeran responds after being attacked for 'slobby' outfit during Beyonce duet - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ed-sheeran-beyonce-outfit-duet-perfect-global-citizen-festival-south-africa-response-a8671856.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB6sPni1nsqeN2OIo-TxX-oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ed-sheeran-beyonce-outfit-duet-perfect-global-citizen-festival-south-africa-response-a8671856.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ed Sheeran responds after being attacked for 'slobby' outfit during Beyonce duet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ed Sheeran has jokingly responded to those who criticised him for being too dressed down while duetting with Beyoncé. An image of the internationally famous singers performing at the Global Citizen Festival: Mandela 100 in Johannesburg went viral as commenters acknowledged the contrast of Sheeran’s T-shirt and jeans combination against Beyoncé’s flamboyant pink dress. The 27-year-old “Shape of You” singer saw the funny side, posting an instagram story featuring an image of the offending T-shirt – featuring the logo HOAXUKSINCE94 – alongside a purchase link. Continuing the joke, Sheeran late...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ed Sheeran Responds To Comments That He Looked Like A Slob Next To Beyoncé - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ed-sheeran-responds-to-comments-that-he-looked-like-a-slob-next-to-beyonce_us_5c09621ae4b0bf813ef55960</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFItA3l_FStneKBgH-fKA7UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:53:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ed-sheeran-responds-to-comments-that-he-looked-like-a-slob-next-to-beyonce_us_5c09621ae4b0bf813ef55960" target="_blank"&gt;Ed Sheeran Responds To Comments That He Looked Like A Slob Next To Beyoncé&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ed Sheeran is owning his look with a tongue-in-cheek response to backlash he sparked online. On Sunday, the “Shape of You” singer performed a duet with Beyoncé at the Global Citizen Festival in Johannesburg, South Africa. While she wore an extravagant pink gown, he looked like he just rolled out of bed. The clashing looks sparked a discussion online about double standards. Many criticized Sheeran for dressing down. I get this. Even tho I appreciate good musicians in normal clothes the double standard is ridiculous... what is expected of female vs male artists. https://t.co/xLEcNXVuX7 — Fat ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Beyoncé, Ed Sheeran and our expectations of men and women - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2018/dec/05/beyonce-ed-sheeran-and-our-expectations-of-men-and-women</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE2fpObbiZwU_0p0cxVsd7UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:31:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2018/dec/05/beyonce-ed-sheeran-and-our-expectations-of-men-and-women" target="_blank"&gt;Beyoncé, Ed Sheeran and our expectations of men and women&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why are people upset about the photos of Beyoncé and Ed Sheeran performing together? Michael, by email Ahh, to see a world in a grain of sand, as William Blake wrote. Just possibly, he was not referring to Ed Sheeran and Beyoncé, but also he possibly was. Who are we to impose limitations on genius? Anyway, last weekend, two of the biggest pop stars in the world, Beyoncé and Sheeran – Sheyoncé? Beeran? – performed Sheeran’s song Perfect together at the Global Citizen festival: Mandela 100 in South Africa. To use a rather au courant phrase, the optics were bad. There was Sheeran, looking as h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Muggings mar international charity concert in South Africa - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/37acba6b88d54aa49e6d1487957f4101</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELGBDTPqZHUknMi05BffrtIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:11:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/37acba6b88d54aa49e6d1487957f4101" target="_blank"&gt;Muggings mar international charity concert in South Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — A spate of muggings early Monday marred a charity concert in South Africa at which Beyonce, Jay-Z and other stars performed in honor of Nelson Mandela. Tens of thousands flocked to the FNB Stadium in Johannesburg on Sunday for a music festival also featuring Usher, Pharrell Williams, Trevor Noah, Oprah Winfrey, Naomi Campbell and South African President Cyril Ramaphosa. Most people had a good time and got home safely, but the night turned ugly for some when they were accosted by thugs as they left the stadium. The witness accounts of thieves brazenly assaulting a crowd s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Beyoncé fans saw just 25 minutes of performance via streaming - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/entertainment/beyonce-global-citizen-festival/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPcIUWMdQ5E7vtlC1GzZkKgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 17:28:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/entertainment/beyonce-global-citizen-festival/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Beyoncé fans saw just 25 minutes of performance via streaming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyoncé and husband Jay-Z were the most anticipated act at the Global Citizen Festival in South Africa this weekend. But only fans who bought a ticket and attended got to see their full performance. Other fans were crushed that only 25 minutes of the pair's appearance at the Mandela 100 event in Johannesburg was streamed. The superstar couple headlined the concert in honor of what would have been President Nelson Mandela's 100th birthday on July 18. Suffice it to say, The Hive was not happy. A tweet from the official account of the TV Channel SABC1 explained the reasoning. "Please note that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Naomi Campbell among stars at Johannesburg concert to honour Mandela - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/02/beyonce-among-stars-at-johannesburg-concert-to-honour-mandela</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBQWxMgqHszQvO4EO-oPpkMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 17:14:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/02/beyonce-among-stars-at-johannesburg-concert-to-honour-mandela" target="_blank"&gt;Naomi Campbell among stars at Johannesburg concert to honour Mandela&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyoncé, Oprah Winfrey, Naomi Campbell, Pharrell Williams, Usher and other international stars gathered in Johannesburg on Sunday for a charity concert honouring Nelson Mandela a century after he was born. Thousands poured into the South African city’s FNB stadium for Global Citizen Festival: Mandela 100. Singer Bob Geldof, who organised the Live Aid concerts for Africa, was also there. Global Citizen, an advocacy group, campaigns for an end to extreme poverty, and other causes. It says many people won tickets to Sunday’s concert through charity work and petition-signing. World leaders prev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Beyonce and other stars to perform at Mandela festival - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/33e0fba9a9f14bf297e88b9d413dab66</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG4RghQG5aYoLj5OAHo35sMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 15:40:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/33e0fba9a9f14bf297e88b9d413dab66" target="_blank"&gt;Beyonce and other stars to perform at Mandela festival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Beyonce and other international stars have gathered in South Africa for a charity concert honoring Nelson Mandela, a century after he was born. Pharrell Williams, Trevor Noah and Oprah Winfrey were among those headlining the Global Citizen Festival: Mandela 100 at Johannesburg's FNB Stadium on Sunday. Model Naomi Campbell and singer Bob Geldof, who organized the Live Aid concerts for Africa, are also attending. Global Citizen, an advocacy group, campaigns for an end to extreme poverty and other causes. It says many people won tickets to Sunday's concert through charity w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Beyonce to Lead Mandela Tribute Concert - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/beyonce-to-lead-mandela-tribute-concert/4683339.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK1d8hYT-q6dV9-YNixvMowqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 14:02:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/beyonce-to-lead-mandela-tribute-concert/4683339.html" target="_blank"&gt;Beyonce to Lead Mandela Tribute Concert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyonce will lead an all-star line-up that includes Ed Sheeran, Jay-Z and Usher in Johannesburg on Sunday when she performs at a concert to honour the life and legacy of Nelson Mandela. The concert is the climax of a year of events celebrating the centennial of Mandela's birth in 1918, and is part of a campaign to tackle poverty, child malnutrition and boost gender equality. This year's Global Citizen Festival will be held at Johannesburg's 94,736-capacity FNB stadium with the concert due to begin at 1200 GMT. Thousands of music fans, many of whom had been given free tickets in return for a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Beyonce to perform at South African concert honoring Mandela - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/500e458d0c9d4cd096de21387d549c1e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKz1lR0DNxL5-haEzjGBGJgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 17:45:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/500e458d0c9d4cd096de21387d549c1e" target="_blank"&gt;Beyonce to perform at South African concert honoring Mandela&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Beyonce, Jay-Z and Ed Sheeran are among the stars scheduled to perform at a South African concert on Sunday in honor of the life and legacy of Nelson Mandela, a century after he was born. The Global Citizen Festival: Mandela 100 will be hosted in Johannesburg by South Africa's Motsepe Foundation, which seeks to reduce poverty through education and job creation. The foundation is partnering with Global Citizen, an international advocacy group that supports sustainable development goals set by the United Nations. The group is also promoting other events ahead of the festiv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Beyoncé Pens Letter To Nelson Mandela: 'Your Work And Your Sacrifices Were Not In Vain' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/beyonce-nelson-mandela-letter_us_5bfed95ee4b03ce3f6e6180c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHRXmVcFeyqLtEoEQ6gQFNgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:53:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/beyonce-nelson-mandela-letter_us_5bfed95ee4b03ce3f6e6180c" target="_blank"&gt;Beyoncé Pens Letter To Nelson Mandela: 'Your Work And Your Sacrifices Were Not In Vain'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyoncé is honoring the late Nelson Mandela with a powerful open letter ahead of her performance at a festival celebrating the former South African president next month. The “Everything Is Love” singer and her husband, Jay-Z, are set to appear at the Global Citizen Festival: Mandela 100 in Johannesburg, South Africa, on Dec. 2 to mark Mandela’s legacy and the 100th anniversary of the anti-apartheid leader’s birth. In a letter titled “Dear Madiba,” also published in the South African newspaper Sowetan, Beyoncé explains how the lessons she took away from a 2004 meeting with Mandela have becom...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>California Governor Plans to Host 2018 Global Climate Summit - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/california-governor-plans-host-global-climate-summit/3931543.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENLVRU1WCHapWEedmsBmUzYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:01:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/california-governor-plans-host-global-climate-summit/3931543.html" target="_blank"&gt;California Governor Plans to Host 2018 Global Climate Summit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;California Governor Jerry Brown has announced that a Global Climate Action summit will be held in San Francisco in September 2018, in a challenge to President Donald Trump's plan to withdraw the United States from the Paris climate accord. Nearly 200 nations have signed the 2015 agreement to reduce greenhouse gas emissions, which are widely thought to be responsible for rising temperatures, and Brown is one of a number of local and regional leaders working to build coalitions without Trump. Brown spoke by video on Thursday to the Global Citizen Festival in Hamburg, Germany, saying the U.S. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Stevie Wonder, Green Day &amp; The Chainsmokers On Board For The 2017 Global Citizen Festival - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2017/08/01/stevie-wonder-green-day-the-chainsmokers-on-board-for-the-2017-global-citizen-festival/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFR-6-GAdHXDlPQ7CtJX_UAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 11:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2017/08/01/stevie-wonder-green-day-the-chainsmokers-on-board-for-the-2017-global-citizen-festival/" target="_blank"&gt;Stevie Wonder, Green Day &amp; The Chainsmokers On Board For The 2017 Global Citizen Festival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES, CA – APRIL 15: Musician Stevie Wonder onstage at Stevie Wonder presented with ‘Key of Life’ Award at the ASCAP ‘I Create Music’ Expo on April 15, 2017, in Los Angeles, California. (Photo by Tommaso Boddi/Getty Images for ASCAP ) As summer comes to a close, New York City residents still do have something to look forward to: the annual Global Citizen Festival, which this year returns to Central Park’s Great Lawn on September 23, and which is bringing some of the most beloved musicians still working today to the stage. This year, the event is set to be headlined by none other than...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Stevie Wonder Interrupts Concert To 'Take A Knee' For America - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/stevie-wonder-takes-a-knee_us_59c70579e4b0cdc77331bd6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENnwCY0N0hv5J6cNHcetrb0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 03:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/stevie-wonder-takes-a-knee_us_59c70579e4b0cdc77331bd6c" target="_blank"&gt;Stevie Wonder Interrupts Concert To 'Take A Knee' For America&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stevie Wonder just expressed his solidarity with Colin Kaepernick’s protests against police brutality and racial injustice against black people. Before performing at the annual Global Citizen Festival in New York City on Saturday night, the 67-year-old music legend took the stage and then took a knee, mimicking a gesture of protest first used by Kaepernick, a former San Francisco 49er quarterback, during national anthems. “Tonight, I’m taking a knee for America,” Wonder said to the audience. “But not just one knee, I’m taking both knees, both knees in prayer for our planet, our future, our ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Jay Z and Coldplay to share festival bill in Mumbai - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2016/nov/09/jay-z-coldplay-share-global-citizen-festival-bill-mumbai-india</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgVCfhKB_84x0KMAP8LA80qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 08:50:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2016/nov/09/jay-z-coldplay-share-global-citizen-festival-bill-mumbai-india" target="_blank"&gt;Jay Z and Coldplay to share festival bill in Mumbai&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jay Z and Coldplay are to share the bill when both play their first ever show in India. The two acts are to appear in Mumbai on 19 November, and the inaugural Indian leg of the Global Citizen festival. Global Citizen, which is intended to encourage social awareness and activism, has taken place in New York annually since 2012, with Chris Martin as creative director. Both acts have previously played the New York event – Jay Z in 2014 and Coldplay in 2015. The festival is free for people who perform various charitable acts. Related: Chris Martin: ‘Coldplay are saying the opposite of walls and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How This Startup Grew To Handle Security At First-Ever Global Citizen Festival In India - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/abehal/2017/01/24/how-this-startup-grew-to-handle-security-at-first-ever-global-citizen-festival-in-india/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDkE10VkEC7rTRvuD-1-wLYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 03:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/abehal/2017/01/24/how-this-startup-grew-to-handle-security-at-first-ever-global-citizen-festival-in-india/" target="_blank"&gt;How This Startup Grew To Handle Security At First-Ever Global Citizen Festival In India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global Citizen India Festival Fire Safety Team. Photo courtesy of Momentum India. When Jay Z and Coldplay rocked the first-ever Global Citizen Festival in India last year, attendees might not even have noticed the 15 medical centers operating at the venue in Mumbai – a rarity for an Indian event. The event, attended by 80,000 people including India’s Prime Minister Narendra Modi and Bollywood celebrities, clearly demanded high-level risk and security assessment and crowd management. A young startup Momentum India, founded by Rohan Oberoi, who heads up the company with co-founder Himmat Ran...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Sean Parker: the internet is not the answer for those seeking change - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/sep/20/sean-parker-the-internet-is-not-the-answer-for-those-seeking-change</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGnE6R5g_SgL0RJeuZYv3cqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 16:06:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/sep/20/sean-parker-the-internet-is-not-the-answer-for-those-seeking-change" target="_blank"&gt;Sean Parker: the internet is not the answer for those seeking change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sean Parker is one of the biggest names associated with the earliest days of social media, but the tech billionaire on Tuesday urged those interested in activism – especially against the Trump administration – to go offline if they wanted to make their voices heard. Related: How social media saved socialism “As much as I thought the internet could be our salvation, I eventually came to the conclusion that we have to solve our own problems, and it took the election of Donald Trump to wake everyone up,” he said. Parker, the creator of Napster and an early president of Facebook, took a shot at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Livestreaming Takes Over At Festivals Like Global Citizen, Panorama - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccalerner/2017/09/23/streaming-takes-over-at-festivals-like-global-citizen-panorama/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELzUnWobRXsJXxVmQOg7Ph4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccalerner/2017/09/23/streaming-takes-over-at-festivals-like-global-citizen-panorama/" target="_blank"&gt;Livestreaming Takes Over At Festivals Like Global Citizen, Panorama&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not going to be in Central Park for Global Citizen Festival today? Don’t sweat it —through online streaming, you can get a look at the action without a ticket. “Our live stream allows us to reach an international audience of people who can tune in to see their favorite artists while learning about important issues and taking action,” explains David Beame, Global Events and Experiences Director for Global Citizen. “We have one goal with our live stream, which is to reach as many people as possible throughout the world, and inspire them to take action to end extreme poverty.” During the first...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Celebs are all over #TakeAKnee - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/09/27/entertainment/celebs-take-a-knee/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDvbfsr_7kku9XZUNJaFKoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 18:47:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/09/27/entertainment/celebs-take-a-knee/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Celebs are all over #TakeAKnee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hollywood is dropping to one knee. It was a full weekend of the NFL responding to President Trump's comments regarding firing players like Colin Kapernick who have chosen to kneel during the National Anthem to draw attention to racial injustice. #TakeAKnee trended and now a few celebs are also visibly showing their support. On Tuesday, "Grey's Anatomy" creator Shonda Rhimes joined some stars of that show and Debbie Allen, who has both acted on and directed episodes of the ABC drama, to kneel "in solidarity of racial justice" while also celebrating their 300th episode. "Grey's" star Ellen Po...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Global Citizen Music Festival Is Taking Over NYC For An Entire Week This Year - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2017/09/19/the-global-citizen-music-festival-is-taking-over-nyc-for-an-entire-week-this-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEImGWKdzQ4m-ZvxjC7lkjPEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2017/09/19/the-global-citizen-music-festival-is-taking-over-nyc-for-an-entire-week-this-year/" target="_blank"&gt;The Global Citizen Music Festival Is Taking Over NYC For An Entire Week This Year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congresswoman Nancy Pelosi speaks onstage at the 2016 Global Citizen Festival in Central Park to end extreme poverty by 2030 at Central Park on September 24, 2016, in New York City. / AFP / ANGELA WEISS (Photo credit should read ANGELA WEISS/AFP/Getty Images) Since it first made a splashy debut back in 2012, the Global Citizen Festival has become one of the biggest and most highly-anticipated musical events of the year in New York City, and that’s no easy task. There is so much going on in the Big Apple every single day, so to not only grab the attention of tens of thousands of people for a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Hugh Jackman, Lupita Nyong'o to Co-host New York's Global Citizen Fest - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/hugh-jackman-lupita-nyongo-co-host-global-citizen-fest-new-york/4021092.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIli6ppTPFCNam0ow-ndReUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 19:11:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/hugh-jackman-lupita-nyongo-co-host-global-citizen-fest-new-york/4021092.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hugh Jackman, Lupita Nyong'o to Co-host New York's Global Citizen Fest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hugh Jackman, Lupita Nyong'o, Aaron Paul and Demi Lovato will co-host this year's Global Citizen Festival, an annual free event held in New York's Central Park. Performers at the Sept. 23 event include Stevie Wonder, Green Day, The Killers, The Lumineers, The Chainsmokers, Pharrell Williams, Big Sean, Andra Day and Alessia Cara. The organization announced Friday that Frieda Pinto, Connie Britton, Deborra-lee Furness, Joan Smalls, Kal Penn, Malin Akerman, Mark Cuban and others will also co-host the multi-hour event. It will air live on MSNBC and Comcast NBCUniversal. Fans can earn their free...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Dakota Johnson wants sexual assault victims to give her a call - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/entertainment/dakota-johnson-number-assault/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA8Si53IfhFx_kRxtz1zjgIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 16:02:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/entertainment/dakota-johnson-number-assault/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dakota Johnson wants sexual assault victims to give her a call&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dakota Johnson isn't just speaking out about violence and sexual harassment against women -- she's inviting others to do the same. And she's giving out her phone number. The "Fifty Shades of Grey" actress was one of the speakers last week at the Global Citizen Festival in New York City. On Monday, she posted a phone number on Instagram seeking others stories. "Women and girls in every corner of the world face extreme violence and sexual harassment on a daily basis," she wrote in the post. "Over 800 women and adolescent girls die every day because they do not have access to reliable contrace...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>In a state of fear, even a popped bottle can set off a panic - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/01/opinions/global-citizen-panic-state-of-fear-mcevoy/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBclmjsXewe-_DEnZ6yYxTQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 19:06:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/01/opinions/global-citizen-panic-state-of-fear-mcevoy/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;In a state of fear, even a popped bottle can set off a panic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jemima McEvoy is a junior from the United Kingdom studying politics at New York University and the editor-in-chief of NYU's student newspaper, Washington Square News. The opinions expressed in this commentary are her own. View more opinion articles on CNN. "Stand up," my friend said to me. Her eyes wide, panicked. "We need to go." I had been sitting on the lawn in Central Park, along with the 60,000 other attendees of this year's Global Citizen Festival, waiting for The Weeknd and Janet Jackson to take the stage. Seconds later, I was running. As my friend stood up to get a better view of th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>MSNBC's Chris Hayes, Ari Melber Swap D.C. Drama For Global Good - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2018/09/29/msnbcs-chris-hayes-ari-melber-swap-d-c-drama-for-global-good/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAioCv2ci1LF5tT-lBoD1_8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 15:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2018/09/29/msnbcs-chris-hayes-ari-melber-swap-d-c-drama-for-global-good/" target="_blank"&gt;MSNBC's Chris Hayes, Ari Melber Swap D.C. Drama For Global Good&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Billie Joe Armstrong of Green Day performs at last year’s Global Citizen Festival in Central Park. (Photo by Greg Allen/Invision/AP) For cable news hosts, 2018 has been a time of relentless and frenetic news coverage, with one giant story breaking–and then another following right behind it. The result has been a kind of adrenaline-fueled pace that leaves little time to reflect–or relax. But today, MSNBC hosts Chris Hayes and Ari Melber will attempt to step out of their Twitter timelines, put away their phones, and shift focus away from the likes of Kavanaugh, Trump and Mueller. “The daily n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Janet Jackson, Cardi B to headline Global Citizen festival - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f77fc7ddcd694259891b07759a85c97f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDISInAIEYYdfldZ7uWS2fkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 14:38:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f77fc7ddcd694259891b07759a85c97f" target="_blank"&gt;Janet Jackson, Cardi B to headline Global Citizen festival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — John Legend, Janet Jackson, The Weeknd and Shawn Mendes are among the artists slated to appear at the 2018 Global Citizen Festival. The event will take place on Sept. 29 on the Great Lawn in New York City's Central Park. Janelle Monae and Cardi B, who gave birth in July, will also perform. Hugh Jackman and Deborra-lee Furness will host the festival, which calls on world leaders to achieve the United Nations' sustainable development goals and end extreme poverty by 2030. The international advocacy group also wants leaders to tackle the maternal health crisis, end child marria...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Beyonce and Jay-Z among headliners at Mandela concert in South Africa - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/09/africa/beyonce-and-jay-z-to-visit-south-africa/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGIoC8rDnlN2mRCzJxVGmHcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 17:15:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/09/africa/beyonce-and-jay-z-to-visit-south-africa/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Beyonce and Jay-Z among headliners at Mandela concert in South Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyonce and Jay-Z will be among headliners at a Nelson Mandela tribute concert to be held in South Africa at the end of the year. The couple will form part of a star-studded line-up at the Mandela:100 event on December 2 to honor the legacy of the anti-apartheid hero in his Centenary year. Other performers include Ed Sheeran, Chris Martin, Pharrell Williams, D'banj, Femi Kuti, Sho Madjozi, Tiwa Savage and Wizkid at the event put together by the non-profit Global Citizen network, who say the concert is the "biggest campaign on the Global Goals to end extreme poverty ever." Global Citizen has...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Beyonce, Jay-Z to headline Africa festival honoring Mandela - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/de2d97f71f4e445bbf4449b11b39f8c1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGCniTkhnF3NYFrs7TF55y8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 08:35:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/de2d97f71f4e445bbf4449b11b39f8c1" target="_blank"&gt;Beyonce, Jay-Z to headline Africa festival honoring Mandela&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Beyonce and Jay-Z will headline a special Global Citizen Festival in honor of Nelson Mandela in South Africa late this year. The Dec. 2 concert in Johannesburg is part of events marking the 100th anniversary of the birth of the anti-apartheid leader and Nobel Peace Prize winner. Others headlining the festival include Ed Sheeran, Usher, Pharrell Williams and African artists including Wizkid, Cassper Nyovest and Femi Kuti. Organizers say Oprah Winfrey will give a keynote address on the legacy of Mandela, who died in 2013. Other hosts include actors Forest Whitaker, Naomi C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Beyoncé and Jay-Z Will Headline Nelson Mandela Tribute Concert - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/beyonce-and-jay-z-will-headline-nelson-mandela-tribute-concert</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHspcW_j6-lUa4QVAjKZbYQqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 19:26:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/beyonce-and-jay-z-will-headline-nelson-mandela-tribute-concert" target="_blank"&gt;Beyoncé and Jay-Z Will Headline Nelson Mandela Tribute Concert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mike Coppola/Getty, In a video released by nonprofit planner, Global Citizen, Chris Martin of Coldplay announced Mandela:100, a benefit concert that will be held December 2nd in Johannesburg. Beyoncé and Jay-Z will be among the performers at the event, which commemorates the continued legacy of Nelson Mandela, who would have been 100 later this month. Fans of The Carters will finally have a chance to see them in Africa, as Beyoncé and Jay have not performed on the continent since 2004 and 2006, respectively. The Carters will join Chris Martin, Ed Sheeran, Pharrell Williams, D'banj, Femi Kut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Ed Sheeran Rises To No. 1 In The U.K. With His New 'Perfect' Collaboration - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2017/12/08/ed-sheeran-rises-to-no-1-in-the-u-k-with-his-new-perfect-collaboration/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDueZ51zgI1Y58sqIhDPOSoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2017/12/08/ed-sheeran-rises-to-no-1-in-the-u-k-with-his-new-perfect-collaboration/" target="_blank"&gt;Ed Sheeran Rises To No. 1 In The U.K. With His New 'Perfect' Collaboration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, NY – SEPTEMBER 26: Ed Sheeran and Beyonce perform onstage during 2015 Global Citizen Festival to end extreme poverty by 2030 in Central Park on September 26, 2015, in New York City. (Photo by Kevin Mazur/Getty Images for Global Citizen) Just one week after Ed Sheeran re-released his already-successful single “Perfect” with Beyoncé contributing vocals to the sappy tune, the updated take has risen to No. 1 on the British singles ranking, granting the guitar-strumming powerhouse another chart leader. “Perfect Duet” is Sheeran’s fourth No. 1 in his home country, and his second this ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Beyoncé and Ed Sheeran teamed up for 'Perfect' duet - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/12/01/entertainment/beyonce-ed-sheeran-perfect-duet/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENi7BWudhqIGMqWAl6YK51YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 20:00:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/12/01/entertainment/beyonce-ed-sheeran-perfect-duet/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Beyoncé and Ed Sheeran teamed up for 'Perfect' duet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congratulations, Beyoncé and Ed Sheeran, for creating the new go-to first dance song for newlyweds everywhere. The powerhouse musicians have teamed up for a duet of Sheeran's romantic ballad "Perfect," from his most recent album, pronounced "Divide." The song was released Thursday evening and quickly sent the Bey Hive into a frenzy. "Just listened to the Perfect duet with Ed Sheeran and Beyoncé .... didn't know my ears could cry until now," wrote one fan. This is not the first time Sheeran and Beyoncé have collaborated. The two shared the stage at a Grammy tribute to Stevie Wonder, along wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Who Ya Gonna Call To Save The World? Well, Rihanna, Of Course! - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40487405/who-ya-gonna-call-to-save-the-world-well-rihanna-of-course</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA8y6GZV14We11sEIVYBwB0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 11:00:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/40487405/who-ya-gonna-call-to-save-the-world-well-rihanna-of-course" target="_blank"&gt;Who Ya Gonna Call To Save The World? Well, Rihanna, Of Course!&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wanna get a politician to act? Get a pop star involved. In an ideal world, passionate reasoning for action from the masses should be enough to get the attention of the people in power. But too often it’s not. Just ask the folks at Global Citizen, the New York global action platform that is working to eradicate extreme poverty. Case in point: The power of Rihanna. When Global Citizen couldn’t get France to commit funds last year to its #EducationCannotWait campaign to help kids affected by natural disasters, poverty, and other crises last year, it got the Barbadian singer involved. It had be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item></channel></rss>