<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Tullow Oil - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRE5qWm5ocmJCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:50:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Tullow to increase oil production to 180000 barrels in 2019 - Myjoyonline.com</title><link>https://www.myjoyonline.com/business/2018/december-7th/tullow-to-increase-oil-production-to-180000-barrels-in-2019.php</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMidmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm15am95b25saW5lLmNvbS9idXNpbmVzcy8yMDE4L2RlY2VtYmVyLTd0aC90dWxsb3ctdG8taW5jcmVhc2Utb2lsLXByb2R1Y3Rpb24tdG8tMTgwMDAwLWJhcnJlbHMtaW4tMjAxOS5waHDSAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:59:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.myjoyonline.com/business/2018/december-7th/tullow-to-increase-oil-production-to-180000-barrels-in-2019.php" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow to increase oil production to 180000 barrels in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Myjoyonline.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Ghana says it is targeting a growth in production from the current 147, 000 barrels to 180000 in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpsOFB1bWpZQU1FY290OURnb0RhQVhLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.myjoyonline.com">Myjoyonline.com</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/sWmo3EtRtN8P9PmUXQ-wll9AmZypR7PMfEGyLw4_GGXK7d6yI51UmT-iuA7qamJl8cO5prbHOObh-D_FJznyWwU51kz5n_2H2VeGyE758jySdII9p3YyEQgWSAtT9i_lLoh8=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Tullow estimates Ghana oil production to go up to 180000 barrels next year - GhanaWeb</title><link>https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/business/Tullow-estimates-Ghana-oil-production-to-go-up-to-180-000-barrels-next-year-706832</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiggFodHRwczovL3d3dy5naGFuYXdlYi5jb20vR2hhbmFIb21lUGFnZS9idXNpbmVzcy9UdWxsb3ctZXN0aW1hdGVzLUdoYW5hLW9pbC1wcm9kdWN0aW9uLXRvLWdvLXVwLXRvLTE4MC0wMDAtYmFycmVscy1uZXh0LXllYXItNzA2ODMy0gEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:27:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/business/Tullow-estimates-Ghana-oil-production-to-go-up-to-180-000-barrels-next-year-706832" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow estimates Ghana oil production to go up to 180000 barrels next year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GhanaWeb&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow-Ghana's drilling program is targeting a significant growth production from around 147, 000 barrels to 180,000 in 2019. The company was working to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ghanaweb.com">GhanaWeb</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/Ne6kCe2I_fsUgGx3rM76GrcYkdOEbdu9y3vcuPIZKQ7V8OCr3bMImOhNn-w_iDqJLxnfLP1xJu1EcKdrNh192kNTOsVX7Q=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Tullow Oil to pay dividends in 2019 - Myjoyonline.com</title><link>https://www.myjoyonline.com/business/2018/november-29th/tullow-oil-to-pay-dividends-in-2019.php</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm15am95b25saW5lLmNvbS9idXNpbmVzcy8yMDE4L25vdmVtYmVyLTI5dGgvdHVsbG93LW9pbC10by1wYXktZGl2aWRlbmRzLWluLTIwMTkucGhw0gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 16:54:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.myjoyonline.com/business/2018/november-29th/tullow-oil-to-pay-dividends-in-2019.php" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow Oil to pay dividends in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Myjoyonline.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Africa-focused Tullow Oil will return to paying dividends, which it suspended in 2015 due to the oil price crash, and expects to pay out at least $100 million from ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.myjoyonline.com">Myjoyonline.com</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/vWwiu7p5cFmdIQ0XAjUlNQ_UZteE7ZjPvUBqX-D9j315kPtRW8oA3HuPtfg4DKPp29--Ds2nTJVDL7OvyL8JwRT6cM89EDAgh01I7jSAU9zqQNxW_YYorw=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Tullow Oil returns to dividends in 2019 | Business News 2018-12-01 - GhanaWeb</title><link>https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/business/Tullow-Oil-returns-to-dividends-in-2019-705208</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdoYW5hd2ViLmNvbS9HaGFuYUhvbWVQYWdlL2J1c2luZXNzL1R1bGxvdy1PaWwtcmV0dXJucy10by1kaXZpZGVuZHMtaW4tMjAxOS03MDUyMDjSAQA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 12:26:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/business/Tullow-Oil-returns-to-dividends-in-2019-705208" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow Oil returns to dividends in 2019 | Business News 2018-12-01&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GhanaWeb&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Africa-focused Tullow Oil will return to paying dividends, which it suspended in 2015 due to the oil price crash, and expects to pay out at least $100 million from ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ghanaweb.com">GhanaWeb</source></item><item><title>Tullow Oil to pay dividend for first time since 2014 - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/3b50baae-f3b9-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF2VaETU7TWETmY4D9ZWihoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 09:31:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3b50baae-f3b9-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow Oil to pay dividend for first time since 2014&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil and gas group Tullow Oil said on Thursday it would reinstate its dividend for the first time since 2014 in a sign of ongoing recovery after years of financial pain. The FTSE 250 company, which has focused on cutting costs and reducing debt in recent years, will pay an annual dividend of at least $100m from 2019 for a yield of around 3 per cent. “Tullow has made excellent operational and financial progress over the past 18 months,” said Paul McDade, Tullow chief executive. “Having reached our target of being a balanced self-funding exploration and production business and having embedded ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>The London Report: Tumbling oil price sees energy stocks slide - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9cd79eb2-ef51-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO8AxC_PR1CQig_m50ciRQsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 19:11:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9cd79eb2-ef51-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;The London Report: Tumbling oil price sees energy stocks slide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Brent crude oil tumbling to a year low of under $60 a barrel, the commodity-heavy FTSE 100 index was down 0.1 per cent. Among the leading casualties were energy and oil stocks such as Vivo Energy , Premier Oil , Cairn Energy and Tullow Oil . A big gainer yesterday was Ibstock , the UK’s largest brickmaker, which jumped more than 8 per cent to top of the FTSE 250. The leap came after news that the group sold its US brick business in a deal worth $110m, according to Reuters. Shares in Flybe closed more than 70 per cent higher after Sky News reported that Virgin Atlantic was in talks abou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>FTSE 100 loses grip of intraday record after U.S. jobs disappointment - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/ftse-100-on-track-for-all-time-high-as-us-records-lift-trading-mood-2017-06-02</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPce5o-8K24L3U3jsqB3AsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/ftse-100-on-track-for-all-time-high-as-us-records-lift-trading-mood-2017-06-02" target="_blank"&gt;FTSE 100 loses grip of intraday record after U.S. jobs disappointment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON MARKETS By Sara Sjolin Oil companies fall as crude prices slide almost 2% Canary Wharf in London Shutterstock/alice-photo U.K. stocks pared back from an all-time intraday high and ended only a slight gain on Friday after U.S. jobs growth fell short of expectations, raising questions about the strength of the world’s largest economy. The FTSE 100 Index (UK:UKX) rose less than 0.1% to close at 7,547.63, trimming an advance of as much as 0.7%. That means the benchmark ended at exactly the same level as the previous record close of 7,547.63 set on May 26. For the week, the FTSE ended fl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Statoil: misfit - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c1c5d1e8-30cc-11e7-9555-23ef563ecf9a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECzwYziTga3zXmySZV5lsK4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 15:10:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c1c5d1e8-30cc-11e7-9555-23ef563ecf9a" target="_blank"&gt;Statoil: misfit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Statoil of Norway has always stood a little apart from the other large oil companies. In Europe it tends to get lumped in with other integrated oil producers. Yet Statoil refines little oil, so it barely qualifies as integrated. Then again, its $53bn market value dwarfs that of other pure oil and gas explorers in Europe. When oil prices fell off a cliff a few years ago, so did Statoil’s cash flow. The threat of that happening again keeps Statoil’s valuation below its peers. This is nothing new. Since 2005, Statoil’s earnings multiple on average has trailed that of the MSCI World Energy inde...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tullow Oil chief executive becomes chairman in boardroom shake-up - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/355120cc-d7d1-11e6-944b-e7eb37a6aa8e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENQCI4KYUfForvL0CPZZuEsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 09:20:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/355120cc-d7d1-11e6-944b-e7eb37a6aa8e" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow Oil chief executive becomes chairman in boardroom shake-up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil has elevated its founder and chief executive, Aidan Heavey, to chairman in defiance of UK corporate governance guidelines. The Africa-focused oil explorer insisted the “unique nature” of its business and relationships required a “phased transition” in the company’s leadership and said Mr Heavey’s tenure as chairman would not exceed a period of two years, starting from its annual meeting on April 26. Simon Thompson, a former Anglo American executive who has been chairman of Tullow Oil for five years, will step down. Mr Heavey, who has been chief executive of Tullow since 1985, wil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>European stocks trim gains after Trump comments send drug stocks lower - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-wander-before-trump-takes-center-stage-2017-01-11</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGxM5d_PNyIUjg2lkSsWdbQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 17:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-wander-before-trump-takes-center-stage-2017-01-11" target="_blank"&gt;European stocks trim gains after Trump comments send drug stocks lower&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Carla Mozee, Sara Sjolin Sainsbury’s jumps after Christmas sales numbers Volkswagen has agreed to pay a penalty in the U.S. Shutterstock.com European stocks rose for a second straight day on Wednesday, but with drugmakers capping gains after a late-session selloff following remarks by U.S. President-elect Donald Trump. The Stoxx Europe 600 (XX:SXXP) ended 0.2% higher at 364.90, adding to a 0.1% advance from Tuesday. The pan-European index traded as high as 366.37 earlier in the day, but trimmed gains after Trump in his first full-scale press conference since July lashed o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Oil bounce, company results keep stocks on high - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-markets-idUSKBN1AB02R</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-Bc9H_7uki-qRiymDk-mEqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 11:56:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-markets-idUSKBN1AB02R" target="_blank"&gt;Oil bounce, company results keep stocks on high&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Patrick Graham LONDON (Reuters) - Oil's rise back above $50 a barrel helped prod stock markets higher on Wednesday, while company results and economic data continued to soothe worries that the world economy may be ripe for a another slowdown. European stock markets .FTEU3 rose around half a percent, led by energy and commodity-linked firms after Brent crude topped the $50 mark for the first time since early June and copper added another 1 percent to this week's surge. CMCU3 A slightly less bullish performance in Asia pulled the MSCI world equity index .MIWD00000PUS, which tracks shares i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>European stocks stumble, ending at 2-week low - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-pull-back-as-auto-makers-oil-producers-struggle-2017-07-24</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL5rM6Mx6jMXc-lGXWCsc3QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 16:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-pull-back-as-auto-makers-oil-producers-struggle-2017-07-24" target="_blank"&gt;European stocks stumble, ending at 2-week low&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Carla Mozee, Victor Reklaitis Ryanair warns on fares; German auto makers also whacked Shutterstock.com European stocks closed lower Monday, with shares of German auto makers and Dutch firm Gemalto NV among those pushing the market to its weakest finish in two weeks. The Stoxx Europe 600 (XX:SXXP) was off 0.2% to end at 379.23, adding to its recent retreat and notching its lowest close since July 11. The index on Friday slid 1%, contributing to last week’s loss of 1.9%. Early Monday, data showed the eurozone economy slowed in July, with Markit saying its composite Purchasin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>European stocks rebound from 2-month low as banks, oil giants climb - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-rebound-from-2-month-low-as-banks-oil-giants-climb-2017-07-03</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIRSH-X_j30BiuTG7rpvdxsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 16:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-rebound-from-2-month-low-as-banks-oil-giants-climb-2017-07-03" target="_blank"&gt;European stocks rebound from 2-month low as banks, oil giants climb&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Sara Sjolin Eurozone manufacturing PMI confirmed at 6-year high Banks in Europe, including Deutsche Bank, rise on Monday Getty Images European stocks broke a four-session losing streak on Monday, buoyed by the commodities sector after upbeat manufacturing data from China and a continued rally in oil prices. Banks also helped to lift the trading mood, rising on hopes of higher interest rates after hawkish comments from central bankers last week. The Stoxx Europe 600 index (XX:SXXP) climbed 1.1% to end at 383.41, marking its first close in positive territory in five session...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>FTSE 100 versus FTSE 250 Brexit split risks getting stale - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d0f14dec-d1a8-11e6-b06b-680c49b4b4c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHwFa23kbp7x4u0PpPau0ZgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 04:03:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d0f14dec-d1a8-11e6-b06b-680c49b4b4c0" target="_blank"&gt;FTSE 100 versus FTSE 250 Brexit split risks getting stale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immediate aftermath of Britain’s vote for Brexit was chaotic for UK equity investors but, given the historic nature of the referendum, it has been a remarkably straightforward market to trade since. If sterling-based investors have favoured the FTSE 100, whose multinational members have far larger international operations, over its sister index, the more domestically focused FTSE 250, Brexit has offered rich investment returns. The large-cap FTSE 100 index is up 13 per cent since polling day, outpacing the 4 per cent gain for the mid-cap FTSE 250. However, with the FTSE 100 setting new ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>European stocks book first loss in 4 sessions as oil shares tumble - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-edge-back-after-4-session-win-streak-2017-03-14</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKZCmD-4MkWi3U7JDY_1E8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 17:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-edge-back-after-4-session-win-streak-2017-03-14" target="_blank"&gt;European stocks book first loss in 4 sessions as oil shares tumble&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Carla Mozee RWE shares jump on report of interest in Innogy unit European stocks closed with their first loss in four sessions Tuesday, with a selloff in the oil prices knocking down oil shares, while investors stepped back before this week’s Dutch election and the Federal Reserve’s policy meeting. The Stoxx Europe 600 index (XX:SXXP) fell 0.3% to finish at 373.46, giving up a modest increase earlier in the session. Only the health-care, consumer-goods and tech groups ended higher. Equity-trading volume was expected to be lighter than usual Tuesday as a snowstorm blankete...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>European stock benchmarks end higher, boosted by commodity shares - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-oil-mining-shares-bounce-up-outpacing-broader-market-2017-05-15</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcxUwEqTljeETvp1E36QMcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-oil-mining-shares-bounce-up-outpacing-broader-market-2017-05-15" target="_blank"&gt;European stock benchmarks end higher, boosted by commodity shares&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Carla Mozee Euro moves back toward $1.10 AFP/Getty Images European equity-index gauges finished with modest gains Monday, scoring a fillip from commodity shares as oil and metals prices rose. The Stoxx Europe 600 index (XX:SXXP) ended up 0.1% at 395.97, marking a second straight advance and keeping the index around its highest since August 2015. But the index moved between small gains and losses throughout the session. The oil-and-gas, basic-materials and financial sectors fared the best, but health-care, consumer-related and telecom shares struggled. Commodities cruise up...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Upbeat China, U.S. data propel European stocks to 1-year high - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/upbeat-china-data-propel-european-stocks-to-1-year-high-2017-01-03</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKh4-ZX0e859AXJ-Ha6Lu-QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 17:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/upbeat-china-data-propel-european-stocks-to-1-year-high-2017-01-03" target="_blank"&gt;Upbeat China, U.S. data propel European stocks to 1-year high&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Sara Sjolin DAX slips while CAC gains Bloomberg European stock markets charged higher again on Tuesday, closing at a fresh one-year high after upbeat Chinese and U.S. manufacturing data fueled optimism over economic growth in the world’s two largest economies. The Stoxx Europe 600 index (XX:SXXP) climbed 0.7% to 365.71, ending at the highest level since Dec. 31, 2015. Boost from China and U.S.: The index got a boost from separate manufacturing reports from China and the U.S. that beat analyst forecasts. The U.S. ISM index climbed to 54.7% in December from 53.2% in Novembe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Oil stocks advance, but fail to substantially lift Stoxx Europe 600 - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-oil-stocks-advance-but-indexes-are-listless-2017-04-05</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgXbEmw9-y8kfViNDe5nLoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 08:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-oil-stocks-advance-but-indexes-are-listless-2017-04-05" target="_blank"&gt;Oil stocks advance, but fail to substantially lift Stoxx Europe 600&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Carla Mozee, Sara Sjolin Germany’s DAX closes off 0.5% AFP/Getty Images European oil stocks showed strength Wednesday, but the moves, along with a reading of eurozone services activity at a near six-year high, failed to beef up the regional indexes. The Stoxx Europe 600 index (XX:SXXP) closed 0.02% higher 380.09, after vacillating between gains and losses throughout the day. The pan-European benchmark on Tuesday rose 0.2% after a choppy session. Oil shares kept the index from sliding into the red, rising even as government data showed an unexpected increase in U.S. crude ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>UK technology listing highlights struggle for energy sector - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1dbc16f4-4777-11e7-8d27-59b4dd6296b8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1NF_cSRkj_EvZy7cHH0W0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 10:52:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1dbc16f4-4777-11e7-8d27-59b4dd6296b8" target="_blank"&gt;UK technology listing highlights struggle for energy sector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK’s biggest technology listing in almost two years got off to flying start when official trading started this week. Shares in Alfa Financial Software, which develops specialist software for the asset financial industry, surged almost 30 per cent from their issue price, generating a massive windfall for its chairman and chief executive. Contrast that performance with the UK’s biggest oil and gas initial public offering in three years, which remains stuck in the starting blocks. Kuwait Energy, which announced plans to IPO a month ago, said on Wednesday that after a period of “investor ed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Oil shares decline but European market pulls out a win at the close - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-rise-but-maersk-sinks-after-cutting-dividend-2017-02-08</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBPdp6Q7piAOGoO4S6lnGfQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 17:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-rise-but-maersk-sinks-after-cutting-dividend-2017-02-08" target="_blank"&gt;Oil shares decline but European market pulls out a win at the close&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Victor Reklaitis, Carla Mozee Tullow Oil, Carlsberg also fall; Sanofi, Storebrand, Vestas gain A container ship, the Maersk MC-Kinney Moller, shown arriving at the Dutch port of Rotterdam. AFP/Getty Images European stocks finished modestly higher Wednesday, but post-earnings drops by Maersk and Tullow Oil and a decline in oil prices kept stronger gains in check. The Stoxx Europe 600 (XX:SXXP) closed up 0.3% to 363.94, but the basic materials, financial and oil and gas sectors were pulled lower. The regional benchmark is roughly flat so far this week after falling Monday a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Guyana oil prospects stir friction between Venezuela and Exxon - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/013bfd26-0a8e-11e7-ac5a-903b21361b43</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECeYbb1KpKWE0ZmOg5x39JcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 05:15:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/013bfd26-0a8e-11e7-ac5a-903b21361b43" target="_blank"&gt;Guyana oil prospects stir friction between Venezuela and Exxon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guyana has emerged as one of the world’s most promising areas for offshore oil exploration, following significant discoveries made by ExxonMobil of the US that have started a wave of excitement in the global industry. However, the new-found oil wealth of Guyana has heightened tensions with its neighbour Venezuela, which is in the throes of an economic crisis caused in part by falling oil production and weak prices. It has also created further friction between Venezuela and ExxonMobil, which have been fighting a decade-long legal battle over compensation for oil projects expropriated by the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>U.K. stocks swing higher as pound falters after lackluster data - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/uk-stocks-fall-for-2nd-day-as-central-bank-fears-persist-2017-07-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDipcnoffP86cJ61sKJdpSQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/uk-stocks-fall-for-2nd-day-as-central-bank-fears-persist-2017-07-07" target="_blank"&gt;U.K. stocks swing higher as pound falters after lackluster data&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON MARKETS By Sara Sjolin FTSE 100 on course for weekly rise Canary Wharf in London Shutterstock/alice-photo U.K. stocks erased earlier losses and ended slightly higher on Friday after the pound gets chopped down following a trio of disappointing data. The FTSE 100 index (UK:UKX) rose 0.2% to close at 7,350.92, after trading as low as 7,314.69 earlier in the day. The benchmark advanced 0.5% for the week, the first week of trade in the second half of 2017. The FTSE had opened in negative territory as investors were spooked by growing signs that global central banks are inching closer to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Stoxx Europe 600 posts 3rd straight loss on commodity slump - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-down-for-third-straight-day-as-commodity-shares-pull-back-2016-10-26</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED5RQCjIykv1_r8ZR8NXHaUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 16:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-down-for-third-straight-day-as-commodity-shares-pull-back-2016-10-26" target="_blank"&gt;Stoxx Europe 600 posts 3rd straight loss on commodity slump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Carla Mozee, Victor Reklaitis Tullow Oil among the day’s notable losers Models at an Alexander McQueen show. The fashion house’s parent Kering posted a jump in sales Wednesday. AFP/Getty Images European stocks finished lower Wednesday, with energy shares slightly paring losses as oil prices came off session lows. Investors also expressed disappointment over a new round of financial updates. The Stoxx Europe 600 (XX:SXXP) gave up 0.4% to close at 341.76, registering its third loss in a row. On Tuesday, the pan-European index fell 0.4%. The oil-and-gas sector (XX:SXER) d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Tullow Oil falls to bigger-than-expected loss - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/03d0c3da-71d8-11e7-aca6-c6bd07df1a3c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF14FpsrXz06UOG_WeUhxh4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 08:57:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/03d0c3da-71d8-11e7-aca6-c6bd07df1a3c" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow Oil falls to bigger-than-expected loss&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil fell to a bigger-than-expected half-year loss after shouldering a near $650m hit from weak oil prices. The Africa-focused oil explorer and producer made a pre-tax loss of $518.8m in the six months ending in June, compared to a $24.1m profit a year earlier, on revenue of $788m, up 46 per cent. Its results were dragged down by a $641.7m charge after tax, reflecting lower oil price forecasts. The company flagged last month that it would book the non-cash impairment but its results were still below analysts’ forecasts of a pre-tax loss of about $439m. Brent crude was boosted this wee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Oil Bonuses an Early Sign Uganda Suffering Resource ‘Curse,' Say Critics - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/uganda-questions-over-bonuses-paid-officials-oil/3666827.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPT4AMFDfYJVOScM0HwRAuoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 02:30:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/uganda-questions-over-bonuses-paid-officials-oil/3666827.html" target="_blank"&gt;Oil Bonuses an Early Sign Uganda Suffering Resource ‘Curse,' Say Critics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hefty bonuses paid to Ugandan officials who oversaw tax dispute settlements with international oil firms are a sign hydrocarbon discoveries are increasing corruption in the country, government opponents and transparency campaigners said. Commercial production is due to start in 2020 and some campaign groups are warning Uganda is already suffering the resource “curse,” in which a rush of petro-dollars suffocates the rest of the economy, encourages graft and stirs unrest. Uganda first discovered oil more than a decade ago but production has been stalled by lengthy rows between government and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Opening Quote: Dixons Carphone proves exception to the rule - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/28b45675-cc8d-317e-a956-866ab74f4d17</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGYguYWmXr8zOKSmhmwgfoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 07:06:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/28b45675-cc8d-317e-a956-866ab74f4d17" target="_blank"&gt;Opening Quote: Dixons Carphone proves exception to the rule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dixons Carphone proves exception to the rule. FT Opening Quote, with commentary by Matthew Vincent, is your early Square Mile briefing. You can sign up for the full newsletter here. If sales of sofas, beer and certain supermarkets’ pizzas are now falling on a like-for-like basis, and there is no big football tournament taking place, what will happen to sales of enormous tellies? (3 marks). If this had been an actual question on the recently-sat GCSE Economics paper – and I wouldn’t have put it past certain exam boards – then the percentage of A* grades might have dipped below the now custom...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>FTSE movers: Metro Bank climbs but Sage sinks after late trading updates - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/5320ac7f-b5c5-3b38-b6fc-92c6482599bb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHlhsOJvFihuZx-ULF4GLFoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 07:36:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5320ac7f-b5c5-3b38-b6fc-92c6482599bb" target="_blank"&gt;FTSE movers: Metro Bank climbs but Sage sinks after late trading updates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metro Bank was one of the biggest risers on a broadly positive morning for UK stocks on Wednesday, after it announced a new share placement and a swing to profit in an update after markets closed yesterday. Shares in the challenger bank rose as much as 3.7 per cent in early trading, though they had fallen back to a 2 per cent rise by publication time. Metro Bank said on Tuesday that it was bringing forward plans to raise new equity after spending £600m on a portfolio of buy-to-let mortgages last month. The company also reported a pre-tax profit of £6m for the first six months of the year, c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tullow clears £607m rights issue ahead of shareholder showdown - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ff330418-7c38-3f2d-be58-1859076b940d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAq1CpYG4ZyUzLxADyszNxwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 15:59:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ff330418-7c38-3f2d-be58-1859076b940d" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow clears £607m rights issue ahead of shareholder showdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil, the Africa-focused energy company, may have passed one significant hurdle on Tuesday, when it announced solid take-up of a £607m rights issue to pay down debt. But the London-listed oil explorer has another barrier to jump on Wednesday at its annual meeting, when its shareholders will be asked to approve the elevation of its founder and chief executive Aidan Heavey to the chairman’s seat – a move that goes against corporate governance best practice. One shareholder, Royal London Asset Management, which holds a 0.95 per cent stake in Tullow, has signalled that the company may be ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>FTSE blue-chip index clings to record mark - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/3e3223d4-4776-11e7-8519-9f94ee97d996</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDAOlAV7iy-6Ekb_WfXjfxUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 18:34:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3e3223d4-4776-11e7-8519-9f94ee97d996" target="_blank"&gt;FTSE blue-chip index clings to record mark&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gains for financial stocks propelled the FTSE 100 to a new intraday record on Friday, before momentum was sapped by weaker resource stocks that left the blue-chip index matching its all-time close from late May. The main London index reached an unprecedented 7,598.99 during the session, but it slipped to close up just 0.05 per cent at 7,547.63, in line with its record close a week ago. Banks and money managers were lifted by growing hopes that a global economic rebound is taking hold, which lifted sentiment across global equities exchanges. South African financial stock Old Mutual rose 2.6 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Fast Europe Open: UK Q2 GDP, France consumer confidence - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cfe0512a-0ab4-3f37-b609-2cf80de2b2d7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF17fA8u2rj0lBo_ggkLC5oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 05:02:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cfe0512a-0ab4-3f37-b609-2cf80de2b2d7" target="_blank"&gt;Fast Europe Open: UK Q2 GDP, France consumer confidence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It turns out there is at least one issue that can still unite legislators in Washington under a banner of bipartisan brotherhood, even after decades of partisan rancour: Russia. The US House of Representatives has voted overwhelmingly to impose sanctions on Russia as Congress attempts to punish Moscow for alleged meddling in the 2016 presidential election. The House approved the sanctions — and separate punitive measures against Iran and North Korea — in a 419-3 vote that underscored the anger on Capitol Hill over the alleged Russian interference. The push to impose sanctions on Russia come...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Market report: BT rallies to five-week high on bullish broker note - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/07/13/market-report-bt-rallies-five-week-high-bullish-broker-note/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF7I2d9D_55MIAanLZx8lekqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 16:29:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/07/13/market-report-bt-rallies-five-week-high-bullish-broker-note/" target="_blank"&gt;Market report: BT rallies to five-week high on bullish broker note&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Telecoms giant BT rallied to a five-week high after broker Numis said sentiment towards the FTSE 100 stock was “much too bearish”. The broker began covering the blue chip stock with a “buy” rating and a target price of 390p. Analyst John Karidis said: “We believe only BT’s Openreach is prepared to deliver the scale, all-fibre infrastructure Britain wants.” Numis believes it is not credible to forecast that BT will spend more than it needs to connect 2m homes with full-fibre by 2020. It also thinks City forecasts “significantly overestimate” Openreach’s unit capital expenditure costs to buil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>North Sea debt battle to drag on as oil price forecasts are slashed - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/06/24/north-sea-debt-battle-drag-oil-price-forecasts-slashed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBLoXCPY2-x4tWYQrogV5uMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 18:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/06/24/north-sea-debt-battle-drag-oil-price-forecasts-slashed/" target="_blank"&gt;North Sea debt battle to drag on as oil price forecasts are slashed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The North Sea’s struggle to overcome its multi-billion pound debt burden has been dealt a setback as hope for a recovery in oil prices begins to wither. Experts cut their forecasts for the global oil market last week as the crude price slumped to 10-month lows, putting the market on course for the steepest first-half drop since the Nineties. The reversal is a major concern for prominent North Sea drillers such as Enquest and Premier Oil, which may now face a much longer battle to reduce their debt pile. The pair were left with a combined debt burden of almost £5bn in the wake of the oil cra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tullow swings to $518.8m loss on sliding oil price - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c31257cc-4ce9-3cac-889f-63aae8d75a54</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFUM5wLkW6ARURfALYXKMMgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 06:09:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c31257cc-4ce9-3cac-889f-63aae8d75a54" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow swings to $518.8m loss on sliding oil price&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil has fallen to a half-year pre-tax loss after taking a significant hit from lower oil prices. The Africa-focused oil explorer and producer made a pre-tax loss of $518.8m in the six months ending in June, compared to a $24.1m profit a year earlier on revenue of $788m, up 46 per cent. Its results were dragged down by a net $641.7m impairment of property, plant and equipment, reflecting lower oil price forecasts. The company had already warned last month that it would book the non-cash impairment and would revise down its medium-term oil price assumptions but the result was still bel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>FTSE 100 breaks 4-day losing streak as oil rallies - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/ftse-100-breaks-4-day-losing-streak-as-oil-rallies-2017-06-26</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOd0ZqaeIVOuide5_rWE4U0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/ftse-100-breaks-4-day-losing-streak-as-oil-rallies-2017-06-26" target="_blank"&gt;FTSE 100 breaks 4-day losing streak as oil rallies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON MARKETS By Sara Sjolin, Victor Reklaitis RBS plans to move jobs to India Shell and other oil companies rise alongside higher oil prices on Monday AFP/Getty Images U.K. stocks closed higher for the first time in five sessions on Monday, with energy companies aiding in the charge north as oil prices continued to rebound after a recent selloff. The FTSE 100 index (UK:UKX) gained 0.3% to end at 7,446.80, after logging its lowest close since June 15 on Friday. Oil heavyweights Royal Dutch Shell PLC (UK:RDSB) (RDS) and BP PLC (UK:BP) (BP) both picked up 0.3%. On the midcap FTSE 250 index...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Tullow shares down 15% after rights issue - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e3265814-7cf6-30bf-8ed2-229f988e5422</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOIbBp5HOjw7ChB5m8kz4Y8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 07:20:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e3265814-7cf6-30bf-8ed2-229f988e5422" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow shares down 15% after rights issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Tullow Oil have dropped by 15 per cent in the wake of its $750m rights issue. The rights issue, announced last month, has now completed, with the new shares starting trading today. At pixel time, the share price is down by 15 per cent at 197p. The cash call has raised concerns that the oil group could return to its high-spending past.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Uganda’s oil reserves bring promise of work and infrastructure - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e057c978-1555-11e7-b0c1-37e417ee6c76</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL2mK8AuvPNYkKi5ybiLEbwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 04:01:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e057c978-1555-11e7-b0c1-37e417ee6c76" target="_blank"&gt;Uganda’s oil reserves bring promise of work and infrastructure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The discovery of large oil reserves in Uganda in 2006 led to widespread expectations that the economy would quickly be transformed. The dream is now set to become a reality. Production licences have been issued for three blocks, a deal has been struck for the route of the pipeline to take the oil to the sea, and the final preparatory studies have begun. Infrastructure construction has started and the government has set up the Petroleum Authority to regulate the industry. Exploration licences have also been issued for new areas. “This project is in a better place than it has ever been,” says...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>European stocks log tiny gain as oil shares recover - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-dragged-down-by-oil-shares-for-third-session-2017-06-22</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOLVJRjl0ujhO0usVe2w0aEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-dragged-down-by-oil-shares-for-third-session-2017-06-22" target="_blank"&gt;European stocks log tiny gain as oil shares recover&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Carla Mozee, Sara Sjolin Euro trading below $1.12 A clerk carries a Union Jack and a flag of the European Union at the European Commission in Brussels. AFP/Getty Images European stocks ended marginally higher after a volatile session on Thursday, as energy shares trimmed losses on the back of a rebound in oil prices. The Stoxx Europe 600 (XX:SXXP) ended 0.01% higher at 388.53, after trading as high as 388.71 and as low as 386.10 earlier in the day. The choppy session came as traders kept a close eye on oil prices, which entered bear-market territory earlier this week on c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Brexit cloud should shift for mid-cap stocks - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/312d3316-a43e-11e7-b797-b61809486fe2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3d55UG9L9UdVItYJAIvFAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 16:19:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/312d3316-a43e-11e7-b797-b61809486fe2" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit cloud should shift for mid-cap stocks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ever since the Brexit vote, pundits have predicted that returns from UK mid-cap stocks would substantially trail those from large-caps because of the former’s heavy domestic exposure. Yet this underperformance has stubbornly failed to materialise. The smaller companies of the FTSE 250 have lagged behind their larger peers in the FTSE 100 by about 2 percentage points in price terms since the June 2016 vote. But over just about every other time period, the FTSE 250 wins. Year-to-date returns also are better in sterling terms than the FTSE All World index. There are several reasons why the ind...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>European stocks log worst week in 9 months on U.S.-North Korea tensions - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-face-worst-week-in-9-months-on-us-north-korea-tensions-2017-08-11</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGWiZ9WcTml8XEOZpMdO_MEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 18:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-face-worst-week-in-9-months-on-us-north-korea-tensions-2017-08-11" target="_blank"&gt;European stocks log worst week in 9 months on U.S.-North Korea tensions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Carla Mozee Oil stocks key off losses for oil prices In Frankfurt, the DAX 30 was under pressure on Friday. Getty Images European stocks sold off Friday, wrapping up their worst week in nine months, as the war of words between the U.S. and North Korea prompted investors to back away from assets perceived as risky. The Stoxx Europe 600 (XX:SXXP) closed down 1% to 372.14, the weakest finish since Feb. 28. No sector finished higher. For the week, the index fell 2.7%, the worst week since early November 2016, just before the U.S. presidential election was held. “The weekend br...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>FTSE 100 falters and pound stuck below $1.22 as ECB leaves rates unchanged - but raises growth and inflation forecasts - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/03/09/ftse-100-falters-pound-stuck-122-choppy-trade-ahead-ecb-rate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYPuynwPU5KDC6r772AoJMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 17:58:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/03/09/ftse-100-falters-pound-stuck-122-choppy-trade-ahead-ecb-rate/" target="_blank"&gt;FTSE 100 falters and pound stuck below $1.22 as ECB leaves rates unchanged - but raises growth and inflation forecasts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Hong Kong stocks fall most in three months as commodity shares slump - UK Budget cold comfort for pound as Brexit fears see it stuck below $1.22 - European bourses falter at opening bell on disappointing earnings - US dollar holds gains on upbeat US ADP jobs data - ECB leaves rates unchanged but raises growth and inflation forecasts - Draghi: The euro is here to stay 5:58PMMarket Report: IAG flies to 14-month high on rating upgrade British Airways owner IAG soared to a 14-month high in intraday trading on the back of a rating upgrade. Liberum backtracked on its bearish view of the airli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Oil regains momentum after sharp slide on supply glut fears, as US jobs growth rebounds sharply in April - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/05/05/oil-prices-collapse-new-five-month-low-supply-glut-fears-iron/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK4UVrWHGXoh4cXaNrhJx1IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 17:23:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/05/05/oil-prices-collapse-new-five-month-low-supply-glut-fears-iron/" target="_blank"&gt;Oil regains momentum after sharp slide on supply glut fears, as US jobs growth rebounds sharply in April&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Iron ore on track for biggest one-day fall in five months on Chinese demand worries - Oil regains momentum after sharp slide on supply glut fears weighs - European shares retreat as commodity-related stocks drift lower - Pound steadies above $1.29 against US dollar - US jobs growth rebounds sharply in April6:23PMMarket report: Barclays slumps on third 'sell' rating in a month, as FTSE 100 climbs on oil rebound British lender Barclays slumped towards the bottom of the blue chip index after it received its third “sell” rating in less than a month. Goldman Sachs lowered its rating from “neut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>France’s CAC slides as key Macron ally departs, pulling European stocks lower - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-pushed-down-led-by-french-shares-oil-prices-2017-06-21</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBLrFOVTe_hoNF6-qGoo_kgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 16:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-pushed-down-led-by-french-shares-oil-prices-2017-06-21" target="_blank"&gt;France’s CAC slides as key Macron ally departs, pulling European stocks lower&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Carla Mozee, Sara Sjolin Queen’s Speech in focus as U.K. government races for deal Oil prices have entered a bear market, pulling European energy stocks lower. Reuters European stocks marched lower Wednesday, as the energy sector was dragged down by sliding oil prices and as the departure of a key ally of President Emmanuel Macron hit French equities. The Stoxx Europe 600 (XX:SXXP) lost 0.2% to close at 388.50, marking a second straight loss. The index tracking European oil and gas stocks (XX:SXEP) fell 0.2% as oil prices (CLN7) (UK:LCOQ7) moved lower. They slid into a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>New year, new highs: FTSE 100 smashes 7,200 and dollar index hits 14-year peak - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/01/03/new-year-new-record-high-ftse-100-smashes-7200-ahead-uk-manufacturing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELSSZsgnd1OWjrhbEs-cWSgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 17:07:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/01/03/new-year-new-record-high-ftse-100-smashes-7200-ahead-uk-manufacturing/" target="_blank"&gt;New year, new highs: FTSE 100 smashes 7,200 and dollar index hits 14-year peak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- FTSE 100 kicks off 2017 at new all-time record high - European bourses tick higher - Hong Kong stocks start 2017 firmer - Pound hits two-week against euro on strong manufacturing data - UK manufacturing growth unexpectedly hits 30-month high - Oil hits 18-month high after Opec production cut deal officially starts - Dow Jones eyes historic 20,000 mark - Dollar index hits 14-year high on US manufacturing data 5:07PMMarket report: Banking stocks push FTSE 100 to new record closing high New year, new highs. London’s benchmark index extended its end-of-year rally, closing at a new record h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>European stocks close with gains as earnings roll in - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-log-gains-as-earnings-roll-in-2017-07-26</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEOk94S8rEodfuZhNOvJFYkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 16:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-log-gains-as-earnings-roll-in-2017-07-26" target="_blank"&gt;European stocks close with gains as earnings roll in&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Carla Mozee Peugeot, Lonza, Tullow among the day’s big winners A Peugeot team competed in a race through Mongolia’s Gobi desert last year. AFP/Getty Images Stocks across Europe finished higher Wednesday, as investors sifted through the latest round of corporate earnings reports ahead of the Federal Reserve’s policy decision. The Stoxx Europe 600 (XX:SXXP) gained 0.5% to end at 382.74, after the benchmark on Tuesday advanced 0.4%. Shares of Swiss medical and biotech industries supplier Lonza Group AG (CH:LONN) and French car maker Peugeot SA (FR:UG) were among the gauge’s ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Tullow Oil takes $600m hit from lower crude price - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d8012594-5be1-11e7-9bc8-8055f264aa8b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJbhnFBMc1si2PCQWS4fa9kqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 12:06:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d8012594-5be1-11e7-9bc8-8055f264aa8b" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow Oil takes $600m hit from lower crude price&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent weakness in crude prices is taking its toll on exploration and production companies, as Tullow Oil, the Africa-focused group, warned it would book a $600m impairment in its half-year results to reflect reduced oil price forecasts. Analysts have warned such writedowns, disclosed in a trading update on Wednesday, would likely become a theme across the sector as oil prices languish below $50 a barrel. Brent crude dropped below $45 a barrel for the first time in 2017 last week, as traders’ faith in the ability of Opec, the oil-producing cartel, to deliver on pledged production cuts w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tullow Oil to resume drilling in Ghana after resolving dispute - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/738f847c-a0fe-11e7-b797-b61809486fe2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0RkZsfjzVML1aeLgRD29YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 11:41:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/738f847c-a0fe-11e7-b797-b61809486fe2" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow Oil to resume drilling in Ghana after resolving dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil is preparing to resume drilling in Ghana after the resolution of a maritime border dispute with Ivory Coast that has halted expansion of an important new field for two years. An international tribunal declared on Saturday that the sovereign rights of Ivory Coast had not been violated by Tullow’s development of oil and gas fields in Ghanaian waters close to the two countries’ border. The ruling clears the way for UK-listed Tullow to resume development of the Tweneboa, Enyenra, Ntomme fields, collectively known as Ten, which have been operating below their potential capacity since ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Fast Europe Open: Bank earnings, Turkey interest rates - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4d482580-405e-3c6c-b0f8-b8ad322d3a29</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMGbcj5Xzj1Ii6D0D5MGGfwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 05:11:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4d482580-405e-3c6c-b0f8-b8ad322d3a29" target="_blank"&gt;Fast Europe Open: Bank earnings, Turkey interest rates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors in Europe will inherit a solid lead from Asia where regional markets were buoyed by Wall Street’s advance to near-record levels. Markets are also still basking in the glow of the result of the first round of France’s presidential race. Centrist Emmanuel Macron will face off against the far-right Marine Le Pen, with the former expected to triumph in the final vote on May 7. On Tuesday, the S&amp;P 500 closed 0.6 per cent higher and is now sitting less than one-third of 1 percentage point away from a record high. Additionally, the Nasdaq Composite closed above 6,000 points for the first...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tullow CEO pledges focus on discipline with oil stuck under $50 - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/391e9d75-d505-3269-9e82-a03539cc8505</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3Gl_YZ6HUrcD9pprtCx08qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 06:16:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/391e9d75-d505-3269-9e82-a03539cc8505" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow CEO pledges focus on discipline with oil stuck under $50&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new chief executive of Tullow Oil has promised to focus on financial discipline as he seeks to return the heavily indebted Africa-focused explorer and producer to growth in “tough” market conditions, as oil prices languish below $50 a barrel. The group, which earlier this year went cap in hand to shareholders for $750m to reduce its debt load, said on Tuesday that it expects to book a $600m non-cash impairment in its half year results, pre-tax, reflecting lower oil price forecasts. Brent crude dropped below $45 a barrel for the first time in 2017 last week, as traders’ faith in the abil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Pound trims gains against euro in choppy trade and FTSE 100 rises after Theresa May triggers Article 50 - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/03/29/pound-tumbles-back-124-theresa-may-prepares-trigger-article/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_2BmcpSPazr3-lp1xEZuIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 18:03:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/03/29/pound-tumbles-back-124-theresa-may-prepares-trigger-article/" target="_blank"&gt;Pound trims gains against euro in choppy trade and FTSE 100 rises after Theresa May triggers Article 50&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- The end of the affair: how the historic day Article 50 is triggered will unfold - From the EU referendum to Article 50: the charts that show how the UK's economy has performed ​ - The UK could have no flights to and from Europe after Brexit, Ryanair warns - Pound climbs slips back towards $1.24 in afternoon trade after Brexit trigger - Pound trims gains against euro in choppy trade - FTSE 100 and FTSE 250 close higher after Article 50 is formally triggered 7:03PMMarkets wrap: Markets shrug off formal triggering of Article 50 Financial markets shrugged off the well-flagged formal triggeri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Oil: gushing with relief - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ba5ad5b8-a2c6-11e7-b797-b61809486fe2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA5X8sC17xRgjyzh0bBTpDoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ba5ad5b8-a2c6-11e7-b797-b61809486fe2" target="_blank"&gt;Oil: gushing with relief&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the best efforts of US shale oil drillers, Opec remains the main source of crude supply for the world. More than once in the past it has promised to curtail supply to support prices, most recently last November. This time the promises have begun to bite. A supply squeeze from key Opec producers is having an impact on inventories. As supply tightens, a more optimistic view on oil is taking hold. Brent crude has rallied strongly, up more than a quarter since late June to $58, hitting new highs for the year. One way to measure the change in sentiment is by observing the spread between ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tullow Oil to tighten its belt as oil market woes wipe out $600m - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/06/28/tullow-oil-tighten-belt-oil-market-woes-wipe-600m/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFKL120m8mvntpVOAElQFGIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 12:48:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/06/28/tullow-oil-tighten-belt-oil-market-woes-wipe-600m/" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow Oil to tighten its belt as oil market woes wipe out $600m&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil has promised to tighten its belt after booking a $600m (£468m) impairment charge due to the slump in oil prices. The Africa-focused oil explorer said it continued to face “tough market conditions” after turning to shareholders to raise $750m through a rights issue earlier this year to help manage its debt burden. The ongoing weakness in the oil market means the group will report a $600m hit in its mid-year report through a non-cash impairment charge on its property and equipment assets. Tullow has shaved $100m from its forecast spending for the year to $400m, down from $900m last...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>North Sea explorers focus on African fields in quest for low-cost oil - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/01/17/north-sea-explorers-focus-african-fields-quest-low-cost-oil/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENvS2hyfW1NP9RGC5dSOI6EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 14:41:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/01/17/north-sea-explorers-focus-african-fields-quest-low-cost-oil/" target="_blank"&gt;North Sea explorers focus on African fields in quest for low-cost oil&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;North Sea oil companies Cairn Energy and Tullow Oil are both planning to tap low-cost African oil fields this year to take full advantage of the rising price of crude oil. Edinburgh-based Cairn Energy told investors that it would start a third round of exploration drilling in Senegal later this month to test the limits of its licence in west Africa, which has so far delivered six successful wells and could contain as much as 27 billion barrels of oil. The update pushed its share price 3pc higher to 248.40p. Cairn Energy Meanwhile shares in Africa-focused explorer Tullow Oil bounced 1.5pc hi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tullow to begin seismic surveys in Jamaica and Uruguay - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/bb0eb1e7-3883-36e1-9494-ceb8e7c6e055</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDmE-IBSM5iPL0gyW-fyBHQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 06:38:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/bb0eb1e7-3883-36e1-9494-ceb8e7c6e055" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow to begin seismic surveys in Jamaica and Uruguay&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil, the Africa-focused energy group, said it is taking full advantage of the current low costs in the industry to carry out seismic surveys in territories such as Jamaica and Uruguay. Such activity is at a “historic high”, the group said in a statement on Wednesday, ahead of its annual general meeting. A number of oil explorers are trying to exploit low prices for everything from drilling rigs to seismic surveys before higher activity levels push up costs again. Services companies were forced to slash prices after crude began its steep downward spiral in 2014 and explorers and produ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Pearson shares decline on worries over virtual schools - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d3c5d510-1aeb-11e7-a266-12672483791a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELCEj5NSK-ateHu7bqluMBcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 17:57:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d3c5d510-1aeb-11e7-a266-12672483791a" target="_blank"&gt;Pearson shares decline on worries over virtual schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pearson led the FTSE 100 lower on Thursday after Exane BNP Paribas raised concerns about virtual schools, one of its fastest growing businesses. Exane worried that growth rates may not be sustainable for Connections Academy, an online-only public primary and secondary schools operator bought by Pearson in 2011. Headwinds for the business include a lack of new school openings, enrolment caps on established schools and regulatory headwinds, it said. Pearson has no new virtual schools due to open for the upcoming academic year, against nine in the past three years, and caps on student numbers ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tullow Oil to battle debt with £607m cash call - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/03/17/tullow-oil-battle-debt-607m-cash-call/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOjOX25tPs8hLhNLD8sKc1kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 11:28:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/03/17/tullow-oil-battle-debt-607m-cash-call/" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow Oil to battle debt with £607m cash call&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil is preparing to issue new shares in a bid to raise £607m to help tackle its $4.8bn debts. The London-based oil company will issue 466.9 million shares at 130p each, which is 45.2pc lower than Thursday's closing price. The heavy discount triggered a market sell-off that caused shares to plummet almost 15pc to 202p. The Africa-focused oil explorer racked up a debt pile of $4.8bn (£3.9bn) after the 2014 oil price crash battered revenues while Tullow was investing heavily in an oil project off Ghana. The strain has propelled the company’s ratio of debt to more than five times its ann...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>UK GDP growth nudges up to 0.3pc; diesel drivers to face increasing taxes - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/07/26/pound-comes-highs-against-dollar-ahead-uk-gdp-data/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENIy8lWUQIs9DwFLQhgz4OAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 16:27:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/07/26/pound-comes-highs-against-dollar-ahead-uk-gdp-data/" target="_blank"&gt;UK GDP growth nudges up to 0.3pc; diesel drivers to face increasing taxes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- The UK economy grew by 0.3pc in the second quarter according to the ONS, a slight pick-up from the first quarter - Reaction muted on the currency markets, growth in line with expecations - Latest rate decision from US Federal Reserve also due today - ITV the top gainer on the FTSE 100 despite fall in ad revenue5:27PMMarkets wrap: FTSE 100 nudges up after paring gains; investor attention turns to Fed meeting Buoyed by more impressive earnings, US indices have risen to fresh all-time highs this afternoon as its European counterparts have faded. The FTSE 100 has nudged up on yesterday's gain...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fast Europe Open: UK house prices, France consumer confidence - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/68ecb81c-7cf4-3911-a7c8-204e2e4f8e41</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSusYmnYONdMHrelVAoxmIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 05:16:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/68ecb81c-7cf4-3911-a7c8-204e2e4f8e41" target="_blank"&gt;Fast Europe Open: UK house prices, France consumer confidence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A global cyber attack has hit some of the world’s largest companies taking out computers, ATMs and supermarket checkouts. Companies including Rosneft and WPP were targeted by hackers demanding a bitcoin ransom in an attack bearing similarities to last month’s WannaCry hack. The attack reached Asia Pacific this morning, taking out a chocolate factory in Tasmania. No one has yet claimed responsibility for the attack. In markets, the euro remained strong during Asia trading after European Central Bank president Mario Draghi gave a relatively bullish assessment of Europe’s economy that sent the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Germany’s DAX ends near 2-year high as euro softens - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-edge-higher-to-flirt-with-2-year-high-2017-03-30</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFCxAitmfOio8fM2oW69-CcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 16:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-edge-higher-to-flirt-with-2-year-high-2017-03-30" target="_blank"&gt;Germany’s DAX ends near 2-year high as euro softens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Sara Sjolin Stoxx Europe 600 ends at highest since Dec. 2015 AFP/Getty Images European stocks rose for a third straight day on Thursday, with the German benchmark logging its highest close since April 2015 on the back of a sliding euro. The DAX 30 index (DX:DAX) rose 0.4% to end at 12,256.43, just 118 points short of its all-time closing high of 12,374.73 reached April 10, 2015. For the quarter, the index was looking at a 6.8% rally, its third quarterly rally in a row. The advance in Frankfurt came as the euro (EURUSD) slumped to an almost two-week low after disappointin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>FTSE 100 ends higher, rebounding from 3-month low as North Korea fears subside - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/ftse-100-rebounds-from-3-month-low-as-north-korea-tensions-subside-2017-08-14</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELiBYomB1lNm-0OOTaisZG0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 16:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/ftse-100-rebounds-from-3-month-low-as-north-korea-tensions-subside-2017-08-14" target="_blank"&gt;FTSE 100 ends higher, rebounding from 3-month low as North Korea fears subside&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON MARKETS By Sara Sjolin, Victor Reklaitis Oil slide as worries over OPEC supply persist U.K. stocks rise for first time in four sessions Shutterstock/alice-photo U.K. stocks closed higher Monday, bringing an end to a three-session losing run as investor anxiety over tensions between the U.S. and North Korea subsided. The FTSE 100 index (UK:UKX) rose 0.6% to finish at 7,353.89, rebounding after closing Friday at its lowest level since early May. The blue-chip benchmark last week slid 2.7%, suffering its biggest weekly decline since the April, thanks in part to a war of words between U...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Tullow sells Uganda stake to Total for $900m - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/01/09/tullow-sells-uganda-stake-total-900m/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcE3TL1eT_dN1bMYPbhPzMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 20:39:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/01/09/tullow-sells-uganda-stake-total-900m/" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow sells Uganda stake to Total for $900m&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil had sold two-thirds of its stake in Uganda's first ever oil development to its partner, French major Total, for $900m. The giant project on the shores of Lake Albert, where Tullow first discovered oil in 2006, is estimated to contain 1.7bn barrels of oil and forecast to eventually produce 230,000 barrels per day (bpd). Its development is expected to cost $3bn to get to first oil production, and require a further $3.5bn to be spent on a new pipeline to export the oil through Tanzania. Ownership of the licence areas had been evenly split between Tullow, Total and China's CNOOC but ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tullow asks shareholders for £607m to cut its large debt load - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a88a2e6c-0ae4-11e7-ac5a-903b21361b43</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBxP_FwCPEB035MoJeuLaq8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 09:43:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a88a2e6c-0ae4-11e7-ac5a-903b21361b43" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow asks shareholders for £607m to cut its large debt load&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil, the Africa-focused oil and gas explorer, caught shareholders off guard on Friday by asking them for a £607m cash injection to reduce its large debt load. Shares in the London-listed company fell after Tullow’s announcement of the deeply discounted rights issue, as analysts pointed out that management had previously appeared to rule out a sale of new stock. Stephane Foucaud, analyst at GMP FirstEnergy, said investors had been hoping the “worst was behind Tullow” after it returned to a position of positive free cash flow in the fourth quarter of 2016. The company’s borrowings have...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Serica Energy on the hunt for North Sea deals as cash pile grows - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/04/06/serica-energy-hunt-north-sea-deals-cash-pile-grows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYjhUqbbHGrZ30m2ERjJLcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 14:28:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/04/06/serica-energy-hunt-north-sea-deals-cash-pile-grows/" target="_blank"&gt;Serica Energy on the hunt for North Sea deals as cash pile grows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;North Sea minnow Serica Energy is on the prowl for a North Sea acquisition as its cash pile continues to grow. Serica is one of the few North Sea producers who weathered the oil market downturn and emerged with cash rather than growing debts. It now plans to follow its 2015 acquisition of a stake in BP gas assets with further purchases. Serica’s full-year results for 2016 show a cash balance of $16.6m (£13.3m) but it expects to report this increasing to $25.7m at the end of the first quarter thanks to stronger sales. Oil prices climbing above $50 a barrel gave the business a sales boost lat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tullow Oil clinches stay of execution as it tackles $5bn debt - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/02/08/tullow-oil-clinches-stay-execution-tackles-5bn-debt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4mUMkN0uWPcsQrFKrfjzAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 13:35:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/02/08/tullow-oil-clinches-stay-execution-tackles-5bn-debt/" target="_blank"&gt;Tullow Oil clinches stay of execution as it tackles $5bn debt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tullow Oil has landed a one year extension on a billion dollar debt facility as it begins the task of tackling a rising debt pile of $4.8bn after a third consecutive year of losses. The Africa-focused oil group took a heavy hit from the fall in the oil price after taking out billions of dollars in debt to develop the TEN oil project off the coast of Ghana. But Tullow’s lenders have agreed to keep its $1bn corporate debt facility open until mid 2019 as the group kickstarts talks for a full-scale overhaul of its debt pile and the TEN project begins to bring in fresh streams of much-needed cas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>European stocks pare gains after U.S. data, but Germany still scores record - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-head-for-2-week-high-with-investors-hopeful-about-key-us-jobs-data-2017-06-02</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIUUPNq4nOVzq2K7FBtDtAgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwmJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 16:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/european-stocks-head-for-2-week-high-with-investors-hopeful-about-key-us-jobs-data-2017-06-02" target="_blank"&gt;European stocks pare gains after U.S. data, but Germany still scores record&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE MARKETS By Sara Sjolin U.K.’s FTSE 100 also aims for record finish All eyes were on the U.S. jobs report. Getty Images European stocks trimmed earlier gains to ended with a small advance on Friday after U.S. jobs data fell short of expectations and raised questions about the strength of the world’s largest economy. The Stoxx Europe 600 Index (XX:SXXP) ended 0.2% higher at 392.55, after rising as much as 0.8% earlier in the day. The pullback came after the closely watched U.S. nonfarm payrolls report showed 138,000 jobs were added to the economy in May, far below the consensus foreca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Mediclinic slips to near two-year low on UAE business worries - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/898e0870-a202-11e7-b797-b61809486fe2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAT52MVNvAAxhP1yofzOHOEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 18:48:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/898e0870-a202-11e7-b797-b61809486fe2" target="_blank"&gt;Mediclinic slips to near two-year low on UAE business worries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mediclinic slipped to its lowest in nearly two years on Monday amid worries about a slow turnround of its United Arab Emirates business. Jefferies analysts advised selling Mediclinic ahead of a trading statement from the private hospital operator due next month. Investors hope the UAE operations have troughed but intensifying competition in Dubai, where the company is investing in a new 150 bed general hospital, and a rebrand of its troubled Abu Dhabi operations make the update a ”potential consensus resetting event”, Jefferies told clients. It put a 550p target on Mediclinic, which closed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>FTSE 100 erases 2017 gains, as pound steadies below six-month high after general election surge - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/04/19/ftse-100-erases-2017-gains-pound-steadies-six-month-high-investors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMTih6kkHsORIhcnr-97dZAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 17:32:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/04/19/ftse-100-erases-2017-gains-pound-steadies-six-month-high-investors/" target="_blank"&gt;FTSE 100 erases 2017 gains, as pound steadies below six-month high after general election surge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- FTSE 100 erases 2017 gains - Pound steadies below six-month high - Investors digest implications of snap election - Gold falls as investors add risk6:32PMMarket report: Oil majors knocked by rating downgrades Oil majors need a reality check. That was the message from US investment bank Citigroup as it downgraded the ratings of Royal Dutch Shell and BP to “sell” and “neutral”, respectively. Analyst Alastair Syme said: “Fine-print of 2016 annual reports indicates that most big oil companies still believe in $70-80s oil prices longer term.” But that’s a level oil has not touched in more th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Pearson slips as investors show pre-results nerves - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0e83d7c6-f795-11e6-bd4e-68d53499ed71</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPfaypSC-NKgqEooMjvP2CoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 18:25:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0e83d7c6-f795-11e6-bd4e-68d53499ed71" target="_blank"&gt;Pearson slips as investors show pre-results nerves&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pre-results jitters put Pearson among Monday’s sharpest fallers. Ahead of its full-year figures due Friday, Pearson faded 3.9 per cent to 642.5p. Since a profit warning in late January, the textbook publisher had rallied as much as 17 per cent amid hopes of another round of cost-cutting. But Pearson has already spent £610m on restructuring since 2013, to net cumulative savings of just £586m even before reinvestment, said Berenberg. “The issue is not that the business was fat, but that it was over-earning,” said Berenberg, which put a 400p target on Pearson shares. Margins for higher educati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Wood Group reports ‘significant’ reduction in work - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4fd000ba-5c94-11e7-9bc8-8055f264aa8b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEInOhWWtCbE00y68450A7ncqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 09:30:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4fd000ba-5c94-11e7-9bc8-8055f264aa8b" target="_blank"&gt;Wood Group reports ‘significant’ reduction in work&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wood Group , the UK oilfield services company, has reported “materially” lower levels of work in key regions such as the North Sea and warned there is “limited” scope for improvement as oil prices continue to flounder below $50 a barrel. The company said a “significant” reduction in projects and modifications work in the North Sea and slower than expected activity in Saudi Arabia had prompted “more cautious” expectations for the full year, although it anticipates a stronger performance in the final six months. The warning, contained in a pre-close trading update on Thursday, adds to evidenc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>FT Opening Quote: GSK’s Emma Walmsley’s first 25 days - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c023cfb6-eb5f-3d1c-a320-8e40d4aa5933</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAIGw7-xAEYElZimzwq1wFAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 06:58:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c023cfb6-eb5f-3d1c-a320-8e40d4aa5933" target="_blank"&gt;FT Opening Quote: GSK’s Emma Walmsley’s first 25 days&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GSK’s Emma Walmsley’s first 25 days. FT Opening Quote, with commentary by Matthew Vincent, is your early Square Mile briefing. You can sign up for the full newsletter here. Twenty five days is barely enough time to unpack one’s office-move crates and order new business cards, let alone make one’s mark as the leader of a multinational organisation. Even desk-tidying US presidents are allowed 100 days. And I am still surrounded by the dusty boxes of colleagues several months into their new roles (if anyone wants a copy of The UK Corporate Governance Handbook 1993, email me). So to expect Emma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Kosmos to test investors’ energy appetite with London listing - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/55f33616-7705-11e7-a3e8-60495fe6ca71</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM44WWNADYMImRS1yytIeBcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 06:06:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/55f33616-7705-11e7-a3e8-60495fe6ca71" target="_blank"&gt;Kosmos to test investors’ energy appetite with London listing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kosmos Energy is aiming to become the biggest oil and gas company to join the London Stock Exchange since the oil price slide three years ago, in a test of investor sentiment towards the sector. The Dallas-based explorer is to pursue a secondary listing on London’s main market in addition to its existing membership of the New York Stock Exchange. Kosmos, which had a market capitalisation of $2.5bn in New York on Tuesday, has earned a reputation as one of the most successful international exploration companies after a string of big discoveries off the coast of west Africa. Andrew Inglis, Kos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>