<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>International Red Cross and Red Crescent Movement - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRE42Y2pVU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:48:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>IFRC: Migrant Children Traveling Alone 'Most Vulnerable People in the World' - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/ifrc-human-trafficking/4684241.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH9L9zvES75hBgsME3kD98wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:18:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/ifrc-human-trafficking/4684241.html" target="_blank"&gt;IFRC: Migrant Children Traveling Alone 'Most Vulnerable People in the World'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A report by the International Federation of Red Cross and Red Crescent Societies (IFRC) says thousands of unaccompanied children and children who have been separated from their families run the daily risk of sexual and gender-based violence as they travel along the world's migratory trails. "A child who is migrating alone, without the love and protection of a parent, family member or guardian, is arguably one of the most vulnerable people in the world," said Francesco Rocca, IFRC president. The report entitled "Alone and Unsafe," is being released ahead of next week's meeting in Marrakech w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Iran Earthquake Leaves 2 Dead, Hundreds Injured - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/iran-earthqake-north-khorasan/3850883.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKBYHunABMDDLhuZHT0BzjUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 07:37:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/iran-earthqake-north-khorasan/3850883.html" target="_blank"&gt;Iran Earthquake Leaves 2 Dead, Hundreds Injured&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 5.7-magnitude earthquake has hit the Iranian city of Pishqaleh in North Khorasan province, killing two people and injuring at least 225 more, according to IRNA, Iran's official news agency. The Red Crescent Society said 37 search and rescue teams were sent to the quake-hit region Saturday, immediately after the earthquake struck. Eighty percent of the injured and survivors have been relocated into tents, the Red Crescent said. The quake was centered at a depth of 11 kilometers. Iran is located atop several major fault lines and is prone to frequent earthquakes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Syria situation ‘an international armed conflict’ after US missile strike – Red Cross to RT - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/384127-us-strike-red-cross/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPF3Ks9JUBHoVmc76-bmWqQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 17:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/384127-us-strike-red-cross/" target="_blank"&gt;Syria situation ‘an international armed conflict’ after US missile strike – Red Cross to RT&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Red Cross has characterized the current situation in Syria as an “international armed conflict” after the US missile strike on Syrian Shayrat airfield near Homs, the ICRC regional spokesperson told RT. The International Committee of the Red Cross (ICRC) spokesperson for the Near and Middle East region, Ralph El Hage, spoke with RT about the shift in the organization’s assessment of the ongoing Syrian conflict. The ICRC previously regarded the conflict as an internal conflict. “When a military of a certain state attacks the military of another state on the territory of that state, and th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Red Crescent: 74 dead refugees wash ashore in Zawiya - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/red-crescent-74-dead-refugees-wash-ashore-zawiya-170221092854189.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJiEHQElw571UyVdgxoBvOUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 11:29:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/red-crescent-74-dead-refugees-wash-ashore-zawiya-170221092854189.html" target="_blank"&gt;Red Crescent: 74 dead refugees wash ashore in Zawiya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libya's Red Crescent has said that 74 bodies of refugees have washed ashore in the western city of Zawiya on the Mediterranean Sea. The aid organisation's spokesman Mohammed al-Misrati told the AP news agency that the bodies washed ashore on Tuesday morning. He said thecircumstances involving the drownings were not clear yet. The agency posted on its Twitter account photographs of dozens of bodies in white and black body bags, lined up along the shore. Misrati also said that local authorities will take the bodies to a cemetery in the capital, Tripoli, that is allocated for unidentified pers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Red Cross: Safe Burial Practices Helped Prevent Spread of Ebola in West Africa - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/red-cross-safe-burial-saved-lived-ebola-west-africa/3912754.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAs-aDjE-P8f3RTJAcJrpwoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 08:52:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/red-cross-safe-burial-saved-lived-ebola-west-africa/3912754.html" target="_blank"&gt;Red Cross: Safe Burial Practices Helped Prevent Spread of Ebola in West Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study by the International Federation of Red Cross and Red Crescent Societies says that safe burial practices may have helped prevent the transmission of thousands of cases of Ebola during the epidemic in West Africa between 2013 and 2016. More than 11,300 people died from Ebola in Liberia, Sierra Leone and Guinea before the epidemic was stopped in those countries in 2016. Ebola is highly contagious and spread by direct contact with blood or other bodily fluids. Symptoms include a sudden fever, aching muscles, diarrhea and vomiting. Red Cross study A co-author of the Red Cross Federat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>UN Chief Urges 'Swift Action' to Alleviate Suffering of Myanmar Muslims - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-chief-urges-swift-action-to-alleviate-suffering-of-myanmar-muslims/4049304.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBBCJaUkbZH4vvKAeSUY_BkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 00:52:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-chief-urges-swift-action-to-alleviate-suffering-of-myanmar-muslims/4049304.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Chief Urges 'Swift Action' to Alleviate Suffering of Myanmar Muslims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.N. Secretary-General António Guterres called Thursday for “swift action” to halt the deteriorating situation in Myanmar’s northern Rakhine State, where a half million mostly Rohingya Muslims have fled to neighboring Bangladesh in the past month. “The situation has spiraled into the world’s fastest developing refugee emergency; a humanitarian and human rights nightmare,” Guterres told an open meeting of the U.N. Security Council. The council has privately discussed the situation three times in the past month, but Thursday’s session was the first time since 2009 that it has publicly discuss...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Bodies of more than 70 migrants wash up on Libya's coast - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/21/africa/libya-migrant-deaths/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAYBEXy6gqhwaNjELFVXwp0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 12:55:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/21/africa/libya-migrant-deaths/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bodies of more than 70 migrants wash up on Libya's coast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bodies of 74 migrants have been recovered by the Libyan Red Crescent after washing up on the country's northern coast near the city of Zawiya. Rescuers say a sole survivor was found near a torn rubber dinghy. Volunteers, who responded to a call yesterday morning, say they believe the individuals drowned while trying to cross the Mediterranean to reach Europe. "There are still bodies in the sea but our team could not reach them because the sea is very troubling and they don't have boats so they can't reach them easily," Taha K. Sultan Elbarghathi, international relations officer for the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Abducted Red Cross Staffer Released - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/cheats/2017/01/15/abducted-red-cross-staffer-released.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJpnxPop0EI5BqAOQP1OGYAqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLzdlwI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 15:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/cheats/2017/01/15/abducted-red-cross-staffer-released.html" target="_blank"&gt;Abducted Red Cross Staffer Released&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a press release from the International Committee of the Red Cross, a staff member who was abducted in Kunduz, Afghanistan on December 19 has been released. "We are relieved and grateful that Juan Carlos is now back with us, safe and sound," said the ICRC head of delegation in Afghanistan, Monica Zanarelli. "His abduction was a terrible ordeal for him, as well as for his family, friends and colleagues." The ICRC is not commenting on the identity of the individuals who abducted him or what their motives were in the event.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Aid Convoy to Besieged Area Comes Under Fire in Syria - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/red-crescent-worker-wounded-in-damascus-attack/3905186.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJFjyXbp-w-KDskMGRggwOUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 11:09:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/red-crescent-worker-wounded-in-damascus-attack/3905186.html" target="_blank"&gt;Aid Convoy to Besieged Area Comes Under Fire in Syria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A convoy delivering aid to a besieged opposition area outside Syria's capital has come under attack, seriously wounding a driver of the Syrian Arab Red Crescent and thwarting the first such mission to the area in eight months, aid groups said Sunday. The 37-truck convoy, jointly organized by the International Committee of the Red Cross, the Syrian Arab Red Crescent and the United Nations, was to deliver food and medicine to 11,000 people in the town of East Harasta. An aid worker and a local council in east Harasta said the delivery had already been aborted before the convoy came under atta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>'Humanitarian catastrophe' unfolding as Myanmar takes over aid efforts in Rakhine state - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2017/sep/15/humanitarian-catastrophe-unfolding-as-myanmar-takes-over-aid-efforts-in-rakhine-state-rohingya</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIMJjsW_Yw2n-Eqd-hjkoO4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 14:11:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2017/sep/15/humanitarian-catastrophe-unfolding-as-myanmar-takes-over-aid-efforts-in-rakhine-state-rohingya" target="_blank"&gt;'Humanitarian catastrophe' unfolding as Myanmar takes over aid efforts in Rakhine state&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Myanmar government has taken control of aid operations in the country’s crisis-hit Rakhine state, as reports continue of massacres and “ethnic cleansing” by soldiers on the Muslim population there. Senior officials and Human Rights Watch have told the Guardian they believe the move could become permanent, ending vital food and health programmes run by international agencies. Already there is an aid blockade on UN agencies that workers say is having a severe impact on malnourished children. Related: Myanmar: footage reveals scorched-earth campaign against Rohingya The UN has described th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Aleppo evacuation set to begin under new deal - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/12/aleppo-161218045722651.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMps50J7NBUIogFW1TtAq-wqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 13:54:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/12/aleppo-161218045722651.html" target="_blank"&gt;Aleppo evacuation set to begin under new deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The evacuation of thousands of increasingly desperate Syrian civilians and fighters stranded in besieged east Aleppo is set to resume after a new deal was reached between rebel and the Syrian government. Buses started entering several neighbourhoods on Sunday under the supervision of the Red Crescent and the International Committee of the Red Cross (ICRC), state news agency SANA said. A source in Aleppo told Al Jazeera that as part of the latest deal, a total of 4,000 people will evacuate the Shia-majority towns of Fua and Kefraya in Idlib province, which are currently besieged by oppositio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>At least 70 civilians killed in Nigeria refugee camp air strike: International Red Cross - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-security-idUSKBN1521UQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFBAN8vMG-N3sS2hmUNPutoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 13:34:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-security-idUSKBN1521UQ" target="_blank"&gt;At least 70 civilians killed in Nigeria refugee camp air strike: International Red Cross&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (Reuters) - At least 70 civilians were killed in Tuesday's Nigerian Air Force strike on a refugee camp and more than a hundred were wounded, the International Red Cross and Red Crescent Movement said on Wednesday. The air force has said an unknown number of civilians were killed and wounded in the mistaken strike in Rann, northeast Nigeria. It said the attack was intended to target Islamist militant Boko Haram fighters. Medical charity Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF) has said 52 were killed and 120 were wounded. (Reporting by Tom Miles; Writing by Alexis Akwagyiram; Editing by Dominic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Thousands in North Korea at risk months after devastating floods: IFRC - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-floods-idUSKBN1420R2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPIy23Ue9KmvxP1azcIW13cqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 08:55:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-floods-idUSKBN1420R2" target="_blank"&gt;Thousands in North Korea at risk months after devastating floods: IFRC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEOUL (Reuters) - Thousands of survivors of floods that hit a remote corner of North Korea in August are in need of urgent aid as winter sets in, a senior international aid official said on Tuesday. The floods, the worst in North Korea for 70 years, hit near its northeast borders with China and Russia and affected 600,000 people and left 70,000 homeless, the International Federation of Red Cross and Red Crescent Societies (IFRC) said. "There is still much to do. Many people lost everything," IFRC president Tadateru Konoé said in a news release following a 10-day visit to the isolated countr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>ICRC: Strike on Nigeria refugee camp killed at least 76 - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/01/icrc-strike-nigeria-refugee-camp-killed-76-170118150235741.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDIiRWNEm9axkaO-6Gmk0s0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 19:17:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/01/icrc-strike-nigeria-refugee-camp-killed-76-170118150235741.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICRC: Strike on Nigeria refugee camp killed at least 76&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of dead has risen to at least 76 people in the accidental Nigerian air force strike on a camp for displaced people, according to the International Red Cross and Red Crescent Movement (ICRC). ICRC said on Wednesday that six Nigeria Red Cross members were among the dead and 13 more were wounded in Tuesday's incident in Rann, in the far north of Borno state. "In addition to aid staff, it is estimated that 70 people have been killed and more than a 100 wounded," ICRC said in a statement. Aid group Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF) has said 52 were killed and 120 were wounded in the inci...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Aleppo evacuation: Here are 16 Syrian aid organisations that need your help - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/aleppo-evacuation-syria-war-crisis-help-aid-organisations-donations-red-cross-white-helmets-pro-a7484181.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI-KdLpHDtbGJOliUILT4UsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 12:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/aleppo-evacuation-syria-war-crisis-help-aid-organisations-donations-red-cross-white-helmets-pro-a7484181.html" target="_blank"&gt;Aleppo evacuation: Here are 16 Syrian aid organisations that need your help&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bombardment has left those civilians still stranded throughout Aleppo without access to medical facilities, food or shelter, while tens of thousands of internally displaced refugees are also in urgent need of aid. Government forces, pro-Assad militias and armed opposition groups have all been accused of obstructing the flow of aid around Syria's largest city. On 18 December, buses intended to convey civilians out of the city were burned by an Islamist anti-government faction, while the Assad regime has repeatedly blocked aid convoys from entering the city. In such circumstances, large chari...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Humanitarian needs of people of Aleppo are ‘huge’, basic services still need to be restored – ICRC - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/372193-aleppo-humanitarian-needs-icrc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELFqCYZqeX9m69yW_h-EltgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 21:55:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/372193-aleppo-humanitarian-needs-icrc/" target="_blank"&gt;Humanitarian needs of people of Aleppo are ‘huge’, basic services still need to be restored – ICRC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the liberation of Aleppo by Syrian government forces, many residents still live in dire conditions while the International Committee of the Red Cross is trying to help restore key services, an ICRC spokeswoman told RT. Many Aleppo residents still have to live in the poor conditions of makeshift shelters allocated in mosques and schools as they cannot return to their homes located in the neighborhoods that were severely damaged during the battle for the city, Krista Armstrong, ICRC spokesperson for Middle East, told RT. At the same time, she stressed that humanitarian access to the cit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>ICRC says total of 25,000 evacuated from Aleppo - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-evacuation-idUSKBN149108</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMMEdom5bpNQRsJ--mQ9KIUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 10:54:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-evacuation-idUSKBN149108" target="_blank"&gt;ICRC says total of 25,000 evacuated from Aleppo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (Reuters) - Some 25,000 people have been evacuated from the rebel-held enclave of Aleppo since Thursday, including 15,000 on Monday and 10,000 last Thursday, the International Committee of the Red Cross said on Tuesday. Teams from the ICRC and the Syrian Arab Red Crescent, who are leading the evacuation, were "working through the night" on Monday, ICRC spokeswoman Krista Armstrong told Reuters. (Reporting By Stephanie Nebehay; Writing by Angus McDowall in Beirut; Editing by Kevin Liffey)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Deadly air strike on Nigerian refugee camp sparks U.N. call for investigation - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-security-idUSKBN1532N0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJTqC_BYXL5k6H73GT9dN3oqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 17:05:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-security-idUSKBN1532N0" target="_blank"&gt;Deadly air strike on Nigerian refugee camp sparks U.N. call for investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Kieran Guilbert MAIDUGURI, Nigeria (Thomson Reuters Foundation) - A botched military air strike on a refugee camp in northeast Nigeria which is estimated to have killed at least 76 people and injured many more must be fully investigated, a United Nations expert said on Thursday. The Nigerian government said the bombing on Tuesday of the camp in Rann in Borno state, the heart of Boko Haram's seven-year bid to create an Islamic caliphate, was aimed at the militants and called it a "regrettable operational mistake". The air force said civilians were accidentally killed and wounded in the at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Red Crescent staff injured in ‘hideous’ US coalition strike on Idlib HQ – Turkish IFCR chief - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/376004-idlib-red-crescent-coalition-strike/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELZxhXUVV5PtvsaPsgJO4CAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 04:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/376004-idlib-red-crescent-coalition-strike/" target="_blank"&gt;Red Crescent staff injured in ‘hideous’ US coalition strike on Idlib HQ – Turkish IFCR chief&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US coalition has struck the headquarters of the Syrian Red Crescent and injured its staff in Syria’s Idlib, President of Turkish Red Crescent Kerem Kinik said, calling the alleged drone strike a “hideous war crime.” The strike happened in the early hours of Wednesday at around 3:00 am (01:00 GMT) and destroyed the building’s upper floors and injured people on the ground level. The victims have reportedly been transported to makeshift hospitals in Idlib. “At least four staff members of the Syrian Red Crescent (SARC) were injured in the airstrikes, one of them is in critical condition,” m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Millions of Disaster Victims Miss Out on Humanitarian Aid - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/millions-of-disaster-victims-miss-out-on-humanitarian-aid/4636419.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIaz2zm8lLJQQ4lryAnt_1sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 03:00:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/millions-of-disaster-victims-miss-out-on-humanitarian-aid/4636419.html" target="_blank"&gt;Millions of Disaster Victims Miss Out on Humanitarian Aid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Federation of Red Cross and Red Crescent Societies has issued an annual report that focuses on the millions of elderly, disabled, and vulnerable victims of natural and man-made disasters who fall through the humanitarian cracks and don't receive desperately needed aid. The United Nations reports more than 134 million people are in need of humanitarian aid and protection. In addition, many of the more than 68 million migrants on the move get caught in emergency situations and also need assistance. The International Red Cross Federation says the world is in the middle of an ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Needs of Migrants Trekking Through Balkans Growing - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/red-cross-scope-of-need-of-migrants-trekking-through-the-balkans-is-increasing/4443428.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9FD6np5-EeepAM3wHH5ukqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 11:47:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/red-cross-scope-of-need-of-migrants-trekking-through-the-balkans-is-increasing/4443428.html" target="_blank"&gt;Needs of Migrants Trekking Through Balkans Growing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Federation of Red Cross and Red Crescent Societies (IFRC) says thousands of migrants trekking through the Balkans are "in desperate need of basic humanitarian services and support." IFRC said Monday, "More than 5,600 people have reached Bosnia and Herzegovina since the beginning of January, compared with just 754 across the whole of 2017." "We are concerned that people are not receiving the assistance they need," said Simon Missiri, IFRC regional director for Europe. "People are keen to keep moving and are reluctant to access state services for fear of being detained." Mis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Red Cross Plans to Fight Disasters with Fast Funding - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/red-cross-working-toward-faster-funding/4384113.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFOPs3Ob-8jOW4tluH7ytZcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 01:50:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/red-cross-working-toward-faster-funding/4384113.html" target="_blank"&gt;Red Cross Plans to Fight Disasters with Fast Funding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fund launched by the Red Cross aims to deliver life-saving humanitarian aid before rather than after floods, droughts and other natural hazards hit, so as to reduce damage and trauma in some of the world's most disaster-prone areas. The "Forecast-based Action Fund", set up by the International Federation of Red Cross and Red Crescent Societies (IFRC), uses weather predictions and historical data to trigger the distribution of money when a natural disaster looms. The German government has committed 3.6 million Swiss francs ($3.6 million) to the new forecast-based fund. It will sit within a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Beyond Survival Kits: Humanitarian Aid Is Going Wireless, Communal, And Autonomous - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40525207/beyond-survival-kits-humanitarian-aid-is-going-wireless-communal-and-autonomous</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB202areTwFUslC7ibWHQKgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 08:30:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/40525207/beyond-survival-kits-humanitarian-aid-is-going-wireless-communal-and-autonomous" target="_blank"&gt;Beyond Survival Kits: Humanitarian Aid Is Going Wireless, Communal, And Autonomous&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;2017 set the record for costly devastation brought about by natural disasters globally. While our discussions about such events often concentrate on the pain and destruction they bring, we also see that these moments can bring about the best of humanity. In the aftermath of Hurricane Maria, for example, chef Jose Andres set up a network of kitchens that served millions of hot meals to Puerto Ricans. In Mexico, a group of 25 social organizations created a Google Crisis Map and took to social media directing updates on where help was most needed after the earthquake toppled buildings there. W...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Red Cross Says 12 More Patients Evacuated From Syrian Suburb - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/red-cross-says-twelve-more-patients-evacuated-syrian-suburb/4182705.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENjkwShelcTE46g63gf21ZoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 15:13:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/red-cross-says-twelve-more-patients-evacuated-syrian-suburb/4182705.html" target="_blank"&gt;Red Cross Says 12 More Patients Evacuated From Syrian Suburb&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A dozen more patients and their families have been evacuated from besieged rebel-held suburbs of the Syrian capital, the Red Cross said Thursday. A prominent war monitoring group meanwhile said the conflict in Syria killed another 39,000 people in 2017. That's despite the establishment of "de-escalation" zones by Russia, Turkey and Iran that have significantly reduced the fighting in much of the country. The International Committee of the Red Cross said the latest evacuations from eastern Ghouta, a suburb of Damascus, were carried out late Wednesday in coordination with the Syrian Arab Red ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>ICRC hopes to resume medical evacuations in Syria's Ghouta - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-aid/icrc-hopes-to-resume-medical-evacuations-in-syrias-ghouta-idUSKBN1EM164</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELrBYPro-oYCgGBHsCgy4rsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 13:06:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-syria-aid/icrc-hopes-to-resume-medical-evacuations-in-syrias-ghouta-idUSKBN1EM164" target="_blank"&gt;ICRC hopes to resume medical evacuations in Syria's Ghouta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIRUT (Reuters) - The International Committee of the Red Cross (ICRC) said it hoped to resume evacuations of critically ill people from Syria's biggest remaining siege on Thursday after bringing some individuals out of the area near Damascus on Wednesday. The evacuation, which started on Tuesday after a deal between Damascus and a rebel faction, involved letting some patients leave rebel-held eastern Ghouta in return for insurgents releasing detainees. International aid agencies voiced concern about the terms of the deal. U.N. humanitarian adviser Jan Egeland told the BBC: "It is a not a g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>With Crises Set to Worsen, What Are Aid Groups' Priorities for 2018? - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/aid-agencies-priorities-for-2018/4181740.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEECtcfdQkhDkJYdXeAL4PqcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 21:46:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/aid-agencies-priorities-for-2018/4181740.html" target="_blank"&gt;With Crises Set to Worsen, What Are Aid Groups' Priorities for 2018?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Violence, displacement and hunger will drive record humanitarian needs in 2018, with nearly 136 million people worldwide in need of aid, according to the United Nations. The U.N.'s Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs (OCHA) has appealed for a record $22.5 billion for humanitarian responses across the globe. Protracted conflicts in Syria, the Democratic Republic of Congo and Yemen, the Rohingya exodus from Myanmar and natural disasters exacerbated by climate change are among many crises. The Thomson Reuters Foundation asked aid agencies to name their top priorities for 2018: ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Children among first medical evacuees from besieged Syrian rebel bastion, after months of delays - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/12/27/children-among-first-medical-evacuees-besieged-syrian-rebel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE58Qke37d5TuQ5i4YdWZBAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 10:47:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/12/27/children-among-first-medical-evacuees-besieged-syrian-rebel/" target="_blank"&gt;Children among first medical evacuees from besieged Syrian rebel bastion, after months of delays&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bashar al-Assad’s government has allowed a handful of some of the hundreds of desperate patients in a besieged area of Damascus out for treatment, after months of delays which left more than a dozen dead. Aid workers began evacuating emergency medical cases from Syria's rebel bastion of Eastern Ghouta on Tuesday night. So far 29 women and children suffering from heart disease, cancer, kidney failure and blood diseases or requiring surgery not available in the suburb, have been granted permission to leave. The first four were a girl with haemophilia, a baby with the autoimmune disorder Guill...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Critically ill Syrians evacuated from Eastern Ghouta - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/12/critically-ill-syrians-evacuated-eastern-ghouta-171228114407151.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ19CUBRUdqvgCjQmkTx7HwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 21:10:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/12/critically-ill-syrians-evacuated-eastern-ghouta-171228114407151.html" target="_blank"&gt;Critically ill Syrians evacuated from Eastern Ghouta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 12 critically ill patients have been evacuated from a suburb of Syria's capital Damascus, while more residents in need of urgent medical care are expected to be removed from the besieged area, according to humanitarian groups. The evacuees, a majority of whom were children, were taken to Damascus to receive medical treatment, according to the Syria branch of the International Committee of the Red Cross (ICRC). Aid agencies have been evacuating critically ill Syrians from Eastern Ghouta, an area home to about 400,000 people that has been under a government-imposed siege since 2013, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Francesco Rocca: No one can prepare for nuclear war - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/12/francesco-rocca-prepare-nuclear-war-171205132112294.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF0xENqCDZ5zuD_fbkHW5qAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 06:39:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/12/francesco-rocca-prepare-nuclear-war-171205132112294.html" target="_blank"&gt;Francesco Rocca: No one can prepare for nuclear war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The incoming president of the International Federation of Red Cross and Red Crescent Societies (IFRC) has expressed hope that dialogue will prevail in escalating tensions between North Korea and the West, saying that nothing could prepare the world for nuclear war. "There is no training, no preparation that could cope with a disaster where we could assist if this weapon would be used," Francesco Rocca told Al Jazeera. "This is something I don't even want to think about ... I hope love for humanity will prevail." Rocca was elected as the new head of the IFRC by his peers from 178 National Re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Iran-Iraq quake: 'A sudden wave of death' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/11/iran-iraq-quake-sudden-wave-death-171113135714789.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM_Wfj651tpRzIRVPxzDT3IqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 05:32:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/11/iran-iraq-quake-sudden-wave-death-171113135714789.html" target="_blank"&gt;Iran-Iraq quake: 'A sudden wave of death'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rescue workers in western Iran struggled to find survivors in a frantic search for those trapped under the rubble after a powerful earthquake struck the Iraq-Iran border region. More than 400 people have been killed in Iran and Iraq and 7,000 injured when the earthquake of magnitude 7.3 hit both countries late on Sunday causing the most damage in Kermanshah province, a rural mountainous region in Iran. The Red Crescent Society of the Islamic Republic of Iran deployed staff and volunteers to assist in rescue-and-relief operations, but they said "chances of survival are slim" for those buried...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>After International Red Cross admits $6 million in Ebola aid stolen: How to vet charities - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/5-ways-to-make-sure-your-hurricane-harvey-donation-does-the-most-good-2017-09-01</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBR17z0jPwRUs6L87ARGuTMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwuJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 16:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/5-ways-to-make-sure-your-hurricane-harvey-donation-does-the-most-good-2017-09-01" target="_blank"&gt;After International Red Cross admits $6 million in Ebola aid stolen: How to vet charities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Kari Paul Be cautious about where to donate in wake of a tragedy A woman carries bottles of water and food during a distribution of relief items, after the area was hit by Hurricane Maria in San Juan, Puerto Rico September 24, 2017. Reuters An estimated $6 million in donations to the International Federation of Red Cross and Red Crescent Societies (IFRC) meant to help the Ebola outbreak in West Africa from 2014 to 2016 disappeared due to corruption, the charity confirmed Saturday. The news of the lost funds comes from an internal investigation by the International Federation of Red Cross...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>ICRC: Safety of aid workers a daily dilemma - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/11/icrc-safety-aid-workers-daily-dilemma-171107123404846.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMpGNhhVEpio69CUoOWk0bUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 14:30:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/11/icrc-safety-aid-workers-daily-dilemma-171107123404846.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICRC: Safety of aid workers a daily dilemma&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Turkish city of Antalya, delegates from 190 countries gathered to discuss safety concerns and challenges faced by humanitarian workers and volunteers in the field. The General Assembly of International Federation of Red Cross and Red Crescent Societies (IFRC) began on November 6. The evolving nature of conflict and disaster zones, access to affected people, and funding were also deliberated. But the long standing question of whether humanitarian aid is helping to prolong conflicts such as those in Syria, Yemen and elsewhere, remains. Al Jazeera spoke with Peter Maurer, president of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Red Cross Federation Chief Vows Corruption Crackdown - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/red-cross-federation-chief-vows-corruption-crackdown/4105329.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9q6rtwg0x554bOQhpmNNEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:22:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/red-cross-federation-chief-vows-corruption-crackdown/4105329.html" target="_blank"&gt;Red Cross Federation Chief Vows Corruption Crackdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new president of the world's largest humanitarian network, the International Federation of Red Cross and Red Crescent Societies (IFRC), promised on Tuesday to crack down on corruption after a scandal over Ebola funds in West Africa. Francesco Rocca, who headed the Italian Red Cross and oversaw its role in the Mediterranean refugee crisis, was elected on Monday to lead the IFRC. He said the organization should have "zero tolerance for any grey area or black hole" and its 190 national societies should adopt "very strict" policies. "What has happened could jeopardize our credibility," Rocc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Plague death toll close to 100 in Madagascar as stigma curbs containment efforts - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-10-22/red-cross-warns-stigma-could-worsen-madagascar-plague-outbreak/9073586</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFy6oeb26tIRujVrUqBqU6AqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 19:30:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-10-22/red-cross-warns-stigma-could-worsen-madagascar-plague-outbreak/9073586" target="_blank"&gt;Plague death toll close to 100 in Madagascar as stigma curbs containment efforts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The death toll from the plague which is spreading in Madagascar has risen close to 100, and the Red Cross has warned that growing stigma attached to the disease could undermine efforts to contain the outbreak. Key points: - The plague is common in Madagascar but this year's epidemic is worst this century - This outbreak is transferred in pneumonic form, as well as bubonic, making it more dangerous - It has also spread to urban centres and areas not previously affected While cases of bubonic plague occur in Madagascar nearly every year, this year's epidemic is "much more dangerous", secretar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Kurdish Red Crescent: IS Attacks Kill at Least 50 in East Syria - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kurdish-red-crescent-islamic-state-attacks-kill-fifty-east-syria/4068166.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGVawd7SFc7zQ2tfcf79MeEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 23:44:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kurdish-red-crescent-islamic-state-attacks-kill-fifty-east-syria/4068166.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kurdish Red Crescent: IS Attacks Kill at Least 50 in East Syria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamic State suicide attackers killed at least 50 people in a triple car bomb attack on Thursday among a group of refugees in northeast Syria, a medical source in the Kurdish Red Crescent said. A large number of people were also injured by the three car bombs, the source said. The attack took place at Abu Fas, near the border of Deir el-Zour and Hasaka provinces, said a war monitor, the Britain-based Syrian Observatory for Human Rights, which said earlier that at least 18 people had been killed. The dead included refugees fleeing the fighting in Deir el-Zour as well as members of the Kurdi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>