<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>The Boring Company - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZrZUdJeVluaDVZeElDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:52:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>The first use of a hyperloop will be incredibly boring - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90277130/the-first-use-of-a-hyperloop-will-be-incredibly-boring</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJJlrFuPxZnxeKuNyG_Jh4cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:00:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90277130/the-first-use-of-a-hyperloop-will-be-incredibly-boring" target="_blank"&gt;The first use of a hyperloop will be incredibly boring&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hyperloop Transportation Technologies, which has received far less fanfare then its similarly named competitor Virgin Hyperloop (née Hyperloop One), today announced a joint venture with a German logistics and transportation company that runs container terminals. Together the two companies will bring HTT’s technology to the Port of Hamburg. Which is to say, the first real use of a hyperloop will be to move freight around a shipyard. Not terribly sexy! Of course, this was always going to be the first use case for this still largely untested transportation method. While many hyperloop hopefuls...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk drops plans for west LA tunnel, instead focuses on Dodger fans - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/elon-musk-drops-out-of-la-tunnel-to-build-another/10570208</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJh_PnCBm-NmGkyJmtRKSQUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:40:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/elon-musk-drops-out-of-la-tunnel-to-build-another/10570208" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk drops plans for west LA tunnel, instead focuses on Dodger fans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk has scrapped plans for a high-speed passenger tunnel under the West side of Los Angeles but is moving ahead with a similar proposal across town designed to whisk baseball fans to and from Dodger Stadium in Chicago. Mr Musk's underground transit venture, the Boring Company, gave up on its development of a 4.4-kilometre tunnel in West LA to settle litigation brought by community groups opposed to the project, the two sides said in a joint statement. The move came six months after Mr Musk, the high-tech baron better known as founder of electric car company Te...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk scraps plans for Los Angeles tunnel after lawsuit settlement - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/28/elon-musk-underground-tunnel-los-angeles-lawsuit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3oUltpuDM-iyyo1JQbufQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 01:01:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/28/elon-musk-underground-tunnel-los-angeles-lawsuit" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk scraps plans for Los Angeles tunnel after lawsuit settlement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk has scrapped his plans to dig through an affluent section of west Los Angeles after his tunneling company reached a settlement in an environmental review lawsuit. The Boring Company “is no longer seeking the development of the Sepulveda test tunnel and instead seeks to construct an operational tunnel at Dodger Stadium”, the firm announced in a statement to NBC News on Tuesday. The tunnels are Musk’s solution to “soul-destroying traffic”, a way to make roads “go 3D”, according to the company’s website. Work began last year on a test tunnel in Hawthorne, California, across the stree...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk Pulls Plug on Boring Company Tunnel Project in Los Angeles - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/elon-musk-pulls-plug-on-boring-company-tunnel-project-in-los-angeles</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELgJTPg0mM6-WFa8cxjIzL8qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 07:13:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/elon-musk-pulls-plug-on-boring-company-tunnel-project-in-los-angeles" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk Pulls Plug on Boring Company Tunnel Project in Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kyle Grillot/Reuters, Elon Musk’s plan to build a high-tech tunnel in Los Angeles has reportedly gone belly up. Musk’s Boring Company announced Tuesday that it has nixed a project to construct a subterranean passageway below the 405 freeway along L.A.’s Westside. The decision came after several community groups sued the city over its move to exempt the project from an environmental review process, resulting in a settlement. "The parties (The Boring Company, Brentwood Residents Coalition, Sunset Coalition, and Wendy-Sue Rosen) have amicably settled the matter of Brentwood Residents Coalition...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Billionaires Love Energy Storage But Can Energy Storage Make Its Own Billionaire - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnparnell/2018/11/30/billionaires-love-energy-storage-but-can-energy-storage-make-its-own-billionaire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKNO_3WcG6nG3hSXXXEw7gMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnparnell/2018/11/30/billionaires-love-energy-storage-but-can-energy-storage-make-its-own-billionaire/" target="_blank"&gt;Billionaires Love Energy Storage But Can Energy Storage Make Its Own Billionaire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year, yet another billionaire took a big bet on energy storage – twice. First, Patrick Soon-Shiong’s company NantEnergy bought zinc-air battery manufacturer Fluidic and earlier this month, he added in Sharp’s SmartStorage division in the US. Soon-Shiong is treading a well-worn path. Wang Chuanfu, the head of Chinese firm BYD, has seen his company become a major electric vehicle and stationary energy storage manufacturer. Elon Musk, of course, segued Tesla into stationary storage as well. And one of the solar industry’s self-made billionaires, Jifan Gao, has also moved into energy stora...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk: Workers should put in 100 hours a week to change the world - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/27/elon-musk-workers-should-put-80-hours-week-change-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENE5OFl2JBa2l69s1MgyZg8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:54:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/27/elon-musk-workers-should-put-80-hours-week-change-world/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk: Workers should put in 100 hours a week to change the world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla and SpaceX workers should put in 80 to 100 hours a week to "change the world", Elon Musk has said. The technology entrepreneur admitted that there were "way easier places to work" than his companies, adding: "Nobody ever changed the world on 40 hours a week." Asked how many hours a week were necessary, Mr Musk said: "Varies per person, but about 80 sustained, peaking above 100 at times. Pain level increases exponentially above 80." Mr Musk's comments attracted criticism from commentators who suggested that overwork could lead to decreased productivity. He is the founder and chief exec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Robo-taxis or high-tech tunnels? The race for traffic utopia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/f8177bb6-ecaf-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJT1Y0pxhu1TBzxXDk8-YFkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 05:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f8177bb6-ecaf-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Robo-taxis or high-tech tunnels? The race for traffic utopia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On my first day as a reporter in Silicon Valley, I witnessed what I thought was the greatest product unveiling I had ever seen. It was a sunny morning, late June 2012. From an airship hovering over downtown San Francisco, a team of stuntmen wearing Google Glass headsets started to leap out into the Californian sky. Inside the Moscone Center, where Google’s annual developer conference was being held, we in the audience watched in awe as they plunged to Earth, the Glass cameras beaming a live video feed of their descent. After landing on the roof and abseiling to the ground, the stuntmen then...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tubular: A Hyperloop Contest As Musk Inches Toward Creating High-Speed Venture - Forbes Now</title><link>//www.forbes.com/sites/alanohnsman/2017/08/27/tubular-a-hyperloop-contest-as-musk-inches-toward-creating-high-speed-venture/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIox_I1F_ZpjILbtl4g9RBAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 02:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="//www.forbes.com/sites/alanohnsman/2017/08/27/tubular-a-hyperloop-contest-as-musk-inches-toward-creating-high-speed-venture/" target="_blank"&gt;Tubular: A Hyperloop Contest As Musk Inches Toward Creating High-Speed Venture&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk addresses the audience gathered at SpaceX for the second Hyperloop Pod Competition in Hawthorne, California. Days after Elon Musk’s Boring Co. won approval to build a two-mile test tunnel under his rocket factory and a month after hinting at approval for an East Coast Hyperloop line, the billionaire tech industrialist hosted an engineering competition to design the futuristic tube train that’s looking increasingly like his next business venture. SpaceX, Musk’s rocket company in suburban Los Angeles, held its second Hyperloop Pod Competition on Sunday, drawing more than 600 enginee...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>From New York to DC in 29 minutes: Musk touts hyperloop - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-07-21/elon-musk-touts-approval-of-new-york-to-washington-dc-hyperloop/8730520</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ7dBTu-ZNJViam4NS7wz2QqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 23:59:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-07-21/elon-musk-touts-approval-of-new-york-to-washington-dc-hyperloop/8730520" target="_blank"&gt;From New York to DC in 29 minutes: Musk touts hyperloop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tech entrepreneur Elon Musk has said he has received "verbal" approval to start building an ultra-high-speed underground transport system linking New York and Washington DC, which would cut travel time between the cities to about half an hour. Key points: - Current high-speed train takes three hours to go from NYC to DC - Mr Musk mentions Los Angeles, Texas and Chicago in high-speed tunnel tweets - NYC mayor's press secretary says any approval is "news to City Hall" He offered no details on what entity had greenlit the project that could result in the world's longest tunnel. Amtrak's high-s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>How Elon Musk and shorter commutes could transform people’s lives - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-elon-musk-and-shorter-commutes-could-transform-peoples-lives-2017-07-20</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBp3pdelgclqMY8z-XZ4fnAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 03:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-elon-musk-and-shorter-commutes-could-transform-peoples-lives-2017-07-20" target="_blank"&gt;How Elon Musk and shorter commutes could transform people’s lives&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Maria LaMagna Musk’s latest project could even be good for commuters’ happiness and health Elon Musk tweeted about a new “hyperloop” project on Thursday. Heiko Junge/Getty Images Elon Musk’s latest project may not just be good for your schedule. It could also be good for your health. Musk, the chief executive of Tesla Inc. (TSLA) and founder of SpaceX tweeted Thursday that his business known as “Boring Co.” had received verbal government approval to build a “hyperloop” train, that would run underground through tunnels, essentially like a subway on steroids. Musk said it would make stop...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Catching the Hyperloop will be faster than the subway, its engineers say - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40450764/catching-the-hyperloop-will-be-faster-than-the-subway-its-engineers-say</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKdesV3eTS9lvIAk0ueXYwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 19:40:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/40450764/catching-the-hyperloop-will-be-faster-than-the-subway-its-engineers-say" target="_blank"&gt;Catching the Hyperloop will be faster than the subway, its engineers say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Hyperloop will allow us to move further away from the center of cities as commuting times get faster, they say. It will support subways, buses, and light rails! It will reduce congestion! It will be as affordable as a Greyhound! You’ll even be able to catch a ride more quickly than you would the subway (especially, one figures, the New York City subway). “We have plenty of mini-platforms within each station to make sure everyone can can comfortably board and exit their pod,” the team building the high-speed vacuum tube transit system at Hyperloop One, wrote in an Ask Me Anything questio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk: Boring Company commits to 600mph Hyperloop and tube network - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/aug/09/elon-musk-boring-company-commits-building-600mph-hyperloop-tunnel-network</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELTJMuTfiB-8-d6YxFcWzskqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 11:19:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/aug/09/elon-musk-boring-company-commits-building-600mph-hyperloop-tunnel-network" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk: Boring Company commits to 600mph Hyperloop and tube network&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk’s Boring Company has recommitted to building a network of high-speed transport tunnels, including a Hyperloop vacuum-tube supersonic transport system between New York and Washington DC, which it claims will whisk people from A to B at 600mph in a vacuum tube. Having originally spawned the idea, releasing plans for the cross between a “Concorde and a railgun and an air hockey table” in a 57-page document free for others to verify and build on, Musk announced his intentions in July saying he had verbal approval from the government to build a New York to DC Hyperloop. Officials from ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>An LA suburb is letting Elon Musk’s Boring Company build a two-mile tunnel under it - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40461281/an-la-suburb-is-letting-elon-musks-boring-company-build-a-two-mile-tunnel-under-it</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHGn4pTp696L_OgzOJ0l3nkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 06:01:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/40461281/an-la-suburb-is-letting-elon-musks-boring-company-build-a-two-mile-tunnel-under-it" target="_blank"&gt;An LA suburb is letting Elon Musk’s Boring Company build a two-mile tunnel under it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Los Angeles suburb of Hawthorne, CA has given Musk the permission for the two-mile, and up to 44-feet deep, tunnel, reports ConstructionDrive. Plans reveal the tunnel will start from underneath one of SpaceX’s parking areas, where the company currently has a 160-foot tunnel already. But the Boring Company doesn’t have all the permission it needs yet to actually start building the miles-long tunnel. It still needs to get permission from the California state labor and transportation departments and there’s no telling how long that will take.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Amid His Most Important Tesla Milestone, Elon Musk Says He May Be Bipolar - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/alanohnsman/2017/07/31/amid-his-most-important-tesla-milestone-elon-musk-says-he-may-be-bipolar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAyiSXIwkW6vMmuLyzi3K-EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 20:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/alanohnsman/2017/07/31/amid-his-most-important-tesla-milestone-elon-musk-says-he-may-be-bipolar/" target="_blank"&gt;Amid His Most Important Tesla Milestone, Elon Musk Says He May Be Bipolar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk discusses his vision for traveling to Mars at the International Astronautical Congress in Guadalajara, Mexico, in September 2016. Elon Musk, much like President Donald Trump, is unusually comfortable sharing views and personal information on Twitter. The guiding force behind Tesla, SpaceX, The Boring Company and Neuralink, a company creating devices to connect human brains and computers, was particularly candid on Sunday when revealing that he may suffer from bipolar disorder. The billionaire tech industrialist seemed a bit downbeat in a media briefing ahead of the handover of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>This is what a Tesla looks like in a Hyperloop tunnel - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40459378/this-is-what-a-tesla-looks-like-in-a-hyperloop-tunnel</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAg00kXIirlwAOrRfQqQLfUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 05:35:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/40459378/this-is-what-a-tesla-looks-like-in-a-hyperloop-tunnel" target="_blank"&gt;This is what a Tesla looks like in a Hyperloop tunnel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk posted this photo showing a Model S in the L.A. tunnel his The Boring Company is digging. Right now the tunnel doesn’t perform any of the functions of a Hyperloop (it’s literally just a tunnel at the moment), but the image gives you a good idea of the scale of things once cars are actually inside. Looks pretty snug. A Model S in The Boring Company tunnel being dug under Los Angeles (starting in Hawthorne) A post shared by Elon Musk (@elonmusk) on Aug 27, 2017 at 6:57pm PDT&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Jeff Bezos’s first Instagram post: ‘ROCKET FACTORY COMING SOON’ - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/jeff-bezoss-first-instagram-post-rocket-factory-coming-soon-2017-07-21</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECWhnp8ioJpss1ZIjB_a0ukqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 16:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/jeff-bezoss-first-instagram-post-rocket-factory-coming-soon-2017-07-21" target="_blank"&gt;Jeff Bezos’s first Instagram post: ‘ROCKET FACTORY COMING SOON’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Sally French The Amazon CEO’s first Instagram shows Blue Origin’s New Glenn rocket production facility Getty Images Amazon (AMZN) CEO Jeff Bezos seems to be taking a page from the social media handbook of Elon Musk. On Thursday, Bezos put up his first Instagram post: a drone video that shows Blue Origin’s New Glenn rocket production facility in Cape Canaveral, Florida. It begins with an aerial view, then pans in toward the building, ending with a photo of Bezos sitting on the roof holding a sign that says “ROCKET FACTORY COMING SOON.” See instagram embed Blue Origin is an aerospace manu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk's Boring Company releases slick video - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2017/04/28/elon-musk-boring-company-releases-video.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENPslfzfjeGdNtxxzEY26hwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 02:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2017/04/28/elon-musk-boring-company-releases-video.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk's Boring Company releases slick video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk's The Boring Company has released a computer-generated video showing a network of underground tunnels for cars. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Is Elon Musk's plan for a road network beneath LA more than a pipe dream? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2017/sep/04/elon-musk-hyperloop-boring-underground-la-traffic</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHYrC0_86GUvM4TGiXkzcbkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 09:13:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2017/sep/04/elon-musk-hyperloop-boring-underground-la-traffic" target="_blank"&gt;Is Elon Musk's plan for a road network beneath LA more than a pipe dream?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In early August, the city council of Hawthorne, California, held a special meeting. It had set aside this time to discuss a major construction project proposed by a high profile company based there in the sprawling Los Angeles basin. The company was Space Exploration Technologies Corporation, or SpaceX, the rocket-building offshoot of the electric car company Tesla, run by the billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk. SpaceX had recently spun off another entity, this one aimed at disrupting the tunnel boring business, cheekily named the Boring Company – and it needed the City of Hawthorne’s coope...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>It’s Not All Hyperloops: Elon Musk Wants To Dig Your City’s Next Sewer - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alanohnsman/2018/11/09/its-not-all-hyploops-elon-musks-boring-co-wants-to-dig-your-citys-next-sewer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFfIHQ9WqAlEn24L-xbIsIMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alanohnsman/2018/11/09/its-not-all-hyploops-elon-musks-boring-co-wants-to-dig-your-citys-next-sewer/" target="_blank"&gt;It’s Not All Hyperloops: Elon Musk Wants To Dig Your City’s Next Sewer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=0] Elon Musk’s big ideas usually involve revolutions in clean power, electric cars, Mars colonies and high-speed tube travel, but the billionaire entrepreneur wants U.S. cities to know that when it comes to the Boring Company he has a practical side too. In fact, his new tunnel-oriented endeavor will do a lot more than just make vacuum-tube Hyperloops — it’ll build your new sewer lines. Musk made his pitch before an audience of 3,800 mayors and city officials from across the U.S. in Los Angeles at the National League of Cities’ 2018 City Summit on Thursday in a chat with L.A. Mayor Eric...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Tesla FireX? Musk ridiculed online for offering to help with California wildfires - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/443625-musk-california-help-backlash/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKt-Y_cC3amTE-79mISY9t0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 13:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/443625-musk-california-help-backlash/" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla FireX? Musk ridiculed online for offering to help with California wildfires&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twitter users have come up with names and even blueprints for something to “help” tackle the raging California wildfires after Elon Musk invited the public to ask Tesla for assistance. Enormous fires visible even from space have gripped the state of California in recent days, forcing tens of thousands to flee. The disaster has already resulted in at least nine fatalities. The incident did not escape Musk’s attention, and the billionaire offered to have his company help by transporting people in California or assisting in any other way. If Tesla can help people in California wildfire, please...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk shows off Boring Co.’s ‘disturbingly long’ tunnel under Los Angeles - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musk-shows-off-boring-cos-disturbingly-long-tunnel-under-los-angeles-2018-11-04</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMj_oZfoLF5DpyhIgkEdBhgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 12:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musk-shows-off-boring-cos-disturbingly-long-tunnel-under-los-angeles-2018-11-04" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk shows off Boring Co.’s ‘disturbingly long’ tunnel under Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Mike Murphy Test tunnel to be unveiled to public next month A section of the Boring Co.'s test tunnel in Hawthorne, Calif. The Boring Co. Elon Musk has given a sneak peek of his Boring Co.’s “disturbingly long” new tunnel under Los Angeles. In a tweet early Saturday morning, Musk said he “Walked full length of Boring Co tunnel under LA tonight. Disturbingly long. On track for opening party Dec 10,” and posted video of the tunnel. See tweet embed The first section of the test tunnel, which runs two miles starting from the company’s headquarters in Hawthorne, Calif., will be unveiled next ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>See Elon Musk's tunnel under Los Angeles - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/11/05/elon-musk-tunnel-underground-orig.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVYBtsePws8dWM3vyC6KooqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 19:25:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/11/05/elon-musk-tunnel-underground-orig.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;See Elon Musk's tunnel under Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk tweeted a video of his Boring Company's 2-mile tunnel underneath Los Angeles. It's part of his plan to combat traffic with high-speed, underground public transportation. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Breaking: Virgin Hyperloop One names former MTA head Jay Walder as CEO - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90264850/virgin-hyperloop-one-names-former-mta-head-jay-walder-as-ceo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMehUCQvtb5LOvOwBEQyDocqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 14:00:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90264850/virgin-hyperloop-one-names-former-mta-head-jay-walder-as-ceo" target="_blank"&gt;Breaking: Virgin Hyperloop One names former MTA head Jay Walder as CEO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As tech companies like Elon Musk’s Boring Company and Hyperloop Transportation Technologies race to roll out the first fully operational hyperloop systems, Virgin Hyperloop One is trying to cement its image as a transportation company first and foremost. Today, Virgin Hyperloop One announced Jay Walder as its new CEO. Walder most recently served as the CEO of Motivate, but previously headed up of some of the world’s largest transportation systems, including the MTA in New York City and MTR in Hong Kong. Ahmed bin Sulayem, CEO of the massive port operator DP world, will become the new chairm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Report: Elon Musk fired a bunch of SpaceX execs in Starlink shakeup - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90259755/report-elon-musk-fired-a-bunch-of-spacex-execs-in-starlink-shakeup</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIhT7Wrv34otSnk1t5m196kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:35:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90259755/report-elon-musk-fired-a-bunch-of-spacex-execs-in-starlink-shakeup" target="_blank"&gt;Report: Elon Musk fired a bunch of SpaceX execs in Starlink shakeup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between Tesla, SpaceX, the Boring Company, tweeting, and appearing on podcasts, Elon Musk apparently doesn’t have enough on his plate. In June, he reportedly flew to Redmond, Washington, and fired a whole bunch of engineers working on SpaceX’s Starlink program in order to get the satellites into space by the middle of next year, according to Reuters. If in the current news cycle you have forgotten where Starlink fits into Musk’s expansive dossier, it’s the satellite internet company meant to compete with companies like OneWeb and Canada’s Telesat. While companies like HughesNet have offered...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Is Elon Musk on the way up or down? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-30/is-elon-musk-on-the-way-up-or-down/10447036</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDfgoyw4RxUWBlwNoqCNN0QqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 10:01:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-30/is-elon-musk-on-the-way-up-or-down/10447036" target="_blank"&gt;Is Elon Musk on the way up or down?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Puffing on a joint is all anyone really remembers about Elon Musk's chat with US comedian Joe Rogan on his popular live-streamed podcast last month. But this line from Silicon Valley's $30 billion man was arguably the more compelling revelation: "I don't think you'd necessarily want to be me … I don't think people would like it that much." That extraordinary admission from one of the most feted innovators of our time was given more context when Rogan asked about Mr Musk's feverish creative drive. "It's very hard to turn it off," Mr Musk said. "It might sound great if it's turned on, but wha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk wants to make supersonic vertical-takeoff electric jet but says his 'head would explode' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/elon-musk-spacex-tesla-electric-jet-head-explode-twitter-boring-company-a8615836.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcIrKXN5Ki2EWo_r03zF94qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 12:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/elon-musk-spacex-tesla-electric-jet-head-explode-twitter-boring-company-a8615836.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk wants to make supersonic vertical-takeoff electric jet but says his 'head would explode'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk has said he wants Tesla to make a supersonic vertical-takeoff-and-landing electric jet, but that his head “would definitely explode” if he were to commit to the project. In an interview with Recode, the Tesla founder revealed he had been thinking about the design for what he called the “VTOL jet” for nearly a decade. Mr Musk’s discussion of the plane comes two years after he told an audience he was “tempted” to build an electric jet that would revolutionise the air transport industry by cutting costs and potentially ditching the need for huge runways. Read more - Elon Musk says tw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk says first tunnel is almost done, opens December 10: tweet - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-boring-musk-tweet/elon-musk-says-first-tunnel-is-almost-done-opens-december-10-tweet-idUSKCN1MW024</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYrv2Pn__l8DaSTGQtooLMqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 03:37:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-boring-musk-tweet/elon-musk-says-first-tunnel-is-almost-done-opens-december-10-tweet-idUSKCN1MW024" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk says first tunnel is almost done, opens December 10: tweet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A company owned by Elon Musk that is trying to lower the cost of building high-speed transit tunnels is nearing completion on the first tunnel, Musk said on Twitter on Sunday. The first tunnel, under Hawthorne in the Los Angeles area, is almost done and will open on Dec. 10, Musk said. Privately held Boring Co has been promoting its plans for tunnels that would allow high-speed travel between cities. (Reporting by Jessica Resnick-Ault; Editing by Sandra Maler)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s tunnel system that will put cars on 150mph ‘skates’ to open in December - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/22/elon-musks-la-tunnel-will-transport-people-150mph-skates-open/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJBThpc5cn9r93l2uSP6Pg4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 09:33:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/22/elon-musks-la-tunnel-will-transport-people-150mph-skates-open/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk’s tunnel system that will put cars on 150mph ‘skates’ to open in December&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk has come a step closer to creating a "loop" transit system beneath Los Angeles to bring an end to "soul-destroying traffic" in the city. Taking to Twitter, the billionaire SpaceX founder said his underground tunnel for the project "is almost done" and will be ready on December 10. In a follow-up tweet, a fan asked whether the December 10 opening was "in real time or Elon time?" and Musk replied "I think real." The tunnel, which is being built by Musk's Boring Company, will contain autonomous electric skates capable of transporting cars and people at speeds of up to 125-150mph. "T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk sets a date for underground test track - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/22/tech/musk-hyperloop-test-tunnel/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGqHsNd7N8FaNQBwp0VHTjMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 18:28:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/22/tech/musk-hyperloop-test-tunnel/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk sets a date for underground test track&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk's underground transport system could be a reality as early as December. Two miles of test track, at least. Musksaid on Twitter Sunday that the tunnel being dug to test the Loop, his traffic beating vehicle transport idea, will be complete on December 10. Once it's ready, Musk is throwing a party. He announced an opening event that night and free rides for the public starting the next day. The tech entrepreneur has been touting the benefits of tube transport for a number of years. In 2016 he launched The Boring Company to dig tunnels under Los Angeles, with the intention of install...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>U.S. judge approves SEC settlement with Tesla, Musk; shares jump - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-tesla-musk-sec/us-judge-approves-sec-settlement-with-tesla-shares-jump-idUSKCN1MQ20R</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFZSrTzR82l8b8qGwQhLrFYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 19:35:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-tesla-musk-sec/us-judge-approves-sec-settlement-with-tesla-shares-jump-idUSKCN1MQ20R" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. judge approves SEC settlement with Tesla, Musk; shares jump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A U.S. judge on Tuesday approved a settlement between a federal regulator, Tesla Inc and its chief executive officer, Elon Musk, over his tweets promising to take the company private, signaling an end to a tumultuous period for investors. Tesla shares rose as much as 5.5 percent to $273.88 before easing to $271.63 in early-afternoon trade on Nasdaq. Despite the gains, the stock is still down more than 20 percent since Aug. 6, the day before Musk said on Twitter he would take the company private and claimed he had secured funding to do so. Judge Alison Nathan of the U.S. District Court for t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tequila, flamethrowers and baseball caps: Elon Musk’s strange brand tie-ins - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/441171-musk-teslaquila-weird-products/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFi9XIWU9YkuSnCZF3VzhWgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 14:18:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/441171-musk-teslaquila-weird-products/" target="_blank"&gt;Tequila, flamethrowers and baseball caps: Elon Musk’s strange brand tie-ins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla founder Elon Musk has trademarked a new tequila named after his famed electric cars. Teslaquila is the latest product-linked idea dreamt up by the Space X mastermind that’s a bit off-brand. Teslaquila Reports emerged Friday that Tesla registered a new trademark with the Patent and Trademark Office for ‘Teslaquila’. Musk appeared to confirm the reports, tweeting, “Teslaquila coming soon…” and sharing a “visual approximation“ of what the new drink’s label could look like. Visual approximation pic.twitter.com/sMn3Pv476Y — Elon Musk (@elonmusk) October 12, 2018 The electric car creator fi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Weed, whiskey, Tesla and a flamethrower: Elon Musk meets Joe Rogan - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/01/tech/elon-musk-joe-rogan/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP9ukho4l8bjHhKL20IwjL4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 23:47:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/01/tech/elon-musk-joe-rogan/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Weed, whiskey, Tesla and a flamethrower: Elon Musk meets Joe Rogan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story originally published on September 7, 2018. There was whiskey, a joint, a Samurai sword and long conversations about artificial intelligence and the end of the universe. Just another installment in the extraordinary saga of Elon Musk, the billionaire leader of two major companies that are trying to change the world. The CEO of electric-car maker Tesla (TSLA) and rocket startup SpaceX spent more than two-and-a-half hours Thursday night talking to podcast host Joe Rogan about what it's like inside his head ("a never-ending explosion"), keeping a car company in business ("very diffic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Tesla shares jump on Model 3 numbers, Musk deal - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-musk-stocks/tesla-shares-jump-on-model-3-numbers-musk-deal-idUSKCN1MB2HW?il=0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFaGMpaAnNllnZxLrexrQJMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 21:54:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-musk-stocks/tesla-shares-jump-on-model-3-numbers-musk-deal-idUSKCN1MB2HW?il=0" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla shares jump on Model 3 numbers, Musk deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares of Tesla Inc (TSLA.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) jumped by almost 18 percent on Monday as Chief Executive Elon Musk settled a lawsuit that had threatened to force him out and said a surge in third-quarter production had driven it to the verge of profitability. Tesla fans cheered the signs of a manufacturing jump while business analysts said the company needed to fulfill the spirit of the settlement by appointing a strong independent chair and new directors. The electric carmaker's shares sank last week after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission accused Musk of secur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Thanks, SEC--Musk's Twitter Feed Has Already Gone Silent - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/lianeyvkoff/2018/09/30/thanks-sec-musks-twitter-feed-has-already-gone-silent/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKFTFBF7z2NpwkPNFdk-L84qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 20:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/lianeyvkoff/2018/09/30/thanks-sec-musks-twitter-feed-has-already-gone-silent/" target="_blank"&gt;Thanks, SEC--Musk's Twitter Feed Has Already Gone Silent&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk, chief executive officer for Space Exploration Technologies Corp. (SpaceX), speaks during an event at the SpaceX headquarters in Hawthorne, California, U.S., on Monday, Sept. 17, 2018. Photographer: Patrick T. Fallon/Bloomberg Elon Musk has been fined $20 million for trying to impress his girlfriend with errant tweets, but let’s face it–we are all paying the price. In addition to forcing Musk to step down from his chairman role of Tesla, the SEC is mandating the company add two independent board members and establish new communications protocols that oversee his communications. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk Sued For Defamation By Thai Cave Rescuer - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/legalentertainment/2018/09/17/elon-musk-sued-for-defamation-by-thai-cave-rescuer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYq9UYoAa7PVohOLClJgn4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/legalentertainment/2018/09/17/elon-musk-sued-for-defamation-by-thai-cave-rescuer/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk Sued For Defamation By Thai Cave Rescuer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FILE – Tesla CEO and founder of the Boring Company Elon Musk speaks at a news conference, in Chicago. (AP Photo/Kiichiro Sato, File) “I hope he f****ing sues me,” Tesla CEO Elon Musk said last month in an email exchange over his public feud with one of the divers involved in the Thai cave rescue. Now, it appears as though Musk has gotten his wish. It was reported Monday that British cave diver Vernon Unsworth, who helped rescue 12 Thai boys and their soccer coach from a flooded cave in July, has filed a defamation suit against Musk after the tech billionaire repeatedly accused him of being ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Calling all suburban Bond villains - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/7bb65d91-3811-3902-9814-310cf585ebd6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOV1GGdHYCwk8hMMuSjl7CcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 04:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/7bb65d91-3811-3902-9814-310cf585ebd6" target="_blank"&gt;Calling all suburban Bond villains&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the HR departments of Silicon Valley which like to test candidates by having them estimate numbers such as today's population of piano tuners travelling by jumbo jet, we'd like to suggest a new question: how many tech mega-millionaires don't like to be seen in public and have Bond-villain inclinations? We'd like to know, because that is the market opportunity for the latest “prototype” from Elon Musk's Boring Company, as reported by the Beach Reporter: Elon Musk’s Boring Company won approval from the Hawthorne City Council on Tuesday night for a prototype of a revolutionary new garage t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk makes unfounded accusation against Thai cave rescuer - CNN</title><link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/07/15/technology/elon-musk-thai-cave-rescue/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENPjRkn9SxFBffjkA8kQ84MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:12:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://money.cnn.com/2018/07/15/technology/elon-musk-thai-cave-rescue/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk makes unfounded accusation against Thai cave rescuer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Billionaire tech entrepreneur Elon Musk, the CEO of several high-profile American companies, broadcast to his 22 million social media followers on Sunday an unfounded and disparaging claim about an expert caver who criticized a miniature submarine he made. Musk attacked Vernon Unsworth, who helped in the rescue mission that saved 12 boys and their soccer coach from a flooding Thai cave. He called Unsworth, a British caver who lives in Thailand, a "pedo" or pedophile in a now-deleted tweet. The unfounded claim came after Unsworth called Musk's miniature sub a "PR stunt." There is no indicati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Do These Five Things And Avoid What Happened To Elon Musk - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bruceweinstein/2018/08/27/do-these-five-things-and-avoid-what-happened-to-elon-musk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKiOkObbna67ro0FIvZfOsoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 19:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bruceweinstein/2018/08/27/do-these-five-things-and-avoid-what-happened-to-elon-musk/" target="_blank"&gt;Do These Five Things And Avoid What Happened To Elon Musk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla CEO and founder of the Boring Company Elon Musk speaks at a news conference, in Chicago. AP Photo/Kiichiro Sato, File Here are five ways you can avoid the mistakes that have plagued Tesla and SpaceX founder Elon Musk for too long. These guidelines emerged from a far-ranging conversation I had recently with Dr. Halee Fisher-Wright, CEO of the Medical Group Management Association (MGMA) and the author of Back To Balance: The Art, Science, and Business of Medicine. As the leader of an organization that represents more than 40,000 medical practice administrators and executives in practice...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Who Are The Investors That Convinced Elon Musk To Keep Tesla Public And Why - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/chuckjones/2018/08/25/who-are-the-investors-that-convinced-elon-musk-to-keep-tesla-public-and-why/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKT0B_HVRLPehTYQfzNQ5x0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 16:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/chuckjones/2018/08/25/who-are-the-investors-that-convinced-elon-musk-to-keep-tesla-public-and-why/" target="_blank"&gt;Who Are The Investors That Convinced Elon Musk To Keep Tesla Public And Why&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SpaceX, Tesla and The Boring Company founder Elon Musk. Photo credit: ROBYN BECK/AFP/Getty Images Elon Musk announced late Friday via a blog on Tesla’s website that he had stopped working to take the company private. In the post Musk wrote, “it’s apparent that most of Tesla’s existing shareholders believe we are better off as a public company” and that “a number of institutional shareholders have explained that they have internal compliance issues that limit how much they can invest in a private company.” Musk also wrote that “it’s clear that it would be even more time-consuming and distrac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s Boring Co. plans high-speed tunnel shuttle to Dodger Stadium - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musks-boring-co-plans-high-speed-tunnel-shuttle-to-dodger-stadium-2018-08-15</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXqKZeHE0A3qGacSRBl-UYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 03:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musks-boring-co-plans-high-speed-tunnel-shuttle-to-dodger-stadium-2018-08-15" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk’s Boring Co. plans high-speed tunnel shuttle to Dodger Stadium&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Mike Murphy Company proposes privately funded, 3.6-mile tunnel to get passengers to stadium in less than 4 minutes Passengers would ride in pods that fit eight to 16 people, and sit on electric skates. The Boring Co. Los Angeles Dodgers fans are notorious for showing up late to games (stuck in traffic) and leaving early (gotta beat the traffic). But Elon Musk is looking to make the trek a lot less of a hassle. Musk’s Boring Co., which digs tunnels, announced Wednesday night a proposal to build a 3.6-mile tunnel under Los Angeles, running from one of three existing subway stations to Dodg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>How Much Is Elon Musk Worth To Tesla? - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/chuckjones/2018/08/18/how-much-is-elon-musk-worth-to-tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDpIIw9gcIsMmUN0J-kQGi4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 13:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/chuckjones/2018/08/18/how-much-is-elon-musk-worth-to-tesla/" target="_blank"&gt;How Much Is Elon Musk Worth To Tesla?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla CEO and founder of the Boring Company Elon Musk. AP Photo/Kiichiro Sato In one aspect you could say that Tesla’s entire value is tied to Elon Musk . It is his dream and determination that has created a disruptive company that has shaken the automotive industry to its core. With Tesla a cash burning, money-losing machine (at least so far) creating over $50 billion in value is tremendous. At some point in time Musk won’t be at Tesla but that will hopefully be a long ways from now. However, the market does provide feedback on how much he is worth to the company . Calculating the changes ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Timeline: Elon Musk's 'difficult and painful' 2018 - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/aug/19/elon-musk-tesla-timeline-difficult-painful-year</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwkxvbuoB7Xb0PO1Su750YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 05:00:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/aug/19/elon-musk-tesla-timeline-difficult-painful-year" target="_blank"&gt;Timeline: Elon Musk's 'difficult and painful' 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;27 January Elon Musk’s Boring Company launches a $500 flamethrower. Critics say it is more like a gun-shaped blowtorch than a flamethrower. Related: Elon Musk: the volatile visionary at risk of steering Tesla off the road 6 February SpaceX, Musk’s upstart rocket company, fires a midnight cherry Tesla Roadster out of Earth’s orbit while playing David Bowie’s Space Oddity. The following day, Tesla announces a $675m quarterly loss, sending stock tumbling on fears the company could run out of cash. 3 March A Model X crashes into a freeway divider, killing the driver and catching fire. Tesla say...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Tesla's stock falls sharply after Elon Musk's tearful interview - CNN</title><link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/17/news/companies/tesla-stock/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKa3tuPKvowpHfgRC26mlzwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 22:24:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/17/news/companies/tesla-stock/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla's stock falls sharply after Elon Musk's tearful interview&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla's stock tumbled after CEO Elon Musk said he's working himself to the bone and relies on Ambien to sleep. In an tearful interviewwith The New York Times, Musk said this has been "the most difficult and painful year" of his career. He said he works 120 hours some weeks and has trouble sleeping. Musk is also CEO of SpaceX and The Boring Company. Investors weren't sympathetic. The stock closed down 9% on Friday, and it's down 21% since the day Musk tweeted he had secured funding for a private takeover of Tesla. Musk hasn't exactly given investors confidence that he's on the ball. He admit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>How Insane Is Elon Musk's $420 Valuation For Tesla? - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hershshefrin/2018/08/12/how-insane-is-elon-musks-420-valuation-for-tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK1gQEXg61t_PRTU4MxiHkUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 19:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hershshefrin/2018/08/12/how-insane-is-elon-musks-420-valuation-for-tesla/" target="_blank"&gt;How Insane Is Elon Musk's $420 Valuation For Tesla?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This past week, Elon Musk tweeted that he was thinking of taking Tesla private at a price of $420 a share. That would be 18 percent more than $356, which is where Tesla’s stock closed last Friday. Is $420 an insane valuation? That depends. SpaceX, Tesla and The Boring Company founder Elon Musk speaks at the 2018 SpaceX Hyperloop Pod Competition, in Hawthorne, California on July 22, 2018. – (Photo by Robyn Beck / AFP) (Photo credit should read ROBYN BECK/AFP/Getty Images) On the one hand, if you bought Tesla at the end of last week, and Musk manages to take Tesla private within a year, you w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk's $82 Billion Tesla Buyout Folly - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/chuckjones/2018/08/09/elon-musks-82-billion-tesla-buyout-folly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJErAHLjfNlJ37Ac7_NIRKMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 16:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/chuckjones/2018/08/09/elon-musks-82-billion-tesla-buyout-folly/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk's $82 Billion Tesla Buyout Folly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla CEO and founder of the Boring Company Elon Musk. AP Photo/Kiichiro Sato, File During market hours on Tuesday Tesla’s CEO, Elon Musk, tweeted that he was, “considering taking Tesla private at $420. Funding secured.” From the initial indications this seems to be more of a fire first, aim later, from Musk’s iPhone (assuming he uses an iPhone vs. Android device) than a well thought through proposal which was reviewed by the Board. In a letter to employees, he has one very good reason for wanting to do this, but it also seems as much a reaction to not wanting to have to take questions from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Has Elon Musk lost control of his hype machine? - CNN</title><link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/07/26/technology/elon-musk-tesla/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPxdISa8NtNPMmthQECBFGUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:11:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://money.cnn.com/2018/07/26/technology/elon-musk-tesla/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Has Elon Musk lost control of his hype machine?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk is hard at work disrupting industries, such astransportation and energy, and plans to go to Mars to save humanity from extinction. But even with these ambitions, the billionaire entrepreneur still found time to silence an anonymous blogger. The latest example of Musk's focus on protecting the image of his companies — and himself — came this week when a blogger critical of Tesla shut down his own Twitter account and stopped writing for the financial website Seeking Alpha. According to the author, who used the pseudynom "Montana Skeptic," Musk called his boss and threatened to sue i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>I know Elon Musk does good, but he's still a bonehead - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/jul/17/elon-musk-boneheadthailand-cave-rescue</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAWPLIIugoXhzZ1dCflGOooqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 08:46:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/jul/17/elon-musk-boneheadthailand-cave-rescue" target="_blank"&gt;I know Elon Musk does good, but he's still a bonehead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I was at school, one of the go-to playground insults, I am afraid, was “paedo”. Mostly the teachers were paedos, but the socially awkward kid in sixth form and the janitor who scuppered your escape at lunchtime were also targets. Of course, I realise now that even jokingly accusing someone of sexually abusing children isn’t witty or clever. You grow out of these baseless, ridiculous epithets, don’t you? Not Elon Musk, aged 47. The tech CEO has called the British diver Vern Unsworth – one of the two divers who found the Thai football team trapped in a cave and was integral to their resc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Will Elon Musk's antics hurt his businesses? - CNN</title><link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/07/16/technology/business/elon-musk-tweet-controversy/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK2XwJoX2wMA4cC6FRPoCSEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 18:47:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://money.cnn.com/2018/07/16/technology/business/elon-musk-tweet-controversy/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Will Elon Musk's antics hurt his businesses?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once again, Elon Musk is in the middle of a controversy of his own making. And he may be testing investors' patience. Over the weekend, the tech entrepreneur caught flak for tweeting an unfounded accusation that one of the cavers who helped rescue 12 boys from a Thai cave is a pedophile. He has since deleted the tweet. The Tesla CEO made the comment at a precarious time for the company, which has struggled to bring the Model 3, its mainstream vehicle, to market. Bottlenecks have severely delayed the delivery timeline Musk promised for the Model 3, and Tesla may need to raise more money from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Hey Elon Musk Fans, Don't Take It Personally, He Is Just Playing The Political Game - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/samabuelsamid/2018/07/15/hey-elon-musk-fans-dont-take-it-personally-he-is-just-playing-the-political-game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENKyy9atWfvvg843Nv8F9uEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 13:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/samabuelsamid/2018/07/15/hey-elon-musk-fans-dont-take-it-personally-he-is-just-playing-the-political-game/" target="_blank"&gt;Hey Elon Musk Fans, Don't Take It Personally, He Is Just Playing The Political Game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHICAGO, IL – JUNE 14: Engineer and tech entrepreneur Elon Musk of The Boring Company listens as Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel talks about constructing a high speed transit tunnel at Block 37 during a news conference on June 14, 2018 in Chicago, Illinois. Musk said he could create a 16-passenger vehicle to operate on a high-speed rail system that could get travelers to and from downtown Chicago and O’hare International Airport under twenty minutes, at speeds of over 100 miles per hour. (Photo by Joshua Lott/Getty Images) Tesla is the first new American automaker making more than a tiny trickle...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Who owns the space under cities? The attempt to map the ground beneath us - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2018/jul/10/who-owns-the-space-under-cities-the-attempt-to-map-the-ground-beneath-our-feet</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJuBtDd1DcvEHHqjgDPmQEEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 06:15:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2018/jul/10/who-owns-the-space-under-cities-the-attempt-to-map-the-ground-beneath-our-feet" target="_blank"&gt;Who owns the space under cities? The attempt to map the ground beneath us&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just over a year ago I was sent a photograph of a tunnel-boring machine in a dirt lot in Los Angeles. The caption read: “Elon Musk is about to start digging.” The message was from Wayne Chambliss, a geographer in southern California, who tends to be prescient in such matters – and indeed, Musk’s freshly minted Boring Company soon set its machine loose, ripping through the subsurface soil under the SpaceX headquarters in Hawthorne to create a short tunnel. This pet project – to test a private mass-transit system based on Hyperloop technology that would magnetically propel small pods and cars...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Will Tesla Be "Tripp'ed" Up By A Whistleblower? - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimcollins/2018/07/12/will-tesla-be-tripped-up-by-a-whistleblower/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFLAQwTPeLn2IxvBWhsJIOUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimcollins/2018/07/12/will-tesla-be-tripped-up-by-a-whistleblower/" target="_blank"&gt;Will Tesla Be "Tripp'ed" Up By A Whistleblower?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Tesla whistleblower scandal intensified Wednesday with reports that Martin Tripp’s counsel, Meissner and Associates, had filed a claim on his behalf with the Securities and Exchange Commission. Other news outlets have done an excellent job of reporting on Tripp’s accusations, but my focus is on the potential downside for Tesla shares from an SEC investigation. Tesla’s stock is less tethered to fundamentals than any I have ever seen, and so the potential involvement of the ultimate truth squad when it comes to reported fundamental data, the SEC, has to be terrifying to those who hold Te...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk offers to help Thailand's government with cave rescue - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/07/06/elon-musk-offers-help-thailands-government-cave-rescue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcZM8dHHI3Z2w3cXrD-NxsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 12:13:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/07/06/elon-musk-offers-help-thailands-government-cave-rescue/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk offers to help Thailand's government with cave rescue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk has sent a team of engineers to help rescue the group of 12 children and their coach trapped in a cave in Thailand. The billionaire entrepreneur said that a group of engineers from his companies, SpaceX and The Boring Company, would leave for Thailand on Saturday "to see if we can be helpful to the government." Musk has commented on the rescue through Twitter since the news broke earlier this week, initially offering help to the Thai government in their rescue operations in response to a request online. He also outlined an idea for a rescue operation, using pumps, battery packs an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk sends engineers to help Thai cave rescue mission - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/06/asia/thai-cave-rescue-elon-musk-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMLUfT1CM3pSdPyU-g5vCnIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 18:17:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/06/asia/thai-cave-rescue-elon-musk-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk sends engineers to help Thai cave rescue mission&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tech billionaire Elon Musk is sending specialist engineers to Thailand to help aid the rescue of the 12 boys and their football coach trapped in a cave. Musk hopes his engineers can join the already huge operation being carried out he Tham Luang Nang Non cave complex, where dozens of Thai Navy SEALs and international experts are attempting to find a way to get the boys out. Musk, founder of the Boring Company, as well as the CEO of Tesla and SpaceX tweeted Thursday: "SpaceX &amp; Boring Co engineers headed to Thailand tomorrow to see if we can be helpful to govt. There are probably many complex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk And The Dangers Of Hero Worship - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/karlkaufman/2018/06/30/elon-musk-and-the-dangers-of-hero-worship/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEamvI-TAb2--atsUPLWgTgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 20:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/karlkaufman/2018/06/30/elon-musk-and-the-dangers-of-hero-worship/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk And The Dangers Of Hero Worship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk speaks onstage at Elon Musk Answers Your Questions! during SXSW(Photo by Chris Saucedo/Getty Images for SXSW) Flamethrowers. Missions to Mars. Strapping Tesla cars to rockets and sending them into space. Elon Musk is a larger-than-life character, the kind of man whose behavior and ideas are so outlandish he even has his own meme generator. If you buy shares of Tesla, you’re buying into the idea that this man, the face of the company, has what it takes to defy the odds, quiet the naysayers and turn Tesla into a profitable company. Hero worship can blind you to certain realities. Yo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Never Bet Against The Ambitions Of Elon Musk - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonmarkman/2018/06/28/never-bet-against-the-ambitions-of-elon-musk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELBfHuZ-9LqWa5S6jyz6qewqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 16:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonmarkman/2018/06/28/never-bet-against-the-ambitions-of-elon-musk/" target="_blank"&gt;Never Bet Against The Ambitions Of Elon Musk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla is set to lay off 9% of its 40,000 employees. But Elon Musk doesn’t seem to be worried about the 425,000 orders that are currently backlogged. That’s because there’s an even more ambitious goal he wants to hit. Musk says existing Teslas will begin the transition to full, self-driving vehicles in August. This evolution should not surprise to Musk followers. He has been teasing full-blown autonomy for years. CHICAGO, IL – JUNE 14: Engineer and tech entrepreneur Elon Musk of The Boring Company listens as Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel talks about constructing a high speed transit tunnel at B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk's Boring Co to build high-speed airport link in Chicago - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-musk-tunnel/elon-musks-boring-co-to-build-high-speed-airport-link-in-chicago-idUSKBN1JA224</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJDdkKy_wSfMiNNALsaLGWsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 22:19:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-musk-tunnel/elon-musks-boring-co-to-build-high-speed-airport-link-in-chicago-idUSKBN1JA224" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk's Boring Co to build high-speed airport link in Chicago&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Suzannah Gonzales CHICAGO (Reuters) - Chicago has selected Elon Musk's Boring Co to build a $1 billion underground transit system that will whisk people from Chicago's downtown Loop district to O'Hare International Airport at 150 miles per hour (240 km per hour), the billionaire entrepreneur and Mayor Rahm Emanuel said on Thursday. The system will travel the 17 miles from downtown to O'Hare, one of the world's busiest airports, in 12 minutes, less time than it takes to get through airport security, Emanuel said at a news conference in an unfinished underground train station in the Loop t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s Boring Company To Build High-Speed Transit Network In Chicago - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/elon-musk-boring-company-chicago_us_5b21f17ce4b09d7a3d7a255a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOX-RJdi_e-99yBik1KH08qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 07:33:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/elon-musk-boring-company-chicago_us_5b21f17ce4b09d7a3d7a255a" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk’s Boring Company To Build High-Speed Transit Network In Chicago&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk’s Boring Company will soon have some boring to do. The tech billionaire’s tunnel-building endeavor confirmed to HuffPost late Wednesday that it had been selected to construct an express transit network between downtown Chicago and O’Hare International Airport. The company claims the trip through its futuristic tunnels will ferry up to 16 passengers in high-speed electric vehicles. The cars, called “skates,” could leave as frequently as every 30 seconds and travel more than 100 miles per hour, The New York Times reported. The trip will reportedly take about 12 minutes each way. We’...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Musk's Boring Company wins bid to build high-speed system in Chicago - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-musk-tunnel/musks-boring-company-wins-bid-to-build-high-speed-system-in-chicago-idUSKBN1JA0C4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI7S8A2EP32mn3bgRufbHekqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 09:30:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-musk-tunnel/musks-boring-company-wins-bid-to-build-high-speed-system-in-chicago-idUSKBN1JA0C4" target="_blank"&gt;Musk's Boring Company wins bid to build high-speed system in Chicago&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Reuters) - The City of Chicago has selected billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk's The Boring Company to build a high-speed underground commuter system from the Loop to O'Hare International Airport, one of the world's busiest, media reported on Wednesday. The system will be comprised of 16-passenger vehicles that will travel up to 150 miles (240 km) per hour through a tunnel that will cut the current 30 to 45-minute trip between the airport and Chicago's business district down to 12 minutes, according to Boring's website. The Chicago Tribune and Bloomberg first reported the deal, citing unna...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Boring Company shoots Tesla car down underground tunnel (VIDEO) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/430008-boring-company-tesla-test/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHUEcJSC1XAszC6DfPjcdYQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/430008-boring-company-tesla-test/" target="_blank"&gt;Boring Company shoots Tesla car down underground tunnel (VIDEO)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Injecting a brief element of excitement into the humdrum work of tunnelling, The Boring Company has sped a Tesla Model X down a channel that founder Elon Musk hopes will become a commuter success. With The Boring Company, Musk is currently on a multi-million dollar mission to develop underground transportation corridors known as the Loop and Hyperloop. According to the company, which is currently eating into the earth for tunnels underneath Los Angeles, the aim is to “solve the problem of soul-destroying traffic.” READ MORE: Elon Musk’s anti-traffic jam tunnels explained in fresh video (VID...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Innovative Transit Projects Like The Express Loop Must Be Responsible Not Just Disruptive - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ellistalton/2018/06/18/innovative-transit-projects-like-the-express-loop-must-be-responsible-not-just-disruptive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKi7fjeOmCgTmt-IyIwpgu4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ellistalton/2018/06/18/innovative-transit-projects-like-the-express-loop-must-be-responsible-not-just-disruptive/" target="_blank"&gt;Innovative Transit Projects Like The Express Loop Must Be Responsible Not Just Disruptive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Boring Company has been selected to build a new rapid transit system from O’Hare Airport to downtown Chicago. Last week, the Chicago Infrastructure Trust announced the selection of Elon Musk’s Boring Company to build its Express Loop rapid transit service from O’Hare International Airport to downtown Chicago. The service employs autonomous passenger pods called “skates,” which are essentially wheeled vehicles built on Tesla’s Model X chassis. These skates are loaded and then lowered underground where, secured by a concrete track, they travel at 150 miles per hour in one of two parallel ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Boring Co.'s Chicago Deal Shows We Haven't Yet Hit Peak Musk - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alanohnsman/2018/06/14/boring-chicago-musk-autonomous-rail-tesla/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHn7HyPie_dZS8XfnQyAjDwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 19:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alanohnsman/2018/06/14/boring-chicago-musk-autonomous-rail-tesla/" target="_blank"&gt;Boring Co.'s Chicago Deal Shows We Haven't Yet Hit Peak Musk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A rendering of the O’Hare International Airport station for the proposed high-speed transit line the company aims to build. Chicago’s plan to let Elon Musk’s Boring Co. have a crack at building a high-speed, subterranean transportation line to whisk passengers between the city’s center and O’Hare International Airport is a coup for the fledgling infrastructure firm and speaks volumes about confidence in its billionaire founder—who hasn’t actually built such a system before. The project includes drilling tunnels from Chicago’s Loop to the airport in which autonomous electric pods, built by T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk's Boring Company to build airport link - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/06/15/elon-musks-boring-company-build-airport-link/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3GeclNRpaYD-KS7kPmGzUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 08:57:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/06/15/elon-musks-boring-company-build-airport-link/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk's Boring Company to build airport link&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Entrepreneur Elon Musk said Thursday a high-speed transportation system that will whisk people between downtown Chicago and O'Hare International Airport at speeds of up to 150 mph could be operational in about three years. Musk joined Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel to formally announce that a Musk-owned enterprise, The Boring Company, was selected for the project and will fully fund it. They say electric vehicles will carry passengers through underground tunnels in about 12 minutes each way. Emanuel called the new transit system "the fast lane to Chicago's future," and said it will create jobs ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Musk says O'Hare express line could open in 2021 - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/6bd17bc052f54214bd19e0540d1bc112</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENR1oqg-VM6jG8H1t2gfleMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 20:29:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/6bd17bc052f54214bd19e0540d1bc112" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Musk says O'Hare express line could open in 2021&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — The Latest on plans for a high-speed transportation system between downtown Chicago and O'Hare Airport (all times local): 3:25 p.m. Entrepreneur Elon Musk says a high-speed transportation system that will whisk people between downtown Chicago and O'Hare International Airport in about 12 minutes could be operational in about three years. Musk joined Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel on Thursday to formally announce that a Musk-owned enterprise, The Boring Company, was selected for the project and will fully fund it. They say the electric vehicles will move through underground tunnels...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s Boring Co. delivers first 1,000 flamethrowers to customers - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musks-boring-co-delivers-first-1000-flamethrowers-to-customers-2018-06-10</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG88MajPIliJfd_4uiMaaWoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 06:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/elon-musks-boring-co-delivers-first-1000-flamethrowers-to-customers-2018-06-10" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk’s Boring Co. delivers first 1,000 flamethrowers to customers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Mike Murphy Company raised $10 million by selling 20,000 ‘Not a Flamethrowers’ An attendee operates a Boring Co. flamethrower Saturday in Hawthorne, Calif. Bloomberg News Turns out, it wasn’t a joke. Six months after Elon Musk raised the eyebrows of sane people everywhere by announcing his Boring Co. would sell flamethrowers for $500 a pop, the first 1,000 deliveries were made Saturday for customers who showed up at the company’s headquarters in Hawthorne, Calif. The flamethrowers went like, well, flaming hotcakes when they went on sale in late January, selling out in just four days. In ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Musk company to build Chicago-to-O'Hare express transport - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/e10821327a5545a4a1d824603fb5770b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJfOxiSQDJ_YCWo1rHsMod4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 02:14:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/e10821327a5545a4a1d824603fb5770b" target="_blank"&gt;Musk company to build Chicago-to-O'Hare express transport&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Entrepreneur Elon Musk said Thursday a high-speed transportation system that will whisk people between downtown Chicago and O'Hare International Airport at speeds of up to 150 mph could be operational in about three years. Musk joined Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel to formally announce that a Musk-owned enterprise, The Boring Company, was selected for the project and will fully fund it. They say electric vehicles will carry passengers through underground tunnels in about 12 minutes each way. Emanuel called the new transit system "the fast lane to Chicago's future," and said it wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk Delivers First Flamethrowers - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/elon-musk-delivers-first-flamethrowers/4434739.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENSx6Gh9MEe-PNmLPfzFPhkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 01:30:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/elon-musk-delivers-first-flamethrowers/4434739.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk Delivers First Flamethrowers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may not be a ride in space or even a rocket-powered roadster, but Elon Musk has delivered the first batch of personal flamethrowers, just in time for the July 4th backyard barbecues. The SpaceX CEO's tunnel construction firm, The Boring Company, delivered 1,000 of the 20,000 limited-run flamethrowers sold last year. "When the zombie apocalypse happens, you'll be glad you bought a flamethrower. Works against hordes of the undead or your money back!" Musk joked when the devices went on sale. Even priced at $500 each, they sold out quickly and brought in $10 million. Musk named the device "...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Buyers travel thousands of miles to pick up first batch of Elon Musk's flamethrowers - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-flamethrower-release-pick-up-boring-company-sells-out-a8392636.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVCU_IfE8OFQFYYYMMA7TcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-flamethrower-release-pick-up-boring-company-sells-out-a8392636.html" target="_blank"&gt;Buyers travel thousands of miles to pick up first batch of Elon Musk's flamethrowers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first batch of flamethrowers sold by Elon Musk’s tunnel construction business The Boring Company have been handed out to customers - with some people traveling thousands of miles to pick one up. The Tesla entrepreneur had suggested the idea of selling a flamethrower at the end of 2017, with the project aiming to raise $10m for The Boring Company, which was founded with the intention of building a network of tunnels to help reduce traffic congestion across the US. Mr Musk claimed that the company had sold 20,000 of the $500 in four days in during January this year, with the first flameth...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Chicago Taps Elon Musk’s Company to Build High-Speed Tunneling System - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/chicago-taps-elon-musks-company-to-build-high-speed-tunneling-system</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEXKKSSiTNSc_8osGnIvrVgqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 05:21:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/chicago-taps-elon-musks-company-to-build-high-speed-tunneling-system" target="_blank"&gt;Chicago Taps Elon Musk’s Company to Build High-Speed Tunneling System&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucy Nicholson/Reuters, Elon Musk’s Boring Company has been chosen by authorities in Chicago to build a transportation system that would take passengers from the city’s downtown area to O’Hare airport at speeds exceeding 100 mph. Mayor Rahm Emanuel announced the news late Wednesday, saying the “transformative project” will help the city “write the next chapter in our legacy of innovation and invention.” A decade ago, Chicago authorities poured more than $250 million into a subway superstation meant to provide high-speed trains to city airports, but the project was later shelved and has hung...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Musk hyperloop: hoover mover - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/7851afca-70b1-11e8-852d-d8b934ff5ffa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJxxBIeQzgDf8lhTqPqp8ikqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 05:30:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/7851afca-70b1-11e8-852d-d8b934ff5ffa" target="_blank"&gt;Musk hyperloop: hoover mover&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will the hyperloop — promising transport at near-supersonic speed — ever justify the hype? Impossible, you might think, given that its effusive cheerleaders include the likes of Elon Musk and Richard Branson. Their enthusiasm belies the scale of the challenge ahead. The idea of propelling passenger-carrying capsules using a vacuum tube is not new. British inventor George Medhurst patented a version of the idea in 1799. The Victorians built several “atmospheric railways”. Mr Musk’s dream of an energy-efficient transit system would use as little as a tenth of the energy per passenger of airpl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk Company Hands Out 'Fun' Flamethrowers In Scorched LA - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/elon-musk-delivers-recreational-flamethrowers-in-california_us_5b1dae7be4b0bbb7a0de6ba1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI0KYjI-nlgTsQfskPyOQTkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 02:34:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/elon-musk-delivers-recreational-flamethrowers-in-california_us_5b1dae7be4b0bbb7a0de6ba1" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk Company Hands Out 'Fun' Flamethrowers In Scorched LA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tech nerds, pyromaniacs and the curious turned up in Los Angeles Saturday to collect hundreds of recreational flamethrowers purchased from the latest company created by SpaceX CEO Elon Musk. A tweet from Musk urged people to avoid “unintentionally burning things down.” Musk sold 20,000 of his latest bizarre consumer products at $500 a pop, apparently to raise both funds and awareness of his futuristic new transportation tube project in Los Angeles. People initially thought he was kidding when he sold the flamethrowers — and then promised to deliver them at “pick up parties.” The devices sho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item></channel></rss>