<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>George H. W. Bush - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRE0wYkhNU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-GH&amp;gl=GH&amp;ceid=GH:en</link><language>en-GH</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:09:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>So now George Bush Sr is celebrated as a titan of unity. How on earth did we get here? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/08/george-hw-bush-titan-of-unity</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMeFLwi_hFyhPB-hDlYsHosqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/08/george-hw-bush-titan-of-unity" target="_blank"&gt;So now George Bush Sr is celebrated as a titan of unity. How on earth did we get here?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;George HW Bush was no one’s idea of a great president. His 1988 presidential campaign was the first I followed as a child in the US – supporting, under my mother’s instruction, his hapless rival, Michael Dukakis – and even then he seemed strangely unquantifiable, a blank. His presidency bore this impression out, in which his credit sheet was cancelled out by enough debit that the balance ultimately came to nothing. A war hero and famously polite, Bush Sr signed the Clean Air Act and the Americans With Disabilities Act (protecting, among others, people with HIV, from discrimination), and eve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Secret Service formally terminates ‘Timberwolf Detail’ protecting President George H.W. Bush - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/secret-service-formally-terminates-timberwolf-detail-protecting-president-george-hw-bush-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL6hw1S5JsnWqj867vOVVM4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/secret-service-formally-terminates-timberwolf-detail-protecting-president-george-hw-bush-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;Secret Service formally terminates ‘Timberwolf Detail’ protecting President George H.W. Bush&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASSOCIATED PRESS By Associated Press A hearse carrying the casket of President George H.W. Bush arriving Thursday at Texas A&amp;M University in College Station, Texas. Reuters COLLEGE STATION, Texas (AP) — The U.S. Secret Service has ended its detail for George H.W. Bush after nearly 40 years of protecting the former president, who was known by the code name “Timberwolf.” The agency says its security detail officially ended at 6 a.m. Friday “with no incidents to report” following Bush’s burial Thursday at his presidential library at Texas A&amp;M University. In its final notification, the Bush Pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>In pictures: Remembering President George H.W. Bush - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/politics/gallery/george-h-w-bush-memorials/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHu4c9kMmyR0zN_1Uw7hD6EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:23:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/politics/gallery/george-h-w-bush-memorials/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;In pictures: Remembering President George H.W. Bush&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peter Olyniec waves an American flag as George H.W. Bush's train passes near Whitehall, Texas, on Thursday, December 6. Bush's body was en route to his presidential library in College Station, Texas, where he was laid to rest. Scott Olson/Getty Images Navy guard Kenneth Knox stands over the flag-draped casket of the late President as a train carries it to his presidential library at Texas A&amp;M University. Joe Raedle/Getty Images People pay their respects as the train carrying the casket passes Spring, Texas. David J. Phillip/Pool/Reuters Police salute as a hearse carries Bush's casket to a t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump surrounding himself with yes-men and yes-women - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/opinions/trumps-yes-men-and-yes-women-psaki/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKqXBgfzfzH2C1XcVFlaBK4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:46:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/opinions/trumps-yes-men-and-yes-women-psaki/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump surrounding himself with yes-men and yes-women&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jen Psaki, a CNN political commentator, was the White House communications director and State Department spokeswoman during the Obama administration. She is vice president of communications and strategy at the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace. Follow her at @jrpsaki. The opinions expressed in this commentary are solely those of the author. Read more opinion articles at CNN. In the olden days of presidential appointments and nominations, the focus was justifiably on the nominees -- their background, what their policy positions said about the role they would play in an administratio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump demands border wall money; shutdown showdown nears - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/37597934930b48a39a51151c7dc3d7ff</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ9iFjEnKGGO6oAUCJY8eEoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:02:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/37597934930b48a39a51151c7dc3d7ff" target="_blank"&gt;Trump demands border wall money; shutdown showdown nears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. (AP) — President Donald Trump said Friday that Congress should provide all the money he wants for his promised U.S.-Mexico border wall, and he called illegal immigration a "threat to the well-being of every American community." Trump spoke hours after signing a short-term spending bill that covers key government departments for two more weeks, until Dec. 21, setting up a pre-Christmas showdown over the wall. The president wants the next spending package to include at least $5 billion for the proposed wall. House Democratic leader Nancy Pelosi of California rejected that a d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The Week in 7 Insane Photos: December 7, 2018 - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-week-in-7-insane-photos-december-7-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBsVh6ytVIwM0hLEvxdQs_QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:02:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-week-in-7-insane-photos-december-7-2018" target="_blank"&gt;The Week in 7 Insane Photos: December 7, 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;From George H.W. Bush's funeral to Santa spreading cheer in Caracas, The Daily Beast brings you the best photos of the week. Richard Gamboa, dressed up as Santa Claus, talks with a boy during the "Santa en las calles" (Santa in the streets) event donating toys, food, and clothes at the slum Cota 905 in Caracas, Venezuela December 1, 2018. Marco Bello/Reuters A winter swimmer swims in a pool carved out of a frozen lake at Beiling Park in minus 10 degrees Celcius air temperature on December 6, 2018 in Shenyang, Liaoning Province of China. VCG/Getty Jack Collins of Canada competes in the Snowb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Pearl Harbor brought out the best in George Bush and others - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/opinions/pearl-harbor-day-anniversary-bush-remembrance-brands/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECrr-u5G9hTEmxQh0ba6BbQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:05:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/opinions/pearl-harbor-day-anniversary-bush-remembrance-brands/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pearl Harbor brought out the best in George Bush and others&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;H. W. Brands teaches history at the University of Texas at Austin. His new book is "Heirs of the Founders: The Epic Rivalry of Henry Clay, John Calhoun and Daniel Webster, the Second Generation of American Giants." The views expressed here are solely his. View more opinion articles on CNN. It's an accident of timing that the funeral of George H. W. Bush occurred within days of the anniversary of Pearl Harbor. But it's no accident that Americans have marked the passing of the former President with an outpouring of respect and admiration typically reserved for war heroes. They remember his pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump Announces Nominees for UN, Attorney General - VOA News</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yLTpdbllqag</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKDPcD6g5Xwqv1rIBtkk0qIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw78Uq</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 03:01:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yLTpdbllqag" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Announces Nominees for UN, Attorney General&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump on Friday confirmed he will nominate State Department spokeswoman Heather Nauert to be the new Ambassador to the United Nations. He also announced William Barr to be the new U.S. Attorney General, a post Barr held under former President George H.W. Bush. VOA'S Jeff Custer reports from Washington. Originally published at - https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-announces-nominees-for-un-attorney-general/4691318.html&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Thousands Line Bush Funeral Train Route for Final Farewell - VOA News</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fodc8c7nWOs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHKlwWumVuGyR1aPPbPIcUgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw78Uq</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:39:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fodc8c7nWOs" target="_blank"&gt;Thousands Line Bush Funeral Train Route for Final Farewell&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of people lined up along the route of the funeral train that was taking the remains of former President George H.W. Bush from Houston about 80 miles northwest to his final resting place, his presidential library in College Station, Texas, on Thursday, Dec. 6. The train is a Union Pacific Corp locomotive, numbered 4141 and bearing the name "George Bush 41" on the side. Bush, the 41st U.S. president, died last week in Texas at age 94. His remains were flown to Texas on Wednesday evening after a state funeral at Washington's National Cathedral attended by U.S. President Donald Trump,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Texas Bids President George HW Bush Final Farewell - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/texas-bids-president-george-hw-bush-final-farewell/4690689.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHu2yP6dnp3p6M0WMI4Im5gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:37:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/texas-bids-president-george-hw-bush-final-farewell/4690689.html" target="_blank"&gt;Texas Bids President George HW Bush Final Farewell&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of rows of carefully placed flags along this Houston sidewalk, just outside the metal gates of West Oak Drive South, is a makeshift memorial filled with flowers and teddy bears, honoring a local resident who was, at least to Donna Platt who lives nearby, more than just a president. “Very nice, we would run into him, and not just me but all the neighbors, in the bank doing his banking business or in the grocery store — he liked to go to the grocery store — and it was just like saying hi to another neighbor,” she told VOA after taking a few pictures to document the memorial for pos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Bush's presidential funeral train first in nearly 50 years - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/fd4a3d8b2a9e4b8199637174ecc4ef26</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRRY4dHhXaYtp7T70HyN2gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:33:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/fd4a3d8b2a9e4b8199637174ecc4ef26" target="_blank"&gt;Bush's presidential funeral train first in nearly 50 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SPRING, Texas (AP) — The locomotive was painted to resemble Air Force One, but George H.W. Bush joked that if it had been around during his presidency, he may have preferred to ride the rails rather than take to the skies. "I might have left Air Force One behind," Bush quipped during the 2005 unveiling of 4141, a blue and gray locomotive commissioned in honor of the 41st president and unveiled at Texas A&amp;M University. On Thursday, that same 4,300-horsepower machine left a suburban Houston railyard loaded with Bush's casket for his final journey after almost a week of ceremonies in Washingto...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Bernie Sanders Explains to Colbert Why Trump Is No George H.W. Bush - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bernie-sanders-explains-to-colbert-why-trump-is-no-george-hw-bush</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBs5_alHav1anGSlC71pQI8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:01:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/bernie-sanders-explains-to-colbert-why-trump-is-no-george-hw-bush" target="_blank"&gt;Bernie Sanders Explains to Colbert Why Trump Is No George H.W. Bush&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Kowalchyk/CBS Senator Bernie Sanders is one of the many progressives “seriously considering” a run for the presidency in 2020. And he took one step closer to that eventuality on The Late Show with Stephen Colbert Thursday night. Ostensibly, Sanders was there to promote his latest book, Where We Go from Here: Two Years in the Resistance, but really he was there to pump up his base. Asked how he’s feeling after the midterm elections, Sanders answered, “A lot better now than before the midterms. Democrats won 40 seats, now control the House, won several governors’ seats and several hundr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Donald Trump nominates William Barr as next attorney general - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/donald-trump-nominates-william-barr-attorney-general</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOon7C1FtVVmnB-lzgLD5usqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:28:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/donald-trump-nominates-william-barr-attorney-general" target="_blank"&gt;Donald Trump nominates William Barr as next attorney general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has named William Barr as his next attorney general, a move that raises fresh concerns about the future of special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation into Russian election interference. Related: Trump to nominate new attorney general and UN ambassador as Kelly eyes exit – live If confirmed by the Senate, Barr – who held the same role under the late George HW Bush from 1991 to 1993 – will take over from Matthew Whitaker, who has served in an acting capacity since Jeff Sessions was forced out a month ago. Democrats have threatened to examine whether Whitaker can legally serve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Trump nominates William Barr to be his next attorney general - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/william-barr-attorney-general-nomination/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJObChhEiVdimktfI1VSKYgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:44:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/william-barr-attorney-general-nomination/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump nominates William Barr to be his next attorney general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump has decided to nominate former Attorney General William Barr to be the next permanent head of the Justice Department, the President told reporters Friday. "I want to confirm that Bill Barr, one of the most respected jurists in the country, highly respected lawyer, former attorney general under the Bush administration, a terrific man, a terrific person, a brilliant man," Trump said as he departed the White House. "I did not know him until recently when I went through the process of looking at people and he was my first choice from day one, respected by Republicans and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kelly may depart in expected White House shakeup - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/4c38f72d4dee48c0b7b7e17fbfb5ee70</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECU9qNdj6p1Iz0aRXlWEk6gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:36:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/4c38f72d4dee48c0b7b7e17fbfb5ee70" target="_blank"&gt;Kelly may depart in expected White House shakeup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is inching closer to his long-teased major White House shake-up, gearing up for the twin challenges of battling for re-election and dealing with the Democrats' investigations once they take control of the House. The biggest piece of the shifting picture: Chief of Staff John Kelly's departure now appears certain. Trump announced Friday he was picking a new U.S. attorney genera l and a new ambassador to the U.N. , and at the same time two senior aides departed the White House to beef up his 2020 campaign. But the largest changes were still to come. Kel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Selective memory? George H. Bush’s passing elicits gushing tributes - RT</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZTvP6rWJ_dA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJNAK7hjXuG1H5bTPmha77gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwzoQo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:00:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZTvP6rWJ_dA" target="_blank"&gt;Selective memory? George H. Bush’s passing elicits gushing tributes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The passing of America's 41st President - George Herbert Walker #Bush - has led to an outpouring of honours and respect being paid. RT's Caleb Maupin looks at whether the assessment of his time in office, may have been tempered somewhat - by the current political climate... RT LIVE https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IFAcqaNzNSc Check out http://rt.com Subscribe to RT! http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=RussiaToday Like us on Facebook http://www.facebook.com/RTnews Follow us on VK https://vk.com/rt_international Follow us on Twitter http://twitter.com/RT_com Follow us on Instag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">RT</source></item><item><title>George HW Bush's funeral follows generations of tradition - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/george-hw-bush-funeral-follows-generations-of-tradition/10593202</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIe4nWTVcZM65gVfPikJ6iAqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:29:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/george-hw-bush-funeral-follows-generations-of-tradition/10593202" target="_blank"&gt;George HW Bush's funeral follows generations of tradition&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former President George HW Bush's state funeral encompassed four days of events, from his arrival in Washington to his burial in Texas. The guidelines for state funerals date back to the mid-1800s and have been shaped over time. Seating arrangements, for example, are detailed with precision, with the presidential party followed by chiefs of state, arranged alphabetically by the English spelling of their countries. Ronald Reagan's state funeral in 2004 was the first of its kind since Lyndon Johnson died in 1973. Gerald Ford's state funeral overlapped the end of 2006 and the beginning of 2007...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>The week in 25 photos - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/world/gallery/week-in-photos-1206/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELlu43jtr0WoMLV1WnNvR1sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:25:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/world/gallery/week-in-photos-1206/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The week in 25 photos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former US President George W. Bush speaks at the state funeral of his father, former US President George H.W. Bush, on Wednesday, December 5. "He showed me what it means to be a President who serves with integrity, leads with courage and acts with love in his heart for the citizens of our country," Bush said in his eulogy. See more photos of people paying their respects Alex Brandon/AP This aerial photo, taken on Friday, November 30, shows damage on Vine Road, south of Wasilla, Alaska, after a magnitude 7.0 earthquake. Marc Lester/AP The US Supreme Court, with newest member Brett Kavanaugh,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Texas Bids President George H.W. Bush Final Farewell - VOA News</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=27tCIP_F124</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAIo7n4HAyWkbx77FwyduT4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw78Uq</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:32:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=27tCIP_F124" target="_blank"&gt;Texas Bids President George H.W. Bush Final Farewell&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After formal services at the National Cathedral in Washington, the final journey for President George H.W. Bush takes place in the state that launched his political career, and where he is now finally laid to rest. VOA's Kane Farabaugh reports on how those in Texas participated in the final ceremonies to honor and remember their former president and war hero. Originally published at - https://www.voanews.com/a/texas-bids-president-george-h-w-bush-final-farewell/4690646.html&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Former U.S. Attorney General Barr may return to job - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/12/06/former-us-attorney-general-barr-may-retu?videoId=489229544</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGuscOIyW_qVS1UjdiFvN50qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:33:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/12/06/former-us-attorney-general-barr-may-retu?videoId=489229544" target="_blank"&gt;Former U.S. Attorney General Barr may return to job&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former U.S. Attorney General William Barr, who served under former President George H.W. Bush, is the leading candidate for the job as a permanent replacement for Jeff Sessions, a source familiar with the matter said on Thursday. Gavino Garay reports.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Analysis: Trump stayed under the radar this week but his fury is 'bubbling behind the scenes' - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/trumps-fury-bubbling-away-despite-staying-under-the-radar/10592812</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP0a0sPBHqgDYhXa87992PAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:01:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/trumps-fury-bubbling-away-despite-staying-under-the-radar/10592812" target="_blank"&gt;Analysis: Trump stayed under the radar this week but his fury is 'bubbling behind the scenes'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Washington bureau chief Zoe Daniel and Emily Olson "What does it tell you that the feel-good events in Washington these days are funerals?" asked journalist Susan Glasser in a piece for the New Yorker this week. Somehow, a politician's death — and the associated ritual of pomp, ceremony and complete cable news domination — has become a symbolic means of reminding the country "that civility is not a dirty word and that partisan combat is not a permanent state of being". The New York Times reports that US President Donald Trump was apparently proud of himself for staying under the radar wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Trump to Nominate William Barr as Attorney General - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-to-nominate-william-barr-as-attorney-general/4691027.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaN3IK4YEpXeIjUAgmtqioqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:08:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-to-nominate-william-barr-as-attorney-general/4691027.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump to Nominate William Barr as Attorney General&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former U.S. attorney general known for supporting sweeping presidential powers is President Donald Trump's choice to again run the U.S. Department of Justice. Trump said Friday that William Barr, who was attorney general during the administration of the late former President George H.W. Bush, is his selection, describing him as "a terrific man, a terrific person, a brilliant man." The president told reporters at the White House that Barr, a 68-year-old conservative Republican and corporate lawyer, "was my first choice from day one. Respected by Republicans and respected by Democrats." Lat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Trump signs funding stopgap, setting holiday fight on wall - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/080b66fe69a4420bb8c6ad20a18117aa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMpv_vElQmCxcpzCUgeaEY0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:06:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/080b66fe69a4420bb8c6ad20a18117aa" target="_blank"&gt;Trump signs funding stopgap, setting holiday fight on wall&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has signed a stopgap spending bill to fund key government departments for two-weeks, setting up a pre-Christmas showdown over border wall funding. Trump's signature on the measure keeps the government open through Dec. 21. Both houses of Congress passed the measure by voice vote on Thursday. Trump says wants the next funding package to include at least $5 billion for his proposed wall, something House Democratic leader Nancy Pelosi rejected Thursday. The stopgap bill avoided a partisan funding fight this week when Washington paused for ceremonies hon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The Leadership Lesson This Young Entrepreneur Learned From George H. W. Bush Will Make You Smile - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/johngreathouse/2018/12/06/the-leadership-lesson-this-young-entrepreneur-learned-from-george-h-w-bush-will-make-you-smile/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP_Dc9H04GmCBFkkPCaBY5QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johngreathouse/2018/12/06/the-leadership-lesson-this-young-entrepreneur-learned-from-george-h-w-bush-will-make-you-smile/" target="_blank"&gt;The Leadership Lesson This Young Entrepreneur Learned From George H. W. Bush Will Make You Smile&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before Dave Dutch was a serially successful CEO, he was a member of the US Navy Special Operations. In, Would You Risk Arrest To Reinforce Your Company’s Culture?, I recently recounted how Dave reinforced his company’s culture by not cutting his hair for over 16-months. He eventually sold that company for over $300 million. In an email in which he thanked me for writing the company culture article, he also included an insightful vignette about George H.W. Bush and how it impacted his leadership style throughout his startup career. I was so moved by the anecdote, I’m compelled to share it wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Flag-waving crowds in Texas watch Bush's funeral train - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/926b1491825d439f9f33a60138559278</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFCx8W9RiUo4qTsICj_xZlQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:10:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/926b1491825d439f9f33a60138559278" target="_blank"&gt;Flag-waving crowds in Texas watch Bush's funeral train&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flag waving-crowds lined the tracks as a special funeral train carried the flag-draped body of former President George H.W. Bush to College Station, Texas, where he'll be buried on the grounds of his presidential library. As the train passed through the towns a group of elementary students could be seen holding a banner that read "THANK YOU," firefighters saluted atop their truck on an overpass and a woman in a red hat held a sign that said "Rest in Peace George" with hearts. Here are some scenes along the route as the train went from the Houston suburb of Spring to College Station: ___ MAK...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Rosenstein, Justice Department vets celebrate Barr nomination - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/doj-rod-rosenstein-william-barr-nomination/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDn_zqqprDKgFwmt8z0CVkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:44:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/doj-rod-rosenstein-william-barr-nomination/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rosenstein, Justice Department vets celebrate Barr nomination&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Department veterans on Friday celebrated President Donald Trump's announcement that he would select William Barr, a member of the Justice Department's old guard and a former attorney general under George H.W. Bush, to be his next attorney general. Barr, who worked his way from a night school law student and up through the ranks of the Department of Justice, is widely viewed by legal observers as a deeply experienced attorney with bipartisan respect. Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein is said to be "elated" by the choice of Barr and former Attorney General Jeff Sessions has alway...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>🇺🇸 'A great-soldier statesman': US bids farewell to George HW Bush | Al Jazeeras English - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=edMoQLG1AWs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZuNyNv93N37_7pbmVwFwMqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwkOgB</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:54:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=edMoQLG1AWs" target="_blank"&gt;🇺🇸 'A great-soldier statesman': US bids farewell to George HW Bush | Al Jazeeras English&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The body of former US President George H W Bush has been flown to Texas where he will be buried this week. He died in his Houston home on Friday at the age of 94. Earlier, politicians past and present were among the mourners at a state funeral for the 41st president in Washington, DC. Al Jazeera's Kimberly Halkett reports from Washington, DC. - Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe - Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish - Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera - Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/ #GeorgeHWBush #GeorgeHWBush #41stUSPre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Trump picks former US attorney-general Barr to head Justice Department - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/trump-picks-former-us-attorney-general-barr-to-return/10596778</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKFiD8VNzXP7ze6VRrULc3MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:15:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/trump-picks-former-us-attorney-general-barr-to-return/10596778" target="_blank"&gt;Trump picks former US attorney-general Barr to head Justice Department&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump has chosen former US attorney-general William Barr to once again lead the Justice Department, a role that would put him in charge of the federal probe into Russian election interference. Key points: - Mr Barr previously served as attorney-general under the late president George HW Bush - If appointed, Mr Barr would have ultimate responsibility for the Russia probe - Mr Trump said Mr Barr was "my first choice from day one" If confirmed by the Senate, Mr Barr would take over from Matthew Whitaker, who has been serving in an acting capacity since Mr Trump forced out Jeff...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Former President George H.W. Bush laid to rest in Texas - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-bush/former-president-george-hw-bush-to-be-remembered-at-houston-funeral-idUSKBN1O513C</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAkj3RSQkZRhPrAW8A2SIsIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:08:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-bush/former-president-george-hw-bush-to-be-remembered-at-houston-funeral-idUSKBN1O513C" target="_blank"&gt;Former President George H.W. Bush laid to rest in Texas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former U.S. President George H.W. Bush was laid to rest at his presidential library in College Station, Texas, on Thursday, following funeral services at his longtime church in Houston. Bush's casket traveled in a special train car about an hour northwest from Houston to College Station and was then carried to the gravesite behind his library by a military honor guard, in a ceremony overseen by his son and former President George W. Bush. Bush, the 41st U.S. president, died last week in Texas at 94. His remains were flown to Texas on Wednesday following a state funeral at the Washington Nat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump to nominate William Barr as his next AG - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3gGrafcZJK0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGLYIqpevsll5_PQleNQLnkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6OVAw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:34:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3gGrafcZJK0" target="_blank"&gt;Trump to nominate William Barr as his next AG&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(7 Dec 2018) President Donald Trump says he will nominate William Barr to serve as his next Attorney General. Trump also says he'll nominate State Department spokeswoman Heather Nauert to be the next U.S. ambassador to the United Nations. (Dec. 7) Subscribe for more Breaking News: http://smarturl.it/AssociatedPress Website: https://apnews.com Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP Facebook: https://facebook.com/APNews Google+: https://plus.google.com/115892241801867723374 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/ ​ You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Bipartisan appeals to Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker to veto bills that would weaken incoming Democrat - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bipartisan-appeals-to-wisconsin-gov-scott-walker-to-veto-bills-that-would-weaken-incoming-democrat-2018-12-06</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAWqnGP2Hn7G-Ex4Z_coqToqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bipartisan-appeals-to-wisconsin-gov-scott-walker-to-veto-bills-that-would-weaken-incoming-democrat-2018-12-06" target="_blank"&gt;Bipartisan appeals to Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker to veto bills that would weaken incoming Democrat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASSOCIATED PRESS By Associated Press Critics say bills would mark the Republican as a sore loser Democratic state Sen. Tim Carpenter, left, questions a list of about 50 appointment referrals submitted to the State Senate at the Capitol in Madison, Wis., Tuesday. Associated Press MADISON, Wis. — A bipartisan group of political figures appealed to Gov. Scott Walker on Thursday to avoid staining his legacy and behaving like a sore loser by signing legislation that would weaken the powers of the Democrat who defeated him. Rather than notching another partisan victory in his final weeks in offic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>William Barr nominated as US attorney general - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/07/william-barr-nominated-us-attorney-general/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI5xzqm4l7gO2ngOdhRs6E0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:38:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/07/william-barr-nominated-us-attorney-general/" target="_blank"&gt;William Barr nominated as US attorney general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has announced he will nominate William Barr to be his new attorney general, a role which includes overseeing the investigation into Russian election meddling that continues to blight his presidency. Mr Barr, 68, held the position for two years under George W Bush, the former US president, and has voiced views on the Russia probe and other key areas which chime with Mr Trump’s stances. I am pleased to announce that I will be nominating The Honorable William P. Barr for the position of Attorney General of the United States. As the former AG for George H.W. Bush.... — Donald J. Tr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Secret Service detail for Bush, code name 'Timberwolf,' ends - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/1eb92801405a413ca57ccfcf7a4230d5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKLXzuQEvAjnOzCoAgf_EZMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:03:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/1eb92801405a413ca57ccfcf7a4230d5" target="_blank"&gt;Secret Service detail for Bush, code name 'Timberwolf,' ends&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;COLLEGE STATION, Texas (AP) — The U.S. Secret Service has ended its detail for George H.W. Bush after nearly 40 years of protecting the former president, who was known by the code name "Timberwolf." The agency says its security detail officially ended at 6 a.m. Friday "with no incidents to report" following Bush's burial Thursday at his presidential library at Texas A&amp;M University. In its final notification , the Bush Protective Division said: "You will be missed by all of us." Agents served as honorary pallbearers during some of this week's events honoring the 41st president. On Twitter, t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump's Justice Department Pick Has Criticized Special Counsel Probes - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-s-justice-department-pick-has-criticized-special-counsel-probes-/4691725.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPe3STZv3vXVBe22UNX7yjgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:29:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-s-justice-department-pick-has-criticized-special-counsel-probes-/4691725.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's Justice Department Pick Has Criticized Special Counsel Probes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By tapping former Attorney General William Barr to head the Justice Department again, President Donald Trump has picked a highly respected lawyer with a wealth of experience leading a major government department and overseeing high-profile independent investigations. But Barr, 68, who led the Justice Department from 1991 to 1993 under the late President George H.W. Bush, has long been skeptical of sweeping probes of government officials and voiced support for a strong executive branch. While at the Justice Department, Barr oversaw two independent investigations. The first, a sprawling inqui...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Private, graveside service ends; Bush buried - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/a241ee5a94e04e69bc84d4234e39d55b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEXLcj94UC9ivFvkfxXHHlUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:15:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/a241ee5a94e04e69bc84d4234e39d55b" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Private, graveside service ends; Bush buried&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — The Latest on events honoring former President George H.W. Bush (all times local): 5:25 p.m. Texas A&amp;M says the private, graveside service for George H.W. Bush's family members has ended and the former president has been buried. Thursday evening's ceremony concludes days of funeral activities honoring the 41st president. After lying in state at the U.S. Capitol and a funeral at Washington's National Cathedral, Bush had a funeral at the Houston church where his family worshipped. His remains then rode on a special funeral train to College Station, where he was buried at his pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>A look back at George HW Bush's presidency; was it really a more civilised era? | Planet America - ABC News</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zh8fA0fvPwA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENrzQT-FCcEuLfWCXeqmh10qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDCnyhw</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:27:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zh8fA0fvPwA" target="_blank"&gt;A look back at George HW Bush's presidency; was it really a more civilised era? | Planet America&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week on Planet America: Death of a President; remembering the good and the bad of America’s 41st Commander in Chief - was it really a more civilised era? Also, why are Americans dying younger? And what will Mueller do about Roger Stone? For more from ABC News, click here: http://www.abc.net.au/news/ Subscribe to us on YouTube: http://ab.co/1svxLVE You can also like us on Facebook: http://facebook.com/abcnews.au Or follow us on Instagram: http://instagram.com/abcnews_au Or even on Twitter: http://twitter.com/abcnews&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Trump picks attorney general and U.N. envoy in fresh staff shake-up - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-idUSKBN1O61YN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrJFrWAUVrSesDVbt1bqPcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:30:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-idUSKBN1O61YN" target="_blank"&gt;Trump picks attorney general and U.N. envoy in fresh staff shake-up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In another senior staff shake-up inside his often turbulent administration, U.S. President Donald Trump said on Friday he has picked the two people he wants to be the next U.S. attorney general and the next U.S. ambassador to the United Nations. He said he will nominate William Barr, who was attorney general under former President George H.W. Bush in the 1990s, to fill that top job again at the U.S. Justice Department. Barr would replace Acting Attorney General Matthew Whitaker, who has been in that position since Trump forced out Jeff Sessions as attorney general a month ago. Trump said he...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump Announces William Barr As Attorney General Nominee - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/william-barr-attorney-general-trump_us_5c0a8560e4b04046345b936b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK1_9VBszyFeXTKRss9VnfEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:44:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/william-barr-attorney-general-trump_us_5c0a8560e4b04046345b936b" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Announces William Barr As Attorney General Nominee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump confirmed Friday that he plans to nominate William Barr as attorney general, after pushing out Jeff Sessions last month. Trump initially replaced Sessions with acting Attorney General Matthew Whitaker, whose appointment came under scrutiny amid questions of its legality. Barr previously served as attorney general from 1991 to 1993 under President George H.W. Bush. After leaving government, he worked as a corporate attorney, including as general counsel for Verizon until 2008. (In 2015, Verizon purchased AOL, now known as Oath, HuffPost’s parent company.) While in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Bird's eye-view of George HW Bush funeral train - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0kbvL98zpbo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGZjf3IdLOuWln5RR45yCaUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6OVAw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:25:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0kbvL98zpbo" target="_blank"&gt;Bird's eye-view of George HW Bush funeral train&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(7 Dec 2018) A special funeral train carries the casket of former President George H.W. Bush a final stop near his burial site in Texas. The blue and gray locomotive was painted to resemble Air Force One. (Dec. 7) Subscribe for more Breaking News: http://smarturl.it/AssociatedPress Website: https://apnews.com Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP Facebook: https://facebook.com/APNews Google+: https://plus.google.com/115892241801867723374 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/ ​ You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/574b06d669031266da41ab927...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>AP Top Stories December 6 P - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P07G_WI3oeo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMqAm5xkhQWlcYtjqa2zaukqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6OVAw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:42:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P07G_WI3oeo" target="_blank"&gt;AP Top Stories December 6 P&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(6 Dec 2018) Here are the top stories for Thursday, December 6th: George H.W. Bush brought to final resting place; Huawei CFO arrested; disciplinary trial set for NYC officer accused in death; Cubans get access to 3G internet. Subscribe for more Breaking News: http://smarturl.it/AssociatedPress Website: https://apnews.com Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP Facebook: https://facebook.com/APNews Google+: https://plus.google.com/115892241801867723374 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/ ​&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>LIVE: The State Funeral for George H.W. Bush at Washington National Cathedral - VOA News</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=50RTXArJmnY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDu_7OydOm79ujkZ0G2rmDQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw78Uq</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:41:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=50RTXArJmnY" target="_blank"&gt;LIVE: The State Funeral for George H.W. Bush at Washington National Cathedral&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The State Funeral for George H.W. Bush at Washington National Cathedral&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Reba McEntire, Oak Ridge Boys sing at Bush's Texas funeral - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/e9d7b446b02e4498a2773066c960b45a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBbN8hZkTovz1ETtmLlKnN4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:07:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/e9d7b446b02e4498a2773066c960b45a" target="_blank"&gt;Reba McEntire, Oak Ridge Boys sing at Bush's Texas funeral&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — Reba McEntire has sung "The Lord's Prayer" at the Houston funeral service of former President George H.W. Bush. The Grammy winner on Thursday followed the Oak Ridge Boys, who were one of the president's favorite musical acts and who sang "Amazing Grace" during the service at St. Martin's Episcopal Church in Houston. Celebrities, including actor-politician Arnold Schwarzenegger, were among the mourners at the church where the Bush family worships. Thursday's ceremony was final public farewell to the 41st president. Bush will be buried during a private service later Thursday at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump picks former Attorney General Barr to return to head Justice Department - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-barr-idUSKBN1O61PR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVIeaal5_1b11G4KyDgtZ8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:20:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-barr-idUSKBN1O61PR" target="_blank"&gt;Trump picks former Attorney General Barr to return to head Justice Department&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump said on Friday he had chosen former U.S. Attorney General William Barr to once again lead the Justice Department, a role that would put him in charge of the federal probe into Russian election interference. If confirmed by the Senate, Barr would take over from Matthew Whitaker, who has been serving in an acting capacity since Trump forced out Jeffrey Sessions a month ago. Whitaker had been Sessions' chief of staff. Barr was "my first choice from day one," and "a terrific man, a terrific person, a brilliant man," Trump said, speaking to reporters outside the White Hous...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump brags about approval rating from 'biased' polling firm hours after George HW Bush funeral - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-approval-rating-george-hw-bush-funeral-latest-polls-rasmussen-reports-nate-silver-a8671131.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECTzaO2JUY3NzC62DzIvt3QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-approval-rating-george-hw-bush-funeral-latest-polls-rasmussen-reports-nate-silver-a8671131.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump brags about approval rating from 'biased' polling firm hours after George HW Bush funeral&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump has bragged about his approval rating using a contentious poll that generally skews in his favour, and pegs his support anywhere between seven and 11 per cent higher than other surveys. Mr Trump tweeted that he had a 50 per cent approval rating on Wednesday, a message he displayed in an image with big, bold lettering. Much smaller was the source, Rasmussen Reports, which has generally shown a higher rate of approval than other outlets. He did so just hours after attending the funeral for former President George HW Bush. Other polling firms — which have conducted polls...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>George H.W. Bush will journey to his final resting place on a train whose engine is named for him - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/us/george-bush-train-union-pacific-funeral-trnd/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKC_tCR5Fx1BYqSShI8lD-gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:20:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/us/george-bush-train-union-pacific-funeral-trnd/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;George H.W. Bush will journey to his final resting place on a train whose engine is named for him&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;George H.W. Bush's journey to his final resting place will be aboard a train whose engine was specifically built to honor his life. After a funeral route that will take the late President by plane from Houston to Washington D.C. and back again, a Union Pacific train led by a locomotive dubbed the "Bush 4141" will carry him to the George H.W. Bush Presidential Library in College Station, Texas. The Bush 4141 is a rare locomotive that was commissioned to honor the former president in 2005. One of only a handful of Union Pacific trains to bear a color scheme other than the company's traditiona...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Thousands salute Bush funeral train 4141 on final Texas ride - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/493dc3946477427ca206a72134bf6f47</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEKRIhqLTXRxsw4PTyoQNjcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:48:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/493dc3946477427ca206a72134bf6f47" target="_blank"&gt;Thousands salute Bush funeral train 4141 on final Texas ride&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;COLLEGE STATION, Texas (AP) — Thousands waved and cheered along the route as funeral train No. 4141 — for the 41st president — carried George H.W. Bush's remains to their final resting place on Thursday, his last journey as a week of national remembrance took on a decidedly personal feel in an emotional home state farewell. Some people laid coins along the tracks that wound through small town Texas so a 420,000-pound locomotive pulling the nation's first funeral train in nearly half a century could crunch them into souvenirs. Others snapped pictures or crowded for views so close that police...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Republican congressman falsely claims George Soros 'assisted the Nazis' in Fox interview - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/republican-george-soros-nazi-fox-news-interview-world-war-two-congressman-louie-gohmert-a8672266.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG8mssrh--RqFvCYrlFtMWUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/republican-george-soros-nazi-fox-news-interview-world-war-two-congressman-louie-gohmert-a8672266.html" target="_blank"&gt;Republican congressman falsely claims George Soros 'assisted the Nazis' in Fox interview&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican congressman Louie Gohmert has been condemned for falsely claiming philanthropist George Soros “helped take the property” of fellow Jews during World War II. Mr Soros’ Open Society Foundations organisation called on the Texas politician to apologise and accused him of making a “disturbing and false antisemitic slur". Mr Gohmert’s remarks came during a Fox Business interview in which he was asked about Google’s plans in China, but went off on a tangent about Mr Soros instead. “George Soros is supposed to be Jewish, but you wouldn’t know it from the damage he’s inflicted on Israel, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>George HW Bush funeral: 1,000 mourners descend on Texas for final goodbye to president 'carved in hard granite of history' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/george-hw-bush-funeral-houston-texas-campy-stream-navy-national-cathedral-a8671521.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENCZweIBsVDjel8IWm9td6IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/george-hw-bush-funeral-houston-texas-campy-stream-navy-national-cathedral-a8671521.html" target="_blank"&gt;George HW Bush funeral: 1,000 mourners descend on Texas for final goodbye to president 'carved in hard granite of history'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deeds that George HW Bush are carved into the "granite of history" former Secretary of State James Baker said as Texas said goodbye to one of its most famous residents. A day after thousands of Americans and every living president mourned the death of Mr Bush at the National Cathedral in Washington, friends and family were given a chance to pay their final respects to the former president. More than 1,000 mourners sang “America the Beautiful” at St. Martin’s Episcopal Church on Thursday, where the 41st commander in chief, who died last week in Texas at age 94, worshipped for over 50 yea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Trump says he’ll nominate Barr to serve as attorney general - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-says-hell-nominate-barr-to-serve-as-attorney-general-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECCmd54CIVCgGPEJR_JvhggqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-says-hell-nominate-barr-to-serve-as-attorney-general-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says he’ll nominate Barr to serve as attorney general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASSOCIATED PRESS By Associated Press William Barr Bloomberg President Donald Trump said Friday he will nominate William Barr, the late President George H.W. Bush’s attorney general, to serve in the same role. Trump made the announcement while departing the White House for a trip to Missouri. He called Barr “a terrific man” and “one of the most respected jurists in the country.” “I think he will serve with great distinction,” Trump said. If confirmed by the Senate, Barr would succeed Attorney General Jeff Sessions, who was forced out by Trump in November following an acrimonious tenure. Sess...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Bush’s greatest virtue was experience - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/839121e0-f9a5-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjz0uaX6uxROT8cB79pn48qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/839121e0-f9a5-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Bush’s greatest virtue was experience&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF Stone once said that funerals were “always an occasion for pious lying”. George HW Bush’s was an exception. Regardless of politics, virtually everyone who dealt with America’s 41st president was struck by his strong sense of personal decency. Regardless of his interlocutor, Bush Sr never short-changed courtesy. “I am a conservative,” he once said, “but I am not a nut about it.” Our standards have fallen. Shortly before the funeral, I tweeted out a prediction: “If Trump doesn’t heckle, spontaneously combust or wander out of the cathedral at the wrong moment, pundits will proclaim how pres...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Political GIFs of the week - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/political-gifs-of-the-week/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGvlOpcMMuY6pivq0dbH42UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:46:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/political-gifs-of-the-week/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Political GIFs of the week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While most of the nation's attention was focused on honoring former President George H.W. Bush this week, the gears of government slowed, but by no means did they grind to a halt. Here are a few things you might have missed. This moment between George W. Bush and Michelle Obama was reminiscent of a moment the duo shared at Sen. John McCain's funeral earlier this year. Friends are the family you choose, y'all. Now that the 2018 election is (mostly) in the rear-view mirror, we're focusing in on 2020. It's less than 700 days away, after all! Former Florida gubernatorial hopeful Andrew Gillum m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>President Bush's Statesman Legacy Complicated by Divisive Politics - VOA News</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ui5AAlI6Rhw</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG_4u95gn2Dd-aUiu0ZNWzcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw78Uq</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:57:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ui5AAlI6Rhw" target="_blank"&gt;President Bush's Statesman Legacy Complicated by Divisive Politics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former President H.W. Bush managed the peaceful aftermath of the Soviet Union's breakup in 1991 and used American military force to oppose Iraqi aggression. Yet, as VOA's Brian Padden reports, Bush's legacy as a successful foreign policy president is complicated by the hardline campaign politics he practiced at home and by how the Republican Party under President Donald Trump seems to have turned away from his internationalist world view. Originally published at - https://www.voanews.com/a/president-bush-statesman-legacy-complicated-by-divisive-politics/4690671.html&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Thousands of women and girls are being trafficked from Myanmar to China and forced to marry, study finds - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/forced-marriage-trafficking-victims-children-vulnerable-china-myanmar-report-a8672451.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIqsaaqtbM52XiZGXhx2UYkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/forced-marriage-trafficking-victims-children-vulnerable-china-myanmar-report-a8672451.html" target="_blank"&gt;Thousands of women and girls are being trafficked from Myanmar to China and forced to marry, study finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of vulnerable women and girls are being trafficked from Myanmar to China and forced to marry and bear children, new research has found. Researchers surveyed 400 women in 40 sites in Myanmar and China, estimating more than 7,400 women and girls were victims of forced marriage in the area and more than 5,000 were forced to bear children with their Chinese husbands. The study, carried out by the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health and Kachin Women’s Association Thailand, also came to the conclusion there were “likely many more victims” of such trafficking beyond the area ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Must-watch videos of the week - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/app-news-section/videos-of-the-week-mobile-december-7/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHL05zO7Dafk4O6bZC5HbooqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:49:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/app-news-section/videos-of-the-week-mobile-december-7/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Must-watch videos of the week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A heartwarming moment at a historic funeral, a scary plane landing attempt and a life-saving shove caught on camera. These are the videos you don't want to miss this week. Any way the wind blows Sometimes the wind is not at your back -- it's all around you. Video shows the harrowing moment an Emirates Boeing 777 attempted to land in the United Kingdom during high crosswinds, but things did not go as planned. Video Watch dramatic Emirates plane landing CNN The friendship keeps sailing Former President George W. Bush thought ahead to keep a sweet tradition alive, even during his father's fune...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump says some GOP candidates 'choke like dogs' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/donald-trump-kansas-city-candidates-choke-like-dogs/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO7Z4jVhV5lXG4OiVI3ly8EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:40:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/donald-trump-kansas-city-candidates-choke-like-dogs/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says some GOP candidates 'choke like dogs'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump lamented the Republican Party's candidate selection for the midterm elections during a wide-ranging speech at the Project Safe Neighborhoods National Conference in Kansas City, Missouri, Friday afternoon. Touting Republican Sen.-elect Josh Hawley's November victory in the race for a US Senate seat in Missouri, Trump referenced some candidates who "choke" on the campaign trail. "You pick somebody. Looks good, sounds good," the President said of backing candidates. "Then they choke. They choke like dogs." "And then you say, 'What did I do? I picked the wrong person,' " ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Thousands line Bush casket train route - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zR0RYnGPyH4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFE1Of7YCIBEtYVd09nA2dQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6OVAw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:56:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zR0RYnGPyH4" target="_blank"&gt;Thousands line Bush casket train route&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(6 Dec 2018) Crowds have lined the route of the special funeral train that is taking former President George H.W. Bush to the city where he'll be laid to rest. (Dec. 6) Subscribe for more Breaking News: http://smarturl.it/AssociatedPress Website: https://apnews.com Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP Facebook: https://facebook.com/APNews Google+: https://plus.google.com/115892241801867723374 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/ ​ You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/8bedc595eec73a64ec3727eb3013590b&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>For Trump, a first look at what presidential veneration could be - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/donald-trump-bush-funeral/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVwVpLPwbHesh--ambxTl4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/donald-trump-bush-funeral/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;For Trump, a first look at what presidential veneration could be&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As he listened to military choirs and honor guards venerate George H.W. Bush on Wednesday, President Donald Trump found himself contemplating the vast scale of the job he holds --and wondering how his own legacy might compare. In private this week, the current commander-in-chief has expressed amazement at the number of events designed to commemorate Bush, a one-term president who has been hailed as an even-handed bastion of civility. Seeing the traditional rites of a state funeral up close impressed Trump, a president highly attuned to ceremony and pomp, according to people he spoke with af...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>News guide: George HW Bush's final farewell, burial in Texas - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/50f9e16bbe0f4ff39ac8bf044e1c2506</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJrz9181FI2zsQ3aGzJmAFIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:45:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/50f9e16bbe0f4ff39ac8bf044e1c2506" target="_blank"&gt;News guide: George HW Bush's final farewell, burial in Texas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — Former President George H.W. Bush will be buried in Texas after a funeral service at the church he attended for many years and a special memorial train that will carry his casket. The nation's 41st president died last week at age 94. His casket returned to Houston after a state funeral Wednesday at Washington National Cathedral. Bush had been lying in repose at St. Martin's Episcopal Church in Houston, where a procession of mourners paid their respects overnight. A look at Thursday's events: ___ THE SERVICE An estimated 1,200 mourners attended a service at St. Martin's, which...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump’s Evangelical Supporters On Apostles’ Creed Gaffe: ‘I Can't Sing Either’ - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trumps-evangelical-supporters-on-apostles-creed-gaffe-i-cant-sing-either_us_5c09b1fce4b0b6cdaf5d7920</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKjlIPivqxcQnza7Jh7YS48qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:18:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trumps-evangelical-supporters-on-apostles-creed-gaffe-i-cant-sing-either_us_5c09b1fce4b0b6cdaf5d7920" target="_blank"&gt;Trump’s Evangelical Supporters On Apostles’ Creed Gaffe: ‘I Can't Sing Either’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When President Donald Trump and first lady Melania Trump neglected to say a core Christian prayer during former President George H.W. Bush’s funeral this week, indignant tweeters were quick to cite it as proof that Trump isn’t the great defender of Christianity some evangelicals have made him out to be. But the Trumps’ failure to recite the Apostles’ Creed or to sing some hymns during the service wasn’t a big deal to some of the president’s staunchest evangelical supporters. Franklin Graham, son of the late evangelist Billy Graham and a longtime Trump ally, came to the president’s defense o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Pelosi takes hard line on paying for Trump's border wall - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/e3fd315c66554c22bfdf97710e0df711</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_j_CgO0Wb7lQhXKT1UDdAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:27:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/e3fd315c66554c22bfdf97710e0df711" target="_blank"&gt;Pelosi takes hard line on paying for Trump's border wall&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democratic leader Nancy Pelosi on Thursday rejected the idea of paying for President Donald Trump's border wall in exchange for helping hundreds of thousands of young immigrants avoid deportation. Funding for the wall — a top Trump priority — and legal protections for so-called Dreamers, a key Democratic goal, should not be linked, Pelosi said. "They're two different subjects," she said. Her comments came as the House and Senate approved a stopgap bill Thursday to keep the government funded through Dec. 21. The measure, approved by voice votes in near-empty chambers,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Navy jets fly over George H.W. Bush burial - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/06/navy-jets-perform-flyover-at-george-hw-bush-burial-sitroom-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENoH6d1X2Vy1XLZ2rAJlH1UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:44:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/06/navy-jets-perform-flyover-at-george-hw-bush-burial-sitroom-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Navy jets fly over George H.W. Bush burial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following a fly over by a number of US Navy jets, the casket of President George H.W. Bush is carried through military honor guard cordon. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Bernie Sanders Dings Donald Trump With 'Honest President' Tribute To George H.W. Bush - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bernie-sanders-donald-trump-honest-president_us_5c0a4e0ee4b04046345afab8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDeicI8hsYZbtqKZPWIGC8AqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:06:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bernie-sanders-donald-trump-honest-president_us_5c0a4e0ee4b04046345afab8" target="_blank"&gt;Bernie Sanders Dings Donald Trump With 'Honest President' Tribute To George H.W. Bush&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) knocked President Donald Trump at the same time as he paid tribute to late former President George H.W. Bush on Thursday’s broadcast of “The Late Show.” Sanders told host Stephen Colbert that “yes, of course I disagreed” with Bush on policies. “But he was an honest man, he was a decent man, he loved his country very much and, you know, we wish that we could have president who is honest back in the White House again,” he added. Sanders also updated Colbert on the rumors that he’s planning a presidential run against Trump in 2020. “The answer is, look, when you run...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump Today: President blasts Mueller in tweetstorm and taps Barr, Nauert for posts - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-today-president-blasts-mueller-in-tweetstorm-and-taps-barr-nauert-for-posts-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELnDppqG9xsSEnUn8xY6C1UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-today-president-blasts-mueller-in-tweetstorm-and-taps-barr-nauert-for-posts-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Today: President blasts Mueller in tweetstorm and taps Barr, Nauert for posts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRUMP TODAY By Robert Schroeder China trade talks ‘going very well,’ Trump tweets after volatile week for markets President Donald Trump speaks to the media before boarding Marine One to depart from the White House on Friday. Getty Images President Donald Trump on Friday freshly attacked the Russia investigation as Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s office was expected to release details about former Trump associates, and said he’s nominating William Barr as attorney general and Heather Nauert as U.S. ambassador to the United Nations. TRUMP SUGGESTS ROSENSTEIN CONFLICTED In a barrage of tweet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>How Obamas greeted Trump at funeral - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/05/trump-george-h-w-bush-funeral-presidents-club-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZwWSgNAqqe8PijzVkKymgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:32:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/05/trump-george-h-w-bush-funeral-presidents-club-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;How Obamas greeted Trump at funeral&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Trump and First Lady Melania Trump attended the funeral for former President George H.W. Bush and sat in the same row with other former presidents. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rain doesn't stop Texans from seeing 'Bush 4141' - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XZWviMMPbIk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDbUKJ47i5Sr-WwoI5qWxpYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6OVAw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:53:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XZWviMMPbIk" target="_blank"&gt;Rain doesn't stop Texans from seeing 'Bush 4141'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(6 Dec 2018) Despite periodic rains, hundreds carrying American flags gathered on either side of the train tracks in Navasota, Texas, to watch the “Bush 4141” go by. (Dec. 6) Subscribe for more Breaking News: http://smarturl.it/AssociatedPress Website: https://apnews.com Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP Facebook: https://facebook.com/APNews Google+: https://plus.google.com/115892241801867723374 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/ ​ You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/0f305ac661fb520c79fafb6fab1d26c2&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Bush Arrives at Presidential Library for Burial - VOA News</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8HtW6QDhI_c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDHiGzn0LhVFlV2aFtPYBakqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw78Uq</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:18:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8HtW6QDhI_c" target="_blank"&gt;Bush Arrives at Presidential Library for Burial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former President George H.W. Bush's casket has arrived for burial in his family's plot on the grounds of his presidential library in Texas. Bush will be buried during a private service Thursday, ending nearly a week of services honoring the life of the 41st president. He will be laid to rest alongside his wife, Barbara Bush, and their daughter Robin, who died at age 3 of leukemia in 1953. (AP)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>At second memorial service, Bush remembered for humility and humor - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/george-hw-bush-houston-funeral-memorial-service/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEo6C1r0Tu-Tz4Yksy8bS1QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:36:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/george-hw-bush-houston-funeral-memorial-service/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;At second memorial service, Bush remembered for humility and humor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former President George H.W. Bush was remembered Thursday as a man of humility, honor and humor at the Bushes' family church in Houston, providing the nation with a last farewell before he begins his journey to his final resting place. Family, friends, politicians, musicians, actors and athletes filled the pews of the St. Martin's Episcopal Church to say goodbye to the 41st president with heartfelt praises and gospel music, as well as some moments of levity. "I must begin with an apology. Jefe, I'm about to do something you always hated and that your mother always told you not to do: Brag a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Don Lemon Says Smack-Talking Trump Should've Skipped Bush's Funeral - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/don-lemon-chris-cuomo-trump-bush-funeral_us_5c08ad8ae4b0bf813ef3f797</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC8rK41UvlUeDmdNajpl9QYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:08:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/don-lemon-chris-cuomo-trump-bush-funeral_us_5c08ad8ae4b0bf813ef3f797" target="_blank"&gt;Don Lemon Says Smack-Talking Trump Should've Skipped Bush's Funeral&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN host Don Lemon tore into President Donald Trump Wednesday night for attending the funeral of George H.W. Bush. Trump, who was seated next to the Obamas and Clintons at the Washington National Cathedral, has repeatedly attacked the Bush family, including the 41st president. Going head to head with fellow CNN anchor Chris Cuomo, Lemon argued that Trump’s attendance wasn’t a show of respect for Bush, but the opposite. “I don’t think it’s respect for the human being if you talk smack about them,” Lemon said. “If you say the nastiest things about them, if you treat them as subhuman, and then...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Congress moves to avert immediate shutdown with two-week funding extension - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/government-funding-extension-shutdown-fight-congress/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN-KN1h3cP4RGkzlvcPFwVcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:32:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/government-funding-extension-shutdown-fight-congress/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Congress moves to avert immediate shutdown with two-week funding extension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congress approved a two-week extension on Thursday for a key government funding deadline, setting up a showdown over spending just days before Christmas that could trigger a partial government shutdown later this month. The stopgap spending measure, which now heads to the White House for President Donald Trump's signature, pushes the deadline when funding will expire for several government agencies from December 7 to December 21. If Trump signs the measure, lawmakers will have averted a partial shutdown this week, but the threat of a potential shutdown still looms on the horizon. Lawmakers ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Major search underway after two US military planes crash into Pacific Ocean - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/us-military-marine-plane-crash-pacific-ocean-japan-search-missing-latest-a8670281.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtbFkuSqxESaaVgedFGiQQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/us-military-marine-plane-crash-pacific-ocean-japan-search-missing-latest-a8670281.html" target="_blank"&gt;Major search underway after two US military planes crash into Pacific Ocean&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A major search is underway after two US Marine planes collided mid-air and crashed into the Pacific Ocean off Japan's south-western coast. Rescuers have so far found two of the seven crew members from an F/A-18 fighter jet and a KC-130 refuelling aircraft. One of the crew members was described as being in a stable condition while details about the second have not yet been released. The jets crashed on 6 December at 2am during a regular refuelling training exercise. . The planes took off from their base in Iwakuni, near Hiroshima in western Japan and crashed 200 miles off the coast, accordin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item></channel></rss>