<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Xiaomi - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR2cyT1RVMVloSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-ET&amp;gl=ET&amp;ceid=ET:en</link><language>en-ET</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:48:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECs8OiMwxPuwcZzcG4cRAdMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes no notch in the Galaxy S10, the 5G S10 confirmed for America, the OnePlus 5G heading to the UK, three new Nokia handsets, a review of the Pocophone F1, Huawei’s ongoing security issues, and an innovation award for the Pixel 3 and 3XL. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). No Notch, But There Will Be A Hole, In The New Galaxy S10 Samsung appe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>China's Xiaomi takes lead over Apple as top seller of wearable technology globally - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/04/chinas-xiaomi-takes-lead-apple-top-seller-wearable-technology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPbjZfrDpoAf3KsArbOjGUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:46:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/04/chinas-xiaomi-takes-lead-apple-top-seller-wearable-technology/" target="_blank"&gt;China's Xiaomi takes lead over Apple as top seller of wearable technology globally&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese smartphone specialist Xiaomi has taken a lead over Apple as the world’s largest manufacturer of wearables, according to new figures from an industry analyst. A report from the International Data Corporation found that Xiaomi took top position in the third quarter of 2018 following positive sales of its Mi Band 3, a fitness tracker. Xiaomi’s push into markets such as India, Europe and the Middle East has been attributed to its overtaking of Apple. The share of the company’s deliveries within its home market has dropped from 80pc to 61pc as its international expansion plans pick up pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Oppo R17 Pro Review: The World's Fastest Charging Phone - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/12/05/oppo-r17-pro-review-the-worlds-fastest-charging-phone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJoY6kkbTRtA6Cs0CJ-gDosqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/12/05/oppo-r17-pro-review-the-worlds-fastest-charging-phone/" target="_blank"&gt;Oppo R17 Pro Review: The World's Fastest Charging Phone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Oppo R17 Pro with its gorgeous gradient-colored back. Most Chinese smartphone brands nowadays pump out four, five, or six devices a year, to a market that’s already beyond saturate. Many of these manufacturers barely differentiate each of these handsets, so much so that they tend to get lost in the noise and are forgotten quickly. However Oppo, for the most part, has done a solid job of making sure each release is worth covering, with at least one head-turning feature. The Find X, for example, was an absolute stunner in design and craftsmanship and will likely end up in one of the top t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Former YY CTO Gets $70 Million In US-China Deal For His New Voice Chat App From Xiaomi's VC Firm - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccafannin/2018/11/30/former-yy-cto-gets-70-million-in-us-china-deal-for-his-new-voice-chat-app-from-xiaomis-vc-firm/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAB4uobA6LDFr8YRuk1u580qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccafannin/2018/11/30/former-yy-cto-gets-70-million-in-us-china-deal-for-his-new-voice-chat-app-from-xiaomis-vc-firm/" target="_blank"&gt;Former YY CTO Gets $70 Million In US-China Deal For His New Voice Chat App From Xiaomi's VC Firm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Live streaming with voice chat is taking off Photo credit: Getty U.S.-China trade winds are prominent in a recent $70 million cross-border investment in cloud communications company Agora.io in Santa Clara and Shanghai. New York hedge fund Coatue Management, an increasingly active tech investor in cutting-edge startups, led the deal along with SIG and China investors Morningside and Shunwei Capital. Tony Zhao, founder and CEO of Agora, brings China and U.S. experience to his latest startup from roles as former CTO of Chinese social media giant YY and founding engineer at WebEx Communicat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nokia 7.1 Review: King Of The Middle Of The Road - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/02/nokia-7-1-review-hmdglobal-android-androidone-specifications/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL7ztJsannlHG2kTaAvBE_sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 01:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/02/nokia-7-1-review-hmdglobal-android-androidone-specifications/" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia 7.1 Review: King Of The Middle Of The Road&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not everyone wants a high-end flagship smartphone. Not everyone wants to pay the high cost to own one of these computational monsters outright or can budget for two years of contract payments. Even options such as the OnePlus 6T or the Xiaomi Mi8 Pro can be seen as overkill for people who just want ‘a decent smartphone’ to get them through the day. The rise in price of the flagship iPhone and Galaxy handsets have left a number of spaces between the high flyers and the ‘as low a price as you can go’ market. In here you will find the affordable flagships from the aforementioned OnePlus and X...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: New Galaxy Details Leak, Nokia 9's Monster Camera, OnePlus 7 Fights OnePlus 5G - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/23/android-google-news-headlines-samsung-galaxy-s10-nokia9-oneplus7-mi-xiaomi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDlUX6Z_GsYndvYLeJuSbkMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/23/android-google-news-headlines-samsung-galaxy-s10-nokia9-oneplus7-mi-xiaomi/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: New Galaxy Details Leak, Nokia 9's Monster Camera, OnePlus 7 Fights OnePlus 5G&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes five lenses for Nokia, six lenses for Samsung, a new OnePlus 5G handset, leaked images of the Pixel 3 Lite, the UK’s first Mi Store from Xiaomi, and Microsoft’s latest fitness feature in its Android launcher. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). How Many Lenses? While the Galaxy S10 likely to make up the bulk of Samsungs’s high-end handset ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>OnePlus 6T Review: Competitors Have Caught Up In Value, But OnePlus Software Still King - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/22/oneplus-6t-review-competition-have-caught-up-in-value-but-oneplus-software-still-king/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECVMFsGN2osEfA5lkyveg1cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 08:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/22/oneplus-6t-review-competition-have-caught-up-in-value-but-oneplus-software-still-king/" target="_blank"&gt;OnePlus 6T Review: Competitors Have Caught Up In Value, But OnePlus Software Still King&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The OnePlus 6T has a 6.4-inch OLED display. The OnePlus 6T is the fifth phone from the upstart brand I’ve tested in a professional capacity, and this is the toughest one to judge. It’s not because the 6T isn’t good, or a step backwards. No, it’s the best OnePlus phone yet. But it’s trickier this time around because circumstances around the phone have changed. For years, OnePlus phones were undoubtedly the best value on the market. Other phones that ran on the same Snapdragon chipset almost always cost several hundred dollars more, and other phones in the mid-tier market were significantly l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>China's Xiaomi swings to net profit in third-quarter on robust sales in India, Europe - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-xiaomi-results-idUSKCN1NO13E</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH1w-ZRrDcJid8DTshLqeJYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 11:08:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-xiaomi-results-idUSKCN1NO13E" target="_blank"&gt;China's Xiaomi swings to net profit in third-quarter on robust sales in India, Europe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese smartphone maker Xiaomi Inc said on Monday it swung to a net profit in the third quarter, beating analyst estimates, driven by robust sales in India and Europe. Profit for the three months through September reached 2.48 billion yuan ($357.23 million), versus an 11 billion yuan loss in the same period a year earlier. That compared with a 1.92 billion yuan average of five analyst estimates compiled by Refinitiv Eikon. Xiaomi also said operating profit sank 38.4 percent to 3.59 billion yuan in the third quarter. Revenue rose 49.1 percent to 50.85 billion yuan. The mixed results come am...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Wednesday Tech Wrap: Facebook's Digital Worlds, Apple 'Prepping 3 iPhones,' Xiaomi's Mi 6 - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/parmyolson/2017/04/19/facebooks-apple-iphones-xiaomi-mi6-baidu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJiF3d_5wG5uYDdRmlzQrDsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 15:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/parmyolson/2017/04/19/facebooks-apple-iphones-xiaomi-mi6-baidu/" target="_blank"&gt;Wednesday Tech Wrap: Facebook's Digital Worlds, Apple 'Prepping 3 iPhones,' Xiaomi's Mi 6&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN JOSE, CA – APRIL 18: Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg delivers the keynote address at Facebook’s F8 Developer Conference on April 18, 2017 at McEnery Convention Center in San Jose, California. The conference will explore Facebook’s new technology initiatives and products. (Photo by Justin Sullivan/Getty Images) Facebook has been holding its annual F8 conference this week and Mark Zuckerberg has been talking a great deal about virtual and augmented reality. During his keynote he unveiled AR Studio, an open source platform that developers so that Facebook’s mobile app can turn into a home for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi on comeback trail as smartphone sales soar - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/bd3e3af2-6ac9-11e7-b9c7-15af748b60d0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECa1GK7utvqGssux0PSMEfoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 02:16:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/bd3e3af2-6ac9-11e7-b9c7-15af748b60d0" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi on comeback trail as smartphone sales soar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi, once the world’s most valuable unicorn, looked set to become one of China’s biggest unicorpses: it burnt cash, and stumbled with supply problems. Now, with fortunes improving, it is staging its next act: Chinese phoenix. The Beijing-based tech company, which makes products ranging from smartphones to smart rice cookers, re-entered the top five of global smartphone makers in the second quarter, as shipments surged 59 per cent year on year to 21m, according to the IDC research firm. The recovery, noted founder and chief executive Lei Jun, “follows a year of setbacks that collectively ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Didi seeks $6 billion funding, to become China's second-most valuable private firm - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/didi-fundraising-idUSL4N1HZ2FZ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKuIn5ir7pZcrtoiDZ8TSCYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 11:17:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/didi-fundraising-idUSL4N1HZ2FZ" target="_blank"&gt;Didi seeks $6 billion funding, to become China's second-most valuable private firm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Julie Zhu and Cate Cadell HONG KONG/BEIJING (Reuters) - Didi Chuxing, China's top ride-hailing firm, is set to become the country's second-most valuable privately owned company, with a valuation of more than $50 billion, through a fund raising round of up to $6 billion, sources said on Thursday. The valuation represents a jump from Didi's $34 billion price tag in August, when it agreed to acquire Uber Technology Inc's China business, and also puts it closer to the U.S. firm's $68 billion. It also propels Didi well above Xiaomi Inc, which held the title of China's most valuable startup af...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Fitbit losing major ground to Apple and Xiaomi - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/fitbit-losing-major-ground-to-apple-and-xiaomi-2017-03-02</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIxfYxUx5BzCUXnzShuzSgsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 08:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/fitbit-losing-major-ground-to-apple-and-xiaomi-2017-03-02" target="_blank"&gt;Fitbit losing major ground to Apple and Xiaomi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jennifer Booton Fitbit’s shipments plunged 23% during the holiday while Xiaomi’s soared 96% and Apple notched its best quarter for wearables Getty Images Fitbit Inc. is barely hanging on to its position as the No. 1 wearable manufacturer in the world and could soon give up the title to Xiaomi or Apple. While Fitbit (FIT) reported an abysmal holiday shopping season that prompted the company to ax 110 jobs, new data show the rest of the wearables industry made out nicely. Worldwide shipments of wearables soared 17% in the fourth quarter to a record high, led by gains from China’s Xiaomi an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Camera Shootout: Xiaomi Mi 6 Vs. Samsung Galaxy S8 - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2017/04/23/camera-shootout-xiaomi-mi-6-vs-samsung-galaxy-s8/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDnhOnINL5QVvxn04sbiw3AqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 08:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2017/04/23/camera-shootout-xiaomi-mi-6-vs-samsung-galaxy-s8/" target="_blank"&gt;Camera Shootout: Xiaomi Mi 6 Vs. Samsung Galaxy S8&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Xiaomi Mi 6 (left); Samsung Galaxy S8 (middle); and the Huawei Mate 9 Pro. In the past week I’ve been testing the newest flagships from Xiaomi and Samsung, and while they’re phones aimed at different markets — the Mi 6 won’t be released in North America and sells for roughly half of what the Galaxy S8 is going for — there are quite a bit of similarities between the two. For example, both phones use Snapdragon 835, the latest and much-hyped chip from Qualcomm (some versions of the S8 also runs on Samsung’s own Exynos 8895 chip); both phones come in all sleek black; and both are following...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Phonemakers pile in to exploit Samsung weakness - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-telecoms-mobileworld-idUSKBN1650V8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECGue7B1Vt6A-UlUDNdtqo4qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 20:45:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-telecoms-mobileworld-idUSKBN1650V8" target="_blank"&gt;Phonemakers pile in to exploit Samsung weakness&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Eric Auchard and Harro Ten Wolde BARCELONA (Reuters) - Phonemakers are piling in to fill a gap in the market left by Samsung (005930.KS: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), still licking its wounds from a costly recall of its flagship Note 7 and with no key device of its own to launch at the telecom industry's biggest annual fair. China's Huawei [HWT.UL], the most likely contender to fill the hole in the premium end of the market, took the wraps off a new phone in its quest to displace Samsung as the world's no. 2 smartphone maker after Apple (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nubia X Review: Two Screens, Two Fingerprint Scanners, Too Weird? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/19/nubia-x-review-two-screens-two-fingerprint-scanners-too-weird/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMRKplmUcXBUJVI9HMccqAkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/19/nubia-x-review-two-screens-two-fingerprint-scanners-too-weird/" target="_blank"&gt;Nubia X Review: Two Screens, Two Fingerprint Scanners, Too Weird?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nubia X has a screen on the front and back of the phone. To what end will Chinese brands go to avoid needing a notch? Vivo designed a phone with a tiny pop-up camera module half a year ago. Then came Oppo with a phone whose entire forehead elevated up and down. And last month, Honor and Xiaomi each introduced slider phones just days apart. In between, there are smaller Shenzhen brands like Bluboo who experimented with a flip-over camera system. Nubia, however, may have come up with the most extreme idea yet. Its latest phone — a surprise release from a brand that was hit with a near dea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ofo, Chinese bike-sharing firm, raises $450 million in latest funding round - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-ofo-fundraising-idUSKBN1683C9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBlRSABaOhTeF9rPqwSJBjkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 06:06:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-ofo-fundraising-idUSKBN1683C9" target="_blank"&gt;Ofo, Chinese bike-sharing firm, raises $450 million in latest funding round&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SHANGHAI/HONG KONG (Reuters) - Chinese bike-sharing start-up ofo said it has raised $450 million in a fresh round of funding, as the firm faces up against deep-pocketed rival Mobike in one of the hottest sectors to attract tech investors. Investment group DST Global, ride-hailing giant Didi Chuxing and CITIC's private equity arm were among investors, the company said in a statement. Ofo and Mobike are two of a growing number of bike-sharing services in China that allow users to find, unlock and pay to rent the bicycles through a smartphone app, targeting younger consumers tired of congested...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China’s tech groups dig deep for employee housing - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/6b67eb56-2884-11e7-bc4b-5528796fe35c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP0hKkEUzRFxcayvRS1ieroqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 23:01:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6b67eb56-2884-11e7-bc4b-5528796fe35c" target="_blank"&gt;China’s tech groups dig deep for employee housing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s lofty property prices are prompting the country’s tech titans to revive old-school communist policies and help put a roof over their employees’ heads. While a few decades ago workers were housed in basic accommodation owned by the state, today some of China’s biggest private companies are doling out interest-free loans and subsidies to enable workers to buy their own homes. Alibaba and Tencent, two of the country’s internet trinity, are among those helping employees buy apartments. Tencent, the social media group headquartered in the southern boomtown of Shenzhen, offers interest-fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi Follows In Footsteps Of Apple And Samsung With Its Own Smartphone Chip - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/aarontilley/2017/02/28/xiaomi-follows-in-footsteps-of-apple-and-samsung-with-its-own-smartphone-chip/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEphCcFSjux-heQ_1Y9oz2QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 22:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/aarontilley/2017/02/28/xiaomi-follows-in-footsteps-of-apple-and-samsung-with-its-own-smartphone-chip/" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi Follows In Footsteps Of Apple And Samsung With Its Own Smartphone Chip&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lei Jun, Chairman and CEO of Xiaomi, presents the new Surge S1 chipset at a launch event in Beijing on February 28, 2017 (Photo credit: NICOLAS ASFOURI/AFP/Getty Images) Once a darling of the global startup scene, Xiaomi has fallen from the number one spot in China’s fast-moving smartphone market. Now the Beijing-based phonemaker is following the examples of smartphone giants Apple, Samsung and Huawei by developing its own chip in hopes of reigniting growth. The company announced its first internally-developed chipset, dubbed the Surge S1, on Tuesday. The new chip will power the company’s l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi Redmi Note 4 becomes fastest-selling smartphone in India - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/xiaomi-redmi-note-4-india-sales-fastest-selling-smartphone-a7629191.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIubdN6E5i75eWLDWiXRK0QqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 15:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/xiaomi-redmi-note-4-india-sales-fastest-selling-smartphone-a7629191.html" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi Redmi Note 4 becomes fastest-selling smartphone in India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi says its new Redmi Note 4 has become the fastest selling smartphone in India. The Chinese firm said it had moved more than one million units in just 45 days since its launch, meaning one sold every four seconds. The phone is the successor to the Redmi Note 3, which shifted more than 2.3 million units in the country following its 2016 launch, making it the best-selling smartphone in India in terms of online sales. Read more - iPhone or Android? Bizarre new case makes dilemma seemingly redundant - Huawei P10: Smartphone aims to stand out in 'colour of the year' - 2017’s smartphone desi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>China smartphone maker Xiaomi designs its first chip - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c18e0cf8-fd88-11e6-96f8-3700c5664d30</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEqeiEa0vU-eR-zP3xIGRY8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 13:05:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c18e0cf8-fd88-11e6-96f8-3700c5664d30" target="_blank"&gt;China smartphone maker Xiaomi designs its first chip&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s Xiaomi has become the world’s fourth smartphone maker to design its own processor, revealing its “Pinecone” chip on Tuesday aimed at breaking its reliance on foreign providers such as Qualcomm. The handset maker is leading a wave of Chinese tech groups that are trying to follow Apple, Samsung and Huawei by creating their own internal intellectual property, rather than relying on external sources. “The ability to create its own chip sets is the pinnacle of achievement for any smartphone company. For Xiaomi, the move is an essential next step in our development,” said Lei Jun, chief e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Tax reform disrupts efforts to lift India’s domestic phone sector - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/5d3f24da-5693-11e7-9fed-c19e2700005f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAZxjsxB2_Z9H70pn5M9-yIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 20:10:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5d3f24da-5693-11e7-9fed-c19e2700005f" target="_blank"&gt;Tax reform disrupts efforts to lift India’s domestic phone sector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A string of Mandarin characters flashes across a blue-lit smartphone display panel at a factory in the north Indian technology hub of Noida, as an Intex Technologies technician tests its latest batch of Chinese supplies. In a larger, adjacent room, long lines of workers in protective white coats and caps are assembling phones from dozens of other components, from microphones to camera sensors, which again come mostly from China. This dependence has sparked condemnation of Intex and other Indian electronics groups, as critics argue that they have simply moved onshore the assembly of Chinese ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>As Apple slows, fast-moving Chinese rivals gain in wealthy markets - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-iphone-china-analysis/as-apple-slows-fast-moving-chinese-rivals-gain-in-wealthy-markets-idUSKCN1BV1GR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIqix29zAfBJuIo9-6apEg4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 11:54:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-iphone-china-analysis/as-apple-slows-fast-moving-chinese-rivals-gain-in-wealthy-markets-idUSKCN1BV1GR" target="_blank"&gt;As Apple slows, fast-moving Chinese rivals gain in wealthy markets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Sijia Jiang and Jeremy Wagstaff HONG KONG/SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Slowing innovation at iPhone maker Apple gives Asian rivals their best chance yet to conquer developed markets, retailers and consumers say - thanks to better designs and lower prices. Apple last week unveiled new iPhones with wireless charging, an edge-to-edge screen and dual cameras - all features already widely available in phones from China's Huawei and Oppo, and Samsung Electronics. While Apple must convince buyers to fork out nearly $1,000 for its high-end model, challengers are tilting at the luxury market, offering s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nokia warns on challenging telecom market conditions - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c4108e52-0b83-3741-9e35-0259dfae8976</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA_oBGEw6cS9kMbk-n6OAMoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 06:43:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c4108e52-0b83-3741-9e35-0259dfae8976" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia warns on challenging telecom market conditions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nokia has warned of a deterioration in the market for telecoms equipment this year in the wake of rival Ericsson’s shock warning last week. The Finnish company however issued a milder view of the market for its kit than Ericsson saying that it expects 2017 to be “slightly more challenging” than it had previously forecast. Ericsson warned that it expected the radio access network market to slump by a “high single digit” percentage but Nokia proved optimistic. Rajeev Suri, chief executive of Nokia, said: We expect our primary addressable market with communication service providers to be sligh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Here's Miracle-Gro for Startups - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidpridham/2017/03/06/heres-miracle-gro-for-startups/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELga3JMH3YdTUa5-4ob9zHEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 20:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidpridham/2017/03/06/heres-miracle-gro-for-startups/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's Miracle-Gro for Startups&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fans of Xiaomi’s best-selling Mi5 smartphone in Spain last year. Credit: Chris Ratcliffe/Bloomberg Just as gardens need fertilizer, startups need nutrients to help them grow. A great product and a little market buzz may be enough to get a business off the ground. But sooner or later, most startups need a potent and sustainable fuel to really power their growth. That’s where patents come in. They’re Miracle-Gro for startups, an entrepreneur’s best friend. This is as true in China, a country that has been accused of stealing intellectual property, as it is in the U.S. Take Chinese startup Xia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Chinese tech firm to take on leading global smartphone makers - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/business/379043-china-xiaomi-chip-challenge-rivals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENff1th-26d62HluJAt0lUUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwroQo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 12:08:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/business/379043-china-xiaomi-chip-challenge-rivals/" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese tech firm to take on leading global smartphone makers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beijing-based electronics company Xiaomi says it's ready to challenge the world’s smartphone market dominated by Apple, Samsung and Huawei. Xiaomi has just become the fourth smartphone manufacturer to introduce its own self-designed processors as well as the first smartphone to be powered by a custom chipset. “The ability to create its own chipsets is the pinnacle achievement for any smartphone company,” said Lei Jun, Xiaomi’s CEO and co-founder at a launch event at the China National Convention Center in Beijing. The Surge S1 chipset was developed by the company’s subsidiary Pinecone forme...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Samsung promises ‘new beginning’ with Galaxy S8 launch - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cc702d18-1499-11e7-b0c1-37e417ee6c76</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAj4QTfCwOVchqugs-AP3wwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 16:25:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cc702d18-1499-11e7-b0c1-37e417ee6c76" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung promises ‘new beginning’ with Galaxy S8 launch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung launched its new Galaxy S8 smartphone with a bombastic event in New York, promising a “new beginning” for mobile handset design as well as for the Korean company amid a series of corporate crises. The Galaxy S8’s signature feature is a new “infinity display” which wraps around the edges of the device to give a larger screen in a smaller body. Claiming the biggest design breakthrough since Apple’s iPhone set the template for touchscreen smartphones a decade ago, Samsung said the S8 and larger S8 Plus would mean less scrolling down a Facebook news feed and allow new kinds of multitask...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>India’s phonemakers cry foul on Chinese rivals - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/6cb6405c-2276-11e7-8691-d5f7e0cd0a16</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI4qbj9RqYsSBOVjLQhkykUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 00:01:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6cb6405c-2276-11e7-8691-d5f7e0cd0a16" target="_blank"&gt;India’s phonemakers cry foul on Chinese rivals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India’s smartphone makers are seeking government action after a dramatic loss of market share to deep-pocketed Chinese rivals, who have been taking the country’s mobile market by storm with aggressive pricing and marketing campaigns. Homegrown companies such as Micromax and Intex had grown to dominate the Indian mobile market, building strong local brands while relying heavily on product designers and component suppliers in China. But over the past year, Chinese smartphone makers such as Xiaomi, Lenovo and Oppo have launched an intense assault on India, where their market share grew to 46 p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Nokia, China's Xiaomi sign patent deal - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-xiaomi-patents-idUSKBN19Q0G9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKIiv86A6Gr0rJ-UADhq8FcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 07:03:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-xiaomi-patents-idUSKBN19Q0G9" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia, China's Xiaomi sign patent deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HELSINKI (Reuters) - Telecoms network equipment maker Nokia and Chinese smartphone maker Xiaomi Technology have signed a patent licensing agreement, the companies said on Wednesday. The companies did not provide financial details of the agreement, saying it includes a cross license to each company's cellular standard patents. Nokia will also provide network infrastructure equipment to Xiaomi. "Xiaomi is one of the world's leading smartphone manufacturers and we are delighted to have reached an agreement with them," Nokia Chief Executive Rajeev Suri said in a statement. Nokia has license dea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Most Influential People of African Descent (MIPAD) honorees - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/05/25/africa/gallery/mipad-africa-honorees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELNrkmmmkFyPXBGqMOXaQLMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 09:53:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/05/25/africa/gallery/mipad-africa-honorees/" target="_blank"&gt;Most Influential People of African Descent (MIPAD) honorees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alek Wek is a South Sudanese-British model and designer who began her fashion career at the age of 18 in 1995. MIPAD Nigerian Imeime Umana is the first black woman to serve as President of the Harvard Law Review. MIPAD Anthony Joshua is a British professional boxer of Nigerian descent. MIPAD Akon Thiam is a singer, rapper, songwriter, businessman, record producer and actor of Senegalese descent. MIPAD Bunmi Akinyemiju is the CEO, Venture Garden Group, Nigeria MIPAD Didier Drogba is a former Chelsea football club player and is one of the most decorated Ivorian footballers. MIPAD Bozoma Saint...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Fast Asia Open: India CPI, Philippines trade data - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/32413a78-25c9-38c5-95ee-05c59e480982</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENizKuuy2-d130QVZUZ9jS4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 23:03:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/32413a78-25c9-38c5-95ee-05c59e480982" target="_blank"&gt;Fast Asia Open: India CPI, Philippines trade data&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All eyes are on Apple this week for the launch of its latest iPhone, which the company hopes will help surmount its growth problem of the past two years. But an upstart rival in China is already staging its own comeback. Beijing-based tech company Xiaomi, which makes products ranging from smartphones to smart rice cookers, re-entered the top five of global smartphone makers in the second quarter, as shipments surged 59 per cent year on year to 21m, according to the IDC research firm. “In the last two years, which have been our most difficult, we have still stuck to our core values…of a high...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi Mi 6 Review: Very Good, In Workmanlike Fashion - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2017/05/04/xiaomi-mi-6-review-very-good-in-workmanlike-fashion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELz_9IzQ2yMoUO9lrT2xBQEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 07:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2017/05/04/xiaomi-mi-6-review-very-good-in-workmanlike-fashion/" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi Mi 6 Review: Very Good, In Workmanlike Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Xiaomi Mi 6. Beijing-based Xiaomi rose to prominence years ago with a clear business model: produce good looking phones with very good specs that sell at a low price. That approach worked so well for a while, Xiaomi was at one point valued at US$45 billion in 2014. And though the company’s growth has stagnated a bit in the last year or two, the company’s not going to change their product strategy – I know because Xiaomi’s senior vice president Wang Xiang told me so. And so, Xiaomi’s lateste product, the Mi 6, is again an insanely good value when compared to other products out on the mar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi shrugs off smartphone sales downturn with earnings rise - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b83add50-ebea-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWrBCtnqBRZGghL1YyBCHQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 11:10:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b83add50-ebea-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi shrugs off smartphone sales downturn with earnings rise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi has reported strong third-quarter earnings despite a global downturn in smartphone sales, cementing two consecutive quarters of growth after a disappointing public offering in June. The technology company made Rmb2.9bn ($420mn) in the three months to the end of September, compared with net profits of Rmb2.1bn the previous three months. The weaker third quarter performance this year compares to a reported loss of Rmb11bn ($1.58bn) during its third quarter last year. Xiaomi said the revenue growth was largely driven by sales of more premium-priced smartphones — which now make up nearly...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Leak, Samsung Folding Phone Images, Xiaomi Mi8 Pro Fights OnePlus 6T - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/16/android-news-headlines-samsung-galaxy-s10-galaxy-x-oneplus-6t-siaomi-mi8-pro-nokia71-revlew/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOz_ZZJEm5clsJ511wu8sFUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 00:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/16/android-news-headlines-samsung-galaxy-s10-galaxy-x-oneplus-6t-siaomi-mi8-pro-nokia71-revlew/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Leak, Samsung Folding Phone Images, Xiaomi Mi8 Pro Fights OnePlus 6T&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes new leaked details on the Galaxy S10, release date and rendered images of the folding Galaxy smartphone, hints of a new OnePlus 5G handset, the OnePlus 6T vs the Xiaomi Mi 8 Pro, a review of the Nokia 7.1, and what is happening to Google Maps. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). Visitors get a look at Samsung Galaxy Note9 smartphone at the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Smartphone prices in India are rising. Blame the weak rupee - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/tech/xiaomi-price-in-india/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYK5UJZmdWoPEPzV5oE8DkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 12:13:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/tech/xiaomi-price-in-india/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Smartphone prices in India are rising. Blame the weak rupee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biggest seller of smartphones in India says it is having to hike prices because of the slump in the value of the country's currency. Chinese electronics firm Xiaomi raised the prices of several of its new products on Sunday, citing the sharp fall in the Indian rupee this year as the main factor behind its decision. "[The] rupee has depreciated against the dollar by nearly 15% since the beginning of the year, which has resulted in a significant rise in input cost for us," the company said on Twitter. Xiaomi added 500 rupees ($7) to the cost of its Redmi 6 smartphone and 600 rupees ($8) t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Meet The Man Behind Oppo's (And OnePlus') Super Fast Charging Speeds - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/16/meet-the-man-behind-oppos-and-oneplus-super-fast-charging-speeds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAUcoiADdnVc6mms2Fi6I2MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/16/meet-the-man-behind-oppos-and-oneplus-super-fast-charging-speeds/" target="_blank"&gt;Meet The Man Behind Oppo's (And OnePlus') Super Fast Charging Speeds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oppo’s most premium phone, the Find X Lamborghini Edition, introduced the fastest charging tech seen in the industry. The biggest gripe I have with the new iPhone has nothing to do with its performance during active use, but rather when I’m not even touching the phone. The new iPhone XS can support fast charging up to 30 watt, but the charging brick Apple includes with the $1,200 phone is a putrid 5w plug that takes over three hours to fully charge. The larger Max needs another half hour on top of that. In the Android space, a fast-charging brick included in the packaging is just about stan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi: Chinese phone maker arrives in the UK, looking to take on Apple and Samsung - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/xiaomi-china-uk-apple-samsung-buy-best-phone-deals-latest-a8626901.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHMX2OsWYmn_mVWD-hNtwu0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/xiaomi-china-uk-apple-samsung-buy-best-phone-deals-latest-a8626901.html" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi: Chinese phone maker arrives in the UK, looking to take on Apple and Samsung&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese phone company Xiaomi has finally launched its phones in the UK, ready to take on companies like Apple and Samsung. As well as its Mi 8 Pro flagship phone – which is now on sale, the first time the phone is available outside of China – the company is selling a wristband and a scooter as it attempts to spread across the world. The company is already the fourth biggest phone company in the world, after Samsung, Huawei and Apple. But it has mostly sold its products in China, and is now seeking to spread into more countries. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 43 show all Gadgets and tec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Smartphone maker Xiaomi launches in Britain with flagship device - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-xiaomi-britain-idUSKBN1ND296</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHfG1yZ03laFdRS-8dp03xYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 16:30:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-xiaomi-britain-idUSKBN1ND296" target="_blank"&gt;Smartphone maker Xiaomi launches in Britain with flagship device&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi, the world's fourth ranked smartphone maker, entered Britain on Thursday with the international debut of its flagship Mi 8 Pro, which it hopes will win fans in a market dominated by Samsung and Apple. Senior vice president Xiang Wang said Britain had a "cool" factor that aligned with the company's appeal to its customers. "The UK is one of the important global centers for technology," he said in an interview ahead of the company's London launch. "It is a young energetic place, so pretty much fits to our culture - we want to be the coolest company in our fans' minds." Xiaomi, which li...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>A matter of volume: threat from ascendant Chinese phones hangs over Apple - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-iphone-pricing-analysis-idUSKCN1NJ26G</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK7HWadWfri9RKaPznJzIocqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 23:53:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-iphone-pricing-analysis-idUSKCN1NJ26G" target="_blank"&gt;A matter of volume: threat from ascendant Chinese phones hangs over Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A raft of profit warnings from Apple Inc (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) suppliers this week has fueled investor concerns that iPhone sales, in terms of volume, have hit a wall that could spell trouble for the company's plans to make services its main pillar of growth. For the past year, investors had largely been willing to overlook stagnating unit sales of the iPhone because average selling prices kept rising. But it now faces fierce competition from mid-priced phones from makers such as Xiaomi Corp (1810.HK: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz). Apple has often stated its...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Three Stunning Surprises You Can See Inside The New Xiaomi Mi 8 Pro - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/08/xiaomi-mi8-pro-uk-launch-release-date-transparent-android-specifications/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ4g87igYXI7tNO28CnGczQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 18:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/08/xiaomi-mi8-pro-uk-launch-release-date-transparent-android-specifications/" target="_blank"&gt;Three Stunning Surprises You Can See Inside The New Xiaomi Mi 8 Pro&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today saw Xiaomi enter the UK smartphone and consumer electronics with the launch of the flagship Mi 8 Pro smartphone, a solid portfolio of Android-powered handsets, a new store in London, and an electric scooter. How will Western markets take to the strange mix of Xiaomi’s consumer products, smartphones, and impactful branding? The bridgehead into the UK begins with the Mi 8 Pro smartphone. Xiaomi Mi 8 Pro (image: Ewan Spence) High Specifications At A Low Price Let’s face it, the table stakes for a flagship device make for a great phone. The Mi 8 Pro has the requisite SnapDragon 845 system...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>India's App Economy: The Opportunity is Huge. The Time is Now. - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/eladnatanson/2018/11/13/indias-app-economy-the-opportunity-is-huge-the-time-is-now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ2qc9xT9SYFrCYrQi6671kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 15:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/eladnatanson/2018/11/13/indias-app-economy-the-opportunity-is-huge-the-time-is-now/" target="_blank"&gt;India's App Economy: The Opportunity is Huge. The Time is Now.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the world’s app economies at the end of 2018, China remains by far the largest in terms of usage and revenue, but the one which has undergone the most rapid change over the last two years is India. While still in its early stages, India’s app economy is maturing so fast that it must now be on the radar for every serious app developer or marketer. The numbers are impressive: - Last year, India overtook the US as the world’s #2 market in app downloads, with 12.1 billion. - App Annie forecasts that by 2022, India will have 37.2 billion downloads a year, a growth rate of 207% — w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Week In Wearables: AirPods 2 Incoming? Black Friday Wearables, Xiaomi Mi Band 3 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/08/week-in-wearables-airpods-2-incoming-black-friday-wearable-deals-xiaomi-mi-band-3-price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFvqXvOpiv4dTx8n_PxBfB4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/08/week-in-wearables-airpods-2-incoming-black-friday-wearable-deals-xiaomi-mi-band-3-price/" target="_blank"&gt;Week In Wearables: AirPods 2 Incoming? Black Friday Wearables, Xiaomi Mi Band 3&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week in wearable news is dominated by the possible arrival of Apple AirPods 2, the first wearable tech deals for Black Friday and why women might like the Michael Kors Access Runway smart watch. Apple’s iPhone X with the Apple Watch, Airpods and upcoming wireless charging pad. The Week in Wearables is a news digest, out each week, focused on some of the things that have happened in the world of tech you can wear on your wrist, perch on your head, stick in your ear, sling around your waist, tuck into the small of your back or, well, you get the idea. The world-conquering Apple AirPods. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: Radical New Galaxy, Secrets Inside The OnePlus 6T, Google's Serious Pixel 3 Problem - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/09/android-news-headlines-google-pixel-3-samsung-galaxy-f-oneplus-6t-xiaomi-mi8-pro/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDs1DNm2MXDdvOh7Rz-3HaQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/09/android-news-headlines-google-pixel-3-samsung-galaxy-f-oneplus-6t-xiaomi-mi8-pro/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: Radical New Galaxy, Secrets Inside The OnePlus 6T, Google's Serious Pixel 3 Problem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes Samsung’s new folding smartphone, a refreshed Note 9, problems with the Pixel 3, the Xiaomi Mi 8 Pro in the UK, BlackBerry Key2 LE reviewed, latest OnePlus 6T details, and the battery advantage of Android’s dark mode. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). Samsung Unveils Radical Galaxy F Folding Smartphone At one point it threatened to overw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What's The Outlook Like For Qualcomm After A Mixed Fiscal 2018? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/08/whats-the-outlook-like-for-qualcomm-after-a-mixed-fiscal-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI6NnDrU2nyV9V5ar1zyo6cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 13:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/08/whats-the-outlook-like-for-qualcomm-after-a-mixed-fiscal-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;What's The Outlook Like For Qualcomm After A Mixed Fiscal 2018?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signage for 5G mobile experiences is seen at the Qualcomm Inc. booth at the Mobile World Congress Shanghai in Shanghai, China, on Thursday, June 28, 2018. Photographer: Qilai Shen/Bloomberg Wireless technology behemoth Qualcomm published its Q4 FY’18 results on Wednesday, November 7, reporting a better than expected set of results that were driven by stronger demand for the company’s chipsets from Chinese smartphone vendors, although this was partially offset by lower revenues from Apple. The company has guided for revenues of $4.5 billion to $5.3 billion for Q1 FY’19, marking a decline of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>China's Tech Fortunes Tumble As Investors Turn Away From Public Listings - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ywang/2018/11/08/chinas-tech-fortunes-tumble-as-investors-turn-away-from-public-listings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANtzojpjuwFXzsr4wFlFCQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ywang/2018/11/08/chinas-tech-fortunes-tumble-as-investors-turn-away-from-public-listings/" target="_blank"&gt;China's Tech Fortunes Tumble As Investors Turn Away From Public Listings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi’s Founder, Chairman and CEO Lei Jun. (Photo: AP Photo/Kin Cheung) Technology companies in China have minted a slew of new billionaires worth almost $30.8 billion this year, but many of those fortunes are now sliding downward as investors grow increasingly skeptical of the sector’s outlook for future growth. Smartphone maker Xiaomi was the top wealth creator among the Chinese tech firms that recently floated their shares publicly, lifting cofounders Hong Feng, Li Wanqiang and Wong Kong Kat into the billionaire ranks alongside partners Lei Jun and Lin Bin. The other notable newcomers i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>China's finance ministry calls out Xiaomi over accounting errors - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xiaomi/chinas-finance-ministry-calls-out-xiaomi-over-accounting-errors-idUSKCN1N40BD</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQ-ROTeIKseP0DT8oJ5SYUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 04:43:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xiaomi/chinas-finance-ministry-calls-out-xiaomi-over-accounting-errors-idUSKCN1N40BD" target="_blank"&gt;China's finance ministry calls out Xiaomi over accounting errors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese authorities on Tuesday said smartphone maker Xioami Corp made errors in its accounting, sending the company's Hong Kong-listed shares down amid a wider sell-off of China tech stocks. Xiaomi was one of several internet firms named in the annual inspection by China's Ministry of Finance. Other firms include e-commerce giant Suning.Com Co Ltd and online game developer Wuhu Shunrong Sanqi Interactive Entertainment Network Technology Co Ltd. Xiaomi's stock was down 4 percent on Tuesday morning. The ministry in its report said Xiaomi had made tax errors on corporate gifts and had incorrec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Honor Magic 2 Hands-On: Huawei's Slider Phone With Six Cameras - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/10/31/honor-magic-2-hands-on-huaweis-slider-phone-with-six-cameras/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJYbN6CzDole5bal1X81KPIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/10/31/honor-magic-2-hands-on-huaweis-slider-phone-with-six-cameras/" target="_blank"&gt;Honor Magic 2 Hands-On: Huawei's Slider Phone With Six Cameras&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Honor Magic 2 has a sliding form factor to allow for an all-screen, notch-less look. This insane month of mobile gadget launches that includes flagship products from, in no particular order, Apple, LG, Google, Razer, Xiaomi, OnePlus, Huawei, and a couple others has finally wrapped up, and it is Honor with the last word. Just launched in Beijing, the sub-brand of Huawei has unveiled the sequel to its experimental 2016 phone, the Magic, and the aptly-titled Magic 2 brings with it the same sliding form factor that Xiaomi introduced — in the same city — just last week. As I wrote from that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Huawei Fortifies #2 Spot In Global Smartphone Market, Beating Apple Again - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/11/02/huawei-fortifies-2-spot-in-global-smartphone-market-beating-apple-again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFDdaxVJxulkw7awuOHVd6cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/11/02/huawei-fortifies-2-spot-in-global-smartphone-market-beating-apple-again/" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei Fortifies #2 Spot In Global Smartphone Market, Beating Apple Again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite a quasi sales ban in the U.S., Huawei retained the number 2 position of the global smartphone market last quarter. Despite a quasi sales ban in the U.S., Huawei retained the number 2 position of the global smartphone market last quarter, according to the latest estimates from IDC. During the third quarter of 2018, smartphone vendors shipped a total of 355.2 million units, a 6% drop from last year, and the 4th consecutive quarter of year-over-year decline for the global smartphone market. Although Samsung is still the clear market leader with 20.3% of total shipments, sales declined ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi Mi Mix 3 Hands-On: The Slider Phone With 10GB of RAM - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/10/25/xiaomi-mi-mix-3-hands-on-the-slider-phone-with-10gb-of-ram/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIXTYu6dM8EZpyatXkx3t3UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 03:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/10/25/xiaomi-mi-mix-3-hands-on-the-slider-phone-with-10gb-of-ram/" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi Mi Mix 3 Hands-On: The Slider Phone With 10GB of RAM&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lei Jun speaks at Xiaomi’s launch event for the Mi Mix 3 at the Palace Museum on Oct. 25 in Beijing, China. (Photo: Liang Shuang/Huanqiu.com/VCG via Getty Images) Xiaomi’s original Mi Mix, released in the fall of 2016, was an industry shaker that ditched several traditional smartphone hardware parts and ignored conventional design cues to achieve its at the time near-bezel-less look. Of course, the competition for jaw-dropping design has gotten much stiffer in 2018, a fact even Xiaomi founder and CEO Lei Jun admitted during yesterday’s launch event of the Mi Mix 3. The Xiaomi Mi Mix 3 (righ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung reports record profit despite smartphone sales slump - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/31/samsung-reports-record-profit-despite-smartphone-sales-slump/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBYgud_XiKI5wXyEUnVZ_JUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:15:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/31/samsung-reports-record-profit-despite-smartphone-sales-slump/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung reports record profit despite smartphone sales slump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has revealed record profit for the third quarter as demand for its memory chips cushioned the impact of slowing smartphone sales. Between July and September, Samsung brought in an operating profit of 17.6 tn won (£12.2 bn), up 21pc from the same quarter in 2017. The Suwon-based firm's net profit for the quarter also rose, reaching 13.1 tn won. The numbers were largely driven by strong sales in Samsung’s semiconductor unit, which designs and manufactures chips for Samsung’s products as well as devices made by its competitors. Operating profit in Samsung’s smartphone division dropped ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>China’s OnePlus 6T has an American carrier in T-Mobile - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90258309/chinas-oneplus-6t-has-an-american-carrier-in-t-mobile</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHY2C9TNjDVqjdcEWWVKuNYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 13:24:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90258309/chinas-oneplus-6t-has-an-american-carrier-in-t-mobile" target="_blank"&gt;China’s OnePlus 6T has an American carrier in T-Mobile&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After notching $1 billion in revenue and turning a profit last year, phone maker OnePlus is getting its first U.S. wireless carrier deal with T-Mobile, which will sell the just-announced OnePlus 6T in 5,600 retail stores. The OnePlus 6T bears several similarities to other high-end phones from Vivo and Oppo, which are also owned by parent company BBK, but don’t have wireless carrier deals. Most notably, it has a fingerprint reader built into the display glass–a first for the U.S. market–and just a small camera cutout near the top of the 6.41-inch screen. Other specs include a Qualcomm Snapdr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>This Tiny, Foldable Treadmill Is Perfect For Urbanites - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/meggentaylor/2018/10/15/this-tiny-foldable-treadmill-is-perfect-for-urbanites/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEqvHQda0HvOBVPZOlDW-H4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 15:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/meggentaylor/2018/10/15/this-tiny-foldable-treadmill-is-perfect-for-urbanites/" target="_blank"&gt;This Tiny, Foldable Treadmill Is Perfect For Urbanites&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As life gets busier, it becomes challenging to balance the different balls that we all have to juggle. Often times, we end up cutting out what’s most important—like making sure to take time out for ourselves, which can include foregoing exercise. Busy work schedules, family responsibilities, and inclement weather are just a few of the reasons that getting daily exercise can be a challenge. WalkingPad, a new foldable treadmill that literally fits under your bed, is trying to change that so you can do your cardio in the comfort of your own home or office without requiring the space that a tra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>5 days, $1 billion: Flipkart and Amazon spur Indian smartphone bonanza - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/12/tech/flipkart-amazon-india-smartphone/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEeDax15RL7rhqoZ1eyJWlIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 11:28:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/12/tech/flipkart-amazon-india-smartphone/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;5 days, $1 billion: Flipkart and Amazon spur Indian smartphone bonanza&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The battle for India's online shoppers has triggereda smartphone gold rush. Flipkart and Amazon are leading an online sales bonanza that will see Indians buy smartphones worth over $1 billion in just five days, according to tech consultancy Counterpoint Research. Bangalore-based Flipkart said it sold 1 million devices during the first hour of an online phone sale on Thursday that was part of its "Big Billion Days" shopping festival. By the end of the day, it had sold more than 3 million phones. Acquired earlier this year by Walmart (WMT), Flipkart estimated that its sale accounted for more ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Here's Every Android Device Compatible With 'Fortnite: Battle Royale' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/12/heres-every-android-device-compatible-with-fortnite-battle-royale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdcudkVJTTF4G0-hn6fWOgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/12/heres-every-android-device-compatible-with-fortnite-battle-royale/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's Every Android Device Compatible With 'Fortnite: Battle Royale'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s an updated list of compatible devices with Fortnite on Android. Now that the Android Fortnite: Battle Royale beta is open to everyone, here’s an updated list of compatible devices and required specs for the game. Not every phone or tablet will play the wildly popular free-to-play title. If you’re curious if you can download the game and start playing, here’s the update list: - Samsung Galaxy: S7 / S7 Edge , S8 / S8+, S9 / S9+, Note 8, Note 9, Tab S3, Tab S4 - Google: Pixel / Pixel XL, Pixel 2 / Pixel 2 XL - Asus: ROG Phone, Zenfone 4 Pro, 5Z, V - Essential: PH-1 - Huawei: Honor 10, H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>WeChat rival 'Bullet' removed from App Store over copyright complaint - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-bulletmessenger-china-socialmedia/wechat-rival-bullet-removed-from-app-store-over-copyright-complaint-idUSKCN1MJ0S1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHNfjCMyv5VYO6O0Hgjyhf8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 08:44:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-bulletmessenger-china-socialmedia/wechat-rival-bullet-removed-from-app-store-over-copyright-complaint-idUSKCN1MJ0S1" target="_blank"&gt;WeChat rival 'Bullet' removed from App Store over copyright complaint&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese chat app Bullet Messenger - touted as an upstart rival to Tencent Holdings Ltd's hugely popular WeChat - says its app has been removed from Apple Inc's App Store just months after its launch due to a copyright complaint. Beijing Kuairu Technology, Bullet's owner, said in a social media posting on Tuesday that it was forced to pull the app after complaints were raised about image content provided by a partner. It was briefly the most downloaded free app in the Chinese App Store, amassing 5 million registered users within 10 days of its August launch. The company did not elaborate on ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Razer Phone 2 First Look: Smoother And Louder Than The Rest - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/10/10/razer-phone-2-first-look-smoother-and-loud/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB8RiVeDhOLIACHdRWLiywoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/10/10/razer-phone-2-first-look-smoother-and-loud/" target="_blank"&gt;Razer Phone 2 First Look: Smoother And Louder Than The Rest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Razer Phone 2 can run the game Gear Club, among others, at 120 frames per second for extra smooth graphics. For a company still relatively new to the smartphone space, Razer isn’t afraid to mix it up with the big boys. The American-Singaporean gaming hardware company has just announced a sequel to its debut gaming phone, and it comes smack in the middle of what is the craziest month ever for smartphone releases. So far in October we’ve already seen LG’s V40, Google’s Pixel 3, and we’re mere days away from Huawei’s Mate 20 launch event. Then in the final week of October, Xiaomi’s got the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung or Xiaomi? It's a two-horse race for India's smartphone market - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/30/tech/samsung-india-xiaomi/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEImPyGpXkPqYlMA_1ImUaPoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 16:09:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/30/tech/samsung-india-xiaomi/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung or Xiaomi? It's a two-horse race for India's smartphone market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article was first published on July 20, 2018. India's booming smartphone market is turning into a two-horse race between Samsung and Xiaomi. The world's biggest smartphone maker and its fast-growing Chinese rival now account for 60% of the country's sales, according to a new report by research firm Canalys. Samsung (SSNLF) and Xiaomi each sold nearly 10 million smartphones in India in the three months to June 30, a new record for both companies, Canalys said. The new sales estimates reflect a big comeback for Samsung, which dominated the Indian market for six years but was overtaken by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Lenovo and ZTE tumble on fears over China hack report - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-tech/lenovo-and-zte-tumble-on-fears-over-china-hack-report-idUSKCN1MF076</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAPBNvqIeF_GpfLuz_S9gEgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 13:49:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-tech/lenovo-and-zte-tumble-on-fears-over-china-hack-report-idUSKCN1MF076" target="_blank"&gt;Lenovo and ZTE tumble on fears over China hack report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lenovo and ZTE Corp shares slid on Friday, hurt by worries about overseas sales after Bloomberg reported that the systems of multiple U.S. companies had been compromised by malicious computer chips inserted by Chinese spies. In a report published on Thursday, Bloomberg Businessweek cited 17 unidentified sources from intelligence agencies and businesses as saying that Chinese spies had placed computer chips inside equipment used by about 30 companies and multiple U.S. government agencies, which would give Beijing secret access to internal networks. Apple and Amazon.com's Amazon Web Services ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Realme 2 Pro Review: Oppo's Sub-Brand Makes A Splash In The Budget Sector - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/27/realme-2-pro-review-oppos-sub-brand-makes-a-splash-in-the-budget-sector/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELnNjcLSvCtQuppJvIpWGEcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/27/realme-2-pro-review-oppos-sub-brand-makes-a-splash-in-the-budget-sector/" target="_blank"&gt;Realme 2 Pro Review: Oppo's Sub-Brand Makes A Splash In The Budget Sector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Realme 2 Pro. Sub-brands appear to be all the rage this year for Chinese phonemakers. Huawei’s Honor has been continuing its big push this year into Europe and Southeast Asia; ZTE began its comeback by releasing a phone under its Nubia banner, Xiaomi recently made a big splash with its insanely low-priced Pocophone, and now Oppo has launched a sub-brand of its own. Named Realme, Oppo’s new side project is, like Huawei’s Honor and Xiaomi’s Poco, aimed at emerging markets such as Southeast Asia and eastern Europe, and meant to stay out of its parent company’s way in developed markets with hig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New OnePlus 6T Leak Reveals Powerful Secret - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/09/29/oneplus-6t-battery-wireless-charging-power-leak/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDCeur3XDOq6qrGIIWTHN1cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 22:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/09/29/oneplus-6t-battery-wireless-charging-power-leak/" target="_blank"&gt;New OnePlus 6T Leak Reveals Powerful Secret&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With just over two weeks to go until its expected launch, the latest OnePlus 6T leak may have revealed a much larger battery to power the flagship smartphone from Shenzhen. The latest details come via social network Weibo, and shows the alleged battery. While the OnePlus 6 has a 3300 mAh battery, the upcoming OnePlus 6T is on course to sport a 3610 mAh battery. We also have a part number – BLP68S – and it should come as no surprise to anyone that the latest Oppo handset (the Oppo R17 Pro) features the same battery. OnePlus 6T pre-launch images (OnePlus) Although different companies, there h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Beats Apple In The Global Smartphone Market As Chinese Brands Close In - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2018/09/13/samsung-beats-apple-in-the-global-smartphone-market-as-chinese-brands-close-in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELmMjijFOAWp5otGDhPSfFwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2018/09/13/samsung-beats-apple-in-the-global-smartphone-market-as-chinese-brands-close-in/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Beats Apple In The Global Smartphone Market As Chinese Brands Close In&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: SeongJoon Cho/Bloomberg Korean smartphone maker Samsung is beating Apple in global smartphone sales, as Chinese makers like Xiaomi, Oppo, and Huawei are closing in. That’s according to a recent report published by Newzoo. “Globally, there were 3.6 billion active smartphones in use in June 2018,” says the report. “The world’s most popular smartphone brand was Samsung, boasting 893 million active devices and a market share of 27%. Apple was a close second, with a market share of 24%. Samsung’s lead is mostly due to the company’s selection of budget devices, which fare well in de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi creates new management jobs aimed at CEO succession planning - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xiaomi/xiaomi-creates-new-management-jobs-aimed-at-ceo-succession-planning-idUSKCN1LU0IA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGF8mtuDy2NU9gr-jD2bIU4qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 06:05:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-xiaomi/xiaomi-creates-new-management-jobs-aimed-at-ceo-succession-planning-idUSKCN1LU0IA" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi creates new management jobs aimed at CEO succession planning&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese smartphone maker Xiaomi Inc (1810.HK: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) said on Friday it will rejig its businesses and create new leadership positions aimed at building a second tier to CEO Lei Jun, amid increased scrutiny of governance and successions at Chinese tech firms. The firm would introduce two new departments to advise Lei on strategy and oversee hiring, promotion and pay, Lei said in a memo to staff dated Sept. 13 and shared with the press on Friday. It also would reshuffle its four main business units into 10 to promote younger managers, Lei said, adding that a majo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Why China's Top Phone Brands Have Turned To Swedish Audio Firm Dirac For Superior Sound - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/10/why-chinas-top-phone-brands-have-turned-to-swedish-audio-firm-dirac-for-superior-sound/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFhqUAO860sK_c1q0XlUmJ8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 03:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/10/why-chinas-top-phone-brands-have-turned-to-swedish-audio-firm-dirac-for-superior-sound/" target="_blank"&gt;Why China's Top Phone Brands Have Turned To Swedish Audio Firm Dirac For Superior Sound&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A graphic provided by Dirac simulating what the power of fine-tuned stereo speakers should sound like — fuller, multi-direction sound. There are still three or four big smartphone releases this year, but it’s very likely that Oppo’s Find X, with its almost bezel-less face, smooth, seamless back that is uninterrupted by camera modules, and elevating forehead (top bezel) will be 2018′s most ambitious and radically-designed handset. But had longtime Oppo business partner Dirac Research gotten their way, the Find X would not have won that title – but it would have pumped out fuller sound. Headq...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why HTC's New Cheap High-End Smartphone Won't Revitalize The Company - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphjennings/2018/09/11/why-htcs-new-cheap-high-end-smartphone-wont-revitalize-the-company/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHs8_XRRP31Q9-rNs-nVnP8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphjennings/2018/09/11/why-htcs-new-cheap-high-end-smartphone-wont-revitalize-the-company/" target="_blank"&gt;Why HTC's New Cheap High-End Smartphone Won't Revitalize The Company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A model shows a HTC U12+ X Mayday smartphone during a media event in Taipei on May 23, 2018. The HTC U12+ started selling in July in Taiwan, HTC’s home market. Now the market is expecting a successor, the U12 Life. (AP Photo/Chiang Ying-ying) HTC has survived a series of hits over the past seven years, but it’s still struggling. Now tech media outlets and industry analysts are tipping the Taiwanese company to release a new smartphone called the U12 Life. The upcoming model, which descends from the flagship U12+ phone released earlier this year as well as the U11 Life unveiled in late 2017, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi's $300 Pocophone Vs. Samsung's $1,250 Galaxy Note 9: It's Closer Than You'd Think - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/10/xiaomis-300-pocophone-vs-samsungs-1250-galaxy-note-9-its-closer-than-youd-think/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPxab-kyNIoTfnbY3K3e1cIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 06:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/10/xiaomis-300-pocophone-vs-samsungs-1250-galaxy-note-9-its-closer-than-youd-think/" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi's $300 Pocophone Vs. Samsung's $1,250 Galaxy Note 9: It's Closer Than You'd Think&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pocophone, left, and the Samsung Galaxy Note 9. Three years ago, Lenovo’s CEO Yang Yuanqing pulled his company out of the high-end smartphone battleground, saying that there were “too many Chinese vendors,” some of whom were “playing irrationally.” He was referring to the price war that saw — and continues to see — Chinese brands push smartphone pricing lower and lower in order to gain an edge. That price war is still going strong three years on. In fact, it may be more irrational than ever. I recently reviewed Samsung’s much-hyped Galaxy Note 9, and though I really liked the phone (so ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why Leery Taiwan Consumers Will Make An Exception For These Chinese Smartphones - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphjennings/2018/09/06/why-leery-taiwan-consumers-will-make-an-exception-for-these-chinese-smartphones/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEyOw3vuyeMjrPC3zxtMEscqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphjennings/2018/09/06/why-leery-taiwan-consumers-will-make-an-exception-for-these-chinese-smartphones/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Leery Taiwan Consumers Will Make An Exception For These Chinese Smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lei Jun, chairman and CEO of Xiaomi Corp., waves during the company’s listing ceremony at the Hong Kong Stock Exchange on July 9, 2018. (Photo: Zhang Wei/China News Service/VCG) Taiwan is hardly a go-to place for Chinese brands. The market is small compared to China or emerging Southeast Asia. But the Xiaomi brand of smartphones looks well placed to bolster its revenues here due to its low unit prices and an overall reputation for durable iPhone-lookalike Android handsets along with other gear that its rivals don’t sell, analysts say. “Owing to a broad product portfolio that covers smart ho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Vivo V11 Review: The Notch Evolution Gets The China Speed Treatment - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/05/vivo-v11-review-the-notch-evolution-gets-the-china-speed-treatment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJhhODLGvqA2_O_7yznbLeYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 08:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/05/vivo-v11-review-the-notch-evolution-gets-the-china-speed-treatment/" target="_blank"&gt;Vivo V11 Review: The Notch Evolution Gets The China Speed Treatment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vivo V11 has a 6.4-inch OLED display with the smallest notch cutout yet. About a year ago Apple introduced the iPhone X, and with it came the notch, which led to a seismic shift in smartphone design for all of 2018. Almost every major smartphone, with the exception of Samsung devices, followed Apple’s cue and used the notch design to achieve as much of a bezel-less look as possible without sacrificing the selfie camera placement. Despite the notch being a design that makes a lot of practical sense — especially for Android, whose status bar up top always has empty space in the middle any...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>China Xiaomi's revenue surges on India smartphone demand but growth doubts stay - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-xiaomi-results/chinas-xiaomi-posts-68-3-percent-jump-in-second-quarter-revenue-on-smartphone-strength-idUSKCN1L70UX</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI9zPRYcTM3Bk9XaJ3ugSo4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 09:28:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-xiaomi-results/chinas-xiaomi-posts-68-3-percent-jump-in-second-quarter-revenue-on-smartphone-strength-idUSKCN1L70UX" target="_blank"&gt;China Xiaomi's revenue surges on India smartphone demand but growth doubts stay&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese smartphone maker Xiaomi Inc's quarterly revenue soared due to strong demand in India and other emerging markets but doubts remained on whether it can sustain the fast pace of growth and its shares reversed early gains to end lower. Xiaomi, which toppled Samsung Electronics as the top smartphone seller in the price-conscious Indian market earlier this year, said on Wednesday in its first results as a listed firm that revenue from overseas markets for the quarter ended June 30 more than doubled from the year-ago period. The company started trading in July after a closely watched but d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi posts $2 billion profit in first earnings report since IPO - CNN</title><link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/22/technology/xiaomi-earnings-post-ipo/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJqV2Ud2XM9hVq4ZS1JvPjYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 11:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/22/technology/xiaomi-earnings-post-ipo/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi posts $2 billion profit in first earnings report since IPO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi has posted a bumper profit in its first earnings report since going public last month. The Chinese smartphone maker said Wednesday it made 14.6 billion yuan ($2.1 billion) in the three months to June 30, beating industry estimates. Revenue grew 68% compared to the same period last year to 45.2 billion yuan ($6.6 billion). Xiaomi stock closed up 1.6% in Hong Kong on Wednesday, ahead of the earnings report. The company went public in Hong Kong in July after raising $4.7 billion in the world's biggest tech IPO since Alibaba's New York listing in 2014. The upbeat earnings come despite do...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Chinese smartphone giant Xiaomi sees 68% rise in revenue after difficult float - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/08/22/chinese-smartphone-giant-xiaomi-sees-68-rise-revenue-difficult/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED_2wQC7KZyLjXo3yVEKkVsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 14:46:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/08/22/chinese-smartphone-giant-xiaomi-sees-68-rise-revenue-difficult/" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese smartphone giant Xiaomi sees 68% rise in revenue after difficult float&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese smartphone giant Xiaomi has posted surging revenue growth and profits as its smartphone sales beat a slowing market. Xiaomi, which listed in July on the Hong Kong Stock Exchange for $4.7bn (£3.5bn), saw revenues rise 68pc year-on-year in its first set of results as a public company. The firm’s smartphone segment, its largest business sector, reported year-on-year revenue growth of 59pc. The firm reported revenues of $6.6bn for the three months ending June 30. Profits increased to around $2bn, after the company posted a loss in the same quarter the year before. The company will hope ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ericsson, Samsung gain share in network gear as ZTE slumps - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-telecoms-networks-ericsson/ericsson-samsung-gain-share-in-network-gear-as-zte-slumps-idUSKCN1L80WR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA8TQJAFa_NYv_89JZ9qTOgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 09:40:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-telecoms-networks-ericsson/ericsson-samsung-gain-share-in-network-gear-as-zte-slumps-idUSKCN1L80WR" target="_blank"&gt;Ericsson, Samsung gain share in network gear as ZTE slumps&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ericsson increased its share of the mobile networks market in the second quarter, while Samsung Electronics jumped into fourth place, data from industry research firm Dell'Oro showed. Ericsson, the second biggest maker of radio access network (RAN) gear, and Samsung benefited from rising U.S. demand as China's ZTE tumbled into fifth place after it was hit by U.S. sanctions in April. The world's biggest network gear vendors - No.1-ranked Huawei [HWT.UL], Ericsson and third ranked Nokia - all increased their market share quarter on quarter, partly because ZTE's sales plummeted from April onwa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>