<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Vasectomy - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNR296TTJJU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-KE&amp;gl=KE&amp;ceid=KE:en</link><language>en-KE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:07:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Husband who did a vasectomy sues hospital and doctors after his wife conceives and he discovers that the procedure did not work - The Standard</title><link>https://www.standardmedia.co.ke/health/article/2001305341/husband-who-did-a-vasectomy-sues-hospital-and-doctors-after-his-wife-conceives-and-he-discovers-that-the-procedure-did-not-work</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiuQFodHRwczovL3d3dy5zdGFuZGFyZG1lZGlhLmNvLmtlL2hlYWx0aC9hcnRpY2xlLzIwMDEzMDUzNDEvaHVzYmFuZC13aG8tZGlkLWEtdmFzZWN0b215LXN1ZXMtaG9zcGl0YWwtYW5kLWRvY3RvcnMtYWZ0ZXItaGlzLXdpZmUtY29uY2VpdmVzLWFuZC1oZS1kaXNjb3ZlcnMtdGhhdC10aGUtcHJvY2VkdXJlLWRpZC1ub3Qtd29ya9IBjQJodHRwczovL3d3dy1zdGFuZGFyZG1lZGlhLWNvLWtlLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3Mvd3d3LnN0YW5kYXJkbWVkaWEuY28ua2UvbW9iaWxlL2FtcC9hcnRpY2xlLzIwMDEzMDUzNDEvaHVzYmFuZC13aG8tZGlkLWEtdmFzZWN0b215LXN1ZXMtaG9zcGl0YWwtYW5kLWRvY3RvcnMtYWZ0ZXItaGlzLXdpZmUtY29uY2VpdmVzLWFuZC1oZS1kaXNjb3ZlcnMtdGhhdC10aGUtcHJvY2VkdXJlLWRpZC1ub3Qtd29yaz9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.standardmedia.co.ke/health/article/2001305341/husband-who-did-a-vasectomy-sues-hospital-and-doctors-after-his-wife-conceives-and-he-discovers-that-the-procedure-did-not-work" target="_blank"&gt;Husband who did a vasectomy sues hospital and doctors after his wife conceives and he discovers that the procedure did not work&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Standard&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Man says his wife became pregnant and tests revealed he was not sterile.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.standardmedia.co.ke">The Standard</source></item><item><title>Seriously? MEN taking part in ground-breaking shoulder rub birth control - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445792-male-birth-control-trial/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPNFOs_2JI-UeVqCiFj0ffMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445792-male-birth-control-trial/" target="_blank"&gt;Seriously? MEN taking part in ground-breaking shoulder rub birth control&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first-ever US patient has undergone testing for male birth control. The contraception works as a gel that men rub on their shoulders once a day to reduce their sperm count. The international year-long trial, based in Washington, began on Tuesday with the first US couple, the second US couple started their trial on Friday while a third US male will be joining later. The groundbreaking study involves 420 couples in total from seven different countries including Chile, England, Scotland, Kenya, Sweden and Italy. The NES/T gel works by inhibiting a man’s natural testosterone production and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>The Barrier To Male Hormonal Birth Control Isn't Science, It's Men - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-male-birth-control_us_5c06f570e4b0fc236110db93</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB92CR3v3OwS4A8Rli8_HaIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:04:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-male-birth-control_us_5c06f570e4b0fc236110db93" target="_blank"&gt;The Barrier To Male Hormonal Birth Control Isn't Science, It's Men&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On today’s episode of “Things We Do To Make Dudes’ Lives Unnecessarily Easier,” a clinical trial recently started for a new male birth control gel. All a guy has to do is apply the gel to his arms and shoulders daily for a few months and his sperm count will, in theory, drop to such low levels that producing babies won’t be a concern. I have thoughts. First off, I’m all for men getting involved in the birth control process. Quite frankly, we don’t rise to the occasion often enough (dad joke completely intended). Guys have been taking a back seat for too long when it comes to contraception ―...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>New Male Contraceptive Gel Under Development: Where Do You Think It Goes? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/12/01/new-male-contraceptive-gel-under-development-where-do-you-think-it-goes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBXR-34dK6bBchs38amW128qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 20:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2018/12/01/new-male-contraceptive-gel-under-development-where-do-you-think-it-goes/" target="_blank"&gt;New Male Contraceptive Gel Under Development: Where Do You Think It Goes?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Condoms have been a mainstay of male contraceptives. However, many men have not been using them. (Photo: Getty Images) A clinical trial funded by the National Institutes of Health (NIH) will be evaluating a new contraceptive gel for men to use. It’s not on the market yet. But it is designed for men to shoulder some more responsibility for birth control. Literally. The phrase “put one’s back into it” typically means “make a strenuous effort”, according to Dictionary.com. And yes, effort during sex is often appreciated. However, if eventually approved by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Chelsea Handler On Why She's Leading The Women's March At Sundance - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/chelsea-handler-on-why-shes-leading-the-womens-march-at-sundance_us_587e81c7e4b0c147f0bb8ea0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBoW7Ip4FYoNM0wVnYaKDd4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 22:14:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/chelsea-handler-on-why-shes-leading-the-womens-march-at-sundance_us_587e81c7e4b0c147f0bb8ea0" target="_blank"&gt;Chelsea Handler On Why She's Leading The Women's March At Sundance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chelsea Handler will be leading a women’s march from the Sundance Film Festival in Park City, Ut. this weekend ― and in a new guest column for The Hollywood Reporter, she wrote exactly why. “There is a groundswell of passion and conviction rising among women and men,” she wrote. “We have an opportunity right now to stand together and use our voices to fight for the very rights women fought for and won years ago.” Handler cites recently announced GOP plans of defunding Planned Parenthood and dismantling the Affordable Care Act as reasons that everyone ― not just women ― should be marching. “...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Texas Rep. Jessica Farrar Trolls GOP By Proposing $100 Fine For Men Who Masturbate - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/texas-fine-for-masturbating_us_58c5f8f0e4b054a0ea6b68d9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI-2G05vQos9tNKyQ6fqYcYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 06:29:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/texas-fine-for-masturbating_us_58c5f8f0e4b054a0ea6b68d9" target="_blank"&gt;Texas Rep. Jessica Farrar Trolls GOP By Proposing $100 Fine For Men Who Masturbate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Democratic lawmaker in Texas has proposed legislation that would fine men $100 for masturbating and require rectal exams before they get a vasectomy, a colonoscopy or a Viagra prescription. State Rep. Jessica Farrar, of Houston, called her bill “satirical,” but said it was meant to highlight the struggles women faced while accessing health care under the restrictive reproductive laws pushed by the state’s GOP-led legislature. Her bill promotes similarly invasive restrictions on men, including the fine for “emissions outside a woman’s vagina” which “will be considered an act against an unb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Tennessee county inmates get reduced jail time for getting a vasectomy - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/07/20/us/white-county-inmate-vasectomy-trnd/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOi_h4-V0cvcVei5eAzQawAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 01:26:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/07/20/us/white-county-inmate-vasectomy-trnd/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tennessee county inmates get reduced jail time for getting a vasectomy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, you read that right. Inmates in White County, Tennessee, can shave 30 days off their jail sentence if they undergo an elective birth control procedure. Both male and female inmates can volunteer for the new program. Women receive a Nexplanon implant in their arm, which provides up to three years of continuous birth control. Men undergo a vasectomy. The procedures are free and conducted by the Tennessee Department of Health. General Sessions Judge Sam Benningfield signed a standing order on May 15 enforcing the program. "I hope to encourage them to take personal responsibility and give ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The male pill: what is it, and how soon (if ever) will it be available? - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/men/thinking-man/male-pill-soon-ever-will-available/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFXOTsNZaO4JBxR99LMYT3wqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDw2bcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 12:43:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/men/thinking-man/male-pill-soon-ever-will-available/" target="_blank"&gt;The male pill: what is it, and how soon (if ever) will it be available?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We men are rather oblivious when it comes to the pill. As the female population will attest, it is a right pain. Side effects include mood swings, intermenstrual spotting, nausea, and many, many more. And yet, since the first rubber condoms became available in 1855, there has been no other temporary male contraceptive – no alternative to the pill for us chaps. Today is the tenth World Contraception Day, and while the female pill has now been around for almost 70 years, there remains no male equivalent on pharmacy shelves. So the question that presents itself is: why? And, by extension, what...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>FitBit saves 73-year-old woman’s life by detecting unusual heart rate - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/fitbit-save-elderly-woman-life-patricia-lauder-heart-rate-detect-unusual-73-year-old-harwinton-us-a7670696.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHLrQNQROou7aotIiAjLkKkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 15:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/fitbit-save-elderly-woman-life-patricia-lauder-heart-rate-detect-unusual-73-year-old-harwinton-us-a7670696.html" target="_blank"&gt;FitBit saves 73-year-old woman’s life by detecting unusual heart rate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman says her fitness tracker helped save her life after it spotted abnormalities in her heart rate. Patricia Lauder, a 73-year-old retiree from the US, had been battling a sinus infection which she had thought was due to the changing season. - Read more Woman thinks her fitbit is broken, turns out she's pregnant But, when her FitBit alerted her to a resting heart rate of more than 140 beats per minute, compared to her normal 60 to 70, she began to get worried. This prompted Lauder to call for an ambulance, and first responders confirmed what the device had been telling her. At the hospi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>World Vasectomy Day: 11 things you need to know about the snip - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/men/health/11-things-about-vasectomies-that-you-need-to-know-but-were-too-a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELaWEcX0g5nOrjHVCviA8rsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDw2bcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 10:26:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/men/health/11-things-about-vasectomies-that-you-need-to-know-but-were-too-a/" target="_blank"&gt;World Vasectomy Day: 11 things you need to know about the snip&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may be a straightforward procedure that hundreds of thousands of men undergo each year, but the vasectomy still strikes fear into many. Today is the fourth annual World Vasectomy Day, a global celebration of men who choose the method, with a view to convincing the naysayers that it's the right option for men concerned about family planning. Last month it was reported that the number of vasectomies performed in the UK has fallen by two thirds in the past decade. “People worry massively and have lots of misconceptions about it – how painful it is, the impact on their sex life, whether they...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Fine men who masturbate for act against unborn child': Read the official bill in full - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/masturbation-fine-bill-unborn-child-read-it-in-full-official-a7629511.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFotdmBaKuBpfrnNU4h3PxwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/masturbation-fine-bill-unborn-child-read-it-in-full-official-a7629511.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Fine men who masturbate for act against unborn child': Read the official bill in full&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Texas politician introduced a bill that would see men who masturbated fined $100 (£82) for committing “an act against an unborn child”. Jessica Farrar created the “Men’s Right To Know Act” to highlight how women are unfairly targeted by regulations in reproductive health care. The legislation, which the Democrat introduced last week, would ensure men were penalised for ejaculating outside a vagina or a sanctioned medical clinic. Ms Farrar said the bill, which imposes a 24-hour waiting period if a man wants a vasectomy or access to Viagra, mirrors real laws and restrictions faced by women ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Tennessee County Offers Inmates Shorter Sentences If They Get A Vasectomy - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/tennessee-inmates-vasectomy_us_59710906e4b0e79ec1982341</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPV32u7bhyvtbJx0O_vzkjAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 20:58:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/tennessee-inmates-vasectomy_us_59710906e4b0e79ec1982341" target="_blank"&gt;Tennessee County Offers Inmates Shorter Sentences If They Get A Vasectomy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK― A jail in White County, Tennessee, is offering reduced sentences to inmates who agree to a vasectomy or birth control implant, ABC 15 reported Wednesday. Inmates who volunteer are rewarded with 30 days less jail time under an order signed in May by Judge Sam Benningfield. The judge told ABC 15 he hopes the procedures, provided for free by the Tennessee Department of Health, will reduce the number of repeat offenders who can’t afford child support. So far, 32 women have gotten the implant, and 38 men are waiting to have their vasectomies. “I hope to encourage them to take personal ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Inmates offered reduced sentence for vasectomy - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2017/07/21/tennessee-inmate-vasectomy-program-orig-pkg-bpb.wtvf</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKNwRt2sJGtJrnCMVkenonAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 01:24:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2017/07/21/tennessee-inmate-vasectomy-program-orig-pkg-bpb.wtvf" target="_blank"&gt;Inmates offered reduced sentence for vasectomy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A program in White County, Tennessee, is drawing criticism for offering inmates reduced jail sentences in exchange for receiving vasectomies or birth control implants. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Number of vasectomies falls by nearly two-thirds in last ten years, NHS figures show - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/20/number-of-vasectomies-falls-by-nearly-two-thirds-in-last-ten-yea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFQUCQtUg5WTnP8bZqgb0ucqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 07:56:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/20/number-of-vasectomies-falls-by-nearly-two-thirds-in-last-ten-yea/" target="_blank"&gt;Number of vasectomies falls by nearly two-thirds in last ten years, NHS figures show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of vasectomy procedures carried out each year has fallen by nearly two-thirds in the last decade, new figures show. In 2004/05 there were 31,216 vasectomies, but there were just 11,113 in 2014/15, according to NHS statistics. Experts believe men are increasingly waiting until they are older to start families, and said many could be avoiding the procedure in case they divorce and want to have more children later in life. The figures also showed that there was a fall of 16 per cent in the number of vasectomies in just one year from 2013/14 to 2014/15. Man finds out his wife is preg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Use Of The Pull-Out Method Has Almost Doubled Since 2002 - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pull-out-method-use_us_59a854bde4b07e81d3562e7f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrNRHVfv-ywfvH-CQBH-YkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 23:26:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pull-out-method-use_us_59a854bde4b07e81d3562e7f" target="_blank"&gt;Use Of The Pull-Out Method Has Almost Doubled Since 2002&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men don’t have very many options when it comes to contraception they can control. But a new national report reveals that one male contraceptive method — withdrawal — has nearly doubled among unmarried men. While rates of condom use and vasectomy have held steady since 2002, the rate of men who say they use withdrawal, or the so-called pull-out method, has increased from about 10 percent in 2002 to 19 percent by 2015, according to a new study published by the National Center for Health Statistics. Rates of withdrawal ― when a man pulls his penis out of his partner’s vagina before ejaculating...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Male Birth Control Could Finally Take Shape As A Gel - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/janetwburns/2017/02/09/male-birth-control-could-finally-take-shape-as-a-gel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFcfbrCdjBIOmL4nVWfik_8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 16:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/janetwburns/2017/02/09/male-birth-control-could-finally-take-shape-as-a-gel/" target="_blank"&gt;Male Birth Control Could Finally Take Shape As A Gel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo credit: Parsemus Foundation) In the past few decades, the promise of upcoming and effective male birth control has mostly amounted to very clickable rumor, and such a product has yet to come to market. Thanks to an innovative Indian method and one woman’s lifelong determination, though, that rumor may soon become a reality in the form of a simple gel (really). A recent study revealed that the injectable polymer Vasalgel provides effective birth control when implemented among male rhesus macaques, meaning American men could soon be able to give it a whirl. Developed as a social ventur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>As Male Fertility Falters, Tennessee Offers To Sterilize Inmates For Reduced Jail Time - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/janetwburns/2017/07/26/as-male-fertility-falters-tennessee-reportedly-offers-to-sterilize-inmates-for-reduced-jail-time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJOj8opGxHegKIzT1mT6esqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 15:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/janetwburns/2017/07/26/as-male-fertility-falters-tennessee-reportedly-offers-to-sterilize-inmates-for-reduced-jail-time/" target="_blank"&gt;As Male Fertility Falters, Tennessee Offers To Sterilize Inmates For Reduced Jail Time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inmates take a break from working out in an exercise yard at San Quentin State Prison in San Quentin, California, U.S., on Tuesday, Aug. 16, 2016. (Credit: David Paul Morris/Bloomberg) This week, news broke that global sperm counts may be plunging, and that one U.S. state has reportedly begun sterilizing inmates in exchange for shorter sentences. In White County, Tennessee, inmates now have the option to volunteer for sterilization in order to reduce their jail time by up to a month. As the Washington Post reported, dozens of inmates have reportedly already signed up for the operations as p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Ken Bone's Past Comments Come to Light in Reddit Session - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/ken-bones-past-comments-come-light-reddit-session/3550632.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPk0wSS12Mcwhb8-RI2bo9UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 14:09:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/ken-bones-past-comments-come-light-reddit-session/3550632.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ken Bone's Past Comments Come to Light in Reddit Session&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ken Bone is learning what it's like to be famous. The Illinois man who became an internet sensation after asking a question of the candidates while wearing a bright red sweater during Sunday's presidential debate answered questions on Reddit late Thursday and early Friday. Bone included his Reddit username in a Twitter post announcing the session. Those who looked up the name found Bone has shared his thoughts on everything from images of a pregnant woman in a bikini to the increased "sexual satisfaction'' he found after undergoing a vasectomy. In another post, he commented that the 2012 fa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Don't avoid vasectomy for fear of prostate cancer: study - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-cancer-vasectomy-idUSKBN1A229L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEdy1d-PdetVSrQn2rZT3-4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 21:43:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-cancer-vasectomy-idUSKBN1A229L" target="_blank"&gt;Don't avoid vasectomy for fear of prostate cancer: study&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Andrew M. Seaman (Reuters Health) - Men considering a vasectomy shouldn't worry that the procedure will increase their risk of prostate cancer, researchers say. In a review of past research, they did find a slight increase in the risk of prostate cancer among men who had vasectomies, but the study's lead author said the finding might be due to other factors and should not be a concern. "It shouldn’t stop you from gaining something that is otherwise very effective for family planning purposes," said Dr. Bimal Bhindi, of the Mayo Clinic in Rochester, Minnesota. A vasectomy is a minor surgi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Texas Bill Seeks Viagra Waiting Period, $100 Masturbation Fine For Men - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/janetwburns/2017/03/15/texas-health-bill-seeks-viagara-waiting-period-100-masturbation-fine-for-men/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA7LGmDc9vaYUUldYg7WnjAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/janetwburns/2017/03/15/texas-health-bill-seeks-viagara-waiting-period-100-masturbation-fine-for-men/" target="_blank"&gt;Texas Bill Seeks Viagra Waiting Period, $100 Masturbation Fine For Men&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shutterstock Supporters of a new bill hope to build a fairer, more informed healthcare market in Texasby giving reproductive restrictionsa bit more gender equality. Billed as the “Man’s Right to Know Act,” H.R. 4260 would enable legislators and lobbyists to take a more active role in men’s health and reproduction by mirroring (in part) some of the laws steering women and girls in Texas. For men of the Lone Star state, it would mean showing a reasonable amount of self-control and simply refraining from successful self-stimulation outside of a medical context or partner, plus a few mandatory ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Investigation launched after Chinese man claims he was beaten and forced to have a vasectomy by officials - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/14/probe-launched-chinese-man-claims-beaten-forced-have-vasectomy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEh3ySo_VyBSkhV23t8iooYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 14:08:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/02/14/probe-launched-chinese-man-claims-beaten-forced-have-vasectomy/" target="_blank"&gt;Investigation launched after Chinese man claims he was beaten and forced to have a vasectomy by officials&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An investigation has been ordered after a Chinese man claimed he was beaten and forced to have a vasectomy in the office of officials who accused him of flouting family planning laws, as China seeks to increase the birth rate. Hu Zhenggao, said in an online post that officials "violently threatened" him before police took away his wife and son and refused to return them until the surgery was complete. Mr Hu, aged 42, had three children from a previous marriage when he lived in Zhaotong, in the south-western province of Yunnan. His former wife underwent a forced sterilisation in 2000 for flo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Mom Of Three Gives Husband Hilarious Cake The Day Before His Vasectomy - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mom-of-three-gives-husband-hilarious-cake-the-day-before-his-vasectomy_us_59bbfb9de4b0edff971ba82c?ncid=NEWSSTAND0001</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFRWrCdM0NgW0GQrKM_ykXwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 17:16:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mom-of-three-gives-husband-hilarious-cake-the-day-before-his-vasectomy_us_59bbfb9de4b0edff971ba82c?ncid=NEWSSTAND0001" target="_blank"&gt;Mom Of Three Gives Husband Hilarious Cake The Day Before His Vasectomy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The day before her husband’s vasectomy, Amber Cole decided to surprise her husband with something hilariously sweet. Her husband, Matt, had his vasectomy appointment on Tuesday. The couple decided together that they were done having kids after welcoming their three boys. On Monday, Amber baked a cake for Matt as “a treat to snack on while he was stuck on the couch” after his appointment. This was no ordinary cake, though. On the top in blue icing, Amber wrote, “I’m glad you can’t knock me up!” “It was truly the most fitting cake for the occasion,” she told HuffPost. “He thought it was hilar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Man up, guys – you’re a snip away from being heroes - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2017/jun/24/man-up-guys-snip-vasectomy-women-contraception</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVJLtAMTf5kGNWERlO-Aq0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCcwRU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 05:45:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2017/jun/24/man-up-guys-snip-vasectomy-women-contraception" target="_blank"&gt;Man up, guys – you’re a snip away from being heroes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the four years since my daughter was born it has become a regular and uncomfortable occurrence that my wife and I wait nervously for proof that we haven’t been caught out by our relaxed attitude to contraception. So I decided to put an end to it once and for all by having the snip. I made the decision some time ago, my wife and I having agreed that we didn’t want to expand our family beyond the two children we already have. So I went to see my GP for a referral. All well and good. The consultation took five minutes and I was sent the paperwork from the clinic asking me to book an appoint...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Satirical' law proposes men be fined for masturbating - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-03-14/satirical-law-proposes-men-be-fined-for-masturbating/8353194</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI5wGsBeNIe4mDmqK4s_-EwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 07:47:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-03-14/satirical-law-proposes-men-be-fined-for-masturbating/8353194" target="_blank"&gt;'Satirical' law proposes men be fined for masturbating&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Texas politician has proposed a bill which would fine men $100 for masturbating in a bid to flip the switch on the struggles women face in accessing reproductive healthcare — particularly regarding abortion — by targeting men. House Bill 4260 was submitted by Jessica Farrar, a Democratic member of the Texas House of Representatives, and states that masturbation "will be considered an act against an unborn child". As per the bill, "emissions outside of a woman's vagina, or created outside of a health or medical facility" would attract a $100 fine for "failing to preserve the sanctity of li...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Contraceptive gel that creates ‘reversible vasectomy’ shown to be effective in monkeys - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/contraceptive-gel-vasalgel-reverse-vasectomy-effective-monkey-trials-men-snip-reversible-a7566856.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJU1e_t64J92J1KBpXFtjdUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 10:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/contraceptive-gel-vasalgel-reverse-vasectomy-effective-monkey-trials-men-snip-reversible-a7566856.html" target="_blank"&gt;Contraceptive gel that creates ‘reversible vasectomy’ shown to be effective in monkeys&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An injectable contraceptive gel that acts as a ‘reversible vasectomy’ is a step closer to being offered to men following successful trials on monkeys. Vasalgel is injected into the vas deferens, the small duct between the testicles and the urethra. It has so far been found to prevent 100 per cent of conceptions. The gel fills the interior of the passage, allowing seminal fluid to be released during ejaculation but blocking sperm, which are reabsorbed by the body. Read more - ‘First man in UK to give birth’ finds sperm donor on Facebook - Male contraceptive pill could become reality - New Ze...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Antonio Cromartie Welcomes 14th Child, 3rd After Vasectomy - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2017/09/10/antonio-cromartie-welcomes-14th-child-3rd-after-vasectomy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN86YQh0VFz9io44h_6H21kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 15:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2017/09/10/antonio-cromartie-welcomes-14th-child-3rd-after-vasectomy/" target="_blank"&gt;Antonio Cromartie Welcomes 14th Child, 3rd After Vasectomy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Allen Robinson of Jacksonville breaks free from the tackle of Antonio Cromartie (L) of Indianapolis during the NFL International Series match between Indianapolis Colts and Jacksonville Jaguars at Wembley Stadium on October 2, 2016 in London, England. (Photo by Ben Hoskins/Getty Images) It’s probably safe to say that Antonio Cromartie’s vasectomy did not work.According to Jimmy Traina writing forSports Illustrated, Cromartie just announced the August 30th birth of his14th child (baby girl Jhett Paxton), his third since his reported vasectomy in 2013. The former San Diego Chargers, Arizona C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Men – don't be squeamish, have the balls to have a vasectomy - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/oct/21/men-squeamish-vasectomy-statistics-contraception</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJJNw3o1NUpz8G2zGElGG9oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 15:55:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/oct/21/men-squeamish-vasectomy-statistics-contraception" target="_blank"&gt;Men – don't be squeamish, have the balls to have a vasectomy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vasectomies can go wrong. But then so can crossing the road and eating cashew nuts. It’s a small thing, gents, let’s face it, a very small thing. Mine took place in 2008. Yes, I had to wear two pairs of tight pants for a few days, and refused to stand in the wall at free-kicks for weeks. Yes, I took a couple of days off work and sat on the sofa watching movies and eating painkillers. But other than that, it was a rather unremarkable experience. Related: Vasectomy – Pass notes No 3,281 I’d like to be able to report that my surgeon had a twinkle of irony in his eye as he said: “You may feel a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>A cut above: the rise of the luxury brosectomy - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/men/thinking-man/cut-rise-luxury-brosectomy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECzPBRSO7-N4Wl19nkt-0o4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDw2bcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 15:33:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/men/thinking-man/cut-rise-luxury-brosectomy/" target="_blank"&gt;A cut above: the rise of the luxury brosectomy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This guy’s possibility of even getting laid for the rest of his life is pretty low. Is this really a necessary procedure?” It's not a question you'd expect to hear in the waiting room of a urology clinic, just moments before a man's vasectomy. But then, this wasn't a normal waiting room. Jeb Lopez, 44, and his best friend Rob Ferretti, 36, had paid $3,250 for a 'vasectomy party' at Obsidian Men's Health clinic. They'd taken the day off work, and now they were sitting in colour-coordinated dressing gowns, enjoying a big screen TV, snacks, and a tumbler of Glenfiddich whisky on ice that woul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>We're One Step Closer To Long-Term Birth Control For Men - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/vasalgel-birth-control-men_us_589a33cae4b09bd304be6303</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKiC0yFHUc5gNrr430ePyBYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2GuAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 23:14:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/vasalgel-birth-control-men_us_589a33cae4b09bd304be6303" target="_blank"&gt;We're One Step Closer To Long-Term Birth Control For Men&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new experiment testing a non-hormonal, injectable form of contraception on male monkeys has proven successful, bringing us one step closer to long-term birth control for men. In a yearslong study involving 16 adult rhesus monkeys, scientists found that a gel-like polymer called Vasalgel, injected into ducts in the monkey’s testes, successfully blocked their sperm and prevented female monkeys from conceiving. The experiment showed that the monkeys with Vasalgel in their testes did not reproduce with female monkeys who shared their habitat, even though scientists observed them participating...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Obamacare in jeopardy, states protect no-cost contraception, including vasectomy - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/01/20/health/states-protect-no-cost-contraception-and-vasectomy-aca/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEObKQA4WTAnotqJYsWmCQZwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 04:25:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/01/20/health/states-protect-no-cost-contraception-and-vasectomy-aca/" target="_blank"&gt;Obamacare in jeopardy, states protect no-cost contraception, including vasectomy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even before President Donald Trump suggested Obamacare was in jeopardy, Republican cries of "replace and repeal" inspired some states to protect the no-cost contraceptive benefit guaranteed under the federal bill. California, Illinois, Maryland and Vermont have passed laws over the past two years requiring cost-free coverage of birth control options. Like the Obamacare provision, the state laws cover one type of contraception per person -- including IUDs, oral contraception and tubal ligation. But all of the states, except California, also extended this benefit to include one other, far les...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Female politician proposes $100 fine for men who masturbate in bid to challenge US abortion laws - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/03/13/female-politician-proposes-100-fine-men-masturbate-bid-challenge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAZmZQNjNagw-YNqTsd6XSwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 17:46:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/03/13/female-politician-proposes-100-fine-men-masturbate-bid-challenge/" target="_blank"&gt;Female politician proposes $100 fine for men who masturbate in bid to challenge US abortion laws&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;House Bill 4260 has all the legal jargon of any other draft law presented to the Texas legislature. And its stated aim – to protect unborn children everywhere – is a hot topic among American politicians. But read its three pages and it turns out Jessica Farrar, a Democratic member of the Texas House of Representatives, has an unusual way of going about it: Fining men $100 for masturbating anywhere except in an approved medical facility. Her aim is clear. The bill is a satirical attack on the way male politicians interfere in women’s bodies and seeks to apply the same health restrictions, at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>16 types of birth control you need to know about - plus their pros and cons - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/sex/16-types-birth-control-need-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENMt6n-9qk6gv30kPLeXWLYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDqy7cF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:48:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/sex/16-types-birth-control-need-know/" target="_blank"&gt;16 types of birth control you need to know about - plus their pros and cons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to birth control many women tend to stick to the Pill or condoms. But there are actually 16 options available right now - and what better time to acquaint yourself with them than on World Contraception Day. Here's the lowdown... When it comes to contraception, many women just think of condoms and the Pill. A Telegraph Women and British Pregnancy Advisory Service (BPAS) study shows 63 per cent of more than 1,000 British women primarily use these types of birth control. It means that the other 13 forms of contraception – yes, there are now a total of 16 – don’t really get a look...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Successful male contraceptive gel trial brings new form of birth control closer - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2017/feb/07/successful-male-contraceptive-gel-trial-brings-new-form-of-birth-control-closer-vasalgel</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIgrkkyf-YI6Os8E_vxrb6MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2017/feb/07/successful-male-contraceptive-gel-trial-brings-new-form-of-birth-control-closer-vasalgel" target="_blank"&gt;Successful male contraceptive gel trial brings new form of birth control closer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A male contraceptive gel has been found to work reliably in a trial in primates, bringing the prospect of an alternative form of birth control for humans closer. The product, called Vasalgel, is designed to be a reversible and less invasive form of vasectomy and in the latest study was 100% effective at preventing conception. A blob of the gel is injected into the sperm-carrying tube, known as the vas deferens, and acts as a long-lasting barrier. Related: Contraceptive jabs for men may work - but what happened to the male pill? Previous tests in smaller animals showed the procedure could be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Chart of the day: How effective is your birth control? - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-28/chart-of-the-day-birth-control-effectiveness/10312830</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENAu_BxvRgzjG7-7RwcFSS4qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:31:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-28/chart-of-the-day-birth-control-effectiveness/10312830" target="_blank"&gt;Chart of the day: How effective is your birth control?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By health reporter Olivia Willis Oral contraception is by far the most popular method, followed by condom use, and vasectomy. Very few women use long-acting reversible contraception, such as contraceptive implants and intrauterine devices (IUDs), which are the most effective in preventing pregnancy. The effectiveness of different contraceptives ranges from more than 99 per cent (less than one pregnancy per 100 women in one year) to 76 per cent (up to 24 pregnancies per 100 women in one year). That's because many contraceptive methods are affected by human error, such as forgetting to take t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Televangelist Accused Of Sexual Abuse, Forcing Vasectomy: The Importance Of Hearing All Victims - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michellefabio/2018/08/27/televangelist-accused-of-sexual-abuse-forcing-vasectomy-the-importance-of-hearing-all-victims/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaeMQOhOOPfPlM5XeGCr3IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/michellefabio/2018/08/27/televangelist-accused-of-sexual-abuse-forcing-vasectomy-the-importance-of-hearing-all-victims/" target="_blank"&gt;Televangelist Accused Of Sexual Abuse, Forcing Vasectomy: The Importance Of Hearing All Victims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;American evangelican preacher Ernest Angley, 1980. (Photo by Paul Natkin/Getty Images) These days, much of the legal talk surrounding religion concerns allegations of decades-long sexual abuse by Catholic priests, but unfortunately it isn’t the only house of worship being sued into facing its demons. This particular story, so far, though, hasn’t been making the kind of headlines it should. Televangelist Ernest Angley, 97, through his church, Grace Cathedral in Cuyahoga Falls, Ohio, has been accused of making life a living hell for one of his employees (I’m paraphrasing) by forcing him to un...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>My life in sex: ‘Erectile dysfunction eats away at your confidence’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/jul/13/life-in-sex-erectile-dysfunction-confidence-vasectomy-patient</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDeJgpvE37jeDrtC9DnoeMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCcwRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 09:00:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/jul/13/life-in-sex-erectile-dysfunction-confidence-vasectomy-patient" target="_blank"&gt;My life in sex: ‘Erectile dysfunction eats away at your confidence’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;My wife and I have been together for more than 15 years and enjoyed a healthy sex life until I had a vasectomy four years ago, and started suffering from erectile dysfunction. My GP prescribed me the blue pills, but all they did was give me a terrible headache. My marriage became strained; erectile dysfunction takes away more than your sex life – it eats away at your confidence. We went to a psychosexual therapist, whom we saw for more than a year and we were put back together, slowly; through intimacy exercises then talk therapy. Last year, while making love, I started to feel pain in one ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Vasectomies Slowly Gaining Acceptance in Kenya - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/vasectomies-slowly-gaining-acceptance-in-kenya/4413227.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMElzupggcPOeev0HHwVY98qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 16:59:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/vasectomies-slowly-gaining-acceptance-in-kenya/4413227.html" target="_blank"&gt;Vasectomies Slowly Gaining Acceptance in Kenya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Kenya and many parts of the world, family planning is mostly considered a woman’s responsibility. Procedures that affect men, like vasectomies, are often shunned and stigmatized. But in Kenya, vasectomies are slowly gaining acceptance. In April, a group of doctors performed about 70 free vasectomies on men in Nairobi. Dr. Charles Ochieng was part of the team. He says 70 seemed like a low turnout, but that figure indicated progress. “Vasectomy is not very popular, not just in Kenya but in sub-Saharan Africa. I think the prevalence rate could be now at 1.4 percent so we are trying to c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Opinion: Here's what's on the horizon for a male contraceptive pill - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-22/male-contraceptive-pill-vasalgel-sperm-mens-fertility/9786070</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGLdNGVgNHNR2lMuboUgRMsqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 01:03:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-22/male-contraceptive-pill-vasalgel-sperm-mens-fertility/9786070" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: Here's what's on the horizon for a male contraceptive pill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The female contraceptive pill has helped millions of women take control of their fertility and reproductive health since it became available in 1961. Yet a male equivalent has yet to be fully developed. This effectively leaves men with only two viable contraceptive options: condoms or a vasectomy. The idea of creating a male contraceptive has been around almost as long as the female contraceptive. In theory, targeting the production of sperm should be a simple process. The biology of sperm production and how they swim towards the egg are well understood. Yet, studies aimed at developing an ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Japanese victims of forced sterilization file more lawsuits over inhumane eugenics law - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/427059-japan-forced-sterilization-lawsuits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOgFneGGH3GMZFcv7XVOZ9cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 01:38:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/427059-japan-forced-sterilization-lawsuits/" target="_blank"&gt;Japanese victims of forced sterilization file more lawsuits over inhumane eugenics law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three Japanese pensioners have filed separate lawsuits against the government over irreversible damage caused by forced sterilization conducted under Japan’s eugenics law, which was in place for almost 50 years. Faced with life-long hardship, three Japanese citizens in their 70s filed lawsuits on Thursday, seeking total compensation of 80 million yen ($720,000) for being forcefully sterilized under a 1948 Eugenics Protection Law that was designed to “prevent the birth of poor-quality descendants.” The trio, two men and a woman, are among at least 16,500 people who were forced to give up the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Male birth control pill one step closer to reality, researchers say - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/03/20/health/male-birth-control-pill-study/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDW-jtgivDGZn90vUwCwNMcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 17:19:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/03/20/health/male-birth-control-pill-study/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Male birth control pill one step closer to reality, researchers say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women have many choices when it comes to avoiding pregnancy, but men have only two. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, 99% of sexually active women used at least one contraceptive method at some point between 2006 and 2010. Here's a look at a variety of birth control methods and how they each work. A male condom is a thin covering worn on the penis during intercourse. It can prevent sexually transmitted diseases, and is about 82% effective at preventing pregnancy. Shutterstock During a vasectomy, a surgeon cuts the vas deferens, the tubes that carry sperm from the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>This Arrow Poison May Make Male Birth Control a Reality - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/this-arrow-poison-may-make-male-birth-control-a-reality</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKD6IzsLfpQK3e2UpNXETMgqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMOif7QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 10:27:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/this-arrow-poison-may-make-male-birth-control-a-reality" target="_blank"&gt;This Arrow Poison May Make Male Birth Control a Reality&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast By Gunda Georg, professor of medicinal chemistry and director of the Institute for Therapeutics Discovery and Development, University of Minnesota; Jon Hawkinson, research professor of medicinal chemistry and associate program director of the Institute for Therapeutics Discovery and Development, University of Minnesota; and Shameem Syeda, principal scientist at the Institute for Therapeutics Discovery and Development, University of Minnesota. After decades of research, development of a male birth control may now be one step closer. My...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Ibuprofen use could hinder testosterone production and impact male infertility, study suggests - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/ibuprofen-testosterone-production-negative-impact-male-fertility-compensated-hypogonadism-research-a8149026.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDfIWX-OD7A8JwCZstX7owqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 08:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/ibuprofen-testosterone-production-negative-impact-male-fertility-compensated-hypogonadism-research-a8149026.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ibuprofen use could hinder testosterone production and impact male infertility, study suggests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prolonged use of ibuprofen could hinder testosterone production by the testicles, research suggests. The study found long-term use of the over-the-counter painkiller resulted in compensated hypogonadism, a condition prevalent among elderly men and associated with reproductive and physical disorders. Researchers based their findings on a six-week clinical experiment of 31 male participants, aged between 18 and 35. Writing in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences (PNAS), the study authors said: “Concern has been raised over declining male reproductive health in humans. “...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>2017 Changed How We’ll Have Babies - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/2017-changed-how-well-think-about-babies?source=hunt-for-the-cure&amp;via=rss</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL0JDUvfJAX93aFLjoqF09EqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMOif7QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 03:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/2017-changed-how-well-think-about-babies?source=hunt-for-the-cure&amp;via=rss" target="_blank"&gt;2017 Changed How We’ll Have Babies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;erierika It used to be that reproduction was a seemingly straightforward thing: A man’s sperm met and clung to a woman’s egg. If the the stars aligned and the sperm successfully fertilized the egg, nine (and some change) months of waiting would result in a baby. But it’s not always that straightforward. Couples deal with infertility, they may not always be a male-female pair, they don’t always want the sperm to meet the egg, and even when things work out, a baby might enter the world much sooner than it should. Reproduction was never as straightforward as the story we got told in sex ed cla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>World's first male contraceptive gel is set for trial next year - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/male-contraception-gel-world-trial-2018-four-months-sperm-levels-a8124516.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSs1VEAAmfTY3Gh5U6f26sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 13:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/male-contraception-gel-world-trial-2018-four-months-sperm-levels-a8124516.html" target="_blank"&gt;World's first male contraceptive gel is set for trial next year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first-ever contraceptive gel, which dramatically reduces sperm count in men, is to be tested next year. Starting in April, the clinical trial will run for about four years and will be the largest effort in the U.S. to test a hormonal form of birth control for men. Currently, men’s only options for birth control are condoms or a vasectomy, after trials testing an injection were halted in 2012 over fears it may cause depression and suicidal thoughts. - Read more Women are switching to apps as a form of hormone-free birth control However this new gel, which is rubbed into men’s upper arms ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Woman throws ‘balls voyage’ party after husband decides to get vasectomy - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/woman-throws-balls-voyage-party-husband-vasectomy-kimberly-hemperly-grenada-mississippi-a8124636.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAtLQTG7IH8BuSFT9E52ZhEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 14:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/woman-throws-balls-voyage-party-husband-vasectomy-kimberly-hemperly-grenada-mississippi-a8124636.html" target="_blank"&gt;Woman throws ‘balls voyage’ party after husband decides to get vasectomy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Mississippi-based mother has celebrated her husband’s decision to get a vasectomy by throwing a “Balls Voyage” party, complete with personalised merchandise. Kimberly Hemperly announced that her and her husband Jason would not be adding to their family in a Facebook post which has since gone viral. With two children already in the mix, the family decided it was time to call it quits and Jason offered to take matters into his own hands to finalise their choice. “We have an announcement to make!” Hemperly begins. “We are thrilled to say we will NOT be adding anymore tiny humans to our famil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Judge rebuked after offering reduced jail time in exchange for vasectomies - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/11/21/us/tn-judge-vasectomy-birth-control-reprimand-trnd/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtXE4a74mDZkOmayAi8L4wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 19:39:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/11/21/us/tn-judge-vasectomy-birth-control-reprimand-trnd/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Judge rebuked after offering reduced jail time in exchange for vasectomies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Tennessee Board of Judicial Conduct has publicly reprimanded a judge who had offered reduced jail time to inmates who agreed to get long-term birth control procedures. Judge Sam Benningfield had offered a 30-day jail credit to female inmates who received a free Nexplanon implant, which provides up to three years of continuous birth control, and to male inmates who received a vasectomy, according to the board's letter. Benningfield, a White County General Sessions judge, signed the standing order on May 15 enforcing the program. Judge Sam Benningfield WTVF "I hope to encourage them to ta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Number of vasectomies plunges amid fears relationships won't last - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/10/05/number-vasectomies-plunges-amid-fears-relationships-wont-last/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDivsFjekKgu4plvBdm-x-QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/10/05/number-vasectomies-plunges-amid-fears-relationships-wont-last/" target="_blank"&gt;Number of vasectomies plunges amid fears relationships won't last&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of vasectomies carried out by NHS hospitals and clinics has dropped by nearly two thirds in a decade, official figures show. Experts said the trend could reflect social shifts, with greater awareness that relationships might not last, and a reluctance to take steps seen as irreversible. It could also be a symptom of deepening NHS rationing, they said, or changes in practices with the surgery increasingly offered by GP practices. The new data from NHS Digital shows 29,344 vasectomies took place in hospitals and sexual health clinics in 2005/6, falling to 10,880 in 2015/16. Over 20...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>My husband went for a vasectomy but bottled it - I'm furious - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/sex/husband-went-vasectomy-bottled-furious/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKoOqFyDvsZIpIh3P_eU9jQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDqy7cF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 11:14:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/sex/husband-went-vasectomy-bottled-furious/" target="_blank"&gt;My husband went for a vasectomy but bottled it - I'm furious&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;My husband got as far as taking a seat in the vasectomy clinic waiting room, before deciding it really wasn’t for him. He returned home, as fertile as ever, unable to accept that I wouldn’t ever agree to “just one more baby”. At that point we had three daughters and were 15 years into a deeply committed marriage. I was adamant: I didn’t want any more children. But it fell on deaf ears. Even now, 10 years on - with him now 53 and me 48 - he says he still hasn’t ruled out the idea we might have another. I admire his optimism, but clearly my best hope for infertility between us is now the meno...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Having a vasectomy: what they don't tell you - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/men/thinking-man/having-vasectomy-dont-tell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOkPtF2jqqLMzBoN98X_wgIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDw2bcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 08:45:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/men/thinking-man/having-vasectomy-dont-tell/" target="_blank"&gt;Having a vasectomy: what they don't tell you&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of vasectomies carried out by the NHS has dropped by nearly two thirds in a decade. Could it be because men are waking up to the terrible truth of the snip? When the surgeon who was about to perform my vasectomy entered the room where I sat waiting on a bed, naked from the waist down, I started singing Gilbert &amp; Sullivan’s “Behold the Lord High Executioner”. He – a small, twitchy man with strands of black hair combed across a balding pate – smiled thinly, as if thinking, “Let’s see if you’re still feeling so jolly in a couple of minutes, my man.” He immediately grew testy on seei...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item></channel></rss>