<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Renewable energy - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFptYUhNU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-KE&amp;gl=KE&amp;ceid=KE:en</link><language>en-KE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:57:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Croatia's HEP to invest $1.85 billion in renewable energy by 2030 - reuters.com</title><link>https://af.reuters.com/article/commoditiesNews/idAFL8N1YB4RW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiPGh0dHBzOi8vYWYucmV1dGVycy5jb20vYXJ0aWNsZS9jb21tb2RpdGllc05ld3MvaWRBRkw4TjFZQjRSV9IBggFodHRwczovL21vYmlsZS1yZXV0ZXJzLWNvbS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL21vYmlsZS5yZXV0ZXJzLmNvbS9hcnRpY2xlL2FtcC9hZi9pZEFGTDhOMVlCNFJXP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:56:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://af.reuters.com/article/commoditiesNews/idAFL8N1YB4RW" target="_blank"&gt;Croatia's HEP to invest $1.85 billion in renewable energy by 2030&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;reuters.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Croatia's state-run power utility HEP aims to boost renewable energy to 50 percent of its total capacity from the current 35 percent, investing 1 billion Croatian ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://af.reuters.com">reuters.com</source></item><item><title>Kenya on track to achieve full transition to renewable energy by 2020, Uhuru says - Capital FM Kenya</title><link>https://www.capitalfm.co.ke/news/2018/12/kenya-on-track-to-achieve-full-transition-to-renewable-energy-by-2020-uhuru-says/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiemh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNhcGl0YWxmbS5jby5rZS9uZXdzLzIwMTgvMTIva2VueWEtb24tdHJhY2stdG8tYWNoaWV2ZS1mdWxsLXRyYW5zaXRpb24tdG8tcmVuZXdhYmxlLWVuZXJneS1ieS0yMDIwLXVodXJ1LXNheXMv0gHKAWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LWNhcGl0YWxmbS1jby1rZS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy5jYXBpdGFsZm0uY28ua2UvbmV3cy8yMDE4LzEyL2tlbnlhLW9uLXRyYWNrLXRvLWFjaGlldmUtZnVsbC10cmFuc2l0aW9uLXRvLXJlbmV3YWJsZS1lbmVyZ3ktYnktMjAyMC11aHVydS1zYXlzL2FtcC8_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:39:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.capitalfm.co.ke/news/2018/12/kenya-on-track-to-achieve-full-transition-to-renewable-energy-by-2020-uhuru-says/" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya on track to achieve full transition to renewable energy by 2020, Uhuru says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Capital FM Kenya&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIVASHA, Kenya Dec 4 —President Uhuru Kenyatta has said his government has added 1063 megawatts of electricity to the national grid since taking over ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.capitalfm.co.ke">Capital FM Kenya</source></item><item><title>New geothermal plant to close gap to renewable sources - Citizen TV</title><link>https://citizentv.co.ke/business/new-geothermal-plant-close-gap-renewable-sources-221938/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiWWh0dHBzOi8vY2l0aXplbnR2LmNvLmtlL2J1c2luZXNzL25ldy1nZW90aGVybWFsLXBsYW50LWNsb3NlLWdhcC1yZW5ld2FibGUtc291cmNlcy0yMjE5Mzgv0gGlAWh0dHBzOi8vY2l0aXplbnR2LWNvLWtlLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3MvY2l0aXplbnR2LmNvLmtlL2J1c2luZXNzL25ldy1nZW90aGVybWFsLXBsYW50LWNsb3NlLWdhcC1yZW5ld2FibGUtc291cmNlcy0yMjE5MzgvP2FtcCZhbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:05:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://citizentv.co.ke/business/new-geothermal-plant-close-gap-renewable-sources-221938/" target="_blank"&gt;New geothermal plant to close gap to renewable sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Citizen TV&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Kenyatta ground-breaks the construction of an additional 83 MW unit at Olkaria I to add to existing geothermal energy capacity in the country.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://citizentv.co.ke">Citizen TV</source></item><item><title>Trump targets pair of Obama-era green rules to boost oil, coal - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-energy-trump/trump-targets-pair-of-obama-era-green-rules-to-boost-oil-coal-idUSKBN1O52L7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELksT9A31uzqYGP4p3AkLRQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:56:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-energy-trump/trump-targets-pair-of-obama-era-green-rules-to-boost-oil-coal-idUSKBN1O52L7" target="_blank"&gt;Trump targets pair of Obama-era green rules to boost oil, coal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration took aim at two Obama-era environmental policies on Thursday to boost the oil and coal industries, proposing to open up a bird's wildlife habitat to drilling and mining and remove hurdles to new coal-fired power plant construction. The moves, part of a broader agenda by U.S. President Donald Trump to revive the ailing coal industry and ramp up domestic energy production, come amid increasingly urgent warnings from within his own government about climate change, and as world leaders gather at a United Nations conference to combat planetary warming. Announced separate...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>EPA Moves To Roll Back Coal Plant Rule In A Stunning Rebuke Of Global Climate Talks - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/epa-coal_us_5c096995e4b0b6cdaf5d16ba</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBkVBQRjiMnNK056lkhymJ0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:58:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/epa-coal_us_5c096995e4b0b6cdaf5d16ba" target="_blank"&gt;EPA Moves To Roll Back Coal Plant Rule In A Stunning Rebuke Of Global Climate Talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Environmental Protection Agency on Thursday proposed gutting an Obama-era rule requiring coal-fired power plants to reduce carbon dioxide emissions, defying increasingly desperate international negotiations to scale down planet-warming gases. At a press conference at the agency’s headquarters, Acting Administrator Andrew Wheeler Administrator Andrew Wheeler called the Obama administration’s rule was too strict, calling it “disingenuous” and “not adequately demonstrated,” and said the new proposal would “set high yet achievable standards that are rooted in reality.” “To put it in clear a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Nominee who said renewable energy ‘screws up’ grid gets confirmed by Senate - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nominee-who-said-renewable-energy-screws-up-grid-gets-confirmed-by-senate-2018-12-06</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOyu6UlIW96_HV_wUgaECXAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nominee-who-said-renewable-energy-screws-up-grid-gets-confirmed-by-senate-2018-12-06" target="_blank"&gt;Nominee who said renewable energy ‘screws up’ grid gets confirmed by Senate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASSOCIATED PRESS By Associated Press Workers repair the electrical grid after Hurricane Michael on October 16, 2018 in Panama City, Florida. Hurricane Michael slammed into the Florida Panhandle on October 10, as a category 4 storm causing massive damage and claiming more that 15 lives. Getty Images WASHINGTON (AP) — The Senate has confirmed President Donald Trump’s nominee for a federal energy board, despite a video that shows the nominee saying that renewable energy “screws up” the nation’s electrical grid. The Senate has approved Bernard McNamee’s nomination to the Federal Energy Regulato...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>This Is Why I’m Pledging To Make The Solar Industry More Diverse - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/this-is-why-im-pledging-to-make-the-solar-industry-more-diverse_us_5be1b7afe4b04367a880f592</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFRWjiGU-IZEQfDN27aoBw8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:38:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/this-is-why-im-pledging-to-make-the-solar-industry-more-diverse_us_5be1b7afe4b04367a880f592" target="_blank"&gt;This Is Why I’m Pledging To Make The Solar Industry More Diverse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Abigail Ross Hopper, president and CEO, Solar Energy Industries Association Employing more than 250,000 Americans, the U.S. solar energy industry is starting a revolution, making our economy stronger and our air cleaner every day. The urgent issue we must now address is ensuring those benefits are accessible to people of all races, genders, ethnicities and economic backgrounds. As an industry, we must make diversity a priority — from those we employ to where solar projects are located. As the CEO of the Solar Energy Industries Association, the national association for the solar energy in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Europe Needs More U.S. Liquefied Natural Gas - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/judeclemente/2018/12/07/europe-needs-more-u-s-liquefied-natural-gas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPReKrMyGQUQBMOQFs5EmP8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/judeclemente/2018/12/07/europe-needs-more-u-s-liquefied-natural-gas/" target="_blank"&gt;Europe Needs More U.S. Liquefied Natural Gas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;trade war between USA and EU concept: barbed wire in a hand between american and european union flags While the U.S.-China trade war installs a cease-fire, there is an emerging opportunity for us to better link with our European allies to supply them more energy. After all, Europe has long sought to lower an over reliance on Russian oil and natural gas, and an expanding capacity for the U.S. to export these essential fuels now seems a perfect fit. U.S. gas especially is the clear need for Europe, with the U.S. having mushrooming LNG export terminals along its Gulf Coast and a facility in Ma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Republicans push through controversial Trump energy nominee - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/d2d20bfd35de4617bf056de9884d400d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEtdxzfXpte-Hxcos0OtklsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:36:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/d2d20bfd35de4617bf056de9884d400d" target="_blank"&gt;Republicans push through controversial Trump energy nominee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Senate has confirmed President Donald Trump's nominee for a federal energy board despite a video that shows the nominee saying renewable energy "screws up" the nation's electrical grid. The Republican-controlled Senate approved Bernard McNamee's nomination to the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission on a 50-49 party-line vote Thursday. McNamee now heads the Energy Department's Office of Policy and worked on a stalled effort to bail out struggling coal and nuclear plants. In the video, McNamee says fossil fuels and nuclear energy "keep the lights on" and that renewable ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>How Energy Companies Will Survive When Renewable Energy Is Free - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffmcmahon/2018/12/06/how-energy-companies-will-survive-when-renewable-energy-is-free/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEET8Dv0P9jBk_eJlziIegqkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffmcmahon/2018/12/06/how-energy-companies-will-survive-when-renewable-energy-is-free/" target="_blank"&gt;How Energy Companies Will Survive When Renewable Energy Is Free&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shanghai at night. Getty Images Envision Energy founder and CEO Lei Zhang likes to look at the numbers. And when he looked at the numbers behind the falling cost of renewable energy, he began to worry. “We are convinced renewable energy is going to be dominating,” said Lei, who heads the Shanghai-based energy company. “It is going to give us almost, close to zero cost of energy, eventually, So we started to be worried. What’s the future of the energy company if you actually have almost-zero cost of energy?” Utility-scale solar is reaching 3 cents per kilowatt hour, Lei said, and in Mongolia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Trump promised to rescue the coal industry. But he can't - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/business/coal-power-trump/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBhmCgVZ99Vi_8w1uH4oRTQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 20:13:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/business/coal-power-trump/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump promised to rescue the coal industry. But he can't&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration attempted a daring rescue of the coal country, but the pro-coal agenda is failing to jump-start a renaissance — and analysts don't see one on the horizon. Despite trying for nearly two years to prop up coal by rolling back climate regulations, the industry remains in sharp decline — coal consumption peaked in 2007. The shale boom created a glut of cheap natural gas in America, and the costs to deploy wind and solar continue to plunge. US coal consumption is projected to decline by nearly 4% in 2018 to the lowest level since 1979, the US Energy Information Administra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump's EPA proposes looser carbon limits on new coal plants - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-coal-idUSKBN1O519C</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHcWEkgUwtx8D0Ev4QnQEVsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:28:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-coal-idUSKBN1O519C" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's EPA proposes looser carbon limits on new coal plants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration on Thursday proposed rolling back an Obama-era rule requiring new U.S. coal plants to slash carbon emissions, a move that could crack open the door in coming years for new plants fired by the fossil fuel. The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency's acting administrator, Andrew Wheeler, a former coal lobbyist, announced the proposal. It would allow new coal plants to emit up to 1,900 pounds (862 kg) of carbon dioxide per megawatt-hour of electricity, up from 1,400 pounds now. The move to revive the ailing coal industry, whose share in the U.S. energy mix has been in d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Utility aims for zero carbon emission from electric power - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/8f609d5df74244ce8c1bd93e8369b400</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJwwzKLm-v0Xh3VN3WoJ1doqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/8f609d5df74244ce8c1bd93e8369b400" target="_blank"&gt;Utility aims for zero carbon emission from electric power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DENVER (AP) — A utility serving 3.6 million electricity customers in eight states said Tuesday it will try to eliminate all its carbon emissions from electrical generation by 2050. Xcel Energy CEO Ben Fowke acknowledged that not all the technologies the company needs to meet that goal are available yet on a commercial scale, but he said he is encouraged by advances in clean energy technology. "If we put our minds to it," Fowke said, "we will find the best solution to get us there." He told the Colorado Sun the goal is a response to climate change. "This risk of climate change isn't going aw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Energy: ERBD to boost Jordan's national electricity company - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/economics/2018/12/05/energy-erbd-to-boost-jordans-national-electricity-company_404ccc94-5e25-47bc-8d1e-74a22c1ed5fe.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENOk2wkojmInj5TxclcqE20qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:43:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/economics/2018/12/05/energy-erbd-to-boost-jordans-national-electricity-company_404ccc94-5e25-47bc-8d1e-74a22c1ed5fe.html" target="_blank"&gt;Energy: ERBD to boost Jordan's national electricity company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMMAN - The European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD) signed a $265-million finance deal with Jordan's National Electric Power Company (NEPCO), to integrate renewable power sources into the national power network, a statement reads. The accord will allow for "construction of new substations, automated grid management systems and transmission infrastructure will improve the integration of green energy into the national electricity network," according to EBRD statement. NEPCO has been facing mounting financial challenges during the past few years in what has been attributed to m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>California first state to mandate solar power for new homes - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/bc726263593d428386af7130d6abdf78</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKErO65dcesNozcF5dhkIRwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:39:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/bc726263593d428386af7130d6abdf78" target="_blank"&gt;California first state to mandate solar power for new homes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — California became the first state in the nation to require homes built in 2020 and later be solar powered, following a vote by the Building Standards Commission. The unanimous action on Wednesday finalizes a previous vote by the Energy Commission and fulfills a decade-old goal to make the state reliant on cleaner energy. "These provisions really are historic and will be a beacon of light for the rest of the country," said Kent Sasaki, a structural engineer and one of six building standards commissioners. "(It's) the beginning of substantial improvement in how we produce e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>These companies are leading the fight against climate change - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/business/climate-change-companies/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAOsSEvy8y-2mfPklC_fryAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:17:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/business/climate-change-companies/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;These companies are leading the fight against climate change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world has only until 2030 to stem catastrophic climate change. Can global companies be part of the solution? A report published Monday by the UN Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change said that "rapid, far-reaching and unprecedented changes in all aspects of society" are needed to avoid disastrous levels of global warming. While often seen as culprits, some businesses are setting a positive example. The companies with the best track records tend to be consumer brands, according to reports from corporate transparency advocate CDP, public opinion consultancy GlobeScan and think tank Su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US Coal Consumption Drops to Lowest Level Since 1979 - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-coal-consumption-drops-to-lowest-level-since-1979/4687288.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEvl0WSk2r3CfWhxkyEuO64qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:31:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-coal-consumption-drops-to-lowest-level-since-1979/4687288.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Coal Consumption Drops to Lowest Level Since 1979&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Americans are consuming less coal in 2018 than at any time since Jimmy Carter's presidency, a federal report said Tuesday, as cheap natural gas and other rival sources of energy frustrate the Trump administration's pledges to revive the U.S. coal industry. A report by the U.S. Energy Information Administration projected Tuesday that 2018 would see the lowest U.S. coal consumption since 1979, as well as the second-greatest number on record of coal-fired power plants shutting down. The country's electrical grid accounts for most of U.S. coal consumption. U.S. coal demand has been falling sinc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The town taking energy prices into its own hands - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/solar-panels-pension-prices/10590772</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELGVSasy4LTWG6fug6oCG5sqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:18:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/solar-panels-pension-prices/10590772" target="_blank"&gt;The town taking energy prices into its own hands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Low-income residents of a regional South Australian city are using an innovative solar scheme to shave money off their power bills. The Port Pirie Regional Council recognised that with more than half of the city's population on government benefits, its residents could not afford runaway energy prices or a $3,000 solar system on their homes. As the Federal energy debate raged without resolution, Councillors in Port Pirie, at the foot of SA's Flinders Ranges, put to tender an ambitious home solar scheme. Photo: Solar panels on a roof at Port Pirie. (ABC North and West: Gabriella Marchant) Por...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Enel vying for solar and wind project in Tunisia - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/energy/2018/12/05/enel-vying-for-solar-and-wind-project-in-tunisia_3e192968-6b87-425f-a53a-a227431c48b9.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEErWTkcK71Vzvm8ZX_TvWnAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:42:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/energy/2018/12/05/enel-vying-for-solar-and-wind-project-in-tunisia_3e192968-6b87-425f-a53a-a227431c48b9.html" target="_blank"&gt;Enel vying for solar and wind project in Tunisia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TUNIS - Italian energy giant Enel is in the running to build and manage a solar plant and wind farm in Tunisia, as its Green Power renewable-energy arm passed the pre-selection phase in a call for tenders by the Tunisian Industry Ministry, the ministry said in a statement on Wednesday. It said 16 companies and consortiums were pre-selected to contend for the bid to provide and manage a 500-megawatt solar plant, and 12 companies were pre-selected to compete in the bid for building and managing a 300-megawatt wind farm. Other companies in the running for the solar plant project include intern...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>White House Seeks to End Subsidies for Electric Cars, Renewables - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/white-house-seeks-to-end-subsidies-for-electric-cars-renewables/4685685.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIrNC0ONRk27PEGxnOvJF5sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 03:05:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/white-house-seeks-to-end-subsidies-for-electric-cars-renewables/4685685.html" target="_blank"&gt;White House Seeks to End Subsidies for Electric Cars, Renewables&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;White House economic adviser Larry Kudlow said on Monday the Trump administration wants to end subsidies for electric cars and other items, including renewable energy sources. Asked about plans after General Motors announced U.S. plant closings and layoffs last week, Kudlow pointed to the $2,500-to-$7,500 tax credit for consumers who buy plug-in electric vehicles, including those made by GM, under federal law. "As a matter of our policy, we want to end all of those subsidies," Kudlow said. "And by the way, other subsidies that were imposed during the Obama administration, we are ending, whe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>White House seeks to end subsidies for electric cars, renewables - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-autos/white-house-seeks-to-end-subsidies-for-electric-cars-renewables-idUSKBN1O22D4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPu20EuK-4TO6EO6Y4j10QQqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 02:43:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-autos/white-house-seeks-to-end-subsidies-for-electric-cars-renewables-idUSKBN1O22D4" target="_blank"&gt;White House seeks to end subsidies for electric cars, renewables&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;White House economic adviser Larry Kudlow said on Monday the Trump administration wants to end subsidies for electric cars and other items, including renewable energy sources. Asked about plans after General Motors Co (GM.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) announced U.S. plant closings and layoffs last week, Kudlow pointed to the $2,500-to-$7,500 tax credit for consumers who buy plug-in electric vehicles, including those made by GM, under federal law. "As a matter of our policy, we want to end all of those subsidies," Kudlow said. "And by the way, other subsidies that were imposed dur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Funding Nemo: £600m power cable connects UK and Belgium - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/05/funding-nemo-600m-power-cable-connects-uk-and-belgium</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIweBL18aCWnqzKQ3j7pVUoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:09:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/05/funding-nemo-600m-power-cable-connects-uk-and-belgium" target="_blank"&gt;Funding Nemo: £600m power cable connects UK and Belgium&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A £600m cable connecting the UK and Belgium’s energy systems is about to be switched on, becoming the first of a new generation of interconnectors that will deepen the UK’s ties to mainland Europe just as it prepares to leave the EU. The Nemo link is in the final stages of testing and from early 2019 is expected to transmit power over an 80-mile route along the seabed between Richborough in Kent and Zeebrugge, becoming the first new electricity interconnector to the continent since 2011 and the first to Belgium. Nemo route map Although built with the expectation of the UK mostly importing e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Energy: firms-government meeting in Cairo on renewable - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/energy/2018/12/04/energy-firms-government-meeting-in-cairo-on-renewable_282edac4-c72d-4e73-9cb4-b57f2c82dfa4.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGEXhgePux9QXUQZ0CSx_IMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:28:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/energy/2018/12/04/energy-firms-government-meeting-in-cairo-on-renewable_282edac4-c72d-4e73-9cb4-b57f2c82dfa4.html" target="_blank"&gt;Energy: firms-government meeting in Cairo on renewable&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAIRO - A conference with entrepreneurs operating in the sector of renewable energy and high officials of the Egyptian government, focusing on the reduction of risks to finance a project, will be held today in Cairo. The event is organized by the association RES4Med&amp;Africa. The high-level B2G (business to government) organized together with law firm Bonelli Erede, according to the program, focuses on how to accelerate the development of renewable energy in Egypt and finds in the reduction of risks to fund the project a way to ensure and push for investments in renewable energy, accelerating...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>The Common Sense 'Extreme' Of The Green New Deal - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamesellsmoor/2018/12/04/the-common-sense-extreme-of-the-green-new-deal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECLy3aC2NSprFugIivtQ4PkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamesellsmoor/2018/12/04/the-common-sense-extreme-of-the-green-new-deal/" target="_blank"&gt;The Common Sense 'Extreme' Of The Green New Deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In what political analysts and journalists described as a “blue wave,” the Democrats regained control of the House of Representatives in the 2018 U.S. midterm elections. The actual wave that turned the tides in the House could perhaps be considered green as well as blue. Among the incoming members of Congress are several outspoken proponents of green technologies and sustainability initiatives. Some of the new political generation, such as New York’s newly elect Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, are lending vocal support to grassroots environmental groups and championing the revival of the “Green N...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 4 Engines of Energy Innovation In Developing Countries - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffmcmahon/2018/12/05/the-4-engines-of-energy-innovation-in-developing-countries/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENuKJQnepRAD2Yqvc8wB8pUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffmcmahon/2018/12/05/the-4-engines-of-energy-innovation-in-developing-countries/" target="_blank"&gt;The 4 Engines of Energy Innovation In Developing Countries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man wearing a face mask cycles along a road in Delhi, India, on Friday, Nov. 9, 2018. Air pollution levels skyrocketed in New Delhi and left India’s capital shrouded in toxic smog as millions of Indians set off firecrackers for Diwali, the Hindu festival of lights. Toxic air is estimated to kill more than 1 million Indians each year, according to the nonprofit Health Effects Institute. Photographer: Ruhani Kaur/Bloomberg There are four themes driving energy innovation in the developing world, according to the chief operating officer of Softbank Energy, a Delhi-based firm that develops sol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Tasmanian businesses close to breaking point over power prices - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-03/tasmanian-businesses-close-to-breaking-point-over-power-prices/10576008</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGDmxfkajzYNHIKh5X4-wdMqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 20:15:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-03/tasmanian-businesses-close-to-breaking-point-over-power-prices/10576008" target="_blank"&gt;Tasmanian businesses close to breaking point over power prices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your last electricity bill gave you a shock, spare a thought for Tasmanian business owners that are struggling to pay annual increases worth tens of thousands of dollars. Key points: - Small to medium Tasmanian businesses have been hit with big power price rises - Many lack the capacity to pass on costs to consumers - Job losses are inevitable, an electricity industry expert says John Dabner, the general manager of Tall Timbers, an accommodation and tourism business in Smithton, said his annual power bill jumped by about $50,000 in the past year to $150,000. If the trend continues he sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Carbon emissions from rich nations set to rise in 2018: IEA - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-climate-change-emissions-iea/carbon-emissions-from-rich-nations-set-to-rise-in-2018-iea-idUSKBN1O31R2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBszSmYmDD82QdlM9b4ZyIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:22:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-climate-change-emissions-iea/carbon-emissions-from-rich-nations-set-to-rise-in-2018-iea-idUSKBN1O31R2" target="_blank"&gt;Carbon emissions from rich nations set to rise in 2018: IEA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carbon dioxide emissions from the world's advanced economies are set to rise slightly in 2018, breaking a five-year decline, mainly due to higher oil and natural gas use, the International Energy Agency (IEA) says. Based on the latest energy data available, energy-related carbon dioxide (CO2) emissions in North America, the European Union and other advanced economies in Asia Pacific are set to increase by around 0.5 percent in 2018. This is lower than the 2.4 percent rise in economic growth but ends the declining trend of the past five years, the IEA said in a statement on Tuesday. This wee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump Wants To Ramp Up Coal. Spain Has Found A Way To Quit It. - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/spain-coal-just-transition-miners-investment_us_5c04e802e4b04fb21169842f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEG5lQOCDn0UmKCxocFtCRYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 10:45:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/spain-coal-just-transition-miners-investment_us_5c04e802e4b04fb21169842f" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Wants To Ramp Up Coal. Spain Has Found A Way To Quit It.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VILLABLINO, Spain — When the shutters come down on the last 10 privately owned pits in northwest Spain’s once mighty coal industry later this month, there will be tears and trauma in the region where the country’s mining unions were born. There is also a fragile hope that a better, cleaner future could follow — but a barely hidden warning that the despair that propelled Trump to power in the U.S. lurks in the wings if it does not. Spain’s uneconomic coal industry has been killed by a pincer movement: cheaper imports from developing countries on one flank and falling renewable energy prices ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump Administration To Double Down On Coal In Katowice, Says Energy Access Requires Fossil Fuels - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dipkabhambhani/2018/12/03/trump-administration-to-double-down-on-coal-in-katowice-says-energy-access-requires-fossil-fuels/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEwP6BPGUSVN2NOYI_RMIB8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dipkabhambhani/2018/12/03/trump-administration-to-double-down-on-coal-in-katowice-says-energy-access-requires-fossil-fuels/" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Administration To Double Down On Coal In Katowice, Says Energy Access Requires Fossil Fuels&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two-week global climate talks in Katowice, Poland, kicked off this week. There are two noticeable differences in the tenor of the meetings from previous years. First, the hostility toward fossil fuels is somewhat muted in Poland, a country reliant on coal, one which consumes more than 135 million tons of it each year according to the International Energy Agency. In fact, the landing page of Poland’s website on COP24 talks about finding ways to use coal. The “Polish government is trying to create favorable conditions for the construction of a profitable, effective and modern hard coal mi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Power ahead: Scotland's pioneering renewables role - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8qtMQMY1nEc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKsasFOENc49maqVtSBBtoAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tt6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:52:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8qtMQMY1nEc" target="_blank"&gt;Power ahead: Scotland's pioneering renewables role&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;► Read more at https://on.ft.com/2DYXoxX Scotland is a testbed for tidal and floating wind farm technologies and hopes to gain an edge in the renewables sector as dependence on oil diminishes. The FT's Mure Dickie reports ► Subscribe to FT.com here: http://bit.ly/2GakujT ► Subscribe to the Financial Times on YouTube: http://bit.ly/FTimeSubs For more video content from the Financial Times, visit http://www.FT.com/video Twitter https://twitter.com/ftvideo Facebook https://www.facebook.com/financialtimes&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>We have the tech to tackle climate change now–here are the next steps - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90272165/we-have-the-tech-to-tackle-climate-change-now-here-are-the-next-steps</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDT_zdNdNlJN1okiOJ89A0QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 07:30:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90272165/we-have-the-tech-to-tackle-climate-change-now-here-are-the-next-steps" target="_blank"&gt;We have the tech to tackle climate change now–here are the next steps&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world has a tiny window of time to change course to avoid the worst-case scenario of climate change in the future–from global food shortages and catastrophic fires and floods to mass deaths from extreme temperatures. The good news: We have the technology we need to tackle the problem. The next step is to roll out the right policy to implement that technology. A new book, Designing Climate Solutions: A Policy Guide for Low-Carbon Energy, explains how to do it. “It’s all solvable if you do the right thing, and do it promptly,” says author Hal Harvey, CEO of the energy and environmental po...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>The Future Of Power Is Wireless - Here's Why - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/miriamtuerk/2018/12/04/the-future-of-power-is-wireless-heres-why/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEISddWspn2GdZIGfPpwLC1IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 16:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/miriamtuerk/2018/12/04/the-future-of-power-is-wireless-heres-why/" target="_blank"&gt;The Future Of Power Is Wireless - Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Power transmission lines are suspended from electricity pylons in Kearny, New Jersey, U.S. Photographer: Steve Hockstein/Bloomberg In the next five years, we will see a transformative shift in the way we power our homes, businesses, and infrastructure. Today, most things are physically plugged into the electricity grid, which works like a master power outlet. This is notoriously inefficient – 50% or more of the cost you pay for energy goes to the grid, the power cable and distribution network. It’s extremely expensive to install, and ongoing maintenance costs are increasing yearly. Think of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>EU's climate chief calls for net-zero emissions by 2050 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-climate-change-eu/eus-climate-chief-calls-for-bloc-to-go-for-net-zero-emissions-by-2050-idUSKCN1NW212</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBfbBtLsQRTE3mj_0PauAVIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 11:56:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-climate-change-eu/eus-climate-chief-calls-for-bloc-to-go-for-net-zero-emissions-by-2050-idUSKCN1NW212" target="_blank"&gt;EU's climate chief calls for net-zero emissions by 2050&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Union's climate chief called for the bloc to take the lead and aim for net-zero greenhouse gas emissions by 2050 in its climate strategy published on Wednesday, ahead of key U.N. talks on curbing global warming. As President Donald Trump pulls the United States out of the Paris climate accord, European Commission climate chief Miguel Arias Canete said the bloc had to lead by example at next week's climate talks in Poland. The EU executive published its strategy on Wednesday, setting out eight pathways to reducing emissions - two of which chart a course for Europe to becoming cl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>As Congress Tackles Climate, Markets Are The Engine But Policies Set The Direction - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmurray1/2018/12/04/as-congress-tackles-climate-markets-are-the-engine-but-policies-set-the-direction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIOSzav5OGcPUFxZ2S38Y9QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmurray1/2018/12/04/as-congress-tackles-climate-markets-are-the-engine-but-policies-set-the-direction/" target="_blank"&gt;As Congress Tackles Climate, Markets Are The Engine But Policies Set The Direction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;States Capitol Close Up with dramatic blue sky, Washington DC As the 116th Congress nears its debut, efforts by both parties to pursue new climate and energy policies are afoot. Representative-elect Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-NY) has announced plans to develop a “Green New Deal,” Meanwhile, three Democrats and three Republicans have introduced a bipartisan Energy Innovation and Carbon Dividend Act to enact a federal carbon tax. Considering the Republican-controlled Senate and the Trump Administration’s opposition to aggressive climate policy to date, the chances that either measure will pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Trump energy nominee clears hurdle after fossil-fuel remarks - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/cd1c791c9b7d4ce0bd26e1958eb244d2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC97kajy0T_C_U1U8TmI9PAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 18:02:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/cd1c791c9b7d4ce0bd26e1958eb244d2" target="_blank"&gt;Trump energy nominee clears hurdle after fossil-fuel remarks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Bernard McNamee's nomination to a top federal energy board cleared a Senate committee on Tuesday even as a video showed him declaring that renewable energy "screws up" the nation's electrical grid. The Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee voted 13-10 to approve McNamee's nomination to the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission and send it to the full Senate. West Virginia Sen. Joe Manchin was the only Democrat joining Republicans in approving the nomination. McNamee is an Energy Department staffer who had worked on a stalled Trump administration bailout for aging co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Wildfires pose threat to California climate goals, officials say - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-wildfires-renewables/wildfires-pose-threat-to-california-climate-goals-officials-say-idUSKCN1NZ2DE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJS2wcd87CEn7cvuqNWkMCYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 18:20:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-wildfires-renewables/wildfires-pose-threat-to-california-climate-goals-officials-say-idUSKCN1NZ2DE" target="_blank"&gt;Wildfires pose threat to California climate goals, officials say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;California’s wildfires could deal a blow to the state’s ambitious climate goals if they inflict too deep a financial wound on utilities, seen as crucial to greening up the grid, according to state officials. The state is relying on Pacific Gas &amp; Electric (PG&amp;E) and its two other big investor-owned utilities to double purchases of renewable energy over the next decade and invest billions of dollars to help electrify the transportation sector, part of California’s nation-leading plan to cut carbon emissions by 40 percent below 2020 levels by 2030. But PG&amp;E now faces untold billions of dollars...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Plunging Prices Mean Building New Renewable Energy Is Cheaper Than Running Existing Coal - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/energyinnovation/2018/12/03/plunging-prices-mean-building-new-renewable-energy-is-cheaper-than-running-existing-coal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHVAAPvVTM-OSakyBwS-EwoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/energyinnovation/2018/12/03/plunging-prices-mean-building-new-renewable-energy-is-cheaper-than-running-existing-coal/" target="_blank"&gt;Plunging Prices Mean Building New Renewable Energy Is Cheaper Than Running Existing Coal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new report revels 42% of global coal capacity is currently unprofitable, and the United States could save $78 billion by closing coal-fired power plants in line with the Paris Climate Accord’s climate goals. This industry-disrupting trend comes down to dollars and cents, as the cost of renewable energy dips below fossil fuel generation. Across the U.S., renewable energy is beating coal on cost: The price to build new wind and solar has fallen below the cost of running existing coal-fired power plants in Red and Blue states. For example, Colorado’s Xcel will retire 660 megawatts (MW) of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How To Teach Climate Science In Coal Country And To Non-Believers - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kensilverstein/2018/12/02/how-to-teach-climate-science-in-coal-country-and-to-non-believers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBRtWlfw-cFlkgK1jLBOtMcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kensilverstein/2018/12/02/how-to-teach-climate-science-in-coal-country-and-to-non-believers/" target="_blank"&gt;How To Teach Climate Science In Coal Country And To Non-Believers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Little boy holding the earth in his hands. After 13 federal agencies released the fourth National Climate Assessment that concluded humans are primarily responsible for global warming, the naysayers once again dismissed those findings — all empowered by a U.S. president who feels it in his gut that the experts are all wrong. But at this point, the 97% of scientists whose models support such a conclusion are backed by not just the global community that is participating in the Paris climate agreement but also much of the United States. Even more significantly, the oil companies that once plan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Oil forecasts will continue to be wildly off the mark - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a79b08a2-d6d8-11e8-aa22-36538487e3d0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBdtwp_MNsR0x6n52QyxHvQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:31:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a79b08a2-d6d8-11e8-aa22-36538487e3d0" target="_blank"&gt;Oil forecasts will continue to be wildly off the mark&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The adage about forecasting being difficult, especially for the long term, might have been coined for the oil industry. Just six weeks ago, Brent had passed $80 and speculators were dreaming of $100. Now it is failing to hold on to $60, they are selling and the end of the oil world is nigh. It is not just the short-term expectations that have proved so wildly wrong. The 2008 World Energy Outlook from the International Energy Agency calculated that fossil fuel use provided 81 per cent of the world’s energy. A decade on, despite the trillions of dollars poured into alternative fuels, that per...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Private players plug in to the green energy revolution - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/76f1e95e-c883-11e8-86e6-19f5b7134d1c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGsdksbRcOKdZUGVSF70ST4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 04:02:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/76f1e95e-c883-11e8-86e6-19f5b7134d1c" target="_blank"&gt;Private players plug in to the green energy revolution&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than $2.3tn of annual investment in the energy sector is needed to meet the “sustainable development” conditions that will help avoid catastrophic climate change, according to the International Energy Agency. That annual commitment must rise again to an average of more than $3.2tn between 2025 and 2040, with much of it skewed towards renewable power sources and improved efficiency, to achieve the best-case scenario set out in the IEA’s latest Energy Outlook report. Commenting on the report this month, Fatih Birol, IEA executive director, said: “Seventy per cent of global energy investm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Opinion: The lights could go out this winter if we close more coal and nuclear power plants - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-lights-could-go-out-this-winter-if-we-close-all-the-coal-and-nuclear-power-plants-2018-12-04</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGXL5veBaPaA5cgOU0u2fy0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-lights-could-go-out-this-winter-if-we-close-all-the-coal-and-nuclear-power-plants-2018-12-04" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: The lights could go out this winter if we close more coal and nuclear power plants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OUTSIDE THE BOX By Terry Jarrett Shortages of natural gas could push the power grid to the limit Ice builds up along Lake Michigan as temperatures dip to 16 below on Jan. 6, 2014, in Chicago. Scott Olson/Getty Images It’s been an early start to winter this year across much of the Central and Eastern United States. And plunging temperatures have highlighted a surprising fact: Not only are natural-gas prices soaring, but fuel stockpiles have dipped to unusually low levels. It’s a somewhat unexpected turn of events — since the United States has been the world’s top producer of natural gas sinc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Spain’s Drive to Go Green May Encounter Roadblocks - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/spains-drive-to-go-green-may-encounter-roadblocks/4672847.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFZ_pEavk12wsaFl1ra6A1sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 09:00:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/spains-drive-to-go-green-may-encounter-roadblocks/4672847.html" target="_blank"&gt;Spain’s Drive to Go Green May Encounter Roadblocks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spain is drafting ambitious plans to switch its energy matrix to renewable sources and ban fossil fuel vehicles by 2040, according to a climate change law unveiled by socialist Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez last week. But some argue the initiative, which follows the lead of other European Union governments, may be too ambitious for a country whose car industry is ill-prepared for such a dramatic transformation. Spain lags far behind other European nations in electric vehicle market share, with electric accounting for 0.22 percent of its market compared with about 2 percent in France, Belgium...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Spain unveils ambitious green energy plan - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b31f99b8-ce31-11e8-8d0b-a6539b949662</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJpCYAGprELrgm9fELHZAIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 04:31:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b31f99b8-ce31-11e8-8d0b-a6539b949662" target="_blank"&gt;Spain unveils ambitious green energy plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As delegates convene at UN-backed climate talks in Poland this week, the Spanish will have a new trophy in hand: a renewable energy plan that seeks to reverse years of rising emissions. Spain’s proposals, set to be adopted by the cabinet in coming weeks, spell out an ambitious target to draw 100 per cent of the country’s electricity from renewables by 2050. The plan also aims to cut emissions by more than 90 per cent over the same period. “We are a government convinced of the importance of working on positive, co-operative multilateralism, and also taking our share of responsibly on domesti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Coal, coal, coal and soaring emissions – as a Liberal, I have had enough - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/03/coal-coal-coal-and-soaring-emissions-as-a-liberal-i-have-had-enough</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDhJZwYO9xp3P3wuvR_WNKkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 01:10:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/03/coal-coal-coal-and-soaring-emissions-as-a-liberal-i-have-had-enough" target="_blank"&gt;Coal, coal, coal and soaring emissions – as a Liberal, I have had enough&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time is up. The Liberal party won’t reform, so it is time to stop fighting, split and take the opportunity to compete for the support of the public. The Liberal party is now broken, brand-damaged and unable to attract new members that would enable it to represent a “broad church”. The failure of the existing Liberal party to address climate change or to support an integrity commission is unacceptable. Nowhere is this failure more obvious than in its continued support for the Adani coalmine and new coal-fired power stations. Related: 'Build a culture of integrity': Coalition urged to adopt f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Coal Power Plants Lose Their Cost Advantage Over Clean Energy - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikescott/2018/12/03/coal-power-plants-lose-their-cost-advantage-over-clean-energy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGMtnbRA0t-iod2vgW3UvQ0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikescott/2018/12/03/coal-power-plants-lose-their-cost-advantage-over-clean-energy/" target="_blank"&gt;Coal Power Plants Lose Their Cost Advantage Over Clean Energy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demonstrators during a ‘Claim the Climate’ march in Brussels, ahead of the COP24 climate change conference, COP24 being held in Poland. Photo credit: ASSOCIATED PRESS When it started becoming as cheap, and then cheaper, to build wind or solar farms than fossil fuel power, the renewable energy plants still faced the barrier of being in competition with coal plants that had already been built. Invariably, these were cheaper. Not any more – in 2018, more than four out of 10 (42%) of the world’s coal-fired power stations are running at a loss and by 2030, in virtually every case (96%) it will b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>India's Electrification Push Raises Environmental Stakes - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andystone/2018/11/29/indias-electrification-push-raises-environmental-stakes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOBd5a0dL8HSa8_0lo6mhXUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 03:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andystone/2018/11/29/indias-electrification-push-raises-environmental-stakes/" target="_blank"&gt;India's Electrification Push Raises Environmental Stakes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian public electricity cables India is in the home stretch of today’s most ambitious electrification effort, one that is akin to the U.S. government’s push to bring power to rural America in the 1930s. Back in 1936, President Roosevelt put forth the Rural Electrification Act as part of his Depression-era New Deal. The policy aimed to create jobs in the near term and, more enduringly, build electric infrastructure that would underpin future economic development in the nation’s rural and agricultural regions, including those that had been economically devastated by a half decade of drought...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Labor to revive National Energy Guarantee 'even if it's not the best' - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-22/bill-shorten-labor-to-revive-national-energy-guarantee/10521468</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOfNysF-D-pOZP1t8k3FXisqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 03:19:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-22/bill-shorten-labor-to-revive-national-energy-guarantee/10521468" target="_blank"&gt;Labor to revive National Energy Guarantee 'even if it's not the best'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal Labor will adopt the energy policy that helped bring Malcolm Turnbull's prime ministership undone, despite admitting it is not the party's preferred option. Key points: - Labor adopts the NRG, abandoned by Malcolm Turnbull in the final days of his prime ministership - The Coalition says Labor's plan would "put a wrecking ball through the country" - But the Australian Energy Council says business supports the NEG Opposition Leader Bill Shorten has announced Labor's new energy policy, which revives the National Energy Guarantee and sets aside billions of dollars for renewable energy. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>The romance of drilling for oil has peaked - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e633ea7a-f253-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEABVf2wPEAwA0lKUlOz_zk0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e633ea7a-f253-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;The romance of drilling for oil has peaked&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the price of crude oil goes through one of its periodic downturns, as it is doing now, it sends a shiver through the oil industry. History promises that higher prices will return. Until then, US shale companies are under severe pressure and big oil companies wonder about the viability of new projects. There is more to worry them this time: not just the 29 per cent fall in the price of Brent crude since the start of October as Russia and Saudi Arabia pump more oil, but the fear of this bear market enduring. The romance of oil exploration is fading at companies such as Royal Dutch Shell,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Disneyland Paris Hopes To Get Glow From Solar Power - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/csylt/2018/12/02/disneyland-paris-hopes-to-get-glow-from-solar-power/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKqMftFqA6A3qYS4OW9HLs0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 21:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/csylt/2018/12/02/disneyland-paris-hopes-to-get-glow-from-solar-power/" target="_blank"&gt;Disneyland Paris Hopes To Get Glow From Solar Power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theme park operator Disneyland Paris has revealed that it is considering building a massive solar power plant which would supply 15% of the electricity at its sprawling site on the outskirts of Paris. It follows the recent opening of a similar facility at Walt Disney World in Orlando, Florida, which is expected to generate enough renewable energy to power two of the four theme parks there. In contrast, Disneyland Paris only has two parks – its eponymous flagship and the movie-themed Walt Disney Studios. However, that’s just the start. Solar power will help Disneyland Paris meet the increase...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Smoke clouds obscure India’s solar revolution - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d77ed284-e41f-11e8-a8a0-99b2e340ffeb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENh3ckoSqHJh2QmWwsWz_qQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 04:31:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d77ed284-e41f-11e8-a8a0-99b2e340ffeb" target="_blank"&gt;Smoke clouds obscure India’s solar revolution&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India is targeting an economic expansion of gargantuan scale over the next few decades. The country, with a population exceeding 1.3bn and annual per capita income below $2,000, has become the world’s fastest-growing big economy. But while India’s annual economic growth — about 7 per cent over the past two years — promises to lift millions out of poverty, environmentalists have warned that unless the country changes its energy mix dramatically, it could have dire consequences for the global climate. Plentiful domestic coal reserves has meant India has long relied overwhelmingly on the highl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>'It's going to destroy Christmas': Workers lose thousands after RCR collapse - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-23/rcr-tomlinson-administration-workers-and-projects-in-doubt/10547688</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA6iSFxm8hwzZrRkwknM49kqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 01:57:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-23/rcr-tomlinson-administration-workers-and-projects-in-doubt/10547688" target="_blank"&gt;'It's going to destroy Christmas': Workers lose thousands after RCR collapse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Lexy Hamilton-Smith The collapse of one of the nation's oldest engineering companies RCR Tomlinson has destroyed Christmas for thousands of families, according to the Electrical Trades Union (ETU) dealing with the fallout from the unexpected job losses. ETU state secretary Peter Ong said hundreds of devastated contractors were calling him saying they were owed hundreds of thousands of dollars and were suffering financial hardship. "I got a text last night from another contractor who is owed $800,000, he is a small electrical contractor," Mr Ong said. "$100,000 owed to a transport contact...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Clean energy trading through blockchain - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/04/brooklyn-microgrid-clean-energy-trading-through-blockchain-vision.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHVzsw8aJcbTADxLWG8jtzgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:11:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/04/brooklyn-microgrid-clean-energy-trading-through-blockchain-vision.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;Clean energy trading through blockchain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since bitcoin, the concept of blockchain has taken the world by storm. A New York start-up is now leveraging this technology in the energy sector. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Opinion: Here’s the good news in that alarming report on climate change - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-the-good-news-in-that-alarming-report-on-climate-change-2018-11-27</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKdYTLbDx1PrskgLybkI7o8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 10:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-the-good-news-in-that-alarming-report-on-climate-change-2018-11-27" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: Here’s the good news in that alarming report on climate change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TIM MULLANEY By Tim Mullaney The solution is at hand: The cost of ditching carbon is much less than you think A wind farm near Palm Springs, Calif. DAVID MCNEW/AFP/Getty Images Of all the things we had to be thankful for last week, the climate-change report that the Trump administration tried to bury by releasing it on a Friday when no one was working wasn’t one of them — at least not on the surface. It paints a tale of a huge pending economic mess if we don’t get serious about slowing down carbon use and global warming. But here’s the good news: The report also makes the case quite clearly...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Tories need to be better than tepid over UK's industrial strategy - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/nov/25/tories-need-to-be-better-than-tepid-over-uks-industrial-strategy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1XglQBGroBcU_fCp45reUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 12:52:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/nov/25/tories-need-to-be-better-than-tepid-over-uks-industrial-strategy" target="_blank"&gt;Tories need to be better than tepid over UK's industrial strategy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not since Robert Donat clambered out of the Flying Scotsman to evade the police in Alfred Hitchcock’s 1935 film The 39 Steps will a crossing of the River Forth have generated as much excitement. In three years time, cameras will be in place to record the first wave of UK driverless vehicles – an autonomous bus service linking Fife with Edinburgh. News of the pilots – another is planned for taxis in London – was carefully timed. The government launched its industrial strategy a year ago and wanted to be able to show there had been progress. There is a paradox here. Theresa May stressed when ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Bitcoin mining is greener than most large-scale industries: report - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bitcoin-mining-is-greener-that-most-large-scale-industries-report-2018-11-30</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYPLrR5f1MogsVZaafnZw8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bitcoin-mining-is-greener-that-most-large-scale-industries-report-2018-11-30" target="_blank"&gt;Bitcoin mining is greener than most large-scale industries: report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE TELL By Aaron Hankin There’s a negative narrative around bitcoin mining costs that CoinShares hopes to disprove DAVID MCNEW/AFP/Getty Images Bitcoin mining: energy sapping or economic enhancing? As miners plug in their computers to solve complicated mathematical puzzles for a fraction of a bitcoin, the knock on the competitive bitcoin mining industry is the significant energy consumption that, according to the Bitcoin Consumption Index, equals the entire country of Bangladesh. But a report from CoinShares, a digital asset management firm, argues that the perception that miners are a dra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>This urban-scale wind turbine could generate power on your fire escape - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90266412/this-urban-scale-wind-turbine-could-generate-power-on-your-fire-escape</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDrgtATzIRY5j391yL8vcpkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:01:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90266412/this-urban-scale-wind-turbine-could-generate-power-on-your-fire-escape" target="_blank"&gt;This urban-scale wind turbine could generate power on your fire escape&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A typical wind turbine is hundreds of feet tall, with blades that stretch wider than a football field. But a new design is small and lightweight enough that it could sit on the balcony of an urban apartment and generate some power there. The design, called O-Wind, is the winner of the 2018 International James Dyson Award, which honors recently graduated design engineering students. The device makes use of a source of energy that is usually untapped: Wind gusts between buildings in skyscraper-filled cities, but standard wind power doesn’t make sense there, because of size, and because wind i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Coal mine closures need careful social engineering - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d820cd62-c883-11e8-86e6-19f5b7134d1c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDGqCPK8X3bcMS-MRKYsd1sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 04:02:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d820cd62-c883-11e8-86e6-19f5b7134d1c" target="_blank"&gt;Coal mine closures need careful social engineering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In late 2015, the UK’s last deep coal mine in North Yorkshire closed, bringing an end to centuries of high-volume coal mining in the country that had helped kick-start Britain’s Industrial Revolution. It is a transition that could be repeated in countries with large coal workforces such as China, Indonesia and South Africa, as the world shifts towards green energy sources to reduce pollution and limit rising global temperatures caused by climate change. Once-thriving coal towns in the Welsh valleys, such as Newport, which now imports coal into its port, still struggle with the impact of hig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Swap gas boilers for hydrogen or miss emission targets, UK told - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/22/uk-hydrogen-heating-2050-emissions-targets-gas-boilers-electric-climate-change</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM3UGOofpCbUC2c9K5EcZEgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:01:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/22/uk-hydrogen-heating-2050-emissions-targets-gas-boilers-electric-climate-change" target="_blank"&gt;Swap gas boilers for hydrogen or miss emission targets, UK told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Millions of gas boilers will need to be replaced with hydrogen alternatives and coupled with electric heating devices if Britain is to hit its carbon targets at the lowest cost, according to the government’s climate advisers. In a report on the role hydrogen could play in the energy system, the Committee on Climate Change (CCC) spelt out the huge but necessary cost the country faces to switch to green heating. The cheapest scenario, it said, is a mix of electrifying heating and fitting hydrogen boilers, and will cost the UK £28bn a year, or 0.7% of GDP, by 2050. While electricity supplies a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Bushveld Minerals eyes vanadium battery market - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4f9fddf4-d510-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENlY7SMBtQyF4f5jMwQTyqcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 12:07:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4f9fddf4-d510-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8" target="_blank"&gt;Bushveld Minerals eyes vanadium battery market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surging prices for vanadium, a niche metal used to harden steel, have been a boon for London-listed Bushveld Minerals this year, helping fuel a share price rally amid a broader industry pullback. Now the South African company wants to target vanadium’s growing use in another industry: batteries, with an ambitious target to manufacture the technology as the country’s electricity grid moves away from coal-powered generation. But Bushveld faces a conundrum: while higher vanadium prices are good for miners, they are detrimental to battery makers, who need to further reduce their costs to make t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Why does Australia's sunniest region have the worst solar uptake? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-23/northern-territory-solar-renewable-energy-renters-roadmap-power/10464656</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECDtslyIphYsDrH1RCTIc3QqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 21:07:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-23/northern-territory-solar-renewable-energy-renters-roadmap-power/10464656" target="_blank"&gt;Why does Australia's sunniest region have the worst solar uptake?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Landlord Robin Thomas is "very pro-renewables" but decided to pass on putting solar panels on his rental properties in Australia's sunniest region. Key points: - The Northern Territory has a higher proportion of renters than the rest of the nation - The NT Government uses a quarter of all electricity in the Territory - Only four per cent of the energy used in the NT is renewable His reason was simple — cost. While a solar unit would give tenants cheaper power, all he would get as a landlord was the installation bill, which one expert said would range in price from $8,000 to $12,000. Finding...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Arsenal And Forest Green Rovers Lead Way In English Soccer's Sustainability Revolution - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stevemccaskill/2018/11/29/arsenal-and-forest-green-rovers-lead-way-in-english-soccers-sustainability-revolution/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKapfiBUJMe2xtT2NNLGpHoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/stevemccaskill/2018/11/29/arsenal-and-forest-green-rovers-lead-way-in-english-soccers-sustainability-revolution/" target="_blank"&gt;Arsenal And Forest Green Rovers Lead Way In English Soccer's Sustainability Revolution&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forest Green Rovers’ planned Eco Park stadium Sporting arenas are increasingly being updated with new technologies designed to improve the fan experience and generate additional revenue, but a novel installation at the Emirates Stadium will improve Arsenal’s green credentials. A battery storage system (BSS) has been installed at the venue and is capable of storing enough energy to power the Emirates for a full 90 minutes. That’s the equivalent of providing enough energy to 2,700 homes for 2 hours. The installation is the largest by any sporting venue in the U.K. and additional storage will ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Taiwan ditches plan to phase out nuclear power by 2025 - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4c55d32a-f2a6-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL8nmlKvoySVzXSQAw-vxSYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 01:13:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4c55d32a-f2a6-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Taiwan ditches plan to phase out nuclear power by 2025&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taiwan has scrapped its target of having no nuclear power by 2025 and is reviewing its energy policy after voters in a referendum on Saturday decided against a government policy of abolishing the energy source. The plan to phase-out nuclear power stemmed from public concern after the 2011 Fukushima nuclear disaster and has been a key part of the ruling Democratic Progressive party’s sweeping energy reforms, which are also aimed at slashing coal use and boosting wind and solar. But the move has been opposed by some business groups concerned about energy security for the country’s high-tech ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>How the airline industry is cleaning up its climate act - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90270016/how-the-airline-industry-is-cleaning-up-its-climate-act</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAA9kemwFZWKqKffagSfAJ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:00:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90270016/how-the-airline-industry-is-cleaning-up-its-climate-act" target="_blank"&gt;How the airline industry is cleaning up its climate act&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At a steel mill outside Beijing, reactors attached to the building capture emissions from the factory. Those waste gases can then be turned into fuel. LanzaTech, a biotech startup that designed a way to turn those emissions into ethanol, recently blended that ethanol into jet fuel that powered a Virgin Atlantic flight from Orlando to London. The jet fuel–with a carbon footprint smaller than regular fuel, but a comparable cost–is one way that the airline industry can begin to tackle its climate problem. In 2017, flights produced 859 million metric tons of CO2. By midcentury, like other indus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>This coal plant closed–now it’s being converted to a solar-powered neighborhood - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90273347/this-coal-plant-closed-now-its-being-converted-to-a-solar-powered-neighborhood</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDBTt9bk2HAsTT0aahXcIIkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:00:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90273347/this-coal-plant-closed-now-its-being-converted-to-a-solar-powered-neighborhood" target="_blank"&gt;This coal plant closed–now it’s being converted to a solar-powered neighborhood&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A little more than two years ago, as the market for coal kept collapsing, a 1-gigawatt coal plant in the U.K. town of Rugeley was one of many that closed around the world. Now, the utility company that owns the site plans to transform it into something quite different: sustainably powered housing. “Rapid change within the energy industry has meant a transition to a lower carbon, flexible, and more decentralized model for power generation,” says Niel Scott, a spokesman for Engie, the France-based utility that owns the coal plant. (The company, formerly called Gaz de France Suez, changed its ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Arsenal Unveils Battery Storage System That Will Power Emirates Stadium - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/cybrown/2018/11/26/arsenal-unveils-battery-storage-system-that-will-power-emirates-stadium/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOY6HVEVXwsCEzzb2IpRXhIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/cybrown/2018/11/26/arsenal-unveils-battery-storage-system-that-will-power-emirates-stadium/" target="_blank"&gt;Arsenal Unveils Battery Storage System That Will Power Emirates Stadium&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A general view of match action at The Emirates Stadium, home stadium of Arsenal as Henrikh Mkhitaryan of Arsenal takes a corner during the UEFA Europa League Group E match between Arsenal and Sporting CP at Emirates Stadium on Nov. 8, 2018 in London, United Kingdom. (Photo by Robbie Jay Barratt – AMA/Getty Images) Arsenal may not be leading the English Premier League, but with the unveiling of a new battery storage system, it has become the league leader in green energy. In an attempt to curb energy costs and support green energy, Arsenal has become the first soccer club in the United Kingd...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Renewables heading for 80 per cent of electricity market by 2030 - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/renewables-now-heading-for-80-per-cent-of-electricity-market/10567838</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKhNL3SY8JBz0eAA2bA2bRcqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 18:34:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/renewables-now-heading-for-80-per-cent-of-electricity-market/10567838" target="_blank"&gt;Renewables heading for 80 per cent of electricity market by 2030&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Renewable generation installation has accelerated to such an extent it is on track to provide almost 80 per cent of the electricity market by 2030, according to research from consultancy Green Energy Markets. Key points: - Rooftop solar installations are up 76pc on this time last year - By end of the year rooftop solar capacity will exceed that of the closed Hazelwood power station - Renewable financing faces big challenges from the likely collapse of power prices GEM director Tristan Edis said the renewable energy industry has built itself up to such a significant scale that even 50 per ce...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Analysis: How China's push for cleaner air is pushing up Australian power prices - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-22/chinese-push-for-cleaner-air-pushes-up-australian-power-prices/10513730</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM_GDsOXGk4BJVo0VI4hdNkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 20:13:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-22/chinese-push-for-cleaner-air-pushes-up-australian-power-prices/10513730" target="_blank"&gt;Analysis: How China's push for cleaner air is pushing up Australian power prices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By business reporter Stephen Letts Amid the finger pointing and theorising about Australia's rising power prices, there's one culprit often missing from the list: China's determined drive to improve its air quality. Sure, the Chinese are still burning coal to generate power and make steel, but they are using higher quality Australian combustible rock rather than their locally mined, higher-ash and more sulphurous product. While gas has traditionally been seen as the marginal price setter for power generation, black coal, and in particular News South Wales black coal, is an increasingly impo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>UK and IEA call for carbon capture push to meet climate targets - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/50b119dc-f249-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOZCBe9bQSvfJPEAdXgHiZ0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 04:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/50b119dc-f249-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;UK and IEA call for carbon capture push to meet climate targets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent report by the UN Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change provided a stark reminder about the need for action on climate change. Boosted by supportive government policies and technological improvements, some clean energy technologies are pushing ahead: solar PV has seen spectacular growth in recent years and offshore wind prices in the UK and elsewhere have fallen in price by as much as 50 per cent. But the latest International Energy Agency data also shows that as we lead up to the climate change talks at COP24, global carbon emissions are set to reach a new historic high in 20...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Why Climate Change Will Burn Energy Production, Water Supplies And The Trump Presidency - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kensilverstein/2018/11/26/why-climate-change-will-burn-energy-production-water-supplies-and-the-trump-presidency/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMkb3KTnU3GVxItAi5pN9OsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kensilverstein/2018/11/26/why-climate-change-will-burn-energy-production-water-supplies-and-the-trump-presidency/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Climate Change Will Burn Energy Production, Water Supplies And The Trump Presidency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Co2 (Carbon Dioxide) is one of the main causes of pollution, the greenhouse effect and climate change Donald Trump thinks he can save heavy industry the hassle of following environmental regulations, which will lead to greater profits and increased hiring. But his own administration says that ignoring the perils of climate change would end up costing the U.S. economy trillions. In fact, taking a laissez-faire approach to corporate polluters would undercut every aspect of American life, including energy production, water availability and infrastructure development. The total cost to society,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Energy: ENI accord with Algeria's Sonatrach on renewable - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/energy/2018/11/26/energy-eni-accord-with-algerias-sonatrach-on-renewable_b15e29f6-dfdb-44b2-9ff0-4a40210d26ff.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEERMmHN3Rqg5ou3pEPBpZoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 11:37:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/energy/2018/11/26/energy-eni-accord-with-algerias-sonatrach-on-renewable_b15e29f6-dfdb-44b2-9ff0-4a40210d26ff.html" target="_blank"&gt;Energy: ENI accord with Algeria's Sonatrach on renewable&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSAmed) - ROME, NOVEMBER 26 - ENI and Algeria's Sonatrach are inaugurating the photovoltaic plant of Bir Rebaa North worth 10 MW and have signed agreements on the renewable energy sector, according to a statement. The statement said that the president director general of the State-run Algerian company Sonatrach, Abdelmoumem Ould Kaddour, and the CEO of ENI, Claudio Descalzi, have inaugurated a solar energy plant worth 10 MW in Bir Rebaa North (BRN) in Algeria. The plant, jointly operated by ENI and Sonatrach through GSA (Groupement Sonatrach-Agip), will provide green energy to the oil fie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item></channel></rss>