<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Diane Rwigara - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZrWm1oNFgzbHpOQklDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-KE&amp;gl=KE&amp;ceid=KE:en</link><language>en-KE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:23:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Kagame critic Diane Rwigara 'not guilty' of inciting insurrection - Daily Nation</title><link>https://www.nation.co.ke/news/africa/Kagame-critic--not-guilty--of-inciting-insurrection/1066-4884394-dk5qk5/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMid2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5hdGlvbi5jby5rZS9uZXdzL2FmcmljYS9LYWdhbWUtY3JpdGljLS1ub3QtZ3VpbHR5LS1vZi1pbmNpdGluZy1pbnN1cnJlY3Rpb24vMTA2Ni00ODg0Mzk0LWRrNXFrNS9pbmRleC5odG1s0gHLAWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LW5hdGlvbi1jby1rZS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy5uYXRpb24uY28ua2UvbmV3cy9hZnJpY2EvS2FnYW1lLWNyaXRpYy0tbm90LWd1aWx0eS0tb2YtaW5jaXRpbmctaW5zdXJyZWN0aW9uLzEwNjYtNDg4NDM5NC12aWV3LWFzQU1QLWRiZGU1cy9pbmRleC5odG1sP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:58:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nation.co.ke/news/africa/Kagame-critic--not-guilty--of-inciting-insurrection/1066-4884394-dk5qk5/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kagame critic Diane Rwigara 'not guilty' of inciting insurrection&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Daily Nation&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prosecution's charges were baseless, judges say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpzcDZtbWpZQU1FVExwNGwxN3hrNDJLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nation.co.ke">Daily Nation</source></item><item><title>U.S. fights for Rwandan activist Diane Rwigara - Citizen TV</title><link>https://citizentv.co.ke/news/u-s-pushes-for-rwanda-govt-to-drop-charges-against-diane-rwigara-221197/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiZWh0dHBzOi8vY2l0aXplbnR2LmNvLmtlL25ld3MvdS1zLXB1c2hlcy1mb3ItcndhbmRhLWdvdnQtdG8tZHJvcC1jaGFyZ2VzLWFnYWluc3QtZGlhbmUtcndpZ2FyYS0yMjExOTcv0gGxAWh0dHBzOi8vY2l0aXplbnR2LWNvLWtlLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3MvY2l0aXplbnR2LmNvLmtlL25ld3MvdS1zLXB1c2hlcy1mb3ItcndhbmRhLWdvdnQtdG8tZHJvcC1jaGFyZ2VzLWFnYWluc3QtZGlhbmUtcndpZ2FyYS0yMjExOTcvP2FtcCZhbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://citizentv.co.ke/news/u-s-pushes-for-rwanda-govt-to-drop-charges-against-diane-rwigara-221197/" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. fights for Rwandan activist Diane Rwigara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Citizen TV&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. congressional lawmakers are pressing Rwanda's government against incarcerating dissident politician Diane Rwigara, who faces up to 22 years in prison ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://citizentv.co.ke">Citizen TV</source></item><item><title>Rwandan court drops charges against opposition politician Rwigara - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/rwandan-court-drops-charges-opposition-politician-rwigara-181206154419075.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAw6M1Nx3XU8Nl5RACY4JFEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:51:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/rwandan-court-drops-charges-opposition-politician-rwigara-181206154419075.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan court drops charges against opposition politician Rwigara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Rwandan court acquitted Diane Rwigara, a critic of veteran President Paul Kagame, on charges that included inciting insurrection and the forgery of documents. Rwigara, 37, was arrested in September 2017 after her attempt to run in Rwanda's presidential election was denied on grounds she allegedly forged the signatures of supporters for her bid. She was also charged with inciting insurrection for comments criticising the government and Kagame in the run-up to the election. She faced 22 years in prison if convicted. 181005174901472 A panel of three judges ruled the prosecution failed to pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Rwandan High Court Clears Opposition Leader of Charges - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/critic-of-rwandan-president-cleared-of-insurrection-forgery/4689389.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEP4ESoxZV6VI3Jllyt2XdMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:38:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/critic-of-rwandan-president-cleared-of-insurrection-forgery/4689389.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan High Court Clears Opposition Leader of Charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rwanda's high court has acquitted opposition leader Diane Rwigara of charges that included forgery and inciting insurrection. Rwigara, the country's highest-profile opposition figure, was imprisoned after her arrest in September 2017. The 37-year-old accountant's arrest came after she tried to run against Paul Kagame in the country's July 2017 presidential election. Rwigara was not allowed to run after accusations she allegedly forged signatures of supporters. The insurrection charge against Rwigara stems from critical comments she made against Kagame and his government before the election....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Rwandan court drops all charges against opposition figure - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/080eb2e22d3943c098bcc47a0c012fd2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEyYYmhOk_e0RHvtPNOzim0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:32:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/080eb2e22d3943c098bcc47a0c012fd2" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan court drops all charges against opposition figure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KIGALI, Rwanda (AP) — Rwanda's high court on Thursday acquitted the country's most prominent opposition figure of all charges related to her election challenge of President Paul Kagame, as judges said the prosecution failed to provide proof of insurrection and forgery. Diane Rwigara's case has drawn global attention as Kagame again faces pressure to give more space to critics in this highly controlled East African country. Rwigara's mother, Adeline, 59, also was acquitted of inciting insurrection and promoting sectarianism. Both women had denied the charges. The courtroom, packed with diplo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Rwandan court acquits prominent opposition leader of forgery, incitement - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-verdict-asequals-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJV4Fnh8VE3WFcssD_W9KFcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:34:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-verdict-asequals-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan court acquits prominent opposition leader of forgery, incitement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN -- Diane Rwigara, the 37-year-old human rights activist who had once hoped to run for the Rwandan presidency, has been acquitted of charges of fraud and inciting insurrection. The verdict was delivered in Kigali's High Court on Thursday. Rwigara's mother, Adeline, who was also in court facing charges of inciting insurrection and sectarian practices, was also acquitted of all charges. "We find that the prosecution charges do not have a basis and find Diane Rwigara and Adeline Rwigara not guilty on all charges," the three-judge verdict read, according to local news website The East Africa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kagame critic acquitted on insurrection charges - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/38e8304c-f9a1-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEEpYIUSqZPBCVa_N8s_jQsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:05:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/38e8304c-f9a1-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Kagame critic acquitted on insurrection charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diane Rwigara, a Rwandan activist and fierce critic of president Paul Kagame, was acquitted on Thursday of charges of inciting insurrection against the state and forgery. The 37-year-old opposition leader, who spent more than a year in prison before she was released on bail last month, welcomed the ruling but said she will continue to push for political reform in the central African state. “I am very happy with the verdict” Ms Rwigara said by phone from the Rwandan capital Kigali. “I will continue with what I started.” Ms Rwigara rose to prominence last year when she sought to run against M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Rwandan government critic acquitted of 'baseless' insurrection charges - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/06/critic-of-rwandan-president-cleared-of-insurrection-and-forgery</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMkQ7GoKuW9om1sxKs58LtsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:11:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/06/critic-of-rwandan-president-cleared-of-insurrection-and-forgery" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan government critic acquitted of 'baseless' insurrection charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A prominent government critic and her mother have been acquitted by Rwanda’s high court of politically motivated charges including inciting insurrection and forging documents. Diane Rwigara and her mother Adeline hugged supporters as cheers broke out in the packed courtroom in the capital Kigali while the verdict was read out. A three-judge panel described the charges as “baseless”. Rwigara, 37, was accused of forgery in relation to her unsuccessful attempt to run against the long-time president Paul Kagame. She was arrested in September last year and held in jail for more than a year, unti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>She tried to run for President, she ended up in jail - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/08/23/as-equals-rwanda-women-politics-kagame-rwigara-lon-orig-ejk.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHHwrUr49aJVv2BlXmx0-4oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:40:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/08/23/as-equals-rwanda-women-politics-kagame-rwigara-lon-orig-ejk.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;She tried to run for President, she ended up in jail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rwanda is a world leader for women in politics, but no woman has managed to become President and the last one who tried ended up in jail. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US congressional support builds for Rwandan opposition leader - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/africa/us-congressional-support-rwanda-diane-rwigara-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM36n_R-8dLKM46aO14S3hoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:50:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/africa/us-congressional-support-rwanda-diane-rwigara-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;US congressional support builds for Rwandan opposition leader&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN -- A group of members of the US Congress are calling on the Rwandan government to drop charges against Diane Rwigara, a fierce government critic who is facing up to 22 years in prison on charges of incitement and fraud. Rwigara, 37, has long said that the charges against her are politically motivated and stem from her bid to run against President Paul Kagame in the 2017 elections. Days after she announced her plan to run for office, nude photos -- allegedly of her -- were posted online. Rwigara says the images were digitally altered and used by the government to discredit her as both a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rwandan Dissident Draws US Congressional Support - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/rwandan-dissident-draws-us-congressional-support/4678705.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDIfmvTxI1AszYT7ZmpUOkcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 21:59:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/rwandan-dissident-draws-us-congressional-support/4678705.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan Dissident Draws US Congressional Support&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. congressional lawmakers are pressing Rwanda's government against incarcerating dissident politician Diane Rwigara, who faces up to 22 years in prison after being convicted of inciting insurrection and forgery. Diane Rwigara, a former presidential candidate, is scheduled to be sentenced December 6, along with her mother, Adeline Rwigara. Both women were tried November 7, with the elder Rwigara convicted of insurrection and promoting ethnic hatred. They had been detained by police in October 2017 and jailed for a year but released on bail last month, prior to trial. They remain at home i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Former Presidential Hopeful in Rwanda Said to Be in Custody - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/former-presidential-hopeful-diane-rwigara-said-to-be-in-custory-/4010930.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENwX3GUpuJYMysVpChygZpwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:15:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/former-presidential-hopeful-diane-rwigara-said-to-be-in-custory-/4010930.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Presidential Hopeful in Rwanda Said to Be in Custody&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A women's rights activist and former presidential hopeful is in police custody in Rwanda, her brother said Thursday, raising concerns about the whereabouts of a rare challenger to longtime President Paul Kagame. Police have said Diane Rwigara is free after her home in the capital, Kigali, was searched on Wednesday. But Rwigara's brother Aristide, who lives in the United States, told The Associated Press that his sister was arrested Wednesday along with three siblings and their mother. Police have said Diane Rwigara is under investigation for tax evasion and forgery. She is accused of forgin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Rwanda's Kagame has 98% lead in presidential election - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/05/africa/rwanda-election-results/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3PF9hV2MVcDwlY91QcxMMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 14:27:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/05/africa/rwanda-election-results/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwanda's Kagame has 98% lead in presidential election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rwandan President Paul Kagame is headed to re-election in a clear landslide victory, according to preliminary election results. Kagame is holding a big lead in preliminary results posted on the National Electoral Commission's Twitter feed, which showed him with more than 98% of the vote so far. Official results won't be announced until August 12, after the National Electoral Commission considers petitions and verifies numbers. Kagame has a seven-year tenure and is likely to enter his third term in office. According to the electoral commission, close to 7 million people took part in the elec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Two terms down, three to go? Rwanda's 'foregone conclusion' of an election - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/03/africa/rwanda-presidential-election-paul-kagame/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKr1iiHDUfm3isk6EnU986IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 09:17:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/03/africa/rwanda-presidential-election-paul-kagame/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Two terms down, three to go? Rwanda's 'foregone conclusion' of an election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former child refugee, Paul Kagame was once a hero to the West, feted for helping to bring Rwanda's bloody genocide to an end. But with allegations of repression, violence and politically-motivated murder dogging his rule, the military and political leader's international reputation has suffered. Undaunted, the Rwandan leader is standing for re-election on Friday. Seventeen years into his presidency -- and with the prospect of as many as 17 more to come -- there seems little doubt Kagame will claim victory again come polling day. "Some people have said that the result of the election is a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Diane Rwigara: Outspoken critic of Rwanda's President Paul Kagame arrested - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/09/05/africa/rwanda-female-presidential-candidate-arrested/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPrCC-YuCTU11rLkXwfgqqsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 10:28:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/09/05/africa/rwanda-female-presidential-candidate-arrested/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Diane Rwigara: Outspoken critic of Rwanda's President Paul Kagame arrested&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diane Rwigara, a leading critic of Rwandan President Paul Kagame, was arrested on charges of tax evasion and forgery. Rwandan police also posted a message on Twitter saying Rwigara and members of her family were held on Sunday for not responding to summons and were later released. "They are accused of tax evasion, and secondly Diane Rwigara is accused of using fake documents while she was gathering signatures for (her) presidential candidacy," Theos Badege, police spokesman, told reporters on Monday, according to local media reports. "They have been brought to CID for questioning, after ref...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rwandan police detain Paul Kagame critic Diane Rwigara - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/rwandan-police-detain-paul-kagame-critic-diane-rwigara-170924191105595.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELSoNqbfMcja43LI3cPqc78qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 21:45:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/rwandan-police-detain-paul-kagame-critic-diane-rwigara-170924191105595.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan police detain Paul Kagame critic Diane Rwigara&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rwandan police have arrested Diane Rwigara, a leading critic of President Paul Kagame, for alleged offences against state security. Rwigara's mother and sister were also detained on tax evasion charges, while she is also being charged with forgery, police said in a Twitter post on Sunday. The three women, who were arrested on Saturday, can be held for up to five days while authorities decide whether to press charges. READ MORE: Paul Kagame wins presidential poll by a landslide "During ongoing investigations, police uncovered credible evidence linking the trio to offenses against state secu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Fake nude photos were used to 'silence me', disqualified Rwandan candidate says - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/04/africa/rwanda-election-nude-photos-candidate/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEElrCqT1FytFv4bLnipVRmcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 11:53:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/04/africa/rwanda-election-nude-photos-candidate/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fake nude photos were used to 'silence me', disqualified Rwandan candidate says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rwanda may have the highest number of female lawmakers in the world, but one disqualified presidential candidate says it's not so easy for women to make it to the top job in the land. Diane Rwigara was the only female challenger to the incumbent President Paul Kagame in Friday's elections. She told CNN that when she announced her campaign to run, she was immediately targeted by the country's ruling Rwandan Patriotic Front (RPF) led by Kagame, who has been the country's leader since 2000. Days after Rwigara's announcement, nude photos of her were posted online, but the 35-year-old entreprene...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rwandan police arrest Diane Rwigara, family members - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/rwandan-police-arrest-diane-rwigara-family-members-170904192211566.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC8Nr5woRh8CkKn4mt0aUtkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 19:47:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/rwandan-police-arrest-diane-rwigara-family-members-170904192211566.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan police arrest Diane Rwigara, family members&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police in Rwanda have arrested Diane Shima Rwigara, a prominent government critic, charging her with forgery and tax evasion. Her mother and sister were also held on Monday on the tax charges. Earlier this year, electoral authorities barred Rwigara from standing in August's presidential vote, which President Paul Kagame won by a landslide, saying she had not submitted enough supporters' signatures and some of the names she did sent in belonged to dead people. Rwigara denied the allegations. "They are accused of tax evasion and secondly Diane Rwigara is accused of using fake documents while ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Rwanda's Kagame wins third presidential term by a landslide - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-election-idUSKBN1AK0RP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFWnnMFqKBOKL4meOPqtJkEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 08:06:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-election-idUSKBN1AK0RP" target="_blank"&gt;Rwanda's Kagame wins third presidential term by a landslide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Clement Uwiringiyimana KIGALI (Reuters) - Incumbent leader Paul Kagame has swept to a landslide victory in Rwanda's presidential election, results showed early on Saturday, securing a third term in office and extending his 17 years in power. Kagame has won international plaudits for presiding over a peaceful and rapid economic recovery in the Central African nation since the 1994 genocide, when an estimated 800,000 people Tutsis and moderate Hutus were killed. But he has also faced mounting censure for what critics and rights groups say are widespread human rights abuses, a muzzling of i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Critic of Rwandan president to face criminal trial on Friday - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-politics/critic-of-rwandan-president-to-face-criminal-trial-on-friday-idUSKBN1CA13X</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBsGP6AF4wd6tPNtr35Zf1gqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 10:49:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-politics/critic-of-rwandan-president-to-face-criminal-trial-on-friday-idUSKBN1CA13X" target="_blank"&gt;Critic of Rwandan president to face criminal trial on Friday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KIGALI (Reuters) - A critic of Rwandan President Paul Kagame will appear in court on Friday charged with inciting insurrection and forgery, the prosecutor's office said on Thursday. Diane Shima Rwigara, a 35-year-old accountant, is the latest political opponent of Kagame to face criminal charges. She was barred from contesting the presidency in an August election he won with 98.8 percent of the vote. She has repeatedly accused him of stifling dissent and criticized his Rwandan Patriotic Front's tight grip on the country since it fought its way to power to end a genocide that killed more tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Amnesty: Rwanda Polls Marred by Chilling 'Climate of Fear' - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/amnesty-international-says-rwanda-polls-marred-by-chilling-climate-of-fear-/3932874.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKD4fi5Y-Xa9Ym-mMFgDfMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 17:30:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/amnesty-international-says-rwanda-polls-marred-by-chilling-climate-of-fear-/3932874.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amnesty: Rwanda Polls Marred by Chilling 'Climate of Fear'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rwanda's presidential election next month will be held under "a climate of fear'' following two decades of often deadly attacks on political opponents, journalists and rights activists, Amnesty International charged Friday, calling for serious political reforms in the East African country. "Since the ruling Rwandan Patriotic Front took power 23 years ago, Rwandans have faced huge, and often deadly, obstacles to participating in public life and voicing criticism of government policy,'' said Muthoni Wanyeki, an Amnesty official in East Africa. "The climate in which the upcoming elections take...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Rwandan rights group calls for release of Kagame critic - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/f05018fe-8e62-11e7-a352-e46f43c5825d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEONYUqxMNHFdSg4fSx2dSfQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 18:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f05018fe-8e62-11e7-a352-e46f43c5825d" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan rights group calls for release of Kagame critic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A rights group has called on Rwandan authorities to release its co-founder and former presidential aspirant, Diane Rwigara, who has been missing since police took her from her home for interrogation this week. The People’s Salvation Movement, which Ms Rwigara helped establish after she was barred from running against President Paul Kagame in elections this month, gave no details od the whereabouts of the 35-year-old accountant. “We are urging the Rwandan government to release Diane Rwigara, immediately and unconditionally,” it said in a statement on Thursday evening. The Rwandan police have...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Kagame, Weakened Opposition Face Off in Rwanda Elections - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kagame-weakened-opposition-face-odd-rwanda-elections/3971162.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBgFYUg0xnIXJRew3m6azmQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 19:30:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kagame-weakened-opposition-face-odd-rwanda-elections/3971162.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kagame, Weakened Opposition Face Off in Rwanda Elections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rwandans head to the polls Friday with President Paul Kagame widely expected to win a third term despite allegations of political repression. Nine of the 11 registered political parties have endorsed the incumbent but a few candidates of other parties are still challenging Kagame. More than 200,000 people attended Kagame's final pre-election rally on Wednesday near Kigali. Supporters drove for hours to the massive hilltop venue. They sang, danced and cheered while waiting for their candidate to arrive. They waved the red, white and blue flag of the ruling party, the Rwandan Patriotic Front....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Paul Kagame re-elected president with 99% of vote in Rwanda election - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/aug/05/paul-kagame-secures-third-term-in-rwanda-presidential-election</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFNBXpCSow32OvnuQz9wkvMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 12:28:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/aug/05/paul-kagame-secures-third-term-in-rwanda-presidential-election" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Kagame re-elected president with 99% of vote in Rwanda election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Kagame, the controversial president of Rwanda, has won a landslide victory in the small African state’s election, securing a third term in office and extending his 17 years in power. The result will surprise no one, inside or outside Rwanda. Kagame has won international praise for the stability and economic development he has brought Rwanda since the 1994 genocide, when an estimated 800,000 people were killed, but he has also been accused of running an authoritarian, one-party state. Some have dismissed the polls as a sham. Related: ‘Rwanda is like a pretty girl with a lot of makeup, b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Rwanda counts votes as Paul Kagame eyes third-term 'coronation' victory - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/08/04/rwanda-counts-votes-paul-kagame-eyes-third-term-coronation-victory/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM37Kl_cBarwT1pdBh9in4EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 16:22:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/08/04/rwanda-counts-votes-paul-kagame-eyes-third-term-coronation-victory/" target="_blank"&gt;Rwanda counts votes as Paul Kagame eyes third-term 'coronation' victory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Kagame, Rwanda’s flinty president, was on the verge of securing a third term in power on Friday after an election that, bereft of serious opposition, was preordained to sweep him to victory. Apparently indifferent to the absence of a meaningful contest, Rwandans dutifully queued outside polling stations to cast their ballots in a vote derided by critics as a “coronation”. The president himself conceded that the election “was just a formality”. Voters line up to cast their vote at a polling station for the presidential electionCredit: AP Had Mr Kagame chosen to uphold the spirit of Rwan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Rwanda prepares for general and presidential polls - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/rwanda-prepares-general-presidential-polls-170802203631353.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHr9Tnn41_cJqy8cxZIRbRgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 15:30:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/rwanda-prepares-general-presidential-polls-170802203631353.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwanda prepares for general and presidential polls&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kigali, Rwanda- Rwanda's President Paul Kagame has campaigned in Gasabo, a suburb of the capital Kigali, in the run-up to the August 4 general and presidential elections. Tens of thousands of his supporters had to be beaten back by police brandishing baton sticks and fenced in on Wednesday as they fought to catch one last glimpse of their leader. Some claim the rally is evidence of the depth of Kagame's support Kagame in the lead-up to Friday's poll. "It's because the people love him. He's our hero, through him we built this country from scratch. Rwanda was dead before and now we are alive,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Rwandan opposition leader stands by her innocence at long-awaited trial - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/07/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-trial-asequals-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFgur_HF5iHOTk9vUlOi0pAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 15:43:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/07/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-trial-asequals-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan opposition leader stands by her innocence at long-awaited trial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN -- The high-profile trial of prominent Rwandan government critic Diane Rwigara and her mother concluded after five hours of proceedings in the High Court in the capital Kigali on Wednesday. Rwigara, 37, is facing charges of incitement and fraud. Her 59-year-old mother, Adeline Rwigara, has been accused of divisionism and inciting insurrection. Both have long said that their charges are politically motivated. Diane Rwigara was the sole female challenger in Rwanda's 2017 presidential election that Rwandan President Paul Kagame won with almost 99% of the vote. She had launched her campaign...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rwandan who challenged president faces 22 years in jail as trial opens - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/07/rwandan-dissident-politician-diane-rwigara-protests-innocence-as-trial-opens</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIZa0Hh867EGL4vG1cE_vDkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 16:52:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/07/rwandan-dissident-politician-diane-rwigara-protests-innocence-as-trial-opens" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan who challenged president faces 22 years in jail as trial opens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial of Rwanda’s leading dissident politician has opened with a demand from prosecutors that she be sentenced to 22 years in prison for inciting insurrection and forgery. Diane Rwigara denies the charges, dismissing them as politically motivated after her blocked attempt to challenge the country’s president, Paul Kagame, in last year’s elections. The 37-year-old appeared in court in Kigali, the capital, on Wednesday alongside her mother, who faces a similar sentence for alleged insurrection and promoting ethnic hatred. The two women had spent more than a year behind bars before being r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Rwanda seeks to jail opposition figure for 22 years - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/32aa0ddbfebd4ed9aa69738e8221331b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJzzpVRjs1LGfX7BZQOHtioqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 17:36:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/32aa0ddbfebd4ed9aa69738e8221331b" target="_blank"&gt;Rwanda seeks to jail opposition figure for 22 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KIGALI, Rwanda (AP) — Rwandan prosecutors want a former presidential candidate jailed for 22 years if she is convicted of forgery and insurrection charges. Diane Rwigara made an appearance in court Wednesday in the capital, Kigali, as the prosecutors made their case. The court will make its ruling on Dec. 6. Rwigara was given bail in October after more than a year behind bars on charges she has denounced as politically motivated after her outspoken challenge of one of Africa's most prominent leaders. The U.S.-educated activist has criticized President Paul Kagame's human rights record and a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Awaiting trial, Rwandan opposition leader says she's determined to hold government accountable - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-interview-asequals-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPcCRzkPQMoljEVEDKSoSR0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 21:14:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-interview-asequals-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Awaiting trial, Rwandan opposition leader says she's determined to hold government accountable&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN -- Diane Rwigara, a leading critic of Rwanda's President Paul Kagame, spent more than a year in prison before she was released on bail Friday. Now, as she awaits her trial in Kigali next month for incitement and election fraud, the 37-year-old human rights activist says she is more determined than ever to make her voice heard. "(Jail) has not squashed my political ambitions at all," Rwigara told CNN in an interview. "On the contrary, it has given me more determination because I just don't see myself and everyone else I know keeping on living in fear." The fear that Rwigara is speaking a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rwandan opposition leader Diane Rwigara and mother freed on bail - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/05/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-bail-asequals-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKG6xmkhxnDekx5jW7XMwKoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 13:23:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/05/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-bail-asequals-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan opposition leader Diane Rwigara and mother freed on bail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN -- Rwanda's fierce government critic Diane Rwigara and her mother Adeline Rwigara have been freed on bail, according to her family. Rwigara appeared in court Friday facing charges of incitement and fraud. Her mother, who was also in court, was being held on charges of discrimination and sectarian practices and inciting insurrection. But three High Court judges ruled that the prosecution did not give credible reasons why they should be detained during their trial, according to local media The East African. They ordered mother and daughter, who have been in jail since September 2017, to b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rwandan opposition activist Diane Rwigara released on bail - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/rwanda-opposition-activist-diane-rwigara-released-bail-181005174901472.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECaHbmVl-f9PlgcGgeoC0zAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:50:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/rwanda-opposition-activist-diane-rwigara-released-bail-181005174901472.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan opposition activist Diane Rwigara released on bail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rwandan opposition activist and former presidential candidate Diane Rwigara has been released on bail after spending more than a year in jail on charges including inciting insurrection against the government of President Paul Kagame. A high court in Kigali on Friday ordered Rwigara and her mother Adeline be released on the condition they do not leave the capital. While the prosecution had pushed for the two women to remain in detention, the court said that was unnecessary as investigations had been wrapped up and they could be bailed while on trial. "It's a great day for us and we are looki...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Release of Rwandan presidential critic raises hopes of political tolerance - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/05/release-rwandan-presidential-critic-rwigara-kagame-hopes-political-tolerance</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOh9ioEIxkbpsiibp0sAI4oqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 13:43:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/05/release-rwandan-presidential-critic-rwigara-kagame-hopes-political-tolerance" target="_blank"&gt;Release of Rwandan presidential critic raises hopes of political tolerance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Rwandan judge has ordered the release on bail of a vocal critic of Paul Kagame, the president, raising hopes for greater political tolerance after the release last month of another jailed high-profile opposition figure. Diane Rwigara, who was jailed in October 2017 on charges of incitement and forgery that were widely seen as politically motivated, will be released immediately but she is not allowed to leave the capital Kigali without the prosecutor’s authorisation. The 37-year-old businesswoman and activist has repeatedly accused Kagame of stifling dissent and criticised his Rwandan Patr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Rwanda court orders critic of president released on bail - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-politics/rwanda-court-orders-critic-of-president-released-on-bail-idUSKCN1MF15O</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG226WtLIT0bvIvxZIph3SMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:58:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-politics/rwanda-court-orders-critic-of-president-released-on-bail-idUSKCN1MF15O" target="_blank"&gt;Rwanda court orders critic of president released on bail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Rwandan high court judge ordered the release on bail on Friday of an opposition activist and her mother who were detained last year on charges of incitement after she was barred from standing against President Paul Kagame in elections. Diane Rwigara, a 37-year-old accountant, repeatedly accused Kagame of stifling dissent and criticized his Rwandan Patriotic Front's near total hold on power since it fought its way to office to end a genocide in 1994. She had planned to run against Kagame in an August election but her candidacy was blocked by the electoral board on the grounds that she had ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Freed Rwandan opposition leader: 'If you have other opinions, they put you in jail' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/02/africa/victoire-ingabire-freed-asequals-africa-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF1ocAs0xDsPQCVyesnb_zAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 08:42:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/02/africa/victoire-ingabire-freed-asequals-africa-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Freed Rwandan opposition leader: 'If you have other opinions, they put you in jail'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Rwandan opposition leader Victoire Ingabire learned that she was going to be released from jail, she couldn't believe the news. The 49-year-old leader of the opposition FDU-Inkingi party had served eight years of her 15-year sentence but there had been no sign of an early release. Yet on September 15, Ingabire, along with more than 2,100 other Rwandan prisoners, was granted a pardon by Rwanda's President Paul Kagame. In her first moments of freedom, Ingabire called on the government to free other political prisoners, including members of her own party and another imprisoned opposition ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Diane Rwigara: trial of Rwandan imprisoned opposition leader postponed - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/24/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-trial-postponed-asequals-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOnMlrs8sRLOcHc0_ngdl6sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 18:38:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/24/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-trial-postponed-asequals-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Diane Rwigara: trial of Rwandan imprisoned opposition leader postponed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN -- The trial of the jailed Rwandan opposition leader Diane Rwigara and her mother was postponed at Kigali's High Court on Monday. The Rwigaras' lawyers have petitioned the court to provisionally release the pair. They want a judge removed from the case who was involved in the pretrial detention hearing, according to the family's representative, Anne Rwigara, who is Diane Rwigara's sister. The pair, who have been imprisoned for over a year, now await a decision and a new trial date. Diane Rwigara, 37, was the sole female challenger in last year's election that Rwandan President Paul Kaga...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rwandan imprisoned opposition leader to go on trial as another walks free -- for now - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/22/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-victoire-ingabire-asequals-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO4JbfQrAc8eFv1hJ5bdhGAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 22:02:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/22/africa/rwanda-diane-rwigara-victoire-ingabire-asequals-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan imprisoned opposition leader to go on trial as another walks free -- for now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN -- Rwandan President Paul Kagame shocked many in his country and around the world last week when he granted more than 2,000 prisoners an unexpected pardon. But while the President was announcing the move in parliament to "rehabilitate our citizens," Diane Rwigara, the sole female challenger in last year's election that Kagame won with almost 99% of the vote, languished in jail, awaiting her fate in court. Rwigara, a 37-year-old accountant and fierce critic of Kagame, launched her election bid three months ahead of the August 2017 presidential vote. Shortly after she began her presidenti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Freed Rwandan opposition leader vows to continue struggle - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/24/freed-rwandan-opposition-leader-victoire-ingabire-vows-to-continue-struggle</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEINRdwUhIRuiBYr1lHJCYcEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 07:40:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/24/freed-rwandan-opposition-leader-victoire-ingabire-vows-to-continue-struggle" target="_blank"&gt;Freed Rwandan opposition leader vows to continue struggle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A prominent opposition politician in Rwanda who was among more than 2,000 prisoners freed this month has vowed to fight on until people in the small central African country can “speak up without fear”. Victoire Ingabire, 49, was arrested in 2010 and given a 14-year sentence two years later. “I am out of prison to start a new struggle. We want Rwandans to speak up without fear. This is what we are going to focus on in future. If demanding free speech, respect of human rights for everybody in this country makes me go back to prison, then I am prepared for it,” Ingabire said. She was convicted...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Rwanda frees opposition leader, 2,100 others from prison - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/ecca19e0ccfd4b4dad18b808eccaf0e2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL9JMf5NVzqItYrbh08gqCYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 14:38:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/ecca19e0ccfd4b4dad18b808eccaf0e2" target="_blank"&gt;Rwanda frees opposition leader, 2,100 others from prison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KIGALI, Rwanda (AP) — A prominent Rwandan opposition leader walked free on Saturday after the government approved the early release of more than 2,100 prisoners with little explanation. Victoire Ingabire Umuhoza's release surprised many because it is unusual for longtime President Paul Kagame to pardon potential challengers. She quickly urged Kagame to release all other political prisoners. "The beginning of opening of the political space in Rwanda, I hope so," she told reporters. Ingabire, head of the FDU-Inkingi opposition party, was arrested in 2010 and found guilty of conspiracy to unde...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Rwanda frees jailed opposition figure Ingabire - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-politiics/rwanda-frees-jailed-opposition-figure-ingabire-idUSKCN1LV049</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN1SlpB3CjxOslxuisSTgywqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 11:00:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-politiics/rwanda-frees-jailed-opposition-figure-ingabire-idUSKCN1LV049" target="_blank"&gt;Rwanda frees jailed opposition figure Ingabire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rwanda on Saturday freed Victoire Ingabire, an opposition leader who has served six years of a 15 year jail term, after President Paul Kagame exercised his power to grant a pardon. Ingabire, who leads the unregistered FDU-Inkingi opposition party, was freed along with other prisoners, including singer Kizito Mihigo, jailed in 2015 for plotting to kill Kagame. She emerged from prison in a red dress, green jacket and a broad smile. Flanked by her lawyer Gatera Gashabana, she told waiting reporters that her release, together with the election of two opposition parliamentarians earlier this mon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Rwandan Opposition Leader, 2,100 Others Walk Free from Prison - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/rwandan-opposition-leader-2100-others-walk-free-from-prison/4572858.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN57jP2QcOFXjZ9JQyTmpHEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 09:54:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/rwandan-opposition-leader-2100-others-walk-free-from-prison/4572858.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan Opposition Leader, 2,100 Others Walk Free from Prison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Rwanda’s most prominent opposition leaders walked free Saturday after the government approved the early release of more than 2,100 prisoners with little explanation. Supporters of Victoire Ingabire Umuhoza and the state-run The New Times newspaper posted photos of the opposition leader walking out of Nyarugenge prison hours after the justice ministry’s announcement. Also approved for early release was musician Kizito Mihigo, who along with Ingabire received a presidential commutation. The ministry statement said both had made their most recent requests for clemency in June. FILE - Rw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Two opposition lawmakers elected in Rwanda for the first time - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-politics/two-opposition-lawmakers-elected-in-rwanda-for-the-first-time-idUSKCN1LL2HI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE2mAFd-SYZZBvxtUUw3InAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 20:45:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-politics/two-opposition-lawmakers-elected-in-rwanda-for-the-first-time-idUSKCN1LL2HI" target="_blank"&gt;Two opposition lawmakers elected in Rwanda for the first time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opposition candidates have won seats in the Rwandan parliament for the first time, election results showed on Wednesday, although the two new lawmakers will be heavily outnumbered by members of President Paul Kagame's ruling party. Kagame's Rwanda Patriotic Front (RPF) declared the results of Monday's election proof that the country is a democracy, but one of the new opposition lawmakers said their tiny numbers meant pressing for democratization would be a long process. Kagame is praised for restoring stability in Rwanda and for rapid economic progress after the 1994 genocide. But rights gr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>She wanted to be president, but ended up jailed instead - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/28/africa/hfr-rwanda-diane-rwigara-asequals-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC41O9Na4zcWls7VLQfJTHEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 07:06:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/28/africa/hfr-rwanda-diane-rwigara-asequals-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;She wanted to be president, but ended up jailed instead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN is committed to covering gender inequality wherever it occurs in the world. This story is part of As Equals, a year-long series. Kigali, Rwanda -- In the darkness of the Kigali night, Eric walks through a maze of cement homes crowned in corrugated metal. Using his phone he lights the road under his feet, a path of compressed red earth still drying out from the rainy season. After nearly an hour of walking through a series of dizzying hills that make up the Rwandan capital, he reaches his safe house. Eric -- whose name has been changed for his safety -- says he's being watched by the gov...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump set to meet with Rwandan President in Davos - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/25/politics/paul-kagame-donald-trump-rwanda/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFzgqpnbEAs5OAaW043SWsoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 00:04:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/01/25/politics/paul-kagame-donald-trump-rwanda/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump set to meet with Rwandan President in Davos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump is poised to meet with President Paul Kagame of Rwanda on Friday, an important meeting in a series of high-profile, one-on-ones with world leaders at the World Economic Forum following controversial comments by the US President. The two leaders will "reaffirm the US-Africa relationship and discuss shared priorities, including trade and security," White House press secretary Sarah Sanders said at a briefing earlier this week. Earlier this month, Trump came under fire for remarks reportedly describing African nations and Haiti as "shithole countries" during a discussion...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rwandan leader's would-be rival Rwigara and her mother denied bail - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-politics/rwandan-leaders-would-be-rival-rwigara-and-her-mother-denied-bail-idUSKBN1CS2FY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECg9iEDE8PU_6V4gHiF125oqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 18:39:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-politics/rwandan-leaders-would-be-rival-rwigara-and-her-mother-denied-bail-idUSKBN1CS2FY" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan leader's would-be rival Rwigara and her mother denied bail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Clement Uwiringiyimana KIGALI (Reuters) - A Rwandan court denied bail on Monday to a vocal critic of President Paul Kagame who was barred from running against him in an August election and later jailed on charges of incitement and forgery that are widely seen as politically motivated. Diane Rwigara and her mother, Adeline, who was also refused bail, said they planned to appeal. Her sister Anne, who is a U.S. citizen, was granted bail. All three women are charged with inciting insurrection while Diane is also accused of forging the signatures of some people she said backed her run for pre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Critic of Rwanda's president asks for freedom in court - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/critic-rwanda-president-asks-freedom-court-171017095704628.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIGYQ2M_1CXa8g9IiCSvts8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 10:42:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/critic-rwanda-president-asks-freedom-court-171017095704628.html" target="_blank"&gt;Critic of Rwanda's president asks for freedom in court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A critic of Rwandan President Paul Kagame asked him to free her and her detained mother and sister as she stood in court on Monday charged with forgery and "inciting insurrection". Diane Shima Rwigara, who was barred from running against Kagame in August elections, moved to comfort her mother Adeline and sister Anne as they cried during the hearing. ”I request the president release me and my family,” she said. She told the court she was “being victimised ... because I have political ambitions”. The 35-year-old accountant is accused of faking the registration papers she filed to stand in the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>U.N. torture watchdog ends trip to Rwanda, citing obstruction - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-rights/u-n-torture-watchdog-ends-trip-to-rwanda-citing-obstruction-idUSKBN1CQ0EI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIYLyk6uT-w6nVjdd8wjg4YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 11:21:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-rwanda-rights/u-n-torture-watchdog-ends-trip-to-rwanda-citing-obstruction-idUSKBN1CQ0EI" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. torture watchdog ends trip to Rwanda, citing obstruction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Clement Uwiringiyimana KIGALI (Reuters) - The U.N. subcommittee on torture prevention has suspended a visit to Rwanda, citing obstructions imposed by the government that compromised its fact-finding mission. Rwandan authorities barred the U.N. delegation from accessing some detention sites and made it impossible for them to conduct "private and confidential interviews", a statement from the U.N. body published on Friday said. The body said it was only the third time in 10 years it had suspended a mission. It called on Rwanda to cooperate with the body and "abide by its international obli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Mother of Rwandan President's Challenger Tells Court of Torture - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/mother-diane-shima-rwigara-rwanda-president-challenger-torture/4069206.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGdxSRN9cXK7sJ9BxnAckgMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 16:07:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/mother-diane-shima-rwigara-rwanda-president-challenger-torture/4069206.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mother of Rwandan President's Challenger Tells Court of Torture&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mother and sister of a prominent critic of Rwanda's president said on Friday all three of them had been tortured and deprived of food as they were held in jail on charges of forgery and inciting insurrection. Adeline Rwigara told a court she and her daughters were handcuffed day and night. She is being held alongside her daughter Diane Shima Rwigara, a 35-year-old accountant who tried to stand against President Paul Kagame in August elections. Diane Rwigara, who is accused of faking registration papers for the election, was eventually barred from running and Kagame went on to win with 9...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Opponent of Rwandan President Denies Insurrection, Forgery Charges in Court - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/opponent-rwanda-president-denies-insurrection-forgery-charges-court/4065774.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKEgircGhWCHZ_W0E0oyabkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 15:20:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/opponent-rwanda-president-denies-insurrection-forgery-charges-court/4065774.html" target="_blank"&gt;Opponent of Rwandan President Denies Insurrection, Forgery Charges in Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A prominent opponent of Rwandan President Paul Kagame pleaded not guilty Wednesday to charges of forgery and inciting insurrection and said she was being prevented from accessing her case file to chart her defense. Any legal misstep in the trial of Diane Shima Rwigara could further mar the reputation of the long-ruling Kagame, who is credited for stabilizing and developing Rwanda after its 1994 genocide but accused by rights groups of suppressing dissent. Rwigara is accused of falsifying registration papers she filed to stand against Kagame in an August election and is the latest in a serie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Report: Rwandan Military Subjects Detainees to Illegal Detention, Torture - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/report-says-rwandan-military-tortured-detainees/4063749.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_xHisnPwn97Xuee2O1MWYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/report-says-rwandan-military-tortured-detainees/4063749.html" target="_blank"&gt;Report: Rwandan Military Subjects Detainees to Illegal Detention, Torture&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human Rights Watch says Rwandan soldiers routinely tortured detainees, engaging in beatings, electric shock and mock executions to extract confessions. The New York-based group issued a 91-page report Tuesday that reveals 104 confirmed cases of people who were illegally detained in Rwandan military detention centers between 2010 and 2016. Many of those arrested were suspected of either being members of, or working with, the Democratic Forces for the Liberation of Rwanda, a predominantly Rwandan Hutu armed group based in the Democratic Republic of Congo. Some members of the group are suspect...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Family of Rwandan Activist Says Her Arrest Is Warning to Critics - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/family-of-rwandan-activist-says-her-arrest-is-warning-to-critics/4053387.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFqGBwMwkOXzXT-5qIm4UfsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 20:27:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/family-of-rwandan-activist-says-her-arrest-is-warning-to-critics/4053387.html" target="_blank"&gt;Family of Rwandan Activist Says Her Arrest Is Warning to Critics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The family of a former Rwandan presidential candidate is demanding answers a week after she was taken into police custody. Officially, Diane Rwigara has been charged with “offenses against state security and forgery” following her arrest on Sept. 23. Her family believes the only crime she committed was challenging the authority of President Paul Kagame by running for president. “These charges are false; they are totally false, and nobody in Rwanda believes the validity of these charges. Everybody knows it’s all made up,” said Rwigara’s brother Aristide Rwigara, who lives in the United State...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>