<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>NTV - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNR2Q2YXpKckVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-KE&amp;gl=KE&amp;ceid=KE:en</link><language>en-KE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:25:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Key NMG staff quit for lack of media freedom - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/03/key-nmg-staff-quit-lack-media-freedom-180327134410182.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKLTR8kAW92SoMbOnF5DbisqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 16:22:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/03/key-nmg-staff-quit-lack-media-freedom-180327134410182.html" target="_blank"&gt;Key NMG staff quit for lack of media freedom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eight prominent columnists working for Kenya's biggest media group quit over what they said was increased meddling by government and a loss of media freedom at its outlets. The columnists include George Kegoro, executive director of the Kenyan Human Rights Commission; Lynne Muthoni Wanyeki, Africa director of the Open Society Foundation; and Nic Cheeseman, professor of democracy at Birmingham University. There was no immediate response from the Nationa Media Group (NMG) to requests for comment said AFP news agency. Meddling In a joint statement, the eight highlighted several incidents in re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Opinion: Why it's a perilous time to be a journalist in Kenya - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/09/africa/kenya-press-freedom-madowo/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAIOij69A7dQbX0EwccIY74qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 13:07:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/09/africa/kenya-press-freedom-madowo/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: Why it's a perilous time to be a journalist in Kenya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Larry Madowo is the Technology Editor and News Anchor at NTV Kenya, one of Africa's biggest private TV stations. He has reported stories from nearly 40 countries and interviewed some of the world's most prominent business, political and cultural icons. The views expressed here are solely his. It was Tuesday January 30 and I was in the NTV Kenya control room producing our coverage of opposition leader Raila Odinga's mock swearing-in when an off-air monitor in the gallery suddenly went dark. 'Karimi, what's happening?' I demanded of an engineer nearby. He shook his head in utter bewilderment ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kenyan broadcasters back on air after government block - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/02/kenyan-broadcasters-air-government-block-180205184508545.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsUaB_Snzfuoxdt_rVIwpkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 20:23:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/02/kenyan-broadcasters-air-government-block-180205184508545.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan broadcasters back on air after government block&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two Kenyan television stations have resumed broadcasting after being taken off air for plans to show a rally held by the country's opposition leader. The NTV and KTN channels were both accessible on Monday, but two others - Citizen TV and Inooro TV - remained blocked, Kenya's Daily Nation newspaper reported on Monday. Earlier in the day, protesters took to the streets in Kenya's capital Nairobi to condemn the media shutdown, it said. The government suspended all four stations on January 30 after they announced plans to air the symbolic "swearing in" of opposition leader Raila Odinga, which ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Kenya TV stations shutdown enters 5th day as government defies court order - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/03/africa/kenya-tv-stations-shutdown/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEM1uho1tafohfpepk8tQgoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 12:29:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/03/africa/kenya-tv-stations-shutdown/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya TV stations shutdown enters 5th day as government defies court order&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Kenyan government continued to defy a court order to put four private television stations back on the air, escalating political tensions as the media blackout enters a fifth day Saturday. Government officials shut down CitizenTV, InooroTV, KTN and NTV, during a live broadcast of an opposition gathering in the capital of Nairobi on Tuesday. The stations had ignored the government's warnings not to cover the rally in which opposition leader Rail Odinga inaugurated himself as "the people's president" -- even though he boycotted last November's elections that saw Kenyatta win with 98% of th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Media censorship casts worrying shadow over Kenya's democracy - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/05/africa/kenya-media-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGuteyFZNrSfApYxXUNPqhEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 19:36:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/05/africa/kenya-media-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Media censorship casts worrying shadow over Kenya's democracy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In September, Kenya was praised by many after its Supreme Court -- citing irregularities -- nullified the election of the country's sitting president. But nearly six months on it appears this applause from observers was premature. As the Court ordered a fresh election for October, President Uhuru Kenyatta, bitterly disappointed by the judges' decision, declared with grace, "I don't agree with the decision, but I respect it." It was seen as an example of how Kenya's rule of law actually held sway. But last year also produced a heavy body count (92 people died during the protracted election p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kenya court suspends government's media shutdown - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/02/kenya-court-suspends-government-media-shutdown-180201143724641.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDikt6yn_GuZwPMki-VQogqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 15:24:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/02/kenya-court-suspends-government-media-shutdown-180201143724641.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya court suspends government's media shutdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya's High Court has suspended the shutdown of three independent television stations, which were blocked earlier this week after they had planned to broadcast a contentious symbolic "swearing in" ceremony for opposition leader Raila Odinga. The country's High Court ordered a 14-day suspension of the government's shutdown - which affected stations NTV, Citizen and KTN TV - while a legal challenge can be heard, NTV said on Thursday. "Government expected to restore NTV, Citizen TV &amp; KTN News signals after High Court suspends switch off for 14 days pending case being heard," the station wrote...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Putting Kenya's media shutdown in context - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/putting-kenya-media-shutdown-context-180202092850790.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIDMSHzjtBAZNdoM8m5MG3oqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 14:15:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/putting-kenya-media-shutdown-context-180202092850790.html" target="_blank"&gt;Putting Kenya's media shutdown in context&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, December 30, the Kenyan government took the unprecedented step of shutting down three of the largest television stations in the country. At KTN, the first independent station in Kenya, the signal was merely switched off. But at Citizen Television and NTV, officials of the Communications Authority of Kenya (CAK) allegedly went to one of their main distribution locations and physically disconnected their machines. This after a Monday evening memorandum from the chair of the Editor's Guild of Kenya, Linus Kaikai, alleging that all senior editors in the country had been summoned by ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Kenyan court orders government to restore TV stations yanked off air - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/01/africa/kenya-tv-stations-shutdown/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEUp7b6Ql7k3HUA6CmurmokqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 07:10:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/01/africa/kenya-tv-stations-shutdown/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan court orders government to restore TV stations yanked off air&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Kenyan high court Thursday ordered the restoration of three major television stations taken off air by the government this week over coverage of a mock presidential inauguration. The court has suspended the shutdown pending a February 14 court hearing challenging the decision to take the private stations off air, according to a court ruling. The government cut the television transmission of KTN, NTV and Citizen TV on Tuesday to prevent them from airing the symbolic swearing-in of opposition leader Raila Odinga the same day. Before the court's ruling, the Interior Ministry had said the sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>UN calls on Kenya to end ongoing TV station suspension - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/02/calls-kenya-ongoing-tv-station-suspension-180202144121458.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDegY8ZXyHTGuKjJ15RaxwIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 15:28:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/02/calls-kenya-ongoing-tv-station-suspension-180202144121458.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN calls on Kenya to end ongoing TV station suspension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations has criticised the government of Kenya for keeping three independent television stations off the air, despite a court ruling ordering the state to lift the suspension. Rupert Colville, spokesperson for the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights, said the stations remained suspended for a third day on Friday "in spite of an interim order by a Kenyan high court". "We call on the government to respect and implement the judicial decision," Colville said in a statement. The NTV, Citizen and KTN TV networks were suspended on Tuesday after they planned to broadcast the symbolic s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Kenya government ignores court order suspending shutdown of three TV stations - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-politics/kenya-court-suspends-government-shutdown-of-three-tv-stations-idUSKBN1FL4V1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPVRba8fcKNGtHFRYU8q5bYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 19:52:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-politics/kenya-court-suspends-government-shutdown-of-three-tv-stations-idUSKBN1FL4V1" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya government ignores court order suspending shutdown of three TV stations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Maggie Fick and George Obulutsa NAIROBI (Reuters) - Three private Kenyan television channels remained off air despite a court order on Thursday that they be allowed to resume broadcasting, overturning a government-ordered shut down. Authorities turned off the three channels as they began to cover opposition leader Raila Odinga's symbolic presidential inauguration on Tuesday. NTV Kenya, three of whose journalists said they had spent the night in their newsroom in fear of arrest, said on its Twitter feed that the privately owned broadcasters were expected back on air after the High Court r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Kenyan government accused of media crackdown in wake of opposition mock inauguration - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/01/31/kenyan-government-accused-media-crackdown-wake-opposition-mock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA5-QuUEcC3polcH_4WNkVEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 19:34:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/01/31/kenyan-government-accused-media-crackdown-wake-opposition-mock/" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan government accused of media crackdown in wake of opposition mock inauguration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Kenyan government was accused of mounting the biggest assault on freedom of expression in the country’s recent history on Wednesday after police arrested a leading opposition MP and attempted to detain three prominent journalists. In scenes redolent of the dictatorial one-party era that ended with the Cold War, police stormed the headquarters of the Nation, Kenya’s biggest private media group, with arrest warrants for three of the country’s best known television personalities. Although it was unclear what charges might be pressed against the reporters, the move was seen as part of a wid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Kenya TV stations still off air despite court order - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/02/africa/kenya-tv-stations-shutdown-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDgFwAE5VJYFXpnQ5Nu21rYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 09:02:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/02/africa/kenya-tv-stations-shutdown-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya TV stations still off air despite court order&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three major Kenyan television channels remained off the air Friday despite a high court order compelling the government to allow them to resume broadcasting. In what has been seen by many as media censorship, the government ordered private channels KTN, NTV and Citizen TV to be switched off Tuesday over coverage of a symbolic "swearing-in" of opposition leader Raila Odinga the same day. The television channels went dark at 10 a.m. (2 a.m. ET) Tuesday -- a move not seen in the country for years. A court ordered the government Thursday to restore all transmissions immediately pending a Februa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Kenyan journalists, fearing arrest, camp out in their newsroom - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-politics/kenyan-journalists-fearing-arrest-camp-out-in-their-newsroom-idUSKBN1FL44X</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGOaKq5kF9FM6ilvb4ZzRlkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 07:03:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-politics/kenyan-journalists-fearing-arrest-camp-out-in-their-newsroom-idUSKBN1FL44X" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan journalists, fearing arrest, camp out in their newsroom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NAIROBI (Reuters) - Three Kenyan journalists said on Thursday they spent the night in their newsroom in fear of arrest, watching plainclothes policemen camped outside, and that their lawyers would file court petitions in the morning seeking to ensure their freedom. Their station, NTV, was one of three independently owned stations shut down by Kenyan authorities on Tuesday after they broadcast live coverage of an opposition ceremony symbolically "swearing in" opposition leader Raila Odinga. "We were doing our job, we had the right to do this, and if I was to do it again, I'd do it the same w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Kenya says three top TV stations to remain off air - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/5cc2f622-069b-11e8-9650-9c0ad2d7c5b5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbXKCN1dX3Glfxd6BmruuwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 17:51:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5cc2f622-069b-11e8-9650-9c0ad2d7c5b5" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya says three top TV stations to remain off air&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya said the country’s three largest private television stations would remain off air indefinitely, pending an investigation into “incitement” linked to the mock presidential inauguration of opposition leader Raila Odinga. The Media Council of Kenya, the industry regulator, described the move to close the KTN News, NTV and Citizen stations as “the greatest threat and assault on freedom of expression and media in Kenya’s recent history”. The government cut the transmission of the stations on Tuesday to prevent coverage of the mock swearing-in, which was a symbolic challenge to the legitima...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>