<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Maize - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFV6ZDI0U0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-KE&amp;gl=KE&amp;ceid=KE:en</link><language>en-KE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:48:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Hotter world threatens the breadbasket of the US - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2eda777e-db68-11e8-b173-ebef6ab1374a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ7u_gRcTZhS40SUPHPq9nUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 04:31:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2eda777e-db68-11e8-b173-ebef6ab1374a" target="_blank"&gt;Hotter world threatens the breadbasket of the US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The past summer was fecund for US farms. Yields per acre of corn, soyabeans and spring wheat are all forecast to break records. The future is less certain, however, with crop yields projected to come under pressure as global warming accelerates. Understanding when, where and how is critical to feeding the world in the decades to come. US field crop agriculture is the most productive on earth. Tens of millions of tonnes of exports make it important to the rest of the world. Farm sales of corn, soyabeans and wheat totalled almost $100bn last year, according to the US Department of Agriculture...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Penny for your corn? Stingy trade-war aid irks U.S. farmers - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/usa-trade-china-aid/penny-for-your-corn-stingy-trade-war-aid-irks-u-s-farmers-idUSL2N1X61AV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECTvvbrxNBYSmwQa9M6r0tQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 18:15:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/usa-trade-china-aid/penny-for-your-corn-stingy-trade-war-aid-irks-u-s-farmers-idUSL2N1X61AV" target="_blank"&gt;Penny for your corn? Stingy trade-war aid irks U.S. farmers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iowa corn farmer Bob Hemesath jokes that the government check he expects as compensation for his trade-war losses will soon allow him to splurge on upscale coffee in town instead of his usual burnt gas-station brew. Rob Sharkey, an Illinois farmer, hopes his corn trade aid check will be big enough for that margarita machine he and his wife have been eyeing – but they doubt they'll be any left over for the booze. Federal economists have calculated that the nation’s losses in corn - its largest crop by harvest and export volume - amount to just a penny per bushel, a pittance farmers call absu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Most And Least Healthy, Authentic Foods This Thanksgiving - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adambarsouk/2018/11/21/the-most-and-least-healthy-authentic-foods-this-thanksgiving/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBObkfzXlmFr9LFx-EQZbXYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/adambarsouk/2018/11/21/the-most-and-least-healthy-authentic-foods-this-thanksgiving/" target="_blank"&gt;The Most And Least Healthy, Authentic Foods This Thanksgiving&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanksgiving can be an important opportunity for family bonding and celebrating our nation’s rich history. But a huge feast with all the wrong foods could actually be inauthentic and detrimental for your health. Below are the best and worst Thanksgiving foods according to the latest nutritional guidelines, and thousands of years of Native American consumption. high angle view of a roast turkey placed on a rustic wooden table next to some bowls with gravy, mashed potatoes, blueberry jam, some slices of roasted potato or a roasted corn Stuffing Stuffing is effectively bread, and usually white...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Four Lies People Tell Themselves To Justify Staying In Toxic Jobs - Forbes Now</title><link>//www.forbes.com/sites/jmaureenhenderson/2017/08/30/four-lies-people-tell-themselves-to-justify-staying-in-toxic-jobs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPl6v_jGuswHar51cs_C458qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="//www.forbes.com/sites/jmaureenhenderson/2017/08/30/four-lies-people-tell-themselves-to-justify-staying-in-toxic-jobs/" target="_blank"&gt;Four Lies People Tell Themselves To Justify Staying In Toxic Jobs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexander KHUDOTEPLY/AFP/Getty Images Recently, Axios ran an interesting piece detailing the reason top White House officials gave (anonymously, of course) for not quitting the Trump administration as so many have done or been forced to do. Their reasons aren’t surprising. In fact, the justifications they give for staying put in what has been widely reported to be a dysfunctional and often toxic work environment are exactly the same ones that anyone else who doggedly sticks it out in a similarly poisonous workplace would give. Here are those reasons and why they’re ultimately untenable. “I’...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Brazilian landless peasants invade farm owned by minister's family - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-land-dispute-idUSKBN1AA1ZD</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC8OlVsgkSGX_vGiTAV_eEMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 15:25:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-land-dispute-idUSKBN1AA1ZD" target="_blank"&gt;Brazilian landless peasants invade farm owned by minister's family&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAO PAULO (Reuters) - About 1,000 landless peasant families invaded a farm belonging to a firm owned by the family of Brazilian Agriculture Minister Blairo Maggi on Tuesday, according to a statement from the group backing the occupation. The landless peasant movement, known as MST, said in a statement on its website that the occupation began early Tuesday morning on a farm 210 kilometers (131 miles) from Cuiabá, capital of Mato Grosso state. The group said the property belongs to Amaggi SA. Mato Grosso is Maggi's home state and the country's agricultural heartland. Press representatives for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Hobby Farmer - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/220945229/hobby-farmer-by-henry-hintermeister</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPVa036cKvapZHeu3AQRuaAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 10:56:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/220945229/hobby-farmer-by-henry-hintermeister" target="_blank"&gt;Hobby Farmer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few hay bales along side a small old weathered barn are watered down reminders of a farmer who years ago depended on this farm for his livelihood. Now a hobby farmer plays at farming. Old farmers often are bemused when young people talk about how hard they work, remembering their own days of shocking grain, picking corn by hand and working 14 hour days in the blazing sun.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Special Report: Drowning in grain - How Big Ag sowed seeds of a profit-slashing glut - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-grains-supply-special-report/special-report-drowning-in-grain-how-big-ag-sowed-seeds-of-a-profit-slashing-glut-idUSKCN1C21AR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAQIVWGSfCGvIB7XqDgFK8IqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 12:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-grains-supply-special-report/special-report-drowning-in-grain-how-big-ag-sowed-seeds-of-a-profit-slashing-glut-idUSKCN1C21AR" target="_blank"&gt;Special Report: Drowning in grain - How Big Ag sowed seeds of a profit-slashing glut&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Rod Nickel CARMAN, Manitoba (Reuters) - On Canada's fertile Prairies, dominated by the yellows and golds of canola and wheat, summers are too short to grow corn on a major scale. But Monsanto Co (MON.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) is working to develop what it hopes will be North America's fastest-maturing corn, allowing farmers to grow more in Western Canada and other inhospitable climates, such as Ukraine. The seed and chemical giant projects that western Canadian corn plantings could multiply 20 times to 10 million acres by 2025 - adding some 1.1 billion bushels, or nearly 3...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Fall Armyworms on March Across Africa - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/fall-armyworms-march-across-africa/3944352.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJhYYywkKlKFxMI6goL7jYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 15:50:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/fall-armyworms-march-across-africa/3944352.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fall Armyworms on March Across Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recently arrived species of armyworm has spread to 21 African countries and threatens the continent's main food staple, maize, report experts from the U.S. Agency for International Development. USAID senior biotechnology advisor Joseph Huesing says the fall armyworms -- transported from their usual habitat in the U.S. state of Florida or the Caribbean -- are attacking maize crops all over sub-Saharan Africa. "From Nigeria and Ghana all the way to South Africa to Ethiopia. The most recent one is South Sudan, which reported fall armyworm infestation toward the end of June," Huesing tells V...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Climate Extremes, Policy Confuse Crop Choices for Malawi Farmers - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/climate-extremes-policy-confuse-crop-choices-for-malawi-farmers/3986989.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJ_ZSFIm-ZoC6zQHuBnXhkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 21:02:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/climate-extremes-policy-confuse-crop-choices-for-malawi-farmers/3986989.html" target="_blank"&gt;Climate Extremes, Policy Confuse Crop Choices for Malawi Farmers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elias Kanyangale is ecstatic about his maize harvest. Balancing on a homemade ladder, the farmer retrieves cobs from a full granary, the bounty of this year's good rains, which broke three years of drought in Malawi. Kanyangale, 44, from Kalumbu village, part of the capital city Lilongwe, says his 5-ton harvest of maize is double the previous year's crop, and he has some soya beans too. But he is still worried about his income. “I am not sure I will get good prices for my crop. I planted more maize for home consumption and more soya beans for sale because the rains were good after the droug...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The remarkable history in your cereal bowl - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/13/health/kellogg-corn-flakes-wellness-history-markel/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPeggoJRg3WDloppYlYdS4IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 04:24:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/13/health/kellogg-corn-flakes-wellness-history-markel/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The remarkable history in your cereal bowl&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Howard Markel, the George E. Wantz distinguished professor of the history of medicine at the University of Michigan, is the author of "The Kelloggs: The Battling Brothers of Battle Creek." This morning, more than 350 million people devoured a bowl of Kellogg's Corn Flakes. All told, more than 128 billion bowls of Corn Flakes are consumed each year. While perusing the cereal box, peering over the bowl and gripping a spoonful of the stuff, few of these sleepy diners know that two men created those famously crispy, golden flakes of corn. John Harvey Kellogg, one of America's most famous ph...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>First commercial mung bean harvest for Ord in decades - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2017-08-09/first-commercial-mung-bean-harvest-in-ord-valley-for-decades/8785536</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJy6fGXW_46dHpM3NrYrGjEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 23:18:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2017-08-09/first-commercial-mung-bean-harvest-in-ord-valley-for-decades/8785536" target="_blank"&gt;First commercial mung bean harvest for Ord in decades&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mung beans are being commercially harvested in the Kimberley's Ord Irrigation Scheme for the first time in decades. After promising trial results last year, a handful of growers have planted around 500 hectares of the pulse crop. Grower Fritz Bolten has been harvesting this month and said the crop had faired well. "It's gone well, although we've probably not quite averaged our original yield target, but we've got about 2 million serves that will go out to feed people from this [harvest], which is not a small feat and something I'm pretty proud of," he said. "But what's really exciting is, b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Biofuel-linked stocks jump as China said to plan 2020 ethanol roll-out - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/31c68837-9eb2-3f22-b10b-7611f7960606</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHnYd55xN5BG5BV41BYyBf0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 02:29:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/31c68837-9eb2-3f22-b10b-7611f7960606" target="_blank"&gt;Biofuel-linked stocks jump as China said to plan 2020 ethanol roll-out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in companies linked to ethanol production in China lifted as much as 10 per cent on Wednesday following state media reports that Beijing was planning to complete a nationwide roll-out of ethanol in gasoline by 2020. Major Chinese agricultural producer Shandong Longlive Bio-technology was up 10 per cent in Shenzhen on Wednesday – the limit for a one day move on the mainland – while COFCO Biochemicals, one of China’s largest agricultural product processors, was up as much as 6.4 per cent. China is also targeting large-scale production of cellulose ethanol and advanced biofuel technolog...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>The Best Trader Joe's Food Products, According To The Brand Itself - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trader-joes-best-products_us_5992fd79e4b090964299f4c6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKVrUFONqoQR3TNhgZ-bOikqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2GuAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 15:05:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trader-joes-best-products_us_5992fd79e4b090964299f4c6" target="_blank"&gt;The Best Trader Joe's Food Products, According To The Brand Itself&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In celebration of Trader Joe’s 50-year anniversary, the grocery store chain has just put out a list of its best foods. The chain polled its customers and crew to discover their favorite products, and that poll has resulted in a grandiose selection. Trader Joe’s curated that list to create what is an epic collection of TJ’s best offerings. There’s just one problem: Trader Joe’s cookie butter is markedly absent from the list. The entire collection can be found in the brand’s Fearless Flyer, but we’ve also listed them out for you below -- minus two beauty products and two floral products - wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>China Plans Nationwide Ethanol Use by 2020 - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/china-plans-nationwide-ethanol-use-by-2020/4026751.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMey-QSF27hHcWGejGg9mYwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 12:47:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/china-plans-nationwide-ethanol-use-by-2020/4026751.html" target="_blank"&gt;China Plans Nationwide Ethanol Use by 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China plans to expand use of ethanol in gasoline nationwide by 2020 to curb smog and fossil fuel demand, the government said Wednesday, joining United States, Brazil and other nations that use blended fuel. The announcement adds to a series of initiatives to clean up smog-choked Chinese cities and control surging demand for imported oil. The government is spending heavily to develop an electric car industry and has raised sales taxes on vehicles with larger engines. Plans call for China to develop a demonstration facility by 2020 that can make 50,000 tons of ethanol a year from cellulose, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Lush - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/218034639/lush-by-ash-taylor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHmkoohmSY1YCK_y0ohDVKcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 06:56:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/218034639/lush-by-ash-taylor" target="_blank"&gt;Lush&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Corn fields in Norfolk UK as the sun went down.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Trade chokepoints risk food price spikes - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/fea9770a-5835-11e7-9fed-c19e2700005f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOXQkKgO8PVc9t2B49bb_xgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 10:34:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/fea9770a-5835-11e7-9fed-c19e2700005f" target="_blank"&gt;Trade chokepoints risk food price spikes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The growing importance of global trade in agricultural commodities has increased the risks of disruption at key transport “chokepoints”, potentially triggering food price surges. The Panama Canal and the Strait of Malacca are among 14 of the world’s critical junctures through which significant amounts of grains and soyabeans trade pass, according to a report from Chatham House. “A serious interruption at one or more of these chokepoints could conceivably lead to supply shortfalls and price spikes, with systemic consequences that could reach beyond food markets,” warns the report. The danger...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Too dry - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/217265779/too-dry-by-hans-lakuse</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENhCLNZ02TAnZxfWVAYzFCYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 06:30:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/217265779/too-dry-by-hans-lakuse" target="_blank"&gt;Too dry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last few month it hardly rain in my part of the country. The potatoes, corn, unions, black currants, they all could use some water. The dark clouds suggested rain but unfortunately it only gave some thunder and lightning, hardy any rain...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>There's A Huge Difference Between The Corn We Eat vs. What Cows Eat - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sweet-corn-vs-field-corn_us_596f6718e4b0a03aba868f75</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENiZGKveiZKDoNMrot-nnNUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2GuAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 10:00:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sweet-corn-vs-field-corn_us_596f6718e4b0a03aba868f75" target="_blank"&gt;There's A Huge Difference Between The Corn We Eat vs. What Cows Eat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States grows over 90 million acres of corn a year, and 99 percent of it is not the kind that humans eat on the cob. That’s right, corn is not just corn ― there are many different types. The kind people eat on the cob (typically in the summertime) is known as sweet corn (Zea mays convar. saccharata var. rugosa), and it makes up only one percent of the corn grown in the U.S. each year. Sweet corn is harvested during the summer months when the tops of the husks start to turn brown. It’s then used to make some of the best summer dishes. The other 99 percent of corn that dominates our...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Bunge issues surprise Q2 profit warning - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b4e772be-a79e-3507-89eb-9dea76e92fbe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFp0xt4lzGr4R0X8_PJ58Z8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 23:29:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b4e772be-a79e-3507-89eb-9dea76e92fbe" target="_blank"&gt;Bunge issues surprise Q2 profit warning&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The agricultural commodities merchant Bunge has made a surprise profit warning as woes deepen in its grain and oilseed trading business. The company, which operates a global network of silos, ports and crushing plants, said Wednesday that profits would be “below the low end” of estimates in the second quarter. It scheduled a conference call for investors Thursday. The disclosure will fan speculation that Bunge could become takeover target. The stock fell 3.4 per cent after exchange hours in New York. Glencore, the Swiss-based commodities powerhouse, in May said it approached Bunge about a b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>‘GM seed choice shouldn’t be dictated’: Italian farmers question EU court ruling on Monsanto corn - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/403685-italy-farmers-gmo-maze/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEClbwnl6gQdY35jmJj7dkzcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 12:36:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/403685-italy-farmers-gmo-maze/" target="_blank"&gt;‘GM seed choice shouldn’t be dictated’: Italian farmers question EU court ruling on Monsanto corn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all Italian farmers welcome a European court ruling this week allowing growers to cultivate genetically-modified corn in Italy. Some farmers told RT that the majority reject GM seeds and question the EU interfering in national laws. The European Court of Justice on Wednesday ruled in favor of Giorgio Fidenato, an Italian activist farmer who faces fines for growing genetically-modified maize MON 810 on his land in 2014, despite a 2013 government decree banning its cultivation. In 2013, Italy asked the European Commission to adopt emergency measures prohibiting the planting of the Monsant...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: EPA eyes limits for agricultural chemical linked to crop damage - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-pesticides-epa-exclusive/exclusive-epa-eyes-limits-for-agricultural-chemical-linked-to-crop-damage-idUSKCN1BG1GT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECDqtK1h4Ls-zQomZo1PZSgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:46:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-pesticides-epa-exclusive/exclusive-epa-eyes-limits-for-agricultural-chemical-linked-to-crop-damage-idUSKCN1BG1GT" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: EPA eyes limits for agricultural chemical linked to crop damage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Tom Polansek and Emily Flitter (Reuters) - The U.S. environmental agency is considering banning sprayings of the agricultural herbicide dicamba after a set deadline next year, according to state officials advising the agency on its response to crop damage linked to the weed killer. Setting a cut-off date, possibly sometime in the first half of 2018, would aim to protect plants vulnerable to dicamba, after growers across the U.S. farm belt reported the chemical drifted from where it was sprayed this summer, damaging millions of acres of soybeans and other crops. A ban could hurt sales by ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Ex-minister, 2 Others Arrested in Malawi Food Import Scandal - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/malawi-maizegate/3950582.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6w5NZBjYuLVnwBzHhgl0sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 16:45:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/malawi-maizegate/3950582.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-minister, 2 Others Arrested in Malawi Food Import Scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malawi's Anti-corruption Bureau, or ACB, has arrested a former agriculture minister and two others linked to a corruption scandal involving maize imports. Malawi was importing the grain to avert food shortages after flooding and drought wrecked last year's harvest. ACB officials Wednesday announced the arrests of former agriculture minister George Chaponda, along with businesswoman Grace Mijiga Mhango and Rashid Tayub, an entrepreneur based in Blantyre. They are accused of illegal actions in the procurement of 100,000 tons of maize from Zambia by Malawi’s grain marketer ADMARC, the Agricul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Could Biofortified Crops Be The Key To Solving Global Hunger? - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40436843/could-biofortified-crops-be-the-key-to-solving-global-hunger</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOGOLsIX02wrgbF8Inpx8osqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 15:00:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/40436843/could-biofortified-crops-be-the-key-to-solving-global-hunger" target="_blank"&gt;Could Biofortified Crops Be The Key To Solving Global Hunger?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For around 2 billion people in the world, a meal is not necessarily a source of nutrition. Among the poorest populations, starchy staple crops like potatoes and cassava make up the bulk of people’s diets. The people surviving off these crops “may not feel hungry,” says Bev Postma, CEO of HarvestPlus, “but they’re not getting a diverse, nutritious meal, and this ‘hidden hunger’ can lead to blindness, disease, and stunting.” For children under the age of 11, who grow up without consistent access to adequate nutrition, the developmental effects are irreversible; mothers who lack essential vita...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Can The Corn Ethanol Lobby Win In Mexico, Too? - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2017/09/25/can-the-corn-ethanol-lobby-win-in-mexico-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMcYy7TRPSJlVy6io02P144qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 17:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidblackmon/2017/09/25/can-the-corn-ethanol-lobby-win-in-mexico-too/" target="_blank"&gt;Can The Corn Ethanol Lobby Win In Mexico, Too?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mike Short, a caucus chairperson speaks to caucus attendees during a Democratic Party Caucus at Jackson Township Fire Station on February 1, 2016 in Keokuk, Iowa. / AFP / Michael B. Thomas (Photo credit should read MICHAEL B. THOMAS/AFP/Getty Images) Despite decidedly mixed scientific research on whether their product helps or harms the environment, the lobby for the use of corn-based ethanol in the United States has been extremely successful in acquiring and perpetuating mandates and subsidies for the use of their product in motor fuels for many years now. This is in spite of the reality ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Crop tourists ponder the prospects of US grain harvest - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1e72480a-8770-11e7-8bb1-5ba57d47eff7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC8mry6UYHM4zKqpTal7QMgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 10:34:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1e72480a-8770-11e7-8bb1-5ba57d47eff7" target="_blank"&gt;Crop tourists ponder the prospects of US grain harvest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grand Island, Nebraska received two types of tourists on Monday. The first gazed heavenwards as a total solar eclipse passed by. The second saw humbler sights: farm fields. This small city directly in the eclipse’s path was also a stop on the annual Farm Journal Midwest Crop Tour, a caravan of farmers, hedge fund managers, brokers and analysts roaming the heart of the world’s leading corn and soyabean growing region. This week they are measuring corn ears and bean pods with a goal of estimating the US harvest. If Chicago’s futures markets are an indication, the crops will be big for a fifth...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>US Wheat Production Lowest in Recorded History - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-wheat-production-lowest-in-recorded-history/4031636.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBHhMYhu_c4kaTVzQQjZO-oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-wheat-production-lowest-in-recorded-history/4031636.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Wheat Production Lowest in Recorded History&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Farmer Russ Higgins' ancestors settled a wide expanse of land south of Morris, Illinois, in 1858. Through the U.S. Civil War and every major event since then, there has been someone from the Higgins family planting and harvesting on the land. Since the first plow churned up the fertile soil here nearly 160 years ago, one crop that always had a place among the fields was wheat. “The next crop is going to go in as soon as we take this year’s soybean crop out, hopefully within the next two and half to three weeks,” Higgins told VOA, before hopping on his all-terrain vehicle to head out into hi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>India's Farmers Revive Traditional Grains in Face of Severe Drought - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/india-farmers-revive-traditional-grains-face-severe-drought/3996412.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBW2nTtcny5WcvsiPJyNTukqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 22:22:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/india-farmers-revive-traditional-grains-face-severe-drought/3996412.html" target="_blank"&gt;India's Farmers Revive Traditional Grains in Face of Severe Drought&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Nel Jayaraman, the realization that hybrid seeds, chemical fertilizers and pesticides were making farmers more vulnerable to extreme weather came slowly. In fields near the town of Thiruthuraipoondi in the southern state of Tamil Nadu, Jayaraman saw yields falling and farmers' debt rising as their reliance on modern seeds and pesticides grew, even as the rains became increasingly fickle. Fifteen years ago, Jayaraman gave up both, returning to traditional varieties and organic farming methods that had become nearly extinct in the Cauvery river delta region where his family had lived for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Unprecedented grains price jump for farmers - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2017-07-04/unprecedented-grains-price-jump/8676424</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI2r_vkhaFGKbHm0NwSdOiYqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 08:10:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2017-07-04/unprecedented-grains-price-jump/8676424" target="_blank"&gt;Unprecedented grains price jump for farmers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The critically dry conditions across southern Australia and a forecast drop in wheat supply have caused grain prices to surge. Grains trader Charlie Brown said the price of wheat had risen by up to 20 per cent in recent weeks. But Mr Brown said he was not sure if the price rise was sustainable. "It's been a big move and almost an unprecedented move in such a short period of time to have markets rally so strongly," he said. "I know it's a tough time for Aussie farmers … so the challenge is trying to have confidence in selling at these prices, knowing that there's always the risk we could go ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>CORN and Lightning - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/219314489/corn-and-lightning-by-aaron-groen</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELvHcphPk-3jEgeFKOpgIygqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 16:46:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/219314489/corn-and-lightning-by-aaron-groen" target="_blank"&gt;CORN and Lightning&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;facebook.com/HomeGroenPhotography Canon EOS 6D and Canon EF16-35mm f/2.8 L III USM lens and LEE Filters Big Stopper @ 10 seconds f/4.5 100iso 16mm Taken north of Huron, South Dakota. HomeGroenPhotography.com&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Cotton prices tumble after hurricanes fail to spoil a bumper crop - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/52c0876a-97e3-11e7-b83c-9588e51488a0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ1fw3Jra2cMBOB3zvM5gfQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 18:49:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/52c0876a-97e3-11e7-b83c-9588e51488a0" target="_blank"&gt;Cotton prices tumble after hurricanes fail to spoil a bumper crop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The price of cotton slid by the maximum allowed after a government report indicated a massive crop was growing in spite of hurricanes’ one-two punch across the US south. The fibre led a broad sell-off in agricultural commodities, with corn and soyabeans also dropping. Triggering the fall was an updated monthly forecast for crop production. The US Department of Agriculture said farmers would harvest 21.8m bales of cotton this autumn, an estimate 6 per cent higher than last month and the most since 2005. ICE December cotton futures were down 4.2 per cent, or the exchange-permitted limit of 3 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Bunge chief says ‘nothing off limits’ in cost-cutting drive - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/42c30d1e-6d4b-11e7-bfeb-33fe0c5b7eaa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOoqIq3aK3QTfH0L4Q3yT8QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 17:50:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/42c30d1e-6d4b-11e7-bfeb-33fe0c5b7eaa" target="_blank"&gt;Bunge chief says ‘nothing off limits’ in cost-cutting drive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bunge, the grain trading house, has detailed plans to slash $450m in costs and capital spending as it deals with weakening profit margins and a possible takeover bid from commodities titan Glencore. The New York-listed company, the world’s biggest oilseed processor and a leading merchant of corn, soyabeans and wheat, issued a second-quarter profit warning late on Wednesday, citing “unprecedented” crop hoarding by South American farmers. Grain middlemen have struggled as bumper harvests depress prices, leaving farmers reluctant to sell and customers wary of paying a premium for advance suppl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Dry season a crisis for WA farming family - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2017-07-06/dry-crisis-for-wa-farmers/8682358</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHQYG5jxlEeBNJl_KkFhp5YqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 22:52:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2017-07-06/dry-crisis-for-wa-farmers/8682358" target="_blank"&gt;Dry season a crisis for WA farming family&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jane Keune and her son Perry St Quintin have been working the land on Anthill Farm near Yuna, 125 kilometres north-east of Geraldton, for 22 years. In that time they have seen both good and bad seasons, but the lack of rain this winter is threatening their future, and Ms Keune has never been so afraid of losing her farm. "We are getting really quite frightened about the bank, I mean, what can they do to help us?" she said. The family planted 3,300 hectares of wheat, canola, lupins and barley this year. It was a bold choice to sow 800 hectares canola so far from the coast, but this was the p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Traders slash bearish soyabean bets as US crop deteriorates - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1938af32-7136-11e7-aca6-c6bd07df1a3c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOiIcSkdsMtMlD7DSJNoumgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 16:11:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1938af32-7136-11e7-aca6-c6bd07df1a3c" target="_blank"&gt;Traders slash bearish soyabean bets as US crop deteriorates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Agricultural traders have slashed their bearish bets on US soyabeans in recent weeks as farmers grapple with deteriorating conditions at a crucial time for crop development. Over the next month plants will reach the critical pod-setting stage in which small beans begin to grow and eventually fill the pods. At the start of the week, the US Department of Agriculture estimated that the condition of the oilseed crop, which had been affected by drought conditions in key growing areas, had deteriorated further. It said 57 per cent of the crop was in good or excellent condition, compared with 61 p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>The Best Summer Dinner Recipes Around - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/summer-dinner-recipes_us_5978c6eae4b0a8a40e84b0cc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECJE5n7FuWd7i1r6r-zHgcoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 10:00:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/summer-dinner-recipes_us_5978c6eae4b0a8a40e84b0cc" target="_blank"&gt;The Best Summer Dinner Recipes Around&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are just a few things required for a great summer dinner. The first is fresh, seasonal produce (which is so easy to come across during these warm months). The second is a recipe that’s able to made outdoors. And third, it should be plentiful enough to share with friends and family, because summer is all about shared meals and impromptu gatherings. The summer dinner recipes we have for you today are just what you need. They’re chock full of tomatoes, corn, zucchini and summer fruit. They’re quick and easy to make. And they’re all meant for sharing. Check them out: 1 Summer Shrimp Zoodl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Russia to boost wheat exports on expectations of record harvest - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/business/402450-russia-wheat-imports-increase/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELI8lPtqHGvaxeQ20tfsCksqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwroQo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 11:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/business/402450-russia-wheat-imports-increase/" target="_blank"&gt;Russia to boost wheat exports on expectations of record harvest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The booming Russian agriculture sector is attracting new customers, with China and Venezuela planning to increase imports of Russian wheat. The country is expecting a record grain crop this year, exceeding the numbers from 1978. Four thousand tons of spring wheat will be delivered to China from Russia’s Novosibirsk region by October 10. It’s the first batch of wheat purchased by China's largest food processor COFCO. "Together with our suppliers, we plan to discuss how to better meet the demand of Chinese mills. We want to know more about the production and the quality of Russian wheat in or...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>The Best Corn Recipes For Summer - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/corn-recipes-for-summer_us_596d04fbe4b010d77672f723</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOltfJd70_DnY1-vdojyaogqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/corn-recipes-for-summer_us_596d04fbe4b010d77672f723" target="_blank"&gt;The Best Corn Recipes For Summer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nothing tastes more like summer than fresh corn. Sweet and satisfying, it’s the perfect accompaniment to any meal served during the sun-filled days of our very favorite season. While it’s really hard to get tired of it served on the cob with nothing more than a slathering of butter, sometimes we feel compelled to take our corn game up a notch. And when we do, we are hugely rewarded. From a simple corn on the cob upgrade to Mexican street corn nachos, these are the recipes you should try at least once this summer. And don’t forget to make use of the cobs and the husks while you’re at it. 1 M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Bumper grain crop in Russia set to break Soviet-era record - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/business/400412-russia-bumper-crop-grain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECwfT7f0cxlzRypwsU-BT0gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwroQo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 14:50:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/business/400412-russia-bumper-crop-grain/" target="_blank"&gt;Bumper grain crop in Russia set to break Soviet-era record&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia is forecast to produce a record grain crop this year, exceeding the numbers last seen in 1978. According to the Moscow-based grain consultant ProZerno, Russia is expected to harvest 130.7 million metric tons this year. It is 2.6 percent more than the previous record set in 1978 before the Soviet-Afghan War. ProZerno predicts a record harvest of wheat of 80.1 million tons. Barley is expected to reach 19 million tons. "Corn is not that far at 16.3 million tons, which is also a record,” said Vladimir Petrichenko, director general of the company in an interview with Agroinvestor.ru. Petr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>While Stock Market Soars, US Farmers Struggle - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-farmers-struggle-despite-stock-market-rise/4024927.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDO8hp9qRb4gfQPDr9YBbf4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 06:09:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-farmers-struggle-despite-stock-market-rise/4024927.html" target="_blank"&gt;While Stock Market Soars, US Farmers Struggle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The annual Farm Progress Show held every other year in Decatur, a town situated among the vast corn and soybean fields of central Illinois, is one of the largest farming exhibitions in the world, where manufacturers and suppliers show their latest and greatest products and equipment. In some cases, it’s a starting point for farmers researching what big-ticket items are available to make their work in the fields more efficient, and easier. But all Tolono, Illinois farmer Jeff Fisher can do at the John Deere exhibit at this year’s show… is look. “A quarter of a million dollars list price for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The Harvest - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/223578977/the-harvest-by-chris-frost</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI_Q3mryMGFLwm7w1knUrmIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 19:30:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/223578977/the-harvest-by-chris-frost" target="_blank"&gt;The Harvest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A black 'Dutch Barn' sits amid a sea of corn as the morning skies are lit up in burst of colours.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>field of maize - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/227047405/field-of-maize-by-dana-mirtschin</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFsU7-J9feN_thJdGsVYqYgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 04:40:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/227047405/field-of-maize-by-dana-mirtschin" target="_blank"&gt;field of maize&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;sunset in the maize field&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>My best summer photograph: sand, scorpions and sausage sarnies - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2017/aug/22/my-best-summer-shot-wolfgang-tilmanns-chloe-dewe-mathews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF1jftu26jrZxQQ9-RqEwFEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 05:00:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2017/aug/22/my-best-summer-shot-wolfgang-tilmanns-chloe-dewe-mathews" target="_blank"&gt;My best summer photograph: sand, scorpions and sausage sarnies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘They came to Aberystwyth from all over’ Chloe Dewe Mathews I was visiting my boyfriend in Aberystwyth when I overheard some people on the seafront asking: “When are the Jews arriving?” I was baffled. When I asked a local person, they explained that a large community of Orthodox Jews came every year for a couple of weeks in August and stayed in the university accommodation at the top of the hill. They would come from all over – New York, Canada, Israel, but mostly London and Manchester. They spent the mornings in a conference and then in the afternoon came down to the seafront or went up to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Why soyabeans are the crop of the century - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/35af007e-49f6-11e7-919a-1e14ce4af89b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIYx5_0_zHAwutaTEp56_H8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 17:54:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/35af007e-49f6-11e7-919a-1e14ce4af89b" target="_blank"&gt;Why soyabeans are the crop of the century&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fields outside Mohall, North Dakota, were until recently a collage of blue flax, yellow sunflowers and amber wheat. But today many are uniform patches of green at the peak of the summer growing season. This new landscape is thanks to farmers such as Eric Moberg, whose 72-row air seeder planted thousands of acres with soyabeans this spring. “We didn’t grow any beans four years ago. Now it’s almost a third of our acre base,” he says. His windswept county on the Canada border is at the frontier of a shift in world food supply. As emerging Asia eats more chicken and pork, the soyabeans that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Worsening Drought Conditions in Parts of US Stressing Crops - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/worsening-drought-conditions-us-stressing-crops/3961909.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB6qrQtlvGB7QST0YpauunQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 20:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/worsening-drought-conditions-us-stressing-crops/3961909.html" target="_blank"&gt;Worsening Drought Conditions in Parts of US Stressing Crops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drought conditions worsened in several states over the past week from extreme heat and weeks with little rain, raising the prospect that grocery staples such as bread and beans could cost more as the region that produces those commodities is hardest hit. Drought conditions have begun to stress corn, soybeans, wheat and livestock in some areas, according to the weekly U.S. Drought Monitor released Thursday by the University of Nebraska-Lincoln. Nearly 11 percent of the continental United States is in moderate drought or worse, said Richard Heim, a meteorologist with the National Oceanic and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Grain inventories forecast to fall for first time in five years - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/02394feb-58eb-3336-bc04-c3e90edce05f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHN8YO_9yZlv22M5Q6FGEwIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 14:39:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/02394feb-58eb-3336-bc04-c3e90edce05f" target="_blank"&gt;Grain inventories forecast to fall for first time in five years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are we at a turning point in the grains markets after years of bumper supplies? With grains consumption climbing, total inventories are forecast to fall for the first time in five years, according to the International Grains Council. In its latest monthly forecast of supply, production and inventories, global grains consumption is predicted to hit a record high of 2.089bn tonnes in the 2017-18 crop year, thanks to continued low prices. This is expected to drive down stocks for the first time since 2012-13. The level of inventories is important as it provides a buffer if there is a crop fail...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Syngenta ordered to pay $218m in damages over biotech corn strain - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4f6d051a-7ac1-34ff-a8e9-fb54de98c38b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDUv3JEOWGnTQuvf4OVL-cUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 18:45:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4f6d051a-7ac1-34ff-a8e9-fb54de98c38b" target="_blank"&gt;Syngenta ordered to pay $218m in damages over biotech corn strain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A jury has ordered Swiss seed company Syngenta to pay $217.7m in compensatory damages to Kansas farmers over its decision to sell a biotech corn strain unapproved by China. China blocked corn imports from the US starting in late 2013 after inspectors detected traces of Agrisure Viptera, a Syngenta corn variety genetically engineered to combat cutworms. Approved for planting in the US, the strain had not yet received a green light from Beijing. Sales of corn to China plummeted after the move, sparking lawsuits against Swiss-based Syngenta from US farmers who claimed they suffered a fall in g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Cuban Farmland Lies Fallow, Production Languishes, Govt. Report Shows - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/cuban-farmland-lies-fallow-production-languishes-according-to-government-report-/3917209.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECICDFF4EaOj_kIu4Hu8pscqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 23:45:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/cuban-farmland-lies-fallow-production-languishes-according-to-government-report-/3917209.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cuban Farmland Lies Fallow, Production Languishes, Govt. Report Shows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than half of Cuba's arable land remains fallow nearly a decade after a government pledge to cultivate it, and food production is sluggish, according to a government report. Cuba has yet to publish an overall figure for last year's agricultural output. But the report released over the weekend by the National Statistics Office indicated only minor improvement in 2016 over the previous year. The state owns 80 percent of the land and leases most of that to farmers and cooperatives. The remainder is owned by private family farmers and their cooperatives. Despite the leasing of small parcels...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Touching the Corn - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/218287811/touching-the-corn-by-hatcat-photography</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6_3jqqoTjn5np-VLRapo4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 11:48:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/218287811/touching-the-corn-by-hatcat-photography" target="_blank"&gt;Touching the Corn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Touching the Corn Shot in Weinheim with #sony #rx1rii Wish you all the best, HatCat Processed in #Lightroom using #vsco #ektachrome160T++ color curve and #sonyclear camera profile. Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/HatCat_Photography Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/HatCatPhotography&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>How Corn Flakes Revolutionized Breakfast - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/how-corn-flakes-revolutionized-breakfast</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJu4oLqwqefapOpn27szqdQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/how-corn-flakes-revolutionized-breakfast" target="_blank"&gt;How Corn Flakes Revolutionized Breakfast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is impossible for someone born after World War I to appreciate the stunning sensation ready-to-eat breakfast cereals created at the beginning of the twentieth century. Long before that event, many American housewives prepared hot cereals from grains such as oats, barley, buckwheat, and corn. Bowls of this thick or thin mess, depending upon one’s budget, were alternatively called “porridge,” “gruel,” or “mush.” It required hours of boiling and cooking to soften up the grain, meaning the cook had to awaken quite early before she could serve it to her family. Other common breakfasts of this...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Bakers scramble for the aristocrat of wheat - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9d342d34-6d5d-11e7-bfeb-33fe0c5b7eaa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJuCQZ8wXtvwBrYkcpKxgK4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 07:51:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9d342d34-6d5d-11e7-bfeb-33fe0c5b7eaa" target="_blank"&gt;Bakers scramble for the aristocrat of wheat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a group of bakers, flour millers and agricultural traders descend on the northern plains of the US this week, they will be looking for the extent of drought damage on this year’s crop of top quality wheat that is grown across the region. The lack of rain and above normal temperatures have hit the hard red spring wheat, which is used for bread and pasta. Conditions of the crop, known as the “aristocrat of wheat”, have deteriorated and prices for the high quality grain have soared to four-year highs. “We’ve had 2 years of low protein crops and the world is needing high quality and high pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Corn, wheat, soyabean prices fall after USDA forecasts - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ad17f208-42b0-378b-9aaa-731b681b74ec</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPu_Rq8HYiBv7mZAT7NZWxQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 01:27:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ad17f208-42b0-378b-9aaa-731b681b74ec" target="_blank"&gt;Corn, wheat, soyabean prices fall after USDA forecasts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Futures prices for a wide range of grains fell sharply on Thursday in the US as positive forecasts from the US Department of Agriculture drove investors off bets that yields for crops including wheat, corn and soybeans would come up short. Futures contracts for those three crops had risen from late June as dry weather in the US prompted concerns about soil moisture. But the department’s latest forecasts out on Thursday came in on the high side of expectations, undercutting bullish sentiment on prices. CBOT corn fell 4 per cent to $3.71 a bushel on Thursday, wheat dropped 3.7 per cent to $4....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Corn - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/223263651/corn-by-ash-taylor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFI0CcrZk5j_Jl_j5Xz5gD8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 03:51:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/223263651/corn-by-ash-taylor" target="_blank"&gt;Corn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Corn field in east England Norfolk&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Whiskey Review: Woodford Reserve Rye, Spirit Works, St. Augustine And More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/fredminnick/2018/11/21/whiskey-review-woodford-reserve-rye-spirit-works-st-augustine-and-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPKkvgSRFbdyy0zgal-TpA4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/fredminnick/2018/11/21/whiskey-review-woodford-reserve-rye-spirit-works-st-augustine-and-more/" target="_blank"&gt;Whiskey Review: Woodford Reserve Rye, Spirit Works, St. Augustine And More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, American whiskey equaled only the new charred oak beauties coming from Kentucky and Tennessee. Those days are over, with the resurgence of distilling all over the country. As I’ve taken a break from straight reviews, focusing on the whiskies of the year and gift guides, I’ve still tasted some new and interesting releases. While none of these made my Top 15, there are some worthy whiskeys in this crop and some craft distillers to keep your eye on. 74, Cardinal Spirits Straight Bourbon, 90 proof About: Distilled and Bottled in Bloomington, Indiana. This young bourbon express...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Inflation Is Coming: 3 Reasons Why Corn Prices Are About Soar - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamsarhan/2018/11/13/inflation-is-coming-3-reasons-why-corn-prices-are-about-soar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDWIrl3bVgP5yDmO6VJTCUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 15:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamsarhan/2018/11/13/inflation-is-coming-3-reasons-why-corn-prices-are-about-soar/" target="_blank"&gt;Inflation Is Coming: 3 Reasons Why Corn Prices Are About Soar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Close up Corn on the stalk in the field. Since the 2008 financial crisis, inflation has largely remained a nonevent, but the Federal Reserve and many large investors are now worried that this is about to change. At the most basic level inflation occurs when prices of energy, goods, food, services, and other items in an economy increase in value. One does not have to look very far to see why inflation will increase in the near future. Let’s just look at one of the most undervalued assets in the world: Corn. Here are a few reasons why Corn prices could explode. Favorable Supply &amp; Demand Econo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Trace Genomics Raises $13 Million To Give Corn And Soybean Farmers Insight Into Soil Health - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2018/11/13/trace-genomics-raises-13-million-to-give-corn-and-soybean-farmers-insight-into-soil-health/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC6T3EMJawcfDEOYtzjdntIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2018/11/13/trace-genomics-raises-13-million-to-give-corn-and-soybean-farmers-insight-into-soil-health/" target="_blank"&gt;Trace Genomics Raises $13 Million To Give Corn And Soybean Farmers Insight Into Soil Health&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=0] Trace Genomics, which uses machine learning to analyze soil samples for farmers, announced Tuesday that it has closed a series A round for $13 million. This round brings the company’s total venture funding to over $19 million, and was led by Stage 1 Ventures. Soil health has become an increasing concern for farmers, who are looking both to maximize yields of their crops while also reducing the cost of inputs like fertilizers and pesticides. This is where Trace Genomics comes in – the company takes soil samples collected by farmers and analyzes them to determine what microbes are pres...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ick or treat? 7 strange facts about candy corn - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2014/10/28/living/candy-corn-facts/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECsELvTSusRqHr7bi8EZTn0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 16:00:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2014/10/28/living/candy-corn-facts/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ick or treat? 7 strange facts about candy corn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manufacturers will produce almost 9 billion pieces of candy corn this year. The tricolored kernels are a beloved Halloween staple for millions, although not everyone loves them. Jupiterimages A worker for the Goelitz Confectionery Co. stirs a kettle of warm candy corn mixture at a New Jersey factory in the early 1900s. The company, which in 2001 changed its name to Jelly Belly, continues to make candy corn today -- by machine, of course. Jelly Belly Candy Co. The blue Goelitz box from the mid-1900s promises "something worth crowing for." Today, Brach's and Jelly Belly are the two leading U....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Drought drives demand for Kimberley's emerging corn industry - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-10-26/drought-drives-demand-for-northern-wa-corn/10423840</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMTvdzLyIGLftxKuWn846fgqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 19:48:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-10-26/drought-drives-demand-for-northern-wa-corn/10423840" target="_blank"&gt;Drought drives demand for Kimberley's emerging corn industry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demand for corn from Western Australia's Kimberley region is booming as drought-affected farmers turn away from the summer crop in main growing regions. Wyndham Port, 100 kilometres north east of Kununurra, exported 11,000 tonnes of corn last year, and the region's farmers are expecting to double that figure this season. The rise in demand comes as traditional corn farmers struggle with water scarcity in eastern states. Photo: Ord Valley farmers have only grown corn for the last three years. (Supplied: Oasis Farms) Unfavoured by drought-affected farmers Corn is grown around Australia, with ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Food Vs. Fuel: What Trump's Ethanol Policy Means For The Food System - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jennysplitter/2018/10/25/food-vs-fuel-what-trumps-ethanol-policy-means-for-the-food-system/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHZjk2fsfKK6zxms0yywp0MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 17:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jennysplitter/2018/10/25/food-vs-fuel-what-trumps-ethanol-policy-means-for-the-food-system/" target="_blank"&gt;Food Vs. Fuel: What Trump's Ethanol Policy Means For The Food System&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Corn sits on top of a combine after being harvested in Shelbyville, Kentucky, U.S. Credit: Photographer: Luke Sharrett/Bloomberg The Environmental Protection Agency is moving forward with President Trump’s directive to lift a federal ban on high ethanol blended gas during the summer months, though not quickly enough for Senator Chuck Grassley of Iowa, who Reuters reports is urging the EPA to lift the ban on a much quicker timeline. Lifting the ban is a policy shift that’s being celebrated by large-scale corn growers and decried by biofuel opponents. But the policy has implications for the f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Monsanto’s top weedkiller now found in pet food as well as cereal - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/442309-glyphosate-pet-food-cereal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO-z45zNA5eDPcUFzv2Sqj8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 03:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/442309-glyphosate-pet-food-cereal/" target="_blank"&gt;Monsanto’s top weedkiller now found in pet food as well as cereal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two new studies show how extensively Monsanto’s best-selling herbicide glyphosate has permeated our food chain. Designated carcinogenic by some health authorities, it was found in over 40 pet foods and breakfast cereals. Researchers at Cornell University found glyphosate in all 18 of the dog and cat food brands they surveyed, including one product that was certified GMO-free. They stressed that the chemical was present in low concentrations – lower than those typically found in human food, at least – but glyphosate's effect on domestic animals in any concentration is unknown, and studies ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Candy corn: Ick or treat? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2014/10/28/living/gallery/candy-corn-facts/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENWOi7H4J1e5v_c9cJDBNAUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 15:34:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2014/10/28/living/gallery/candy-corn-facts/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Candy corn: Ick or treat?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manufacturers will produce almost 9 billion pieces of candy corn this year. The tricolored kernels are a beloved Halloween staple for millions, although not everyone loves them. Jupiterimages A worker for the Goelitz Confectionery Co. stirs a kettle of warm candy corn mixture at a New Jersey factory in the early 1900s. The company, which in 2001 changed its name to Jelly Belly, continues to make candy corn today -- by machine, of course. Jelly Belly Candy Co. The blue Goelitz box from the mid-1900s promises "something worth crowing for." Today, Brach's and Jelly Belly are the two leading U....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump administration to loosen rules on sales of fuel ethanol - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cacde2c0-cbd6-11e8-9fe5-24ad351828ab</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKiMHbRwnF0SKk5ZyJvpTbcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 17:28:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cacde2c0-cbd6-11e8-9fe5-24ad351828ab" target="_blank"&gt;Trump administration to loosen rules on sales of fuel ethanol&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration intends to loosen rules inhibiting domestic sales of fuel ethanol, a move that could build demand for corn as US agriculture struggles with oversupplied grain markets. The technical shift would allow the year-round sales of E15, or motor fuel containing 15 per cent ethanol and 85 per cent petrol, according to reports. Most fuel blends today contain no more than 10 per cent ethanol. More than a third of this year’s US corn crop is expected to be consumed by ethanol refineries, underlining the biofuel’s importance to growers. President Donald Trump was expected to hig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Grain-To-Glass Texas Whiskey Distillery Celebrates One Year in Business - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/claudiaalarcon/2018/09/30/grain-to-glass-texas-whiskey-distillery-celebrates-one-year-in-business/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMPkdSNWm5lI7aabYZYsEfAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/claudiaalarcon/2018/09/30/grain-to-glass-texas-whiskey-distillery-celebrates-one-year-in-business/" target="_blank"&gt;Grain-To-Glass Texas Whiskey Distillery Celebrates One Year in Business&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still Austin is the first urban distillery to open since prohibition. Still Austin, the first urban Whiskey distillery to open since prohibition, celebrated its first year in business in Austin over the weekend. Located in the heart of the growing St. Elmo business district in South Austin, Still Austin opened last fall producing three distinct spirits created by Master Distiller Michael Delevante. Still Austin prides itself in using only Texas-grown heirloom grains sourced within 100 miles of the state-of-the-art distillery. Delavante uses a hardy indigenous white, Aztec Black, and “Butche...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Some farmers worry Trump's bailout checks won't be enough - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/53ff57c0cd0a4d71bdb4b7bf1a30105c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELRxlxiyiowVWm_cXt0y35oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 05:18:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/53ff57c0cd0a4d71bdb4b7bf1a30105c" target="_blank"&gt;Some farmers worry Trump's bailout checks won't be enough&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Farmers across the United States will soon begin receiving government checks as part of a billion-dollar bailout to buoy growers experiencing financial strain from President Donald Trump's trade disputes with China. But even those poised for big payouts worry it won't be enough. And while support for Trump is near unwavering in the heartland, some growers say that with the November election nearing, such disappointing aid outcomes could potentially affect their vote. "It's pretty obvious that the rural agriculture communities helped elect this administration, but the way t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>US start-up nurtures market for organic and non-GMO crops - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b7713f30-9b19-11e8-88de-49c908b1f264</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDxzuT6WnOf4w67sGekOulQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 04:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b7713f30-9b19-11e8-88de-49c908b1f264" target="_blank"&gt;US start-up nurtures market for organic and non-GMO crops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An American entrepreneur is building a wholesale commodity market to meet rising demand for food that is free from pesticides and bioengineering . Kellee James leads Mercaris, a US company that hosts online auctions for organic or non-genetically modified crops. Hundreds of thousands of bushels of grain and oilseeds now change hands on its platform every year. The auctions have brought an element of transparency to a hazy sector. Most deals for natural foodstuffs are struck in private. Mercaris allows approved buyers and sellers to make anonymous bids and offers in an active market where pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Indigo Ag's Natural Seed-Coating Technology Helps Plants Thrive - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffkart/2018/09/24/indigo-ags-natural-seed-coating-technology-helps-plants-thrive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEERwhZLqbuPD5-YiDQ06Du0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 19:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffkart/2018/09/24/indigo-ags-natural-seed-coating-technology-helps-plants-thrive/" target="_blank"&gt;Indigo Ag's Natural Seed-Coating Technology Helps Plants Thrive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dig this: Indigo Agriculture, a tech startup in Boston, Massachusetts, makes seed treatments that help plants grow. The technology involves coating the seeds of corn, rice, soybeans and wheat with natural microbes. The result? Plants thrive like they’re supposed to. The private company also appears to be thriving, and recently announced $250 million in new venture capital investments along with a new digital marketplace for buying and selling grain. Indigo Ag was founded in 2014 by Flagship Pioneering, a Cambridge biotech investment firm, and reportedly has crops growing on about 1 million ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Senegalese Chef Puts Supergrain on New York Menus to Boost African Farmers - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/senegalese-chef-puts-supergrain-on-new-york-menus-to-boost-african-farmers/4585430.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELELB-fpt9TmsviCBMwyA-wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 22:25:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/senegalese-chef-puts-supergrain-on-new-york-menus-to-boost-african-farmers/4585430.html" target="_blank"&gt;Senegalese Chef Puts Supergrain on New York Menus to Boost African Farmers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A gluten-free grain that grows in Africa's impoverished and semi-arid Sahel region is taking off as a health food in New York, the Senegalese chef who masterminded its revival said Monday, outlining plans to almost double production by 2023. Pierre Thiam began exporting fonio to New York last year, hoping to help smallholder communities in the Sahel, which stretches from Mauritania and Mali in the west to Sudan and Eritrea in the east and is home to more than 100 million people. The grain is now on the menus of more than 60 New York restaurants and will soon be in all the city's Whole Foods...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>How To Make The Most Perfect Breakfast Taco Ever - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/how-to-make-breakfast-tacos_us_5b9c053ee4b013b0977a97dc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO55Um10hXONpJSxdWLWRe4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 09:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/how-to-make-breakfast-tacos_us_5b9c053ee4b013b0977a97dc" target="_blank"&gt;How To Make The Most Perfect Breakfast Taco Ever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avocado toast is an amazing breakfast dish. It’s strange to start a story about breakfast tacos with that sentence, though it’s true: The toast is filling, delicious, creamy and easy to make. But after gorging myself on breakfast tacos at Texas favorite Torchy’s Tacos (now with locations in Colorado and Oklahoma) more than a few times, I’ve come to appreciate how essential a truly satisfying breakfast taco can be. But with so many different versions of breakfast tacos to choose from — Torchy’s features versions made with everything from scrambled eggs to potatoes to smoked beef brisket — wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Further reading - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/30874853-16bb-323c-961c-3f689d8c4de2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMhR4r0LXg3UDVJpqT_Wn3sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 05:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/30874853-16bb-323c-961c-3f689d8c4de2" target="_blank"&gt;Further reading&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere on Monday... -- Jesus' wife -- The zero lower-bound -- Pray for Wonga -- Summers on macro -- The corn syrup lobby -- Not the best stat -- Fraud lingers -- Discount retailers in the US -- Data breaches and stock prices -- Kavanaugh's accuser steps forward&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>