<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Omar al-Bashir - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREl6TURkb0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-KE&amp;gl=KE&amp;ceid=KE:en</link><language>en-KE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:10:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Sudan president Bashir closer to being president for life - Daily Nation</title><link>https://www.nation.co.ke/news/africa/Sudan-Bashir-closer-to-be-life-president/1066-4882256-pmcjiaz/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5hdGlvbi5jby5rZS9uZXdzL2FmcmljYS9TdWRhbi1CYXNoaXItY2xvc2VyLXRvLWJlLWxpZmUtcHJlc2lkZW50LzEwNjYtNDg4MjI1Ni1wbWNqaWF6L2luZGV4Lmh0bWzSAcABaHR0cHM6Ly93d3ctbmF0aW9uLWNvLWtlLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3Mvd3d3Lm5hdGlvbi5jby5rZS9uZXdzL2FmcmljYS9TdWRhbi1CYXNoaXItY2xvc2VyLXRvLWJlLWxpZmUtcHJlc2lkZW50LzEwNjYtNDg4MjI1Ni12aWV3LWFzQU1QLXdhZ3BxZS9pbmRleC5odG1sP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:33:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nation.co.ke/news/africa/Sudan-Bashir-closer-to-be-life-president/1066-4882256-pmcjiaz/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan president Bashir closer to being president for life&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Daily Nation&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bashir came to power in 1989 through military coup and has been elected twice in 2010 and 2015.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nation.co.ke">Daily Nation</source></item><item><title>Sudan lawmakers back amendment to let Bashir stand again - Standard Digital</title><link>https://www.standardmedia.co.ke/article/2001305247/sudan-lawmakers-back-amendment-to-let-bashir-stand-again</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOSSqBzcWijU1k5HyrNG0jkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowiIiACzDO0IsDMOGu9wU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:53:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.standardmedia.co.ke/article/2001305247/sudan-lawmakers-back-amendment-to-let-bashir-stand-again" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan lawmakers back amendment to let Bashir stand again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Standard Digital&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bashir is wanted by the ICC for war crimes after being indicted in 2008 over killings and persecution in Sudan's Darfur province between 2003 and 2008.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.standardmedia.co.ke">Standard Digital</source></item><item><title>Sudan Lawmakers Back Amendment to Let Bashir Stand Again - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-lawmakers-back-amendment-to-let-bashir-stand-again/4686785.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEECfR5afNPVS3kUuOcMWI0gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:55:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-lawmakers-back-amendment-to-let-bashir-stand-again/4686785.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan Lawmakers Back Amendment to Let Bashir Stand Again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudan's long-serving President Omar al-Bashir came closer Tuesday to another term in office after a majority of lawmakers backed a constitutional amendment to extend term limits that would have required him to step down in 2020. Unless the constitution is changed, Bashir, in power since 1989, is not permitted to stand again when his present term ends, having won two elections since a 2005 constitutional amendment took effect imposing a two-term limit. Parliament speaker Ibrahim Ahmed Omar said he had received a letter signed by a majority of lawmakers backing an amendment that would extend ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sudan’s economy struggles to shake off pariah status - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/345c1bf0-e822-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECUokdaUnr4qSt82e-4aNJQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 04:00:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/345c1bf0-e822-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan’s economy struggles to shake off pariah status&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day in Sudan’s dusty capital Khartoum, queues for cash machines fill the shaded sidewalks as anxious customers try to access their savings in banks that have imposed withdrawal limits as low as $11 per day. After a 20-year US trade embargo was lifted last year, government officials predicted an economic revival as their country came in from the cold. Instead, the economy has faltered, the value of the Sudanese pound is plummeting, and citizens are lining up for cash so they can convert it into hard goods. “We have an acute economic crisis because inflation is skyrocketing and the nati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>South Arica to quit International Criminal Court - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/south-africa-international-criminal-court-war-crimes-quite-leave-latest-a7374516.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJbpBKeVACasoZ_MkiRspCQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/south-africa-international-criminal-court-war-crimes-quite-leave-latest-a7374516.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Arica to quit International Criminal Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa is quitting the International Criminal Court (ICC) because membership conflicted with diplomatic immunity laws, dealing a new blow to the struggling court and angering the political opposition. Pretoria signalled its intention to leave after the ICC criticised it for ignoring a court order to arrest Sudanese President Omar Hassan al-Bashir, who is accused of war crimes, when he visited. Mr Bashir has denied the accusations. The ICC was not immediately available for comment, but the announcement puts new pressure on the world's first permanent war crimes court, which has had to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Sudan's Bashir announces one-month ceasefire extension - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-ceasefire-idUSKBN14L0VT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELEmgmxy38reY4_F4QRhzwQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 09:00:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-ceasefire-idUSKBN14L0VT" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan's Bashir announces one-month ceasefire extension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KHARTOUM (Reuters) - Sudanese President Omar Hassan al-Bashir has announced a one-month extension of his unilateral ceasefire in fighting with rebels in the country's war zones. The announcement, in an independence day speech on Saturday, comes after earlier short-term truces in June and October 2016, which were followed by a fall-off in fighting in the southern Blue Nile and Kordofan regions but continued clashes in Darfur. The latest outbreak of fighting between the army and rebels in Kordofan and Blue Nile broke out in 2011, when adjacent South Sudan declared independence. Conflict in Da...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Sudan Extends Cease-fire by Six Months - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-cease-fire/3677015.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKh8NepgeeTUk3fQOEqy8MwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 14:29:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-cease-fire/3677015.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan Extends Cease-fire by Six Months&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudan said on Sunday it would extend a unilateral cease-fire in fighting with rebels in the country's warring regions to six months, state news agency SUNA reported. The move comes after the United States said on Friday it would lift a 20-year-old trade embargo against Sudan, but would wait 180 days before doing so to see whether Sudan acts further to improve its human rights record and resolve political and military conflicts, including in warring regions such as Darfur. Sudanese President Omar Hassan al-Bashir asked the government at a special Cabinet meeting on Sunday to prepare procedur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sudan president pardons, frees rights activist: family - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-rights-idUSKCN1BA0DR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL-ZX-H5hSenAe7SogQwe9oqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 04:46:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-rights-idUSKCN1BA0DR" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan president pardons, frees rights activist: family&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KHARTOUM (Reuters) - Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir has pardoned and released a prominent human rights activists who had been jailed since last year on spying and other charges, his family said. The release of Mudawi Ibrahim Adam came after a visit by U.S. President Donald Trump's aid administrator to Sudan and before an October deadline when the administration will decide whether to permanently lift 20-year-old sanctions. "He is home after a presidential amnesty and he seems in good health," his wife Sabah told Reuters late on Tuesday. International rights groups had often called for th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>U.S. set to lift some financial sanctions against Sudan - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-sudan-sanctions-idUSKBN14X04Q</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEECPOlnEjh4xLQxr5a37LmMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 01:11:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-sudan-sanctions-idUSKBN14X04Q" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. set to lift some financial sanctions against Sudan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Lesley Wroughton WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The United States is set to announce the easing of some financial sanctions against Sudan on Friday for its recent efforts in helping tackle terrorism, a senior U.S. official said on Thursday. "The limited sanctions relief is an acknowledgement of progress by the government of Sudan," the official told Reuters ahead of the announcement expected from the White House. It was not immediately clear which sanctions would be lifted. The United States first imposed sanctions on Sudan in 1997, including a trade embargo and blocking the government's assets,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>South Africa to Exit War-Crimes Court - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/cheats/2016/10/21/south-africa-to-withdraw-from-war-crimes-court.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFTpUchxwU-LOgz_EE7_w3MqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLzdlwI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 10:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/cheats/2016/10/21/south-africa-to-withdraw-from-war-crimes-court.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa to Exit War-Crimes Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa has formally begun the process of exiting its membership with the International Criminal Court (ICC), telling member states that it does not want to be responsible for arrest warrants leading to “regime change.” The withdrawal stems from criticism the South African government has taken for refusing to arrest Sudan’s President Omar al-Bashir during his visit to the African Union summit in Johannesburg last year. Bashir is wanted by the ICC for alleged war-crimes against rebels and minority groups in Sudan’s tumultuous Darfur region. “The Republic of South Africa has found that i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Western Envoys Shun Qatar Event Attended by Sudan's Bashir - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3851081.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB5qQdA3DRt-Iqr9lpMv5uIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 15:28:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3851081.html" target="_blank"&gt;Western Envoys Shun Qatar Event Attended by Sudan's Bashir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Western diplomats shunned the opening ceremony of a conference in Qatar on Sunday attended by Sudan's president, who is wanted for war crimes by the International Criminal Court (ICC). Omar Hassan al-Bashir, who came to power in Sudan in a 1989 Islamist and military-backed coup, has continued to travel abroad since the ICC charged him with genocide and crimes against humanity in 2008. But his appearance on a list of speakers at a humanitarian conference in Doha on Sunday attended by the deputy head of the United Nations prompted the U.S., Canadian and Australian ambassadors to boycott the e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sudan's renegade sheikh - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/09/sudan-renegade-sheikh-170909175651542.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_qc9zYSKn01yNrQE0xGeYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 08:54:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/09/sudan-renegade-sheikh-170909175651542.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan's renegade sheikh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tensions between the Sudanese regime and militia commander Sheikh Musa Hilal has reached a tipping point in recent weeks. On July 20, Sudanese Vice President Hassabo Abdel Rahman announced the launch of a disarmament campaign to confiscate weapons and unlicensed vehicles across Darfur. In response, Hilal made a number of inflammatory statements, saying that the disarmament campaign aimed to eliminate him and threatened military action against it. As the commander of the Border Guards militia, he currently has around 3,000 men based in an enclave under his control in North Darfur. The situat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Egypt's Sisi rejects Bashir accusations, says not conspiring against Sudan - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-egypt-idUSKBN18K2JE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENgpLwPGyaXxww4nL2Ovm6sqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 17:47:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-egypt-idUSKBN18K2JE" target="_blank"&gt;Egypt's Sisi rejects Bashir accusations, says not conspiring against Sudan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Mahmoud Mourad CAIRO (Reuters) - Egyptian President Abdel Fattah al-Sisi rejected on Wednesday his Sudanese counterpart's accusation that Cairo backs rebels aiming to topple the government in Khartoum, saying Egypt does not conspire against anyone. Sudanese President Omar Hassan al-Bashir accused Egypt on Tuesday of supporting rebels at war with his government, a week ahead of a visit to Cairo by Sudan's foreign minister that is meant to ease tensions between the neighboring states. "Egyptian policy is constant, unchanging, and will not change; we do not interfere in the affairs of other...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>ICC declines to refer South Africa to U.N. for not arresting Sudan's Bashir - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-sudan-safrica-idUSKBN19R1VI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAFC_1hFgnIQpaNWnHKmw3cqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 13:27:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-sudan-safrica-idUSKBN19R1VI" target="_blank"&gt;ICC declines to refer South Africa to U.N. for not arresting Sudan's Bashir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HAGUE (Reuters) - South Africa violated its obligations to the International Criminal Court by failing to arrest Sudan's President Hassan al-Bashir when he visited in 2015, the court's judges said in a ruling on Thursday. However, the war crimes court judges declined to refer South Africa to the U.N. Security Council over the matter. They noted that South African courts had already censured the government for its failure in Bashir's case and said referring it to the UN would likely have little effect. (Reporting by Toby Sterling; editing by Andrew Roche)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Europe’s crackdown on African immigration is hitting vulnerable refugees - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/jan/26/europe-crackdown-africa-immigration-vulnerable-refugees-sudan-eritrea</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrGKHlKpftdelRzgXsV31QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 16:50:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/jan/26/europe-crackdown-africa-immigration-vulnerable-refugees-sudan-eritrea" target="_blank"&gt;Europe’s crackdown on African immigration is hitting vulnerable refugees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Documents cited in the Guardian on Monday showing that the UK government downplayed the risk of human rights abuses in Eritrea in an attempt to reduce asylum-seeker numbers are the latest indication of Britain’s determination to reduce African immigration. But this is a Europe-wide initiative, co-ordinated in Brussels. With French, German, Dutch and Italian elections later this year, there is intense pressure across the European Union to cut the flows of refugees and migrants across the Mediterranean. European plans to deal with the question have been veiled in secrecy, since they involve c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Sudan Freezes Talks With US After Delay in Lifting Sanctions - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-postpones-decision-on-sudan-sanctions-for-three-months/3938612.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMTgB_xj5kOy-uolXPxvlq4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 01:55:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-postpones-decision-on-sudan-sanctions-for-three-months/3938612.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan Freezes Talks With US After Delay in Lifting Sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudan's President Omar al-Bashir is freezing all negotiations with the United States following President Donald Trump's postponing of a final decision on whether to permanently lift economic sanctions against Sudan for another three months, state media reported. "President of the republic Omar al-Bashir issued a presidential decree ordering the suspension of the committee that was negotiating with the United States" over the lifting of sanctions, the official news agency SUNA said, quoting a presidential decree issued by Bashir. President Trump's predecessor, Barack Obama, signed an executi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>South Africa Says It Did Not Have to Arrest Sudan's Al-Bashir - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-international-criminal-court-sudan-omar-al-bashir-arrest/3800341.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE1V2yeKXOD9r-a4Cd_tf6sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 09:44:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-international-criminal-court-sudan-omar-al-bashir-arrest/3800341.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa Says It Did Not Have to Arrest Sudan's Al-Bashir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa is insisting to International Criminal Court judges that it did not have to arrest Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir when he visited Johannesburg in 2015. At a hearing Friday lawyers for South Africa said the court's founding treaty, the Rome Statute, does not oblige authorities to arrest heads of state of countries that are not members of the court, such as Sudan. South African lawyer Dire Tladi told judges that "there is no duty under international law in general, and in particular under the Rome Statute, on South Africa to arrest a serving head of a non-state party." ICC pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Saudi Summit May Host Both US President Trump and Sudan’s al-Bashir - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-president-bashir-goes-to-riyadh-no-word-on-trump-meetingminister-says/3854091.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFISTHHGjQdglyUjBQJuiFEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 13:27:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-president-bashir-goes-to-riyadh-no-word-on-trump-meetingminister-says/3854091.html" target="_blank"&gt;Saudi Summit May Host Both US President Trump and Sudan’s al-Bashir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysts and rights advocates are expressing concern about reports that Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir has been invited to a summit this weekend in Saudi Arabia which U.S. President Donald Trump also expects to attend. The invitation to Bashir has stirred controversy, as the Sudanese leader has been charged with war crimes by the International Criminal Court. The International Criminal Court considers al-Bashir a fugitive from justice and has sought his arrest since 2009. Elise Keppler, an associate director at Human Rights Watch, says interactions between a U.S. president and an alleged...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Obama accused of 'making a deal with the devil' as he eases sanctions on Sudan - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/01/13/obama-accused-making-deal-devil-eases-sanctions-sudan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK8bdkMyoG5BePNCcJ89O9MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 18:58:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/01/13/obama-accused-making-deal-devil-eases-sanctions-sudan/" target="_blank"&gt;Obama accused of 'making a deal with the devil' as he eases sanctions on Sudan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barack Obama was accused of making “a deal with the devil” after he eased sanctions against Sudan on Friday, reversing two decades of policy towards an Islamist regime that massacred its own people and sheltered Osama bin Laden. The American president signed an executive order that, by relaxing a 20-year-old trade embargo on Khartoum, represents the culmination of a grand rapprochement by his administration towards “rogue” regimes like Iran, Cuba and Burma. US officials characterised what is likely to be Mr Obama’s last significant diplomatic initiative at the White House as a reward for pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Sudan's Bashir visits Darfur ahead of U.S. sanctions decision - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-usa-sanctions/sudans-bashir-visits-darfur-ahead-of-us-sanctions-decision-idUSKCN1BU1MH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAG4VuWbfPlg6g_mHOkr8e0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 12:41:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-usa-sanctions/sudans-bashir-visits-darfur-ahead-of-us-sanctions-decision-idUSKCN1BU1MH" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan's Bashir visits Darfur ahead of U.S. sanctions decision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Khalid Abdelaziz KHARTOUM (Reuters) - Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir visited the war-torn Darfur region on Tuesday in an effort to show his country is ready to have 20-year-old sanctions lifted by the United States just weeks before Washington is expected to issue a decision. In July the Trump administration postponed for three months the decision to permanently lift sanctions, setting Oct. 12 as a deadline for Sudan to meet conditions, including resolving conflicts and stepping up its humanitarian efforts. Conflict in Darfur began in 2003 when mainly non-Arab tribes took up arms agai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Barack Obama orders easing of sanctions against Sudan - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d6304fa8-d9a8-11e6-944b-e7eb37a6aa8e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENW_M8NaXYF1vCHsXQ3pfl8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 16:52:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d6304fa8-d9a8-11e6-944b-e7eb37a6aa8e" target="_blank"&gt;Barack Obama orders easing of sanctions against Sudan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barack Obama has ordered the easing of two decades of sanctions on Sudan, recognising what the US president called “positive actions” taken by the once pariah government in Khartoum. In an executive order issued on Friday, Mr Obama revoked parts of a trade embargo imposed in 1997 by then-president Bill Clinton on the Sudanese government for harbouring terrorists including Osama bin Laden. Mr Obama also lifted a freeze on certain assets of the government of Omar al-Bashir. In a letter to Congress announcing the changes, Mr Obama said the move was intended to reward Khartoum for better co-ope...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>South Africa's move to quit ICC challenged in court - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/12/south-africa-icc-161205094151913.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPQJshhdzx5SnWQ_rL2TmXgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 12:05:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/12/south-africa-icc-161205094151913.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa's move to quit ICC challenged in court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa's main opposition, the Democratic Alliance, has taken the government to court over its decision to pull out of the International Criminal Court (ICC). The High Court in Pretoria is scheduled to begin hearings on Monday to determine the constitutionality of a government move to withdraw from the Hague-based ICC, an international tribunal set up to prosecute individuals for genocide, crimes against humanity and war crimes. In June 2015, South Africa failed to arrest visiting Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir, who is wanted by the ICC for war crimes in the western Sudanese provinc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>ICC to Discuss South Africa's Failure to Arrest Sudan's Bashir - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/international-criminal-court-south-africa-failure-arrest-sudan-omar-al-bashir/3628779.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGq21AnVh_fCmxmmdSpD6VkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 21:43:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/international-criminal-court-south-africa-failure-arrest-sudan-omar-al-bashir/3628779.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC to Discuss South Africa's Failure to Arrest Sudan's Bashir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;International Criminal Court judges asked South Africa on Thursday to send representatives to a hearing next year to determine whether it had breached its obligation to arrest Sudan's President Omar al-Bashir in June. The public hearing will further strain frayed relations between the war crimes court and African leaders, many of whom accuse the mainly European-backed institution of singling out Africa for prosecution. The decision of South Africa's President Jacob Zuma to let Bashir depart after an African Union summit unleashed a storm of protest in June, prompting legal challenges agains...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sudan's Bashir to attend Saudi gathering, no word on Trump meeting: minister - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-president-idUSKCN18D1LB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENEH97RuA8N0FqbByvsLA4AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 15:03:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-president-idUSKCN18D1LB" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan's Bashir to attend Saudi gathering, no word on Trump meeting: minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Tom Miles GENEVA (Reuters) - Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir will attend a gathering in Saudi Arabia on Saturday where Donald Trump will also be present but it is uncertain whether he will meet the U.S. president, Sudan's foreign minister said on Wednesday. Bashir is wanted for war crimes by the International Criminal Court (ICC) and is shunned by Western leaders, so direct contact between him and Trump would be a diplomatic bombshell, despite a thawing of relations between Washington and Khartoum in recent months. "On the question of the Trump-Bashir handshake, nobody can pretend anyt...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Top Sudanese Officials Cancel Planned Egypt Visit Amid Mutual Recriminations - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3877436.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKcp4OljCtnGnIv3mZTwj7UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 14:01:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3877436.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top Sudanese Officials Cancel Planned Egypt Visit Amid Mutual Recriminations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Relations between Egypt and Sudan have taken a turn for the worse as each side accuses the other of supporting terrorism. Sudanese Foreign Minister Ibrahim Ghandour postponed a planned visit Tuesday to Cairo, amid the tensions. Sudanese President Omar Hassan al-Bashir accused Egypt last week of supporting terrorists in South Sudan and Darfur, after allegedly capturing rebels Sudan says were driving Egyptian armored vehicles. Bashir says Sudan's armed forces uncovered a large plot, with fighters coming from two directions — one group from South Sudan and the other from Libya — on the same da...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>South African court says government's ICC withdrawal is unconstitutional - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-icc-idUSKBN1610RS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBua5ITCzqMM10pwK84UzgwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 09:20:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-icc-idUSKBN1610RS" target="_blank"&gt;South African court says government's ICC withdrawal is unconstitutional&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (Reuters) - A decision by South Africa to withdraw from the International Criminal Court (ICC) is unconstitutional, the country's High Court ruled on Wednesday. The ICC, which launched in July 2002 and has 124 member states, is the first legal body with permanent international jurisdiction to prosecute genocide, crimes against humanity and war crimes. South Africa notified the United Nations of its intent to withdraw from the Rome Statute, the 1998 treaty establishing the Hague-based court, last October. The withdrawal would take this October. High Court Judge Phineas Mojapelo ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Court rules ICC withdrawal plan unconstitutional - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/court-rules-icc-withdrawal-plan-unconstitutional-170222100708895.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPv34KSs1leRjY00tLJBFaoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 11:10:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/court-rules-icc-withdrawal-plan-unconstitutional-170222100708895.html" target="_blank"&gt;Court rules ICC withdrawal plan unconstitutional&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A South African court has ruled the government's plan to withdraw from the International Criminal Court (ICC) was "unconstitutional and invalid", providing a boost to the embattled Hague-based institution. The court has recently been fighting off allegations of pursuing a neo-colonial agenda in Africa, where most of its investigations have been based. Three African states - South Africa, The Gambia and Burundi - last year signalled their intention to quit the ICC. The Gambia's President Adama Barrow, elected in December, said earlier this month it will remain in the ICC. READ MORE: Africa's...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>South Africa set to withdraw from the International Criminal Court because of focus on Africa prosecutions - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/21/south-africa-set-to-withdraw-from-the-international-criminal-cou/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAwLD8M0Q3qIzb5W54kop_EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 08:55:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/21/south-africa-set-to-withdraw-from-the-international-criminal-cou/" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa set to withdraw from the International Criminal Court because of focus on Africa prosecutions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa has told the United Nations it wants to withdraw from the International Criminal Court amid perceptions The Hague-based tribunal focuses too much on African prosecutions. Maite Nkoana-Mashabane, the South African foreign minister, signed an Instrument of Withdrawal delivered to the UN secretariat in New York on Thursday, saying it found its own obligations to international human rights “incompatible” with the ICC’s interpretation. Maite Nkoana-Mashabane said the South Africa's obligations to peace were "incompatible" with the courtCredit: AFP If South Africa’s parliament does n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Sudan's Bashir names long-time ally and general prime minister - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-politics-idUSKBN1685KP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFXy2nOghHlSiFqwu18oLysqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 21:25:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-politics-idUSKBN1685KP" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan's Bashir names long-time ally and general prime minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Khalid Abdelaziz KHARTOUM (Reuters) - Sudanese President Omar Hassan al-Bashir named his first vice president and long-time ally Hassan Saleh to the newly created post of prime minister on Wednesday, the clearest sign yet that he intends for him to one day take over. It is the first time Sudan has had a prime minister since Bashir came to power in a 1989 Islamist and military-backed coup. Saleh is the last member of the group of officers that launched the coup to remain at Bashir's side. "The party leadership meeting chaired by President Bashir approved the nomination of Hassan Saleh as ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Sudan security forces arrest opposition leaders amid protests - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-arrest-idUSKBN13I2KP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBu8MuInvlKrZyHpqxnU5pYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 21:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-arrest-idUSKBN13I2KP" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan security forces arrest opposition leaders amid protests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KHARTOUM (Reuters) - Sudan arrested four opposition leaders on Wednesday including veteran politician Sadiq Youssef as part of a crackdown on protests, the country's opposition coalition said. Khartoum has seen a series of small but rare protests over the past week amid rising prices and government austerity measures that have included price hikes on electricity and fuel as well as import restrictions. Sudan's economy has struggled since South Sudan seceded in 2011, taking with it three-quarters of the country's oil output, a key source of foreign currency and government revenue. Youssef, o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>ICC withdrawal revoked after court ruling: UN - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/03/icc-withdrawal-revoked-court-ruling-170308084628230.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN-ppZp6G5jRMWSf86rmXdoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 09:07:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/03/icc-withdrawal-revoked-court-ruling-170308084628230.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC withdrawal revoked after court ruling: UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa's withdrawal from the International Criminal Court has been revoked, the United Nations secretary-general says. A notice dated on Tuesday on the UN treaty website said the move came after a South African court ruled last month that the country's decision to withdraw without parliament's approval was unconstitutional. South Africa shocked the international community last year when it informed the UN chief it would withdraw from the court that pursues cases of genocide, war crimes and crimes against humanity. Withdrawal comes a year after notification. South Africa's main opposit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>U.N.'s Zeid says Jordan should not have hosted Sudan's Bashir - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-icc-un-idUSKBN1721O0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIBKK5WxeY9kWOyV0a7dZpgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 12:42:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-icc-un-idUSKBN1721O0" target="_blank"&gt;U.N.'s Zeid says Jordan should not have hosted Sudan's Bashir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (Reuters) - Jordan has broken its treaty obligations by hosting Sudanese President Omar Hassan al-Bashir, who is wanted by the International Criminal Court, U.N. High Commissioner for Human Rights Zeid Ra'ad al Hussein said in a statement on Friday. "I very much regret that Jordan, a state party to the Rome Statute of the International Criminal Court, received the President of Sudan, against whom an arrest warrant has been issued. By doing so, it is failing the ICC and weakening the global struggle against impunity, and for justice," he said. (Reporting by Tom Miles; Editing by Andre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Sudan's PM Reshuffles Cabinet - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-prime-minister-reshuffles-cabinet/3848403.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAHeVKGGhmac22AeOiGxX34qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 23:01:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-prime-minister-reshuffles-cabinet/3848403.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan's PM Reshuffles Cabinet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudanese Prime Minister Hassan Saleh announced a new government Thursday, with changes to economic ministers, including the oil, investment and finance chiefs. Sudan's constitution was amended in December to introduce the position of prime minister, a demand of opposition parties that took part in a national dialogue with the government, with the aim of redistributing some of the president's extensive powers. President Omar Hassan al-Bashir's long war against various rebel groups has coincided with a severe economic downturn. This year's budget foresees a growing deficit and slower growth. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Burkina Faso to withdraw Darfur peacekeepers by July - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-burkina-darfur-idUSKBN1300DK?il=0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGGpJR4Dj4YxQQR9FTkdKtIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 11:11:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-burkina-darfur-idUSKBN1300DK?il=0" target="_blank"&gt;Burkina Faso to withdraw Darfur peacekeepers by July&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OUAGADOUGOU (Reuters) - Burkina Faso has notified the United Nations that it will withdraw soldiers deployed as peacekeepers in Sudan's troubled Darfur region by July next year, the foreign minister said late on Friday. The West African nation, which has a battalion of 850 soldiers serving in the nearly 14,000 troop strong U.N.-African Union hybrid mission, has suffered a series of deadly attacks at home amid a rise in Islamist militant violence. Burkina Faso's government said in May that it would seek to bring some troops home to help reinforce domestic security. "We have great need of bat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New USAID Chief Visits Sudan as Sanctions Deadline Nears - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/new-usaid-chief-sudan-visit/4002732.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKhIMO8K_RoeONEMVQjlbB8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 16:52:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/new-usaid-chief-sudan-visit/4002732.html" target="_blank"&gt;New USAID Chief Visits Sudan as Sanctions Deadline Nears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump's new aid chief, Mark Green, kicked off an African tour in Sudan on Sunday, where he will assess whether Khartoum has done enough to get help into conflict areas to deserve eased sanctions. It is Green's first trip as administrator for the U.S. Agency for International Development, a job he began two weeks ago amid talk of budget cuts and a wide-reaching reorganization of the agency by the Trump administration. He is due to visit aid projects in drought-hit zones including neighboring Ethiopia, at a time when Washington is considering an estimated 30-percent cut ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sudan's Wanted President to Visit Russia Next Month - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-president-to-visit-russia/3925991.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBK8mqM1nQ3ZT4VMAc4e4QAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 13:20:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-president-to-visit-russia/3925991.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan's Wanted President to Visit Russia Next Month&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudanese President Omar Hassan al-Bashir will travel to Russia next month, Khartoum authorities said on Monday, a rare overseas trip for a leader wanted by the International Criminal Court on charges of crimes against humanity. Sudan's Foreign Ministry said Bashir was invited by Russian President Vladimir Putin to discuss bilateral, regional, and global issues. The visit, scheduled for the second half of August, comes as Sudan awaits a decision by the United States on whether to lift a 20-year-old trade embargo and other major sanctions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sudan to Continue Cooperation with US Despite Sanctions - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-sanctions-us/3942598.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH6Ocw8By4irUUextW_Ur_8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 13:47:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/sudan-sanctions-us/3942598.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan to Continue Cooperation with US Despite Sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudan said on Thursday it would continue bilateral cooperation with the United States, including on intelligence-sharing, despite Khartoum's decision to halt the work of a committee formed to negotiate relief from U.S. sanctions. Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir on Wednesday froze the work of the committee, which was formed with the United States, after Washington postponed for three months a decision on whether to permanently lift sanctions against Sudan. They were imposed partly over concern about human rights. "We continue to cooperate with the United States at the bilateral level betwe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sudanese rebel group releases 127 prisoners - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/03/sudanese-rebel-group-releases-127-prisoners-170305143557003.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEEjBpCyvl7zS2BEXV-j3S0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 17:48:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/03/sudanese-rebel-group-releases-127-prisoners-170305143557003.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudanese rebel group releases 127 prisoners&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Sudanese rebel group has freed 127 people it had captured in fighting with government forces, according to the country's army. Those released by the Sudan People's Liberation Movement-North (SPLM-N) included 109 soldiers and 18 civilians, Brigadier Ahmed Khalifa al-Shami, the army spokesman, said in a statement on Sunday. "The Sudanese army recognises this as a positive step towards achieving peace in the country." The SPLM-N had captured the prisoners in Blue Nile and South Kordofan states, where the group has been fighting Sudanese government forces for years. It was not clear how long ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>South Africa to Leave International Criminal Court - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-to-leave-icc/3560651.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELDcWJ57PgQW5Jn9RdWDKeIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 13:35:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-to-leave-icc/3560651.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa to Leave International Criminal Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Africa says it plans to withdraw from the International Criminal Court. Justice and Correctional Services Minister Michael Masutha said Friday a bill will be submitted to parliament recommending that South Africa repeal implementation of the Rome Statute that created the court. The statue obligates its signatories to arrest anyone sought by the ICC. Analysts fear South Africa's decision could encourage other African nations to abandon the Hague-based tribunal, which prosecutes war crimes and crimes against humanity Broker of peace But Masutha defended the decision, citing his nation’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>US Lifts Economic Sanctions on Sudan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-lifts-economic-sanctions-sudan/4059945.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEUCJ3Ab1uXwUKCq32oNVHYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 20:48:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-lifts-economic-sanctions-sudan/4059945.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Lifts Economic Sanctions on Sudan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States has lifted long-standing economic sanctions on Sudan, citing the country's progress in human rights and counterterrorism. Friday's announcement by the State Department comes after what officials say was a careful review of Sudan's positive actions since January and a "focused, 16-month diplomatic" effort between the U.S. and Sudan. The lifting of sanctions is "in recognition of the Government of Sudan's sustained positive actions to maintain a cessation of hostilities in conflict areas in Sudan, improve humanitarian access throughout Sudan, and maintain cooperation with th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>South Africa defends decision to ignore ICC's Bashir arrest warrant - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-sudan-safrica-idUSKBN1791FN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI_enrgRFTdtMmKclGFtp_wqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 09:57:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-sudan-safrica-idUSKBN1791FN" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa defends decision to ignore ICC's Bashir arrest warrant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Stephanie van den Berg THE HAGUE (Reuters) - South Africa told the International Criminal Court on Friday that it believed it was under no obligation to arrest Sudanese President Omar Hassan al-Bashir during a visit two years ago even though he was subject to an ICC arrest warrant. The ICC warrant did not outweigh a South African law that grants sitting heads of state immunity from prosecution, South African legal representative Dire Tladi told judges at a hearing to discuss Pretoria's failure to arrest al-Bashir in 2015. "There is no duty under international law and the Rome Statute to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>ICC: South Africa Failed Obligations by Not Arresting Sudan's Bashir - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-south-africa-sudan-bashir-arrest-failure/3930865.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGO_2OfCgnpCX-PUPSWS5wEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 14:45:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-south-africa-sudan-bashir-arrest-failure/3930865.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC: South Africa Failed Obligations by Not Arresting Sudan's Bashir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Judges at the International Criminal Court have ruled that South Africa failed in its obligations to the war crimes court by failing to arrest Sudan's wanted president when he visited the nation for a summit of African leaders in 2015. The ruling comes as South African officials dig in their heels in their decision to withdraw from the court after the controversial incident. Two years after Omar al-Bashir’s whirlwind visit to South Africa, judges at the International Criminal Court unanimously ruled the nation’s officials erred by failing to arrest Sudan’s president on an international war...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Should African Presidents Have Immunity From Prosecution? - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/african-president-immunity-from-prosecution/3883794.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGk-Im_1W2UexQL6Qnn8xIAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 03:30:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/african-president-immunity-from-prosecution/3883794.html" target="_blank"&gt;Should African Presidents Have Immunity From Prosecution?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human rights groups see two pivotal moments in the mounting of resistance to the International Criminal Court in Africa. Both involve the indictments of sitting heads of state. “If you look at the history of the pushback of the ICC by the AU (African Union), it dates back to the time the arrest warrant was issued for Omar al-Bashir and then subsequently on the Kenyan officials,” said Netsanet Belay, Africa director of research and advocacy for Amnesty International. “We believe there is no legal or normative reason to support the impunity of heads of state of governments, especially when it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Robert Mugabe’s Wife on the Lam for Attacking Model - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/after-bashing-a-model-madam-mugabes-on-the-lam</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECORxYfbupb32D0wROJQuysqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLzdlwI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/after-bashing-a-model-madam-mugabes-on-the-lam" target="_blank"&gt;Robert Mugabe’s Wife on the Lam for Attacking Model&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KAMPALA, Uganda—The family of a young model allegedly attacked with an extension cord by Zimbabwe’s first lady at a Johannesburg hotel has rejected a cash offer to drop charges against Grace Mugabe. Pressure is mounting on Zimbabwe’s scandal-prone 52-year-old first lady—touted by some as a successor to her infamous 93-year-old husband—to face charges related to the assault of 20-year-old Gabriella Engels in the upmarket suburb Sandton on Sunday. “This woman is not going to get off scot-free for what she did to my child,” the victim’s mother, Debbie Engels, said at a media conference Thursda...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Top South African Jurists Urge Parliament to Stay in International Criminal Court - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-jurists-international-criminal-court/3755266.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGMw_FNj1RGajvWQttuPE1UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 16:22:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-jurists-international-criminal-court/3755266.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top South African Jurists Urge Parliament to Stay in International Criminal Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Top legal scholars say the fight for South Africa to stay in the International Criminal Court is just beginning, a day after the government officially revoked its notice of intent to withdraw from the war crimes court. That decision came after a South African court ruled last month that that notice, given by South Africa's Cabinet, was unconstitutional, and the matter needs to go through parliament. At the time, legal activists praised the ruling because they said it showed South Africa's commitment to following proper procedures. But retired Constitutional Court justice Zak Yacoob says thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>South Africa Denies Non-Compliance Over al-Bashir - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3800968.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWqcCWoRAxQksDnR15JdK0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 17:10:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3800968.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa Denies Non-Compliance Over al-Bashir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court held a hearing Friday on South Africa's refusal to arrest Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir when he visited the country in 2015. The ICC wanted South African authorities to detain and hand over the Sudanese leader, who is wanted on charges of genocide. South Africa told the International Criminal Court it was under no duty to arrest Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir when he came to Johannesburg in 2015. The ICC filed a complaint against South Africa for non-compliance after authorities there refused to detain Al-Bashir. The legal representative for South Af...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Did South Africa Break ICC Rules? Court to Rule This Week - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-international-criminal-court/3930475.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGmGLuUr5Aw2cy1NceT0OKsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 03:06:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/south-africa-international-criminal-court/3930475.html" target="_blank"&gt;Did South Africa Break ICC Rules? Court to Rule This Week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Judges at the International Criminal Court (ICC) will rule Thursday on whether South Africa violated ICC rules by failing to arrest Sudan’s president during a 2015 visit to Johannesburg, in a case that will test international support for the court. There is an outstanding ICC warrant for President Omar Hassan al-Bashir’s arrest on genocide charges, which he denies. Thursday’s ruling will be closely watched for its possible implications for Bashir and other sitting heads of state as well as for the court itself. If the ICC rules that South Africa’s decision to let Bashir go was an act of non...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Gunmen kidnap three UNHCR workers in Sudan's Darfur: local official - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-violence-un-idUSKBN13N0ZQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP0Vpz5jPBCUCq7J85-kgZAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 11:29:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-violence-un-idUSKBN13N0ZQ" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen kidnap three UNHCR workers in Sudan's Darfur: local official&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KHARTOUM (Reuters) - Unidentified gunmen have kidnapped three workers from the United Nation's refugee agency in Sudan's restive Darfur region, a local official told Reuters on Monday. The three workers, one Sudanese and two Nepalese, were kidnapped from Geneina, the capital of West Darfur state and were taken to an unknown location, said West Darfur government spokesman Abdallah Gar al-Nabi. Security forces were working to retrieve them and locate the culprits, he added. An official from the United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR) declined to comment. Security remains fragile...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>US to lift sanctions on Sudan - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/10/06/politics/us-to-lift-sanctions-sudan/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDrTYxE8IAUB32_uTQx2H14qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 19:35:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/10/06/politics/us-to-lift-sanctions-sudan/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;US to lift sanctions on Sudan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States will lift a myriad of economic sanctions against Sudan next Thursday, marking a significant warming of relations with a country whose leader has been charged with genocide by the International Criminal Court. The move follows 16 months of diplomatic negotiations, initiated under former US President Barack Obama and continued under President Donald Trump, who signed off on the sanctions relief. "This marks one step forward on a long and hard road where much more progress is needed," a senior administration official told reporters Friday. Starting October 12, however, Sudan ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>South Africa condemned by international court for failing to arrest Sudanese president accused of genocide - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/south-africa-icc-sudan-president-omar-hassan-al-bashir-arrest-war-crimes-a7828036.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDW12e-Wn-2VAn3zZCELcHYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/south-africa-icc-sudan-president-omar-hassan-al-bashir-arrest-war-crimes-a7828036.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa condemned by international court for failing to arrest Sudanese president accused of genocide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court (ICC) has ruled that South Africa failed to comply with its obligations when it did not arrest Omar Hassan al-Bashir, the Sudanese president wanted by the court on charges of war crimes, during a visit - but said any further action was "futile". The public gallery was packed as the court addressed for the first time on the obligation that member states of the ICC have to arrest and surrender the Sudanese president. Mr Bashir remains in office and in addition to the visit to the African Union summit in June 2015, he has been travelling freely since two intern...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Sudan's President, who faces genocide charges, to attend Saudi summit with Trump - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/05/17/politics/trump-bashir-saudi-summit/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEERDjOzx8_dqplwu4Vr3V44qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 14:09:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/05/17/politics/trump-bashir-saudi-summit/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan's President, who faces genocide charges, to attend Saudi summit with Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudan's controversial President Omar al-Bashir is due to attend a summit in Saudi Arabia that will bring together US President Donald Trump and leaders of Muslim majority nations, a senior Sudanese lawmaker said Wednesday. Bashir, who's led his country for almost three decades, has been charged with crimes against humanity, including genocide, by the International Criminal Court related to the Darfur conflict in Sudan in 2010. But he denies the charges, has yet to cooperate with the court and continues to travel freely around the continent, including to South Africa and Uganda, which have b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Immigration fears make the EU prepared to do business with murderers - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/belief/2016/oct/13/immigration-fears-make-the-eu-prepared-to-do-business-with-murderers</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGBX3gJ8t0vZTJfQk-52rrIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 16:36:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/belief/2016/oct/13/immigration-fears-make-the-eu-prepared-to-do-business-with-murderers" target="_blank"&gt;Immigration fears make the EU prepared to do business with murderers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2009 the international criminal court issued an arrest warrant for Sudanese president Omar al-Bashir on seven counts of crimes against humanity and war crimes. In 2010 it issued a further warrant on three counts of genocide. He is the only sitting head of state charged with committing genocide against his own people. In a majority Arab country, the ethnically African groups, especially those around the Darfur area, have long been politically marginalised. But since 2003 Bashir has been trying to systematically eliminate them, not least through his proxies, the hated Janjaweed (literally ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>In war-torn Darfur, new U.S. aid chief stresses need for humanitarian access - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-aid-sudan-idUSKCN1B825W</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIWl4CwXbbK-XP2eH76RvikqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 20:57:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-aid-sudan-idUSKCN1B825W" target="_blank"&gt;In war-torn Darfur, new U.S. aid chief stresses need for humanitarian access&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Lesley Wroughton ZAM ZAM CAMP, North Darfur (Reuters) - Washington's top aid official, Mark Green, visiting Sudan's North Darfur state, stressed on Monday the importance of unfettered humanitarian access as a key demand for easing U.S. sanctions against the government of President Omar al-Bashir. Just two weeks into the job as U.S. President Donald Trump's new aid administrator, Green is on a fact-finding mission to Sudan before an Oct. 12 deadline for when the administration will decide whether to permanently lift 20-year-old sanctions. The United Nations has reported progress in the op...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Sudan to continue cooperation with U.S. despite sanctions: ministry - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-sanctions-idUSKBN19Y1ER</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIYZJJZXm37N2MuZSm5gZ_MqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:25:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-sudan-sanctions-idUSKBN19Y1ER" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan to continue cooperation with U.S. despite sanctions: ministry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KHARTOUM (Reuters) - Sudan said on Thursday it would continue bilateral cooperation with the United States, including on intelligence-sharing, despite Khartoum's decision to halt the work of a committee formed to negotiate relief from U.S. sanctions. Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir on Wednesday froze the work of the committee, which was formed with the United States, after Washington postponed for three months a decision on whether to permanently lift sanctions against Sudan. They were imposed partly over concern about human rights. "We continue to cooperate with the United States at the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>