<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Kalenjin people - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREpyTnpWa0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-KE&amp;gl=KE&amp;ceid=KE:en</link><language>en-KE</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:11:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>SANG: Are Kalenjin CEOs corrupt or just victims of circumstances? - The Star, Kenya</title><link>https://www.the-star.co.ke/news/2018/12/08/sang-are-kalenjin-ceos-corrupt-or-just-victims-of-circumstances_c1862352</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMic2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZS1zdGFyLmNvLmtlL25ld3MvMjAxOC8xMi8wOC9zYW5nLWFyZS1rYWxlbmppbi1jZW9zLWNvcnJ1cHQtb3ItanVzdC12aWN0aW1zLW9mLWNpcmN1bXN0YW5jZXNfYzE4NjIzNTLSAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:01:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.the-star.co.ke/news/2018/12/08/sang-are-kalenjin-ceos-corrupt-or-just-victims-of-circumstances_c1862352" target="_blank"&gt;SANG: Are Kalenjin CEOs corrupt or just victims of circumstances?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star, Kenya&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Kenya, appointment to public office through a political process is a poisoned chalice. Rarely do you get into office and leave happily. Many who genuinely ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.the-star.co.ke">The Star, Kenya</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/ywCpATby0npW8vExbPCBTy3xsbEcKkvm-L0vSgXOeN6hF-KB2Th-wG3xdg0eKQyUP6lTVMXIu8jT4MFji1woNDFVfsiKwbZKJx2K9oK4aKO_ALInsZ8inafbia9gngzocFpRYfxrQBd1xq9sP4V45gA_tR-oC3-wbQ1ZfCRHqmJ8SiAFEZ7gUM2J_lYrzg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Kalenjin elders warn Ruto and Moi - Daily Nation</title><link>https://www.nation.co.ke/news/politics/Elders-urge-Ruto-and-Moi-to-bury-hatchet/1064-4884862-fpto35/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5hdGlvbi5jby5rZS9uZXdzL3BvbGl0aWNzL0VsZGVycy11cmdlLVJ1dG8tYW5kLU1vaS10by1idXJ5LWhhdGNoZXQvMTA2NC00ODg0ODYyLWZwdG8zNS9pbmRleC5odG1s0gEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:40:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nation.co.ke/news/politics/Elders-urge-Ruto-and-Moi-to-bury-hatchet/1064-4884862-fpto35/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kalenjin elders warn Ruto and Moi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Daily Nation&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kalenjin elders have warned that the community risks losing the 2022 presidential race due to the battle of egos pitting Deputy President William Ruto against ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nation.co.ke">Daily Nation</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/nu6IeKSJyjNjkShc7gSJoq_PQItkBxbiR5qmzg2vyH8OsNH63iauyI7yfUv09pHEXnBT3h0vXa_o_TyYmASVQ-wTSgWVXI3zWjGoRq4EEAqxRG04xZAdtwbMys_Se6LvF0iK6FrhUQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Ruto urges Kalenjin not to worry, 2022 gameplan is intact - The Star, Kenya</title><link>https://www.the-star.co.ke/news/2018/11/26/ruto-urges-kalenjin-not-to-worry-2022-gameplan-is-intact_c1856152</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZS1zdGFyLmNvLmtlL25ld3MvMjAxOC8xMS8yNi9ydXRvLXVyZ2VzLWthbGVuamluLW5vdC10by13b3JyeS0yMDIyLWdhbWVwbGFuLWlzLWludGFjdF9jMTg1NjE1MtIBAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.the-star.co.ke/news/2018/11/26/ruto-urges-kalenjin-not-to-worry-2022-gameplan-is-intact_c1856152" target="_blank"&gt;Ruto urges Kalenjin not to worry, 2022 gameplan is intact&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star, Kenya&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deputy President William Ruto has asked the Kalenjin community not to have any worries about the 2022 succession, assuring them that “it is well planned.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.the-star.co.ke">The Star, Kenya</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/BZtTt9Ei6oXzxThK2eScvaiFkKtz1fTAOCNM4aUwwazWnJEfHUZA_px9VOp1fINmT9CTOUN8oaQTKqHP-QlHrP08TSDOTjESJtBFQ-1njh7AkTh41nT6VNTOznwW6XtmzP22ypQmCQgtLs2EIXPTQ4ITofypnrHYY8L4-5yQfAfLa0qn6MbK6mwbruWwKQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Kenya election tensions fill the air - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e1040994-77a8-11e7-90c0-90a9d1bc9691</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ1v4X8x1wxaZ4SUE7fPhxIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 13:08:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e1040994-77a8-11e7-90c0-90a9d1bc9691" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya election tensions fill the air&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a corner of Kibera, a large informal settlement clinging to muddy slopes in the heart of Nairobi, men hawk illegal charcoal by the side of the red-mud alleyways that criss-cross Kenya’s biggest slum. Kids play football with a half-inflated ball. Nearby a group of men engage in an animated discussion about Tuesday’s presidential, legislative and local elections in a country where politics is part national sport and part deadly obsession. There is a lot to discuss. Kibera is awash with rumours about recent events. In the past few days, the man in charge of the electoral commission’s techno...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Kenya backs devolution to defuse political tensions - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/17e8d1c2-a73b-11e6-8b69-02899e8bd9d1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFoYmrGMc7CKonwgqgMahWEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 07:09:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/17e8d1c2-a73b-11e6-8b69-02899e8bd9d1" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya backs devolution to defuse political tensions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reputation of the main hospital in Iten was so bad that the only people who went there were those who wanted to “die quickly”, says Alex Tolgos, the county governor. But four years since Kenya started what the World Bank calls “one of the most rapid and ambitious devolution processes” on the planet, the hospital in the western Kenyan town has been transformed. More than half the patients in its 200 beds are from nearby counties, a sign, hospital administrators say, of its success. The turnround, Mr Tolgos believes, is largely the result of new funding local authorities receive. “Before ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Kenyans Forced Off Tea Highlands by British Colonialists Seek Justice - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3878160.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC60utH9VOxpyJ8XoHLQQTAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 20:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3878160.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyans Forced Off Tea Highlands by British Colonialists Seek Justice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a roadside cafe in Kenya's majestic highlands, Elly Sigilai cradled a steaming mug of tea and recalled how 17 relatives died after British colonialists ousted them in 1934 to plant tea on their family land. The 79-year-old is one of hundreds of elderly Kenyans seeking to sue the British government for alleged displacement and torture by its colonial predecessor, in a case that could encourage other former colonies to press similar claims. "Those on this list died from malaria and sleeping sickness," said Sigilai, a neatly folded piece of paper in his hand naming the dead in his family, i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>As They Prepare for Local Elections, Kenyans Remember 2007-2008 Violence - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenyans-remember-2007-2008-ekection-violence/3974412.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEATxrNcYSBu7HEYQQxSR5OsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 15:17:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenyans-remember-2007-2008-ekection-violence/3974412.html" target="_blank"&gt;As They Prepare for Local Elections, Kenyans Remember 2007-2008 Violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenya’s Rift Valley was the epicenter of the 2007-2008 post-election violence. While there are few concerns of mounting tensions this year over the ongoing local races, residents have held youth marches and a special church service to remember the victims of 2008 Kiambaa church massacre. Worshipers sang and prayed for peace in Kiambaa Church in Eldoret in the Rift Valley region of Kenya. It was here Kikuyu men and women ran to after armed Kalenjin youth attacked their homes. The violence followed them to the church. Children, women, and men were burnt. David Irungu, who was eight at the tim...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kenyan elections: The ethnicity factor - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/08/kenyan-elections-ethnicity-factor-170806081143385.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECH5XlnSsLgwNvJgaX9WZ4oqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 12:25:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/08/kenyan-elections-ethnicity-factor-170806081143385.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenyan elections: The ethnicity factor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nairobi, Kenya - A convoy of pick-up trucks wrapped in shiny touched-up photos of candidates and mounted with huge speakers drive slowly in front of Anne Wanjiru Kamau's food stall in Nairobi's Pangani area, blasting campaign speeches by politicians from Kenya's opposition coalition. On August 8, Kamau and millions of Kenyan voters will cast their ballots in the country's general election, but today, Kamau is not paying much attention to the campaign slogans passing by, nor are her customers. "I will vote for Kenyatta. He is our son. They are wasting their time," Kamau tells Al Jazeera as s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Kenya Evicts Forest Settlers to Protect East Africa’s Water - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-evicts-forest-settlers-to-protect-east-africa-s-water-/4523448.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKuV1Ys740WlSt5HZbfkt3gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 21:04:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kenya-evicts-forest-settlers-to-protect-east-africa-s-water-/4523448.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kenya Evicts Forest Settlers to Protect East Africa’s Water&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenyan authorities are evicting thousands of settlers they say are encroaching on the protected Maasai Mau Forest, the source of several rivers that feed lakes across East Africa. The settlers from the Kalenjin community say they were duped by wealthy landowners into buying fake titles to public land. Authorities have neither prosecuted the landowners nor offered those evicted any compensation. Simon Towett lived in the Maasai Mau Forest for 30 years, but when police arrived, they burned down his house and evicted him from the forest. Samuel Towett has lived in the Maasai Mau Forest for thr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>In Kenya, polarizing election re-run rekindles ethnic tensions - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-election/in-kenya-election-re-run-polling-incomplete-and-next-steps-uncertain-idUSKBN1CX07N</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJFJ3GbrrTHWUYl-hH-96Q4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 20:18:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-kenya-election/in-kenya-election-re-run-polling-incomplete-and-next-steps-uncertain-idUSKBN1CX07N" target="_blank"&gt;In Kenya, polarizing election re-run rekindles ethnic tensions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Maggie Fick MUHORONI, Kenya (Reuters) - Kenya's repeat presidential election, boycotted this week by millions, has reignited long-running tensions between ethnic communities in some areas, leading inhabitants of one small village in the west to pick up traditional arms on Saturday. In the bright green sugarcane fields where the western Nyanza region rolls toward the Nandi hills, two tribes -- the Luo and the Kalenjin -- have lived in relative peace for years. But in the village of Koguta, down the road from the town of Mugoroni in Kisumu County, Thursday's polarizing vote reignited old g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>