<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Edgar Lungu - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV5TjNoeVpIb1NBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-SG&amp;gl=SG&amp;ceid=SG:en</link><language>en-SG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:21:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Zambian court says Lungu can stand for third term as president in 2021 - Channel NewsAsia</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/zambian-court-says-lungu-can-stand-for-third-term-as-president-in-2021-11011030</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiemh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNoYW5uZWxuZXdzYXNpYS5jb20vbmV3cy93b3JsZC96YW1iaWFuLWNvdXJ0LXNheXMtbHVuZ3UtY2FuLXN0YW5kLWZvci10aGlyZC10ZXJtLWFzLXByZXNpZGVudC1pbi0yMDIxLTExMDExMDMw0gEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:36:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/zambian-court-says-lungu-can-stand-for-third-term-as-president-in-2021-11011030" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian court says Lungu can stand for third term as president in 2021&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Channel NewsAsia&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUSAKA: Zambia's Constitutional Court ruled on Friday that President Edgar Lungu can stand in presidential elections due in 2021, finding that he ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWotZ29PbmpZQU1FY0lfT3BmT19zRU1LQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.channelnewsasia.com">Channel NewsAsia</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/RlXwz8VpWa0f7qFLi-9MFOu77x0upX8hRHaSF-eTvIIL4foJAawlTO1NMuqsUUFZNiIlAkoSjiNduFRp7jXPl39p0ajh-gpN-9rrkY4DBVgF7dYS-1y9m_tixVkWuehnC-syWAkV_jW4hXj2IR_zsuDtD66bVtG8LVw=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Zambia: Lungu to Grace Sports Awards - AllAfrica.com</title><link>https://allafrica.com/stories/201811290588.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiL2h0dHBzOi8vYWxsYWZyaWNhLmNvbS9zdG9yaWVzLzIwMTgxMTI5MDU4OC5odG1s0gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 12:51:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://allafrica.com/stories/201811290588.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia: Lungu to Grace Sports Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;AllAfrica.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT Edgar Lungu is next month expected to grace the Sports Council of Zambia (SCZ) organised National Sports awards which are aimed at promoting ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://allafrica.com">AllAfrica.com</source></item><item><title>On solo Zambia trip, Prince Harry offers help to boost elephant numbers - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-britain/on-solo-zambia-trip-prince-harry-offers-help-to-boost-elephant-numbers-idUSKCN1NV2E0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJkKDxKA4BzU2SJx7Gs3QMQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 19:20:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-britain/on-solo-zambia-trip-prince-harry-offers-help-to-boost-elephant-numbers-idUSKCN1NV2E0" target="_blank"&gt;On solo Zambia trip, Prince Harry offers help to boost elephant numbers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain's Prince Harry on Monday offered Zambia support with boosting the country's dwindling elephant population, as he began a two-day working visit without his pregnant wife Meghan. The Duke of Sussex, 34, was received at Lusaka airport by dignitaries and colorfully-dressed traditional dancers, later holding a closed-door meeting with Zambian President Edgar Lungu and his ministers. As president of animal conservation charity African Parks, Harry offered to bring elephants from neighboring Botswana. “Prince Harry told the president during closed-door talks that African Parks will help mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Zambian opposition leader detained, accused of defaming president - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN1AJ2FF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENVU_9RM-if81IAPm7Xx3gcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 16:58:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN1AJ2FF" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian opposition leader detained, accused of defaming president&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUSAKA (Reuters) - Police arrested a Zambian opposition leader on Thursday and said he would be charged with defaming President Edgar Lungu, an offence that carries a maximum five-year prison term. Officers did not say how Saviour Chishimba, the head of the United Progressive People (UPP) party, had defamed the president. Chishimba hit the headlines in July criticizing Lungu's decision to impose emergency powers and suggesting the president should go to hospital for mental tests. Political tensions in Zambia, once seen as one of Africa's more stable and functional democracies, have been ris...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Opposition leader warns Zambia faces violence if talks with president fail - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKCN1BB1S5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH_FTYlOv1Nd9M_-JJPutEEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 14:18:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKCN1BB1S5" target="_blank"&gt;Opposition leader warns Zambia faces violence if talks with president fail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Wendell Roelf CAPE TOWN (Reuters) - Zambia faces violence if a national dialogue brokered by the Commonwealth between the government and the opposition fails to reconcile the two sides, the main opposition leader Hakainde Hichilema said on Thursday. Hichilema was freed from prison in August after the state dropped charges of plotting to overthrow the government, but a judge warned him he could be arrested again at any time. The case heightened political friction in Zambia, a major copper producer which is seen as one of Africa's more stable democracies, after a bruising election last yea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Zambian opposition leader charged with treason after 'refusing to give way to president’s motorcade' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/12/zambian-opposition-leader-charged-treason-refusing-give-way/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJfSy2p7zwm6f4ZUwx2-29AqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 23:31:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/12/zambian-opposition-leader-charged-treason-refusing-give-way/" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian opposition leader charged with treason after 'refusing to give way to president’s motorcade'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambian opposition leader has been charged with treason for obstructing president Edgar Lungu's motorcade on a main road in one of the country's provinces at the weekend. Hakainde Hichilema's convoy declined to pull over to allow the presidential convoy to pass. Both were on their way to a traditional ceremony. "It has been established that the opposition leader disobeyed police orders to give way to the Presidential motorcade on Limulunga road in an attempt to put the life of the Republican President in danger,” said Kakoma Kanganja, the inspector general of police, in Lusaka. "I wish to r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Zambian Opposition Denies Arson, says Government Plotting Against it - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/zambian-opposition-denies-arson/3822985.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOD5WV75yELvM8ybZEMgIMMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 12:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/zambian-opposition-denies-arson/3822985.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian Opposition Denies Arson, says Government Plotting Against it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's main opposition party, whose leader has been arrested and charged with treason, accused the government on Monday of trying to frame it for arson as an excuse for greater political suppression. President Edgar Lungu said last week he might declare a state of emergency in some areas after public buildings were torched in attacks he blamed on opposition members protesting at the arrest of their leader, Hakainde Hichilema. The opposition United Party for National Development (UPND) denied that and said the arson accusation was a government ploy. "They are creating deliberate confusion ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambian president says emergency powers invoked after mysterious fires - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4181dde4-6261-11e7-8814-0ac7eb84e5f1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECyeexg6BACsoZeXtW97KcwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:36:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4181dde4-6261-11e7-8814-0ac7eb84e5f1" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian president says emergency powers invoked after mysterious fires&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambian president Edgar Lungu on Thursday said he had invoked emergency powers to counter “acts of sabotage” after a series of suspected arson attacks on public buildings. But analysts and critics accuse him of becoming increasingly autocratic and seeking to use the measures to ramp up a crackdown on the main opposition in what had been one of southern Africa’s most vibrant democracies. “It’s an exaggerated and unnecessary step [and] a basis upon which to oppress the opposition further,” said Bradford Machila, a lawyer and former cabinet minister. Mr Lungu’s decision to invoke the powers on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Zambia denies opposition leader barred access to lawyer - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/zambia-denies-opposition-leader-barred-access-lawyer-170413145810828.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKwwPRAYOZ8avDN82SqvQToqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 16:19:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/zambia-denies-opposition-leader-barred-access-lawyer-170413145810828.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia denies opposition leader barred access to lawyer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambian police have denied the main opposition party's claim that its detained leader Hakainde Hichilema was denied access to his lawyers and family members. Hichilema was arrested on Tuesday and charged with treason for allegedly obstructing President Edgar Lungu's motorcade on a main road. "We have not blocked lawyers and Mr Hichilema's members of the family from visiting him because that is his constitutional right," police spokeswoman Esther Mwaata-Katongo said. READ MORE: UPND leader Hakainde Hichilema charged with treason Hichilema's lawyer Jack Mwiimbu, however, said he that had seen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Zambia Emergency Declaration Divides Politics, Could Scare Investors - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-emergency-declaration-divides-politics-could-scare-investors/3941039.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHWYZZjGbY4HVQHQlApPmUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 13:57:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-emergency-declaration-divides-politics-could-scare-investors/3941039.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia Emergency Declaration Divides Politics, Could Scare Investors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's parliament has imposed a 90-day state of emergency, after the president last week declared the need for one. The situation is likely to deepen the political crisis in the country, and analysts say it also could scare away much needed investors to the copper-dependent, landlocked nation. The president called for the state of emergency after a fire destroyed the capital’s main market earlier this month. He described the fire as an arson attack by "a few unpatriotic citizens" and said, in a speech to the nation, that this and other fires were "premeditated acts, which if left unchecke...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Hakainde Hichilema pleads not guilty to treason charges - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/hakainde-hichilema-pleads-guilty-treason-charges-170814175023908.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBeJrqOmbJbE1qv5iF3WmQwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 19:08:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/hakainde-hichilema-pleads-guilty-treason-charges-170814175023908.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hakainde Hichilema pleads not guilty to treason charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's opposition leader has pleaded not guilty to treason charges, four months after his arrest for failing to make way for President Edgar Lungu's motorcade. Hakainde Hichilema, who was first charged with treason for allegedly putting Lungu's life in danger and later accused of plotting to overthrow the government, appeared in a Lusaka court on Monday. The case stoked political tensions in Zambia after Hichilema and five others were arrested in April. All six "denied the charge of treason and the state has decided to take the matter to Wednesday for trial," said Charles Kakoma, the spok...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Neoliberalism, big capital and the Zambian crisis - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/06/zambia-political-crisis-democracy-170614082021928.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBImmd-aEkqhPdgMpKcTXbQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 12:47:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/06/zambia-political-crisis-democracy-170614082021928.html" target="_blank"&gt;Neoliberalism, big capital and the Zambian crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's opposition leader Hakainde Hichilema and five others were arrested two months ago on treason charges. As the court proceedings drag on, they remain in custody and have recently been transferred to a maximum security prison. According to the state prosecutors, Hichilema's motorcade intentionally blocked President Edgar Lungu's convoy on the way to an important traditional ceremony in western Zambia. Hichilema is accused of trying to overthrow the government. He contested last year's presidential election at the head of the United Party for National Development (UPND) and lost to Lun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Zambia’s opposition leader detained after police raid his home - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c536f150-1ebf-11e7-a454-ab04428977f9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPOr15cSwnxcmXqItpjfWhoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 16:20:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c536f150-1ebf-11e7-a454-ab04428977f9" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia’s opposition leader detained after police raid his home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia’s opposition leader was detained and accused of treason on Tuesday after police raided his home, his lawyer said, in an escalation of political tensions in Africa’s second-biggest copper producer. Police surrounded the home of Hakainde Hichilema, a wealthy businessman who heads the United Party for National Development (UPND), on Monday night. The following day he was taken to a police station. “They broke into the house, they broke the doors down, everything, they beat my workers,” Mr Hichilema told the Financial Times, adding that police tear-gassed his home. “It was extremely brut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Zambia's Opposition Leader Charged with Treason - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3806880.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHfv02P1_dzXtZthE3Dvq4UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 13:29:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3806880.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia's Opposition Leader Charged with Treason&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia’s outspoken opposition leader has been charged with treason after allegedly blocking the president's motorcade recently, police said Wednesday. Hakainde Hichilema, who has said he does not recognize former opponent Edgar Lungu as the legitimate president, was arrested late Monday. "It has been established that the opposition leader disobeyed police orders to clear the way, thereby putting the life of the head of state in danger," police chief Kakoma Kanganja told reporters in Lusaka. "We have charged Hichilema and five others with treason." There is no bail on the treason charge, whi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambian opposition leader's lawyers ask court to dismiss treason case - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN17L1K5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEqAHwit33tszSffHVtAVNIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 12:39:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN17L1K5" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian opposition leader's lawyers ask court to dismiss treason case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Chris Mfula LUSAKA (Reuters) - Lawyers for a Zambian opposition party leader accused of trying to overthrow the government asked a court on Wednesday to throw out the case, saying the state charges are vague and ambiguous. Hakainde Hichilema, the United Party for National Development (UPND) leader, was arrested last week in a police raid on his home. He was initially accused of treason on the grounds that he had refused to give way to President Edgar Lungu's motorcade as it passed through Mongu, a town west of the capital Lusaka. On Tuesday, Hichilema was charged in court with plotting w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Zambians seeking food aid killed in stampede - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/03/zambians-seeking-food-aid-killed-stampede-170306140945875.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3yj98GJJTU0lVioxN9wD0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 21:12:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/03/zambians-seeking-food-aid-killed-stampede-170306140945875.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambians seeking food aid killed in stampede&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least eight people were killed in a stampede as thousands of Zambians, who have been affected by a humanitarian crisis caused by a prolonged and severe drought in southern Africa, scrambled for food handouts, police said. The stampede on Monday in the capital Lusaka took place at a public sports centre where a church was donating food to about 35,000 people, mostly from the city's slums. "Eight people died while 28 others were injured in a stampede which happened at the Olympic Youth Development Centre around 0400GMT today as a crowd jostled to enter the premises," police said in a state...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Zambian Police Free Opposition Leader Accused of Defaming President - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-lungu-defamation-case/3980110.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJoiNYyd_YhCKxf8UuoZrQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 13:51:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-lungu-defamation-case/3980110.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian Police Free Opposition Leader Accused of Defaming President&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police in Zambia freed an opposition leader on Thursday after holding him in detention for a week on accusations of defaming President Edgar Lungu, an offense that carries a maximum five-year prison term. Police arrested United Progressive Party leader Saviour Chishimba last Thursday and said he would be charged with defaming the president. "We have discontinued the case," police spokeswoman Esther Mwaata-Katongo said in a statement, without giving any reasons. Chishimba hit the headlines in July after criticizing Lungu's decision to impose emergency powers and suggesting the president shou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>South Africa's Mmusi Maimane 'barred' from Zambia - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/05/south-africa-mmusi-maimane-barred-zambia-170526081020059.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIZG2JQPMyk8UHaXzLx76k4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 10:47:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/05/south-africa-mmusi-maimane-barred-zambia-170526081020059.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa's Mmusi Maimane 'barred' from Zambia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mmusi Maimane, South Africa's main opposition leader, has accused Zambian officials of denying him entry to their country as he tried to show support for an imprisoned Zambian opposition leader who is being held on treason charges. Maimane, of the Democratic Alliance party, planned to attend the trial of Hakainde Hichilema, the leader of Zambia's United Party for National Development (UPND), on Friday. But Zambian officials boarded his plane on arrival in Zambia's capital, Lusaka, and prevented him from leaving the aircraft. "[The Zambian government sent an] arrest team ... to meet me at th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Zambia's Biggest Market Gutted, Government Suspects Arson - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-biggest-market-gutted-arson/3927747.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMYRgFipI1lYNe9jTnwbRi0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 15:18:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-biggest-market-gutted-arson/3927747.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia's Biggest Market Gutted, Government Suspects Arson&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fire gutted part of Zambia's biggest market in the nation's capital on Tuesday in what the government suspected was an act of arson as tensions rise following the arrest of an opposition leader. United Party for National Development (UPND) leader Hakainde Hichilema was arrested in April and charged with treason for impeding president Edgar Lungu's motorcade. The arrest of the opposition leader has stoked political tensions in what is regarded as one of Africa's more stable and functional democracies following a bruising election last year. The blaze started at dawn and destroyed property wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambian Police Question Opposition Leader in Motorcade Spat - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3805450.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO5N24AmYp4EoOjNRUTRI_oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 14:44:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3805450.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian Police Question Opposition Leader in Motorcade Spat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia’s outspoken opposition leader has been arrested for the second time in about six months, a party spokesman told VOA Tuesday. The arrest is part of deepening fallout from a contentious August presidential poll that both contenders claim to have won. Opposition spokesman Charles Kakoma said police broke through the doors of opposition leader Hakainde Hichilema’s upscale home late Monday, blocked the gates and doors to prevent escape, tear-gassed the occupants and then took Hichilema away. Kakoma said police had not charged Hichilema by morning and had taken him to a police training aca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambia's biggest market gutted, government suspects arson - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/zambia-crime-idUSL8N1JV2AU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP0FuasEJMaqTsp--4qpdW4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 12:47:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/zambia-crime-idUSL8N1JV2AU" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia's biggest market gutted, government suspects arson&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUSAKA (Reuters) - Fire gutted part of Zambia's biggest market in the nation's capital on Tuesday in what the government suspected was an act of arson as tensions rise following the arrest of an opposition leader. United Party for National Development (UPND leader Hakainde Hichilema was arrested in April and charged with treason for impeding president Edgar Lungu's motorcade. The arrest of the opposition leader has stoked political tensions in what is regarded as one of Africa's more stable and functional democracies following a bruising election last year. The blaze started at dawn and des...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Zambian opposition leader Hichilema arrested, charged with treason: police - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN17E1CH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECmlY-3SNPqS7nsSqyk-q8cqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:19:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN17E1CH" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian opposition leader Hichilema arrested, charged with treason: police&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUSAKA (Reuters) - Zambian opposition leader Hakainde Hichilema has been arrested and charged by police with treason for allegedly obstructing the motorcade of President Edgar Lungu, the southern African nation's police chief said on Wednesday. Hichilema, an economist and wealthy businessman, was detained on Tuesday after an incident involving the motorcade as it passed through Mongu, 500 km (310 miles) west of the capital Lusaka. "It has been established that the opposition leader disobeyed police orders to clear the way, thereby putting the life of the head of state in danger," police chi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Zambia Extends State of Emergency by Three Months - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-extends-state-of-emergency-by-three-months/3938151.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHEzuR8P3d2VLYFLFmCl5E8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 22:10:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-extends-state-of-emergency-by-three-months/3938151.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia Extends State of Emergency by Three Months&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's parliament voted on Tuesday to extend the state of emergency by three months, the presidency office said, as tensions rose following the arrest of the main opposition leader. Africa's second-largest copper producer, is usually seen as one of the continent's more stable democracies. But it has been on a political knife-edge since the detention in April on treason charges of Hakainde Hichilema, who narrowly lost to President Edgar Lungu in a bruising election last year. Lungu invoked the emergency powers last week to deal with "acts of sabotage" by his political opponents, after fire...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambian Opposition Leader Pleads Not Guilty to Treason Charges - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambian-opposition-leader-pleads-not-guilty-to-treason-charges/3984992.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIxYWS41ZON_twga_ONZ1JgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 16:44:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambian-opposition-leader-pleads-not-guilty-to-treason-charges/3984992.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian Opposition Leader Pleads Not Guilty to Treason Charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia’s top opposition leader pleaded not guilty to treason charges in court Monday, disappointing those who had hoped the prosecution would drop the charges to make way for talks between Hakainde Hichilema and his arch-rival, President Edgar Lungu. The case has intensified the African nation’s deepening political crisis and prompted international mediators to intervene. Hichlema’s lawyer was tight-lipped about what he plans to say when the opposition leader appears in court later this week. “They have pleaded not guilty to the charge,” Keith Wemba told VOA from Lusaka, the capital. “And...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Treason charge plunges Zambia into political crisis - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/de8b6202-348c-11e7-bce4-9023f8c0fd2e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKsvpK-NDhiuVpgQZWm5pA8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 10:31:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/de8b6202-348c-11e7-bce4-9023f8c0fd2e" target="_blank"&gt;Treason charge plunges Zambia into political crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In many African countries, a traffic violation generally results in nothing worse than a fine or demand for a bribe. In Zambia, one man faces a somewhat stiffer charge: treason. The man in question is Hakainde Hichilema, an opposition leader who claims he was cheated of the presidency, and the violation, which was his refusal to move over for President Edgar Lungu, helps explain why the seemingly minor incident has plunged Zambia into a political crisis. Mr Hichilema, a businessman who narrowly lost August’s presidential election, a result he unsuccessfully challenged in court, has been cha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Zambia to drop treason charges against opposition leader - sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-exclusive-idUSKCN1AT081</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI149VG5Yl6Fg6M2M_6GY5oqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 08:15:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-exclusive-idUSKCN1AT081" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Zambia to drop treason charges against opposition leader - sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Chris Mfula LUSAKA (Reuters) - Zambia plans to drop treason charges against the country's main opposition leader and free him from prison on Monday under a deal brokered by the Commonwealth secretary-general, government and legal sources told Reuters. The United Party for National Development (UPND) leader Hakainde Hichilema and five others were arrested in April and charged with treason after Hichilema's convoy failed to make way for President Edgar Lungu's motorcade. Hichilema's trial had been due to begin on Monday but two sources said the prosecution would apply to the court to disco...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>South African opposition leader says barred from entering Zambia - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-opposition-zambia-idUSKBN18L2WA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIn2vw0nsXblHjf3r4d5E5YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 22:01:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-safrica-opposition-zambia-idUSKBN18L2WA" target="_blank"&gt;South African opposition leader says barred from entering Zambia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (Reuters) - South African opposition leader Mmusi Maimane said Zambian immigration officials barred him from entering their country late on Thursday, stopping his visit to a detained opposition leader there. Maimane of South Africa's Democratic Alliance said on Twitter the officials boarded his plane after it landed, "took away my phone so I couldn't get help" then forced him to return home. Zambia's immigration police and government were not immediately available for comment. Maimane said he was planning to visit Hakainde Hichilema, the leader of Zambia's United Party for Nati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>How One Zambian Traffic Incident Led to a Treason Charge - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-traffic-incident-treason-charge/3872802.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOPoaJtVLPkQhnUn0A-yU7MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 18:33:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-traffic-incident-treason-charge/3872802.html" target="_blank"&gt;How One Zambian Traffic Incident Led to a Treason Charge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One traffic spat in western Zambia has grown into an international incident with life-or-death implications — one that could taint Zambia's history of peaceful and democratic rule. For more than six weeks now, opposition leader Hakainde Hichilema has been in jail, awaiting trial on treason charges, which carry a possible death penalty. He was arrested in April, after his convoy crossed paths with the motorcade of President Edgar Lungu on a country road, and Hichilema's drivers refused to yield to the president. Days later, police stormed into his upscale Lusaka home, sprayed tear gas and ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Once-stable Zambia Tense as President Invokes Extra Powers - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-tensions/3932531.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPpcXywaIF37VvsEiUPE4X4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 13:57:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-tensions/3932531.html" target="_blank"&gt;Once-stable Zambia Tense as President Invokes Extra Powers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are edgy times in Zambia, once considered one of Africa's most stable democracies. President Edgar Lungu this week announced extra police powers to deal with what he says are growing security challenges, including a fire that destroyed the biggest market in the capital, Lusaka. The cause of the fire has not been determined, leading critics to accuse Lungu of intensifying a purported crackdown on legitimate political opposition. Lungu says he is not targeting “political players.” Hakainde Hichilema, the main opposition leader, has been charged with treason after he was accused of obstr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambian Opposition Leader Remains in Jail - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/zambian-opposition-leader-hakainde-hichilema-remains-in-jail/3827045.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECpVjILwlZEGKsFgt3856L4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 21:35:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/zambian-opposition-leader-hakainde-hichilema-remains-in-jail/3827045.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian Opposition Leader Remains in Jail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's opposition leader Hakainde Hichilema has been behind bars for two weeks. He will remain there as a judge in Magistrate's Court said Wednesday he did not have the power to rule on a defense motion to drop the charge of treason. Zambia does not allow bail for treason cases. The spokesman for Hichilema's UPND party, Charles Kakoma, told VOA Wednesday the defense has filed another application to dispute the treason charge before another magistrate court. Those proceedings were adjourned until Thursday. Amnesty International has criticized the case as “political persecution through pros...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambian Opposition Leader Detained, Accused of Defaming President - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-opposition-leader-accused-defaming-president/3971479.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKi5pQg4FbnL8RIaaeJAglIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 21:34:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-opposition-leader-accused-defaming-president/3971479.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian Opposition Leader Detained, Accused of Defaming President&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police arrested a Zambian opposition leader on Thursday and said he would be charged with defaming President Edgar Lungu, an offense that carries a maximum five-year prison term. Officers did not say how Saviour Chishimba, the head of the United Progressive People (UPP) party, had defamed the president. Chishimba made headlines in July, criticizing Lungu's decision to impose emergency powers and suggesting the president should go to hospital for mental tests. Political tensions in Zambia, once seen as one of Africa's more stable and functional democracies, have been rising since main opposi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambia's president to seek parliament backing for state of emergency - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN19Q2OB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELSPGgmGXqtVrW7ARcMRhNIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 20:34:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN19Q2OB" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia's president to seek parliament backing for state of emergency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Chris Mfula LUSAKA (Reuters) - Zambian President Edgar Lungu said on Wednesday he would seek parliament's approval to impose a state of emergency after fire gutted the country's biggest market in what he said was politically motivated arson. Political tensions in Zambia, seen as one of Africa's more stable and functional democracies, have been rising since the arrest on treason charges of main opposition leader Hakainde Hichilema, who narrowly lost to Lungu in a bruising election last year. Hichilema, along with five others, is accused of trying to overthrow the government after a column...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Zambia extends state of emergency by three months: presidency office - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN19W2CI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEZRC5zipRGkrA4Kv5f1O6AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 18:46:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN19W2CI" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia extends state of emergency by three months: presidency office&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUSAKA (Reuters) - Zambia's parliament voted on Tuesday to extend the state of emergency by three months, the presidency's office said in a statement. President Edgar Lungu invoked emergency powers last week to deal with "acts of sabotage" by his political opponents, after fire gutted the country's biggest market. (Reporting by Chiwoyu Sinyangwe; Writing by Tiisetso Motsoeneng; Editing by Alison Williams)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Zambian Opposition Leader Calls on Government to Free Detained Party Members - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-hichilema-detained-party-member/3987796.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJ8nG6DqrhRNtb_f9wlca0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 13:01:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-hichilema-detained-party-member/3987796.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian Opposition Leader Calls on Government to Free Detained Party Members&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambian opposition leader Hakainde Hichilema called on the government to free several members of his party who are still being detained over various charges hours after he was released from prison on Wednesday. The state prosecutor dropped charges against him of plotting to overthrow the government. Hichilema and five others were arrested in April and charged with treason after his convoy failed to make way for President Edgar Lungu's motorcade. "I can't say I am free when our members are in detention," he told hundreds of supporters outside his party's headquarters and called for the end o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambia Court to Rule on Opposition Leader's Treason Case Next Week - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3819647.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIiqoqYWs1HUqb7scK32RdcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 01:00:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3819647.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia Court to Rule on Opposition Leader's Treason Case Next Week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Zambian court will rule next week on whether to throw out a treason case against the leader of the main opposition party whose lawyers say the charges are ambiguous, a magistrate said on Thursday. United Party for National Development (UPND) leader Hakainde Hichilema was arrested last week in a police raid on his home and charged with trying to overthrow the government. His lawyers asked the court on Wednesday to dismiss the case, saying the charges were not specific. Magistrate Greenwell Malumani said he needed time to decide whether to dismiss the treason charge and consider other preli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambia's Political Rift Deepens as Opposition MPs Suspended - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-political-rift-deepens-opposition-lawmakers-suspended/3900403.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPFO0YG6Sj_6DDK6G3cno5oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 19:30:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-political-rift-deepens-opposition-lawmakers-suspended/3900403.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia's Political Rift Deepens as Opposition MPs Suspended&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's parliament has suspended 48 opposition lawmakers for boycotting a speech by President Edgar Lungu earlier this year, a sign of mounting tensions as the jailed opposition leader awaits trial on a treason charge. For the next 30 days, the 48 opposition lawmakers will not be allowed to attend parliamentary sessions. The move will effectively kneecap many parliamentary committees, which will no longer form a quorum since 48 of the nation's 166 lawmakers will be out of commission. And politically, it will only further deepen the widening chasm between the increasingly entrenched ruling ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambia parliament approves 'enhanced security measures' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/zambia-parliament-approves-90-day-state-emergency-170711200535989.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKeFl6n9y3u2D_w8KjMwAmwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 08:01:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/zambia-parliament-approves-90-day-state-emergency-170711200535989.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia parliament approves 'enhanced security measures'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's parliament has approved enhanced measures for security services for a 90-day period in a decree by President Edgar Lungu, a move critics say is an effort to tighten his grip on power. Opposition legislators boycotted the vote on Tuesday, leaving only the 85 members of the president's majority party to pass the measure. Lungu invoked the emergency powers last week, alleging that opposition parties were behind a string of arson attacks intended "to create terror and panic," including one that burned down the main market in the capital Lusaka. Nobody was killed or injured in the blaze...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Africa's Richest Man Aliko Dangote Plans More Investments In Zambia - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/mfonobongnsehe/2017/01/31/africas-richest-man-aliko-dangote-plans-more-investments-in-zambia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENq5an2o7Xw1c_ZXGd9ZmxQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 12:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/mfonobongnsehe/2017/01/31/africas-richest-man-aliko-dangote-plans-more-investments-in-zambia/" target="_blank"&gt;Africa's Richest Man Aliko Dangote Plans More Investments In Zambia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aliko Dangote Africa’s richest man, Aliko Dangote, plans to invest in the energy and agricultural sectors of Zambia. According to Nigeria’s Punch newspaper, Dangote made this known on Sunday when he paid a courtesy call to Zambian President, Edgar Lungu, in Lusaka. While urging the Zambian government to roll out policies that would encourage foreign investments in the country, Dangote noted that energy is a critical requirement for economic development and called on President Lungu to expand Zambia’s energy supply footprint both for local consumption, and export to regional markets. “I am h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Zambia's President to Seek Parliament Backing for State of Emergency - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-president-seek-parliament-backing-state-emergency/3929952.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF9_wkJvwn_7hkQvJuNAgG0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 21:53:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-president-seek-parliament-backing-state-emergency/3929952.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia's President to Seek Parliament Backing for State of Emergency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambian President Edgar Lungu said Wednesday that he would seek parliament's approval to impose a state of emergency after fire gutted the country's biggest market in what he said was politically motivated arson. Political tensions in Zambia, seen as one of Africa's more stable and functional democracies, have been rising since the arrest on treason charges of main opposition leader Hakainde Hichilema, who narrowly lost to Lungu in a bruising election last year. Hichilema and five others are accused of trying to overthrow the government after a column of opposition vehicles failed to make w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambian opposition leader charged with trying to overthrow government - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN17K22J</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJpmd3oN1gnXZ50oC5v05wUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 18:15:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics-idUSKBN17K22J" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian opposition leader charged with trying to overthrow government&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Chris Mfula LUSAKA (Reuters) - Zambia opposition leader Hakainde Hichilema, arrested last week on suspicion of treason, was charged in a magistrate's court on Tuesday with trying to overthrow the government. Relations between the government and opposition have been raw since last August, when President Edgar Lungu's Patriotic Front (PF) party beat Hichilema's United Party for National Development (UPND) in a vote the opposition says was rigged. Police in Africa's No. 2 copper-producing country raided Hichilema's house on April 11 to arrest him and he was initially charged with treason fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Is China really to blame for Zambia's debt problems? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/china-blame-zambia-debt-problems-181009140625090.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBNwix7hEkOsv3BQiNudao0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 10:26:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/china-blame-zambia-debt-problems-181009140625090.html" target="_blank"&gt;Is China really to blame for Zambia's debt problems?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's public debt has increased significantly in recent years, and concerns over a possible crisis have lately attracted the attention of Western media. On September 3, a report by British business intelligence outlet Africa Confidential warned of escalating debt caused by allegedly unsustainable Chinese loans and claimed that Zesco, the state-owned national electricity company, has been in talks about a takeover by a Chinese company. The Zambian government refuted the allegations and denied the existence of plans for Zesco's privatisation. The allegations coincided with increased Wester...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>TV tax stirs Zambian fears over Chinese ‘debt-trap’ diplomacy - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/fa54acda-c7ef-11e8-ba8f-ee390057b8c9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENW_1P3_1LaqhSPh5rhKV3QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 03:00:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/fa54acda-c7ef-11e8-ba8f-ee390057b8c9" target="_blank"&gt;TV tax stirs Zambian fears over Chinese ‘debt-trap’ diplomacy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Muntemba says there is something odd about the levy he has to pay to watch state television in Zambia. “I’ve heard the rumours,” the clothes seller said in hushed tones. He pays less than a dollar a month in tax meant to support the Zambia National Broadcasting Corporation. But the payment lies at the heart of accusations that Zambia has given up its sovereignty in return for $9.4bn of debt, up to one-third of it owed to China. Mr Muntemba’s suspicion, widely shared in Zambia, is that part of his K10 ($0.86) TV levy, which has more than doubled in a year, is being used to service a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Zambian president fires minister in charge of misused donor funds - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-corruption/zambian-president-fires-minister-in-charge-of-misused-donor-funds-idUSKCN1LZ222</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELwKe9hPFsclcrUtdFqVRRkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:01:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-corruption/zambian-president-fires-minister-in-charge-of-misused-donor-funds-idUSKCN1LZ222" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian president fires minister in charge of misused donor funds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambian President Edgar Lungu fired a cabinet minister in charge of social welfare funds on Wednesday after Britain and Finland froze aid over suspicions that $4 million of funding may have been misused. The money was channeled into the social cash transfer scheme, a donor-supported program under which the government relays money to vulnerable households in rural areas. Lungu's spokesman Amos Chanda said Olipa Phiri had been made Community Development and Social Welfare Minister, replacing Emerine Kabanshi. "The new minister has been given a clear mission to get down to work and clean up th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Zambia Fires Minister Over Graft Scandal - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-fires-minister-over-graft-scandal/4578324.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAr8_DPdKS3JNHKaBdzLNvgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:59:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-fires-minister-over-graft-scandal/4578324.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia Fires Minister Over Graft Scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia sacked its development minister on Wednesday a day after Britain suspended aid payments to the country over a mounting row about alleged corruption in President Edgar Lungu's government. Community Development Minister Emerine Kabanshi, who was in charge of a social payments program which Britain said had been abused, was fired for alleged misuse of funds, government spokeswoman Dora Siliya said in a tweet. On Tuesday, Britain's ambassador to Lusaka, Fergus Cochrane-Dyet, tweeted that Britain had frozen "all bilateral funding to Zambian government", adding that "UK Aid takes zero-tole...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>UK freezes millions in aid to Zambia amid allegations of fraud and looting - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/18/uk-freezes-millions-aid-zambia-amid-allegations-fraud-looting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH36SRypRZ_pPN9cWbh5eBYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 18:43:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/18/uk-freezes-millions-aid-zambia-amid-allegations-fraud-looting/" target="_blank"&gt;UK freezes millions in aid to Zambia amid allegations of fraud and looting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain has frozen its entire funding programme to Zambia amid allegations that state officials have looted millions of pounds of aid to set up shell companies and buy expensive cars. The Department for International Development (Dfid) has also demanded a forensic audit of Zambian government spending after evidence emerged suggesting aid had been embezzled on a significant scale since 2012. A spokesman said the move, worth £42m a year, was part of Dfid's "zero tolerance" approach to fraud and corruption. While allegations of fraud have been levelled at a series of government departments, pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Corruption in Zambia: 42 fire trucks for $42m - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/corruption-zambia-42-fire-trucks-42m-180620084648448.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKqTQ4TEVzBQHOfsik0FqW8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 08:48:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/corruption-zambia-42-fire-trucks-42m-180620084648448.html" target="_blank"&gt;Corruption in Zambia: 42 fire trucks for $42m&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The African Union (AU) will host a heads of state summit in Mauritania on June 25, under the theme Winning the Fight against Corruption: A Sustainable Path to Africa's Transformation. Zambia's President Edgar Lungu will also be at the summit, showing support for its cause. Yet on the very same day his country will be moving further away from the anti-corruption ideals of the AU. As Lungu sits down with other African leaders to talk about possible ways to eradicate corruption, six Zambian activists will sit in a dock in Lusaka to be prosecuted for protesting against corruption. On 29 Septemb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>'We are facing a sanitation crisis': Zambia's uphill struggle against the deadly scourge of cholera - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/facing-sanitation-crisis-zambias-uphill-struggle-against-deadly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM15W-lUlB1-70SBeHwCYiIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 10:28:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/facing-sanitation-crisis-zambias-uphill-struggle-against-deadly/" target="_blank"&gt;'We are facing a sanitation crisis': Zambia's uphill struggle against the deadly scourge of cholera&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;May is a glorious month in Lusaka. The Flamboyants along the streets are in full bloom and the freshness of the just-concluded rains can still be felt in the breeze. But the spring in the step of those walking through Mtendere, a bustling township in the northeast of the Zambian capital, this month probably has less to do with the weather or the flowers than the alcoholic possibilities afforded by the absence of bullying soldiers. Until a fortnight ago, the army had been on the streets of Lusaka for four months, sent into action by Edgar Lungu, Zambia’s president, to do battle with a silent...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Zambia withdraws military personnel deployed to fight cholera - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-cholera/zambia-withdraws-military-personnel-deployed-to-fight-cholera-idUSKCN1HB22W</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEy6Hnj8UFFq5ZySH8kyScIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 14:27:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-cholera/zambia-withdraws-military-personnel-deployed-to-fight-cholera-idUSKCN1HB22W" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia withdraws military personnel deployed to fight cholera&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUSAKA (Reuters) - Zambia has withdrawn military personnel deployed in December to help clean up the capital and other cities at the height of a cholera outbreak that has killed more than 80 people in seven months, the government said on Wednesday. President Edgar Lungu directed the military to help fight the spread of cholera under emergency measures to contain the waterborne disease, including the closure of markets. Home Affairs Minister Stephen Kampyongo told a briefing on Wednesday that the joint operations of the defense and security personnel had helped restore order and Lungu had or...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Zambia Asks Cuba to Recall Ambassador for Backing New Opposition Party - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-asks-cuba-to-recall-almbassador-for-backing-new-opposition-party/4326583.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJPlGRC3z4uvh5k13HJPHrEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 15:09:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-asks-cuba-to-recall-almbassador-for-backing-new-opposition-party/4326583.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia Asks Cuba to Recall Ambassador for Backing New Opposition Party&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia has asked Cuba to recall its ambassador for openly supporting the newly launched opposition Socialist Party, the president's spokesman said on Sunday. Amos Chanda said ambassador Nelson Pages Vilas spoke at the party's launch on Saturday. Political tensions were rekindled in Zambia last month when the count ry's main opposition party, the United Party for National Development (UPND), filed a motion seeking to impeachPresident Edgar Lungu over accusations of breaching the constitution. The UPND challenged Lungu's 2016 election victory in court, alleging fraud, arguing that that oblige...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambia Cholera Epidemic Continues to Slow as Number of Deaths Declines - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-cholera-epidemic-continues-slow-number-deaths-declines/4262326.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP7AgI0-ESCmKg5DiGBkV6gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 15:26:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambia-cholera-epidemic-continues-slow-number-deaths-declines/4262326.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia Cholera Epidemic Continues to Slow as Number of Deaths Declines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's cholera epidemic continues to slow with seven deaths recorded over the last month, Health Minister Chitalu Chilufya said on Tuesday. Eighty five people have now died since the outbreak of the disease in October, out of 4,202 cases, Chilufya said in a statement in parliament. "I must confirm that the cholera outbreak is ab[at]ing," he said. Zambia closed some schools and markets, among other measures, to curb the spread of the disease but relaxed them in mid-January after the number of new cases reported halved. The disease has mostly affected the capital Lusaka which had registered...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zambian Hip-Hop Artist Flees Amid Threats Over Song - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zambian-hip-hop-artist-flees-amid-threats-over-son/4229503.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFsxSgG6DHC84JJSHIa24rkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 15:44:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zambian-hip-hop-artist-flees-amid-threats-over-son/4229503.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian Hip-Hop Artist Flees Amid Threats Over Song&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambian hip-hop artist Fumba Chama won’t say where he is, or whom he is referring to in a song that caused him to run for his life. But when the artist, who goes by the stage name Pilato, spoke to VOA this week, after fleeing condemnation and death threats from supporters of the ruling party, it’s clear why the dance track has upset some of Zambia’s ruling class. “A rat has entered into the house and is stealing,” he raps in the Bemba language over a drum-heavy track filled out with African instruments. "Rats steal even the things they do not need. They steal briefs which they don’t wear.” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Is Zambia making progress in its fight against cholera? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/01/zambia-making-progress-fight-cholera-180114073131342.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHKeDT_upQOzNOkkZ-_Hr5gqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 11:20:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/01/zambia-making-progress-fight-cholera-180114073131342.html" target="_blank"&gt;Is Zambia making progress in its fight against cholera?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's government plans to open its international school and a few shopping centres after saying it has have made progress in its fight against cholera, which has killed at least 72 people since September 2017. The move, announced on this week, comes amid fears the government has not done enough to provide information on the outbreak. More than 3,100 cases have been reported nationwide over the last four months with the capital city of Lusaka the highest affected by the water-borne disease. Large gatherings including church meetings, weddings and funerals in the affected parts of Lusaka h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Zambia relaxes restrictions as cholera outbreak slows - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-cholera/zambia-relaxes-restrictions-as-cholera-outbreak-slows-idUSKBN1F30OW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMzLQggGR70jEy3-1oND6fgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 15:10:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-cholera/zambia-relaxes-restrictions-as-cholera-outbreak-slows-idUSKBN1F30OW" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia relaxes restrictions as cholera outbreak slows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUSAKA (Reuters) - Zambia on Sunday relaxed rules imposed to curb the spread of cholera as the number of new cases being reported has halved, Health Minister Chitalu Chilufya said. Schools and some markets will be allowed to re-open, Chilufya told a news conference in Lusaka. Police arrested 55 people in the capital on Friday after residents rioted over a curfew and ban on street vending. The outbreak has killed 74 people since Oct. 4, including 68 in Lusaka, Chilufya said. The number of new cases has fallen to around 80 from 164 a week ago. Of the more than 3,200 cases reported in total, m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Zambian foreign affairs minister resigns over 'swelling' corruption within country - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/zambia-corruption-harry-kalaba-resigns-foreign-affairs-resigns-africa-patriotic-front-edgar-lungu-a8140151.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGQ4zcoAACT9vjYXMIpTiRAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 16:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/zambia-corruption-harry-kalaba-resigns-foreign-affairs-resigns-africa-patriotic-front-edgar-lungu-a8140151.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian foreign affairs minister resigns over 'swelling' corruption within country&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harry Kalaba, Zambia‘s foreign affairs minister, has resigned over what he claimed were “swelling” levels of corruption in the southern African nation. He posted his resignation letter on Facebook as a struggle in the ruling Patriotic Front (PF) over President Edgar Lungu’s ambitions to run for another term in office intensifies. Mr Kalaba is seen as a potential PF candidate in a 2021 presidential election. But analysts suggested his chances of winning the PF nomination could stall if Mr Lungu won a court battle allowing him to run for a third term. - Read more Corruption and inequality fue...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Zambia deploys army to fight cholera outbreak - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/12/zambia-deploys-army-fight-cholera-outbreak-171230190812235.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGt8c2x2FjmHqUUdGJcIGPYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 19:59:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/12/zambia-deploys-army-fight-cholera-outbreak-171230190812235.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zambia deploys army to fight cholera outbreak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zambia's President Edgar Lungu has dispatched the military to help fight a cholera outbreak, which has killed 41 people in the capital, Lusaka, and affected more than 1,500 others since September. In a Facebook post late on Friday, Lungu said "all three wings of the Defence Force" had been deployed "to escalate efforts" to minimise the spread of the disease. "Lusaka has been recording an average of 60 new cases every day. I've noted with great sadness that a total of 41 people have died of the disease since its outbreak," he said. {articleGUID} The outbreak began in two densely populated ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Zambian president warns judges of chaos if they block his re-election - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics/zambian-president-warns-judges-of-chaos-if-they-block-his-re-election-idUSKBN1D323H</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHipYSS9HjGn8pva-f_r_FMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 18:05:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zambia-politics/zambian-president-warns-judges-of-chaos-if-they-block-his-re-election-idUSKBN1D323H" target="_blank"&gt;Zambian president warns judges of chaos if they block his re-election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LUSAKA (Reuters) - Zambian President Edgar Lungu has warned constitutional court judges not to stop him running for another term in office, state media reported, drawing a rebuke from a top legal body. Lungu told supporters on Thursday the judges could plunge the southern African country into chaos if they made any "adventurous" rulings, the Zambia Daily Mail and Times of Zambia reported. Allies of Lungu's Patriotic Front party have asked the Supreme Court to confirm that he will be eligible to stand again in presidential elections scheduled for 2021. Opponents say that would break the cons...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>