<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Phil Murphy - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRGRyT0RkZmFCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-SG&amp;gl=SG&amp;ceid=SG:en</link><language>en-SG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:43:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>New Jersey Governor Murphy Criticized for Storm Response - Bloomberg</title><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-16/as-nyc-area-digs-out-wrath-for-murphy-s-storm-flub-in-jersey</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECvAnYf1ELLTtzGi7LlmfEMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4uzwCjCF3bsCMK3JrwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-16/as-nyc-area-digs-out-wrath-for-murphy-s-storm-flub-in-jersey" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Governor Murphy Criticized for Storm Response&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Bloomberg&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spillover from early New York City-area snow led to a second-straight commuting horror Friday for New Jersey mass-transit riders as some lawmakers called for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.bloomberg.com">Bloomberg</source></item><item><title>Rhode Island governor becomes chair of Democratic group - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/b11486ea25aa4828ae96c628d1f83433</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIA1It1oaLpgUc32Yrjmv4MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 15:42:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/b11486ea25aa4828ae96c628d1f83433" target="_blank"&gt;Rhode Island governor becomes chair of Democratic group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Weeks after an election that boosted its membership, the Democratic Governors Association selected Rhode Island Gov. Gina Raimondo as its new chairwoman on Saturday. She was elected by her peers during the group's annual meeting in New Orleans, taking over for Washington Gov. Jay Inslee. New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy was elected vice-chair, putting him in line to lead the group in 2020, the next presidential election year. In November's midterm elections, Democrats flipped seven seats to their control without losing any governor's offices currently held by the party. Raimon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Natural disasters will be a priority for incoming governors - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/75437c1f0aef4cd680f89ff323864fa6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFp3NrwTJfgCpGuHuHj8eVYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 20:17:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/75437c1f0aef4cd680f89ff323864fa6" target="_blank"&gt;Natural disasters will be a priority for incoming governors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governors have a wide range of priorities they want to tackle in the coming year, from tax reform to education. Yet it's a topic that receives less attention on the campaign trail and in their speeches that could determine their success — natural disasters. In the last two years alone, storms and natural disasters have killed scores of people, damaged or destroyed tens of thousands of homes and cost tens of billions of dollars. Wildfires in the West and hurricanes in the South have been especially destructive, and scientists say climate change is making this more common. As the severity esc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trains, Not Drains: New Jersey Lobbyists Set to Swamp DC - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/new-jersey-lobbyists/3727410.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEId51ycSRXAY3nAKLxe8l8QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 17:42:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/new-jersey-lobbyists/3727410.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trains, Not Drains: New Jersey Lobbyists Set to Swamp DC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As President Donald Trump vows to "drain the swamp" in Washington, a swarm of 1,000 lobbyists, business owners and politicians are boarding a train from the swamps of New Jersey on Thursday for a day of lobbying. The state Chamber of Commerce's 80th annual trip — nicknamed the "Walk to Washington" because rail riders generally pace the train's corridors schmoozing and handing out business cards — comes after a national election that hinged in part on repudiating insiders and establishment politics. Trump, whose job approval rating is in negative territory, rose to victory in part on a promi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The 'Single Most Important Race' You've Barely Heard Of Kicks Off Next Week - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-gubernatorial-race_us_592f265be4b09ec37c31639c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB6koGbAG_4h-BIhybfOq94qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 22:35:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-gubernatorial-race_us_592f265be4b09ec37c31639c" target="_blank"&gt;The 'Single Most Important Race' You've Barely Heard Of Kicks Off Next Week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― Next week, voters in New Jersey will begin the process of choosing a new governor, an election that former Vice President Joe Biden recently called the “single most important race in the country.” Yet barely anyone outside of the state is paying attention. One would think the race to replace Chris Christie, the most unpopular governor in the nation and a favorite Democratic boogeyman, would draw more interest. Democrats have their best opportunity this year to flip a seat from red to blue, a move that would bolster the Donald Trump resistance and give the party unified control ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Murphy, Guadagno projected winners of New Jersey gubernatorial primary - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/06/politics/new-jersey-governor-primary/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEzL45OarlGiGnzHBLy7PswqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 02:08:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/06/politics/new-jersey-governor-primary/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Murphy, Guadagno projected winners of New Jersey gubernatorial primary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Goldman Sachs executive Phil Murphy and New Jersey Lt. Gov. Kim Guadagno have clinched the Democratic and Republican nominations, respectively, for New Jersey governor. The state's gubernatorial primary has been the subject of much less national attention than a spate of four special elections for House seats and next week's primary in the Virginia governor's race -- in part because polls in New Jersey have shown each party has a clear leading candidate to replace current Gov. Chris Christie. Murphy, a 59-year-old former US ambassador to Germany during President Barack Obama's admini...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>N.J. voters to pick candidates for governor to succeed Christie - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-new-jersey-election-governor-idUSKBN18X2I5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGLU8a74SY4yHmER8TpYh5sqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 18:44:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-new-jersey-election-governor-idUSKBN18X2I5" target="_blank"&gt;N.J. voters to pick candidates for governor to succeed Christie&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Peter Szekely NEW YORK (Reuters) - New Jersey voters went to the polls on Tuesday to choose their parties' nominees to succeed two-term Governor Chris Christie, a once-rising Republican star whose popularity has plummeted in recent years. Lieutenant Governor Kim Guadagno leads a pack of five Republican candidates in Tuesday's primary election, while Phil Murphy, a former Goldman Sachs Group Inc executive who served as U.S. ambassador to Germany under former President Barack Obama, is the front-runner among six Democrats. But the biggest challenge for candidates in either party may be dru...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Democrat Faces Criticism For Goldman Sachs Investment In Abusive Company On His Watch - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/phil-murphy-goldman-sachs-yue-yuen-investment_us_59332ee5e4b02478cb9c1c18</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOtk_HWIRRmcW8BCNTsue4AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 01:03:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/phil-murphy-goldman-sachs-yue-yuen-investment_us_59332ee5e4b02478cb9c1c18" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Democrat Faces Criticism For Goldman Sachs Investment In Abusive Company On His Watch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phil Murphy, the front-runner in New Jersey’s Democratic gubernatorial primary, faces new questions about his tenure at Wall Street giant Goldman Sachs with the election just days away. The campaign of attorney Jim Johnson, Murphy’s closest competitor in the race, criticized Murphy for serving as president of Goldman Sachs Asia at a time when the division profited from an investment in Yue Yuen Industrial, a Taiwan-based shoemaker. Human rights groups claim to have documented widespread labor abuses by Yue Yuen, including the company docking workers’ already modest pay for mistakes and runn...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Chris Christie Accuses Democrats Of Trying To 'Poison Our Kids' By Legalizing Marijuana - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/chris-christie-marijuana_us_5907b427e4b0bb2d0870a41d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENl652jyP5Iu1WSZNSFzXmcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 23:58:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/chris-christie-marijuana_us_5907b427e4b0bb2d0870a41d" target="_blank"&gt;Chris Christie Accuses Democrats Of Trying To 'Poison Our Kids' By Legalizing Marijuana&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie, a vocal critic of marijuana legalization, accused Democrats of attempting to “poison our kids” in pursuit of tax dollars from recreational cannabis sales. Speaking at a conference on substance abuse hosted by the New Jersey Hospital Association on Monday, the Republican governor criticized an effort by state lawmakers to regulate and tax recreational cannabis similarly to alcohol, as states like Colorado and Washington have done. Despite growing support across the nation for legalization, Christie remains firmly opposed to the idea, claiming pot is a gateway ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Phil Murphy And Kim Guadagno To Face Off In New Jersey Gubernatorial Election - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-governor-primary_us_5936ab37e4b0099e7faf1d5d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDsh_rwzwCT4WiAcRcaN8XgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 01:20:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-governor-primary_us_5936ab37e4b0099e7faf1d5d" target="_blank"&gt;Phil Murphy And Kim Guadagno To Face Off In New Jersey Gubernatorial Election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tuesday’s New Jersey primary results will pit Democrat Phil Murphy against Republican Lt. Gov. Kim Guadagno in the Nov. 7 election to succeed term-limited Republican Gov. Chris Christie. It is one of the first statewide contests since the 2016 election. Murphy, a former U.S. ambassador to Germany and onetime Goldman Sachs executive, defeated a slate of candidates in the Democratic primary, including former prosecutor and Treasury official Jim Johnson, state Assemblyman John Wisniewski, state Sen. Ray Lesniak, and activist and former firefighter Bill Brennan. Guadagno, who spent much of her ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Finger pointing, frustration in eastern US storm's aftermath - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/eb0260b7d233463396a02be653d764ae</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO0NVTGxXogogCeWnUFe2YIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 23:03:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/eb0260b7d233463396a02be653d764ae" target="_blank"&gt;Finger pointing, frustration in eastern US storm's aftermath&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — Exhausted commuters pointed fingers and demanded answers Friday, a day after a modest snowstorm stranded motorists on slippery roads for hours, paralyzed the public transit network serving New York City and its suburbs and even forced some New Jersey children to stay overnight in their schools. How, they asked, could a few inches of snow in a region used to this sort of weather lead to such chaos? "Clearly we could have done better and we will do better," New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy said. New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio promised a "full review." "We're all unhappy wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Facing long Senate odds, Democrats must first secure New Jersey - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-new-jersey/facing-long-senate-odds-democrats-must-first-secure-new-jersey-idUSKCN1NA16D</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAo8qml3YwiL5h8llzW0cXwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 18:10:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-new-jersey/facing-long-senate-odds-democrats-must-first-secure-new-jersey-idUSKCN1NA16D" target="_blank"&gt;Facing long Senate odds, Democrats must first secure New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Democrats, Tuesday's New Jersey U.S. Senate election should have been a breeze. Bob Menendez, 64, has held the seat for more than a decade in a state that has not elected a Republican to the U.S. Senate in 46 years. But June's Democratic nominating contest exposed his potential weakness following his federal corruption trial last year: 40 percent voted for a virtually unknown challenger who spent zero dollars in the race. Menendez is locked in a tough and expensive race with a Republican who has hammered Menendez as unethical, former pharmaceutical executive Bob Hugin, also 64. Top Demo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Jersey viral outbreak leaves six young patients dead, 12 others ill - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-new-jersey-health/new-jersey-viral-outbreak-leaves-six-young-patients-dead-12-others-ill-idUSKCN1MX2WL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOsZWi3bih4RSCZafLt_ZmQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 07:17:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-new-jersey-health/new-jersey-viral-outbreak-leaves-six-young-patients-dead-12-others-ill-idUSKCN1MX2WL" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey viral outbreak leaves six young patients dead, 12 others ill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six young patients died and 12 others became sick following an outbreak of adenovirus at a rehabilitation center in Haskell, New Jersey, the state's Health Department said on Tuesday. Adenoviruses frequently cause mild illness, with cold-like symptoms, particularly in young children. But the children affected in this case have compromised immune systems, the health department said. The 18 patients range in age from a toddler through young adulthood and most are under 18 years old, health department spokeswoman Nicole Kirgan said in an email. The department is not releasing exact ages of any...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Governor Calls for Sheriff to Resign After Alleged Racist Remarks - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/new-jersey-governor-calls-for-sheriff-to-resign-after-alleged-racist-remarks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDloAH4Xh6PYbATYRgDEe8UqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 01:04:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/new-jersey-governor-calls-for-sheriff-to-resign-after-alleged-racist-remarks" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Governor Calls for Sheriff to Resign After Alleged Racist Remarks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lucas Jackson/Reuters, New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy called on Bergen County Sheriff Michael Saudino to resign Thursday after he was reportedly caught on tape making racist remarks about African-Americans and the state’s Sikh attorney general. WABC reports that Saudino criticized Murphy’s inauguration speech in the recording, saying certain reforms Murphy mentioned would cater to the black community and “tie the hands of cops.” “He talked about the whole thing, the marijuana, sanctuary state... better criminal justice reform,” Saudino reportedly said. “Christ Almighty, in other words, let the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>New Jersey sheriff steps down after uproar over racist remarks - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/22/us/nj-sheriff-resign-remarks/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEaPQLJZKBCgDOLNcFK-ylcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 19:53:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/22/us/nj-sheriff-resign-remarks/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey sheriff steps down after uproar over racist remarks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sheriff of New Jersey's most populous county has resigned after an outcry over racist remarks he made about black people andthe state's attorney general, who is a Sikh. Bergen County Michael Saudino and four undersheriffs resigned Friday. Gov. Phil Murphy said he will be choosing an interim sheriff for the northern New Jersey county of nearly 1 million residents. The furor erupted this week after radio station WNYC posted audio clips of the sheriff's remarks from a January discussionfollowing Murphy's inauguration. The station said it obtained a secret recording of the remarks. Sound bi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy Calls On Sheriff To Resign After Racist Remarks Caught On Tape - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-sheriff-racist-tape-report_us_5ba3e520e4b0181540db4913</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4uHS2tU2wCQAHAr1guj9kqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 20:59:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-sheriff-racist-tape-report_us_5ba3e520e4b0181540db4913" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy Calls On Sheriff To Resign After Racist Remarks Caught On Tape&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy said Thursday that Bergen County Sheriff Michael Saudino should resign if an explosive WNYC report is true and it was Saudino’s voice caught on tape making racist remarks. The New York City radio station reported earlier Thursday that Saudino was secretly recorded making racist comments about black people and the state’s Sikh attorney general during a January conversation about the new governor’s agenda. The source who gave WNYC the tape claims it took place in a county office building and asked to remain anonymous for “fear of backlash.” The sheriff can allegedl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Sheriff Who Was Caught Making Racist Remarks Resigns - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/michael-saudino-new-jersey-racist-sheriff_us_5ba54514e4b0181540dcd98a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOltPtWf3MLVXAObnqjW0z0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 20:52:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/michael-saudino-new-jersey-racist-sheriff_us_5ba54514e4b0181540dcd98a" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Sheriff Who Was Caught Making Racist Remarks Resigns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A New Jersey sheriff has resigned after he was caught on tape making racist remarks, including claiming that legalized marijuana would “let the blacks come in.” Bergen County Sheriff Michael Saudino faced a call to resign from New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy (D) on Thursday after Saudino admitted it was his voice on a recording made in January, after Murphy indicated his support for legalizing marijuana in his inaugural address. “He talked about the whole thing, the marijuana, sanctuary state... better criminal justice reform,” Saudino is heard saying of Murphy. “Christ almighty, in other words...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>No instant end to New Jersey's takeover of Atlantic City - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/04314ac531694e5799723fe1f563a46f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAmFcmV7fB_tM_NRQUXYfAUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 19:48:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/04314ac531694e5799723fe1f563a46f" target="_blank"&gt;No instant end to New Jersey's takeover of Atlantic City&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. (AP) — Democrat Phil Murphy campaigned for governor of New Jersey in part on a promise to end the state takeover of Atlantic City, the cash-strapped seaside gambling resort whose assets and major decision-making power were seized by his Republican predecessor, Chris Christie. But after nearly nine months in office, Murphy is leaving the takeover in place, possibly for as long as the next three years — the entire term Christie intended. Murphy's administration released a plan for helping Atlantic City get back on its feet that involved numerous study groups, task forces a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Radio hosts facing heat for 'turban man' comments - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/6b4b6845a90e48deaea70dff81e43090</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIDDWoaTpWH1bMQBBkE3d3IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 02:32:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/6b4b6845a90e48deaea70dff81e43090" target="_blank"&gt;Radio hosts facing heat for 'turban man' comments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — Two New Jersey radio hosts are receiving heavy criticism for repeatedly referring to the state's attorney general as "turban man" on air. The Record reports WKXW-FM hosts Dennis Malloy and Judi Franco made the comments Wednesday while discussing Gurbir Grewal's recent order to suspend marijuana prosecutions in the state. Grewal is the country's first Sikh-American attorney general. Malloy and Franco acknowledged their words might be offensive, but Malloy said "if that offends you then don't wear the turban and maybe I'll remember your name." Neither host has responded t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Radio hosts suspended for slur against Sikh attorney general - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/5d8f58fc9ac54493a6bbd6aa5eddc59b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMqgQwFhiUIOL5dU3QIcy0YqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 21:21:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/5d8f58fc9ac54493a6bbd6aa5eddc59b" target="_blank"&gt;Radio hosts suspended for slur against Sikh attorney general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hosts of a popular New Jersey radio show were suspended for 10 days Thursday for calling the nation's first Sikh attorney general "turban man" — the latest slur against a career prosecutor who says he faces countless "small indignities and humiliations" no matter how far he rises or how important his position. WKXW-FM hosts Dennis Malloy and Judi Franco issued a written apology to Attorney General Gurbir Grewal and the Sikh and East Asian communities, writing they were "deeply sorry" for the pain they caused. The station also apologized and suspended the pair without pay until Aug. 6. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>New Jersey radio hosts suspended for calling attorney general 'turban man' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jul/26/dennis-malloy-judi-franco-turban-man-new-jersey-radio-hosts-suspended</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDtDpqAHhaVpVcPriw2vkEIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 15:47:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jul/26/dennis-malloy-judi-franco-turban-man-new-jersey-radio-hosts-suspended" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey radio hosts suspended for calling attorney general 'turban man'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two New Jersey radio hosts have been suspended after repeatedly describing the state’s attorney general, a practicing Sikh, as “turban man” and “the guy who wears a turban” on the air. WKXW hosts Dennis Malloy and Judi Franco made the comments on Wednesday while discussing Gurbir Grewal’s recent order to temporarily suspend marijuana prosecutions in the state. Grewal is the first Sikh attorney general in US history. Malloy wondered aloud: “Is that highly offensive?” Franco responded: “To me? No. To people who wear turbans? Could be.” Related: New Jersey police officer caught on video saving...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>New Jersey will stop prosecuting marijuana cases, for now - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/25/us/new-jersey-marijuana-prosecution/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHe5mR4T1LY4oDeHOZGZYsQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 18:51:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/25/us/new-jersey-marijuana-prosecution/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey will stop prosecuting marijuana cases, for now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey's top law enforcement official has instructed prosecutors statewide to hold off on pursuing convictions for marijuana-related crimes until the fall. The guidance, issued by New Jersey Attorney General Gurbir Singh Grewal in a memo to local prosecutors, comes as Grewal's office prepares to establish a working group to study local authority in matters of marijuana decriminalization. "I ask that all municipal prosecutors in New Jersey seek an adjournment until September 4, 2018, or later, of any matter involving a marijuana-related offense pending in municipal court," Singh wrote. P...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Murphy: Sky Blue soccer woes 'unacceptable,' will be fixed - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/a1625dea61a042e0880228e63ec2db44</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMwe3lqTZiN6unXyzVHVs28qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 18:28:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/a1625dea61a042e0880228e63ec2db44" target="_blank"&gt;Murphy: Sky Blue soccer woes 'unacceptable,' will be fixed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONG BRANCH, N.J. (AP) — New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy says reports of bleak living and working conditions for members of the women's soccer team he co-owns are "unacceptable" and will be fixed. The Democratic governor says Friday he takes seriously published reports outlining shortcomings with Sky Blue FC. Murphy says the buck stops with him, and promised to address complaints lodged by former players and others. Complaints include players living in ramshackle housing , playing in facilities without showers and practicing in dirty clothes because of a lack of laundry service. Murphy owns the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>New Jersey poised to invest $5 million into local journalism - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2018/07/03/media/new-jersey-civic-info-bill/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZdgm1HfksQ2Qvf33tcfZwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 16:48:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2018/07/03/media/new-jersey-civic-info-bill/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey poised to invest $5 million into local journalism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What if every state in the union provided some seed money for local journalism -- as a way to rebuild some of what's been lost through years of budget cuts and layoffs? That's what New Jersey is on the verge of doing. Public media advocates are calling it a historic legislative victory. Last month, both houses of the New Jersey legislature passed the "Civic Info Bill." The bill sets up a nonprofit group that will be supported by five of the state's universities. A board of directors will approve grants to strengthen local news coverage. New Jersey governor Phil Murphy signed a state budget ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Gov. Signs Bills Giving Transgender Residents More Rights - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-gov-signs-bills-transgender-rights_us_5b3cbee9e4b09e4a8b291569</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6eZFltaCAmsGY5ZfoRSqoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 13:51:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-gov-signs-bills-transgender-rights_us_5b3cbee9e4b09e4a8b291569" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Gov. Signs Bills Giving Transgender Residents More Rights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy (D) signed three bills into law on Tuesday that offer more rights and protections for the LGBTQ community. The first two measures, SB478 and SB493, allow birth and death certificates for transgender residents to be amended to reflect their gender identity. People may identify themselves as female, male or undesignated. Previously, transgender or genderqueer residents had to undergo gender confirmation surgery and obtain proof from their doctor to update their birth certificate. The third bill, SB705, establishes the Transgender Equality Task Force, which will ens...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>New Jersey averts government shutdown with last-minute budget - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-new-jersey-budget/new-jersey-averts-government-shutdown-with-last-minute-budget-idUSKBN1JR12L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKdRlzDk9VnFWC4sidi3Zp0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 01:38:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-new-jersey-budget/new-jersey-averts-government-shutdown-with-last-minute-budget-idUSKBN1JR12L" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey averts government shutdown with last-minute budget&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Hilary Russ NEW YORK (Reuters) - New Jersey Governor Phil Murphy struck a last-minute budget deal on Saturday, ending threats of a government shutdown that had raged for weeks as he struggled to reach an accord with members of his own party. It was the state's first budget deal in eight years with a Democrat at the helm, instead of Republican firebrand and one-time presidential hopeful Chris Christie. Nonetheless, Murphy spent months disagreeing with the Democrat-run legislature over which taxes to hike and by how much. Threats of a shutdown had raged for weeks. If the state government c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>US Governors Pull National Guard Over Immigration Policy - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-governors-pull-national-guard-over-immigration-policy/4446441.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECwWw7uigsO_eGNUrW0ZJs0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 01:11:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-governors-pull-national-guard-over-immigration-policy/4446441.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Governors Pull National Guard Over Immigration Policy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The governors of multiple East Coast states have announced that they will not deploy National Guard resources near the U.S.-Mexico border, a largely symbolic but politically significant rejection of the Trump administration's "zero-tolerance" immigration policy that has resulted in children being separated from their families. Maryland Governor Larry Hogan, a Republican, announced Tuesday morning on his Twitter account that he has ordered four crew members and a helicopter to immediately return from where they were stationed in New Mexico. FILE - Maryland Gov. Larry Hogan speaks at a lunche...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Is Now The United States' Hottest Clean Energy Economy - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/energyinnovation/2018/06/18/new-jersey-is-now-the-united-states-hottest-clean-energy-economy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFIqd0EMDQ1jcDNBnog06-8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/energyinnovation/2018/06/18/new-jersey-is-now-the-united-states-hottest-clean-energy-economy/" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Is Now The United States' Hottest Clean Energy Economy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Governor Murphy recently signed a landmark clean energy bill into law, New Jersey reclaimed the national policy leadership it abdicated during years of stagnation under the Christie Administration, and jump-started the state’s clean energy economy. The state is now a member of the exclusive “50×30” club that includes New York, Hawaii, California, and Vermont as the only states requiring 50% renewable energy by 2030 (Colorado and Iowa may reach that mark through voluntary utility leadership). New Jersey now has America’s most ambitious offshore wind and energy storage targets , and Gove...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>As Sports Betting Launches in New Jersey, Can Sports Books Remain Competitive With 8 Percent Tax? - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattrybaltowski/2018/06/14/as-sports-betting-launches-in-new-jersey-can-sports-books-remain-competitive-with-8-percent-tax/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENPiTZa0EQ13IGbbOwzrwy4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattrybaltowski/2018/06/14/as-sports-betting-launches-in-new-jersey-can-sports-books-remain-competitive-with-8-percent-tax/" target="_blank"&gt;As Sports Betting Launches in New Jersey, Can Sports Books Remain Competitive With 8 Percent Tax?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey governor Phil Murphy placed a sports wager at Monmouth Park June 14, the first legal sports bet in state history. It came days after Murphy signed a bill allowing sports betting at casinos and racetracks in N.J. (Photo by Dominick Reuter/Getty Images) When Monmouth Park began accepting sports bets on Thursday for the first time in the 118-year history of the track, New Jersey governor Phil Murphy stood at the front of the line. Murphy, who took office in January, placed the first legal sports wagers in state history — a $20 bet on the New Jersey Devils to win the 2019 Stanley Cup...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Murphy places state's first legal sports bets - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/cf1ce7c53db24a41be99416112c9f7ca</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMjBeFyaaj6Zi6xPKAz7S4oqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 14:50:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/cf1ce7c53db24a41be99416112c9f7ca" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Murphy places state's first legal sports bets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OCEANPORT, N.J. (AP) — The Latest on the start of legal sports betting in New Jersey (all times local): 10:45 a.m. New Jersey has launched sports betting. Democratic Gov. Phil Murphy kicked off a new era of gambling in the state, making the first official bets on Thursday morning at Monmouth Park, a racetrack near the Jersey shore. He placed two $20 bets — one on Germany to win soccer's World Cup and another on the New Jersey Devils to win next year's Stanley Cup. New Jersey won a U.S. Supreme Court case last month that cleared the way for all 50 states to offer sports betting should they c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Chris Christie and the state of New Jersey sued for release of Jared Kushner correspondence - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40585111/chris-christie-and-the-state-of-new-jersey-sued-for-release-of-jared-kushner-correspondence</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHVYnTra-qunVyJnsGgnLjQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 09:30:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/40585111/chris-christie-and-the-state-of-new-jersey-sued-for-release-of-jared-kushner-correspondence" target="_blank"&gt;Chris Christie and the state of New Jersey sued for release of Jared Kushner correspondence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MapLight is a nonprofit organization that reveals the influence of money in politics. MapLight, a California-based campaign finance watchdog, filed a lawsuit today to force New Jersey officials to release copies of correspondence between former Gov. Chris Christie’s office and senior White House adviser Jared Kushner. The lawsuit was filed in New Jersey Superior Court in the wake of a decision by Democratic Gov. Phil Murphy’s administration that would allow Christie to veto the release of public records. Christie–now a private citizen–issued a letter during his last week in office that orde...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>New Jersey's Tough Gun Laws Just Got Even Stronger - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-gun-laws_us_5b203d57e4b0bbb7a0e2849b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAZY0vM-vViBMc_Lbxml_xQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 18:52:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-gun-laws_us_5b203d57e4b0bbb7a0e2849b" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey's Tough Gun Laws Just Got Even Stronger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey gun laws, long considered among the nation’s strongest, became even stronger on Wednesday, with the governor’s signature on a package of firearms legislation. Among the six bills are measures to expand gun background checks, tighten the handgun carrying permit process, reduce the legal capacity of ammunition magazines and establish a so-called red flag law, which allows people to petition for guns to be temporarily removed from individuals deemed to be dangerous. At a bill signing ceremony in Trenton, New Jersey, Gov. Phil Murphy (D) commended lawmakers and advocates for their wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>New Jersey governor's signature paves way for sports betting - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-betting-new-jersey/new-jersey-governors-signature-paves-way-for-sports-betting-idUSKBN1J72E8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGn-oBTMHUctduB9h4e6ny8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 20:23:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-betting-new-jersey/new-jersey-governors-signature-paves-way-for-sports-betting-idUSKBN1J72E8" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey governor's signature paves way for sports betting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Hilary Russ (Reuters) - New Jersey Governor Phil Murphy on Monday signed a bill to legalize sports betting, opening the door for the state to begin regulating and taxing the activity at casinos and racetracks. "Our casinos in Atlantic City and our racetracks throughout our state can attract new business and new fans, boosting their own long-term financial prospects," Murphy said in a statement. "This is the right move for New Jersey and it will strengthen our economy." Monmouth Park Racetrack, where the U.S. unit of U.K.-based William Hill PLC has already built a sports book, expects to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Advice To New Jersey, The Garden State, As It Expands Its Cannabis Market - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/julieweed/2018/05/25/advice-to-new-jersey-the-garden-state-as-it-expands-its-cannabis-market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM6vmB3Hm4buw9yKzqB1AXoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 13:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/julieweed/2018/05/25/advice-to-new-jersey-the-garden-state-as-it-expands-its-cannabis-market/" target="_blank"&gt;Advice To New Jersey, The Garden State, As It Expands Its Cannabis Market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey Governor Phil Murphy is fighting to legalize recreational marijuana in his state, and while the reaction from his legislators has been decidedly mixed, the number of New Jerseyans in favor of legalization is on the rise. Thirty states including New Jersey have legalized medical marijuana and eight of those have legalized recreational adult use, so the Governor has examples to look to. Cannabis entrepreneurs across the country are watching the garden state’s industry unfold and have some advice to share. Harmony Dispensary, Secaucus, NJ Medical use in New Jersey was legalized in 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>New Jersey OKs $300M annually to rescue nuclear industry - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/c962c3f0ab7646f9949330d8236205fd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOLxBYCsJtiwgfYlNTWymh8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 17:46:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/c962c3f0ab7646f9949330d8236205fd" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey OKs $300M annually to rescue nuclear industry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOUTH BRUNSWICK, N.J. (AP) — Legislation that would authorize $300 million annually to rescue New Jersey's nuclear energy industry — a request for financial help made by the state's largest utility company — was signed into law Wednesday. Democratic Gov. Phil Murphy alongside lawmakers at a solar array in central New Jersey also signed a measure aimed at strengthening the state's renewable energy goals. The nuclear measure will be funded by ratepayers; the cost of the renewable energy legislation is unclear. The nuclear legislation stems from a request from Public Service Enterprise Group f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Study: Some public pensions funds could run dry in downturn - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f1f873f4e73e4d429bf4012b6d1f6fd4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGuu3Vt7K2HoM_YW8iEDB0QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 23:07:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f1f873f4e73e4d429bf4012b6d1f6fd4" target="_blank"&gt;Study: Some public pensions funds could run dry in downturn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHERRY HILL, N.J. (AP) — Many pension funds for public workers already owe far more in retirement benefits than they have in the bank, and the problem will only grow worse if the economy slows down, according to a report released Thursday. The study from The Pew Charitable Trusts found that the New Jersey and Kentucky funds are in such perilous shape that they risk running dry. "Even after eight years of economic recovery — eight straight years of stock market gains — the public pension plans are more vulnerable than they've ever been to the next recession," researcher Greg Mennis said in a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Crews move school bus wrecked in deadly crash - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/ca153cdeaf39458697201283eba57e47</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMm7nSb-p5b-HHtLUNbMjpsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:29:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/ca153cdeaf39458697201283eba57e47" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Crews move school bus wrecked in deadly crash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOUNT OLIVE, N.J. (AP) — The Latest on a school bus crash with a dump truck in New Jersey (all times local): 8:25 p.m. Cleanup crews have moved the wreckage of a school bus that collided with a dump truck on a New Jersey highway, killing a student and a teacher. The yellow school bus was carrying 38 students and seven adults when it crashed on Thursday, leaving it lying on the median of Interstate 80 in Mount Olive with its front end sheared off and its steering wheel exposed. Crews loaded the wrecked bus onto a flat-bed truck on Thursday night. The Paramus (puh-RAM'-uhs) school district sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Student, teacher killed in NJ school bus crash - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/05/17/student-teacher-killed-in-nj-school-bus?videoId=427857995</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHf_Elc8LpYugK0v2TlBsVgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 21:16:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/05/17/student-teacher-killed-in-nj-school-bus?videoId=427857995" target="_blank"&gt;Student, teacher killed in NJ school bus crash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey Governor Phil Murphy says one adult and one student were killed when a school bus collided with a dump truck on a highway in New Jersey on Thursday. Rough Cut (no reporter narration).&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Quick release of gun data called trailblazing and troubling - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/2b91456c75b24c899a1e3aad0d7a6790</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECX8dg14lOa8HA_ipIe8gY0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 13:09:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/2b91456c75b24c899a1e3aad0d7a6790" target="_blank"&gt;Quick release of gun data called trailblazing and troubling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — Gun control advocates are hailing New Jersey's release of near-real-time firearms trafficking data as a trailblazing use of federal information. But Second Amendment advocates and skeptical Republicans question whether the report amounts to a way around a federal limitation on the release of some data. Democratic Gov. Phil Murphy unveiled the data for the first time on Tuesday as part of a campaign promise to strengthen New Jersey's already-tight gun laws. The report uses Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives gun-trace data for the first quarter of 2018 an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>No longer a haze: New Jersey governor says he tried pot - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/13d9044cc1e94febb22e39701e26da77</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFNl1N7vGyLDnn5s2bfpbTsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 20:01:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/13d9044cc1e94febb22e39701e26da77" target="_blank"&gt;No longer a haze: New Jersey governor says he tried pot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy has lifted the haze over whether he's ever used marijuana. He says he has, but just "once or twice." The 60-year-old Democratic governor is pushing for the legalization of recreational marijuana and was questioned on Wednesday about whether he had ever taken a toke. He answered by saying, "I've never been a marijuana guy," but didn't say whether he'd ever tried it. Murphy's response created a bit of buzz in the state that didn't mellow out until Murphy took to Twitter to more directly answer the question on Thursday. "Here's the deal: I've tr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>New Jersey workers can now get sick and get paid - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/5e5f9a4338a6414880bd07873799ba7e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEMUv2A7znCQZUCB-8t6vjoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 19:06:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/5e5f9a4338a6414880bd07873799ba7e" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey workers can now get sick and get paid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — Safiyyah Muhammad once felt that her job as a cashier was threatened when she informed her boss she had a sick child and wanted to miss work. Now Muhammad and an estimated 1.2 million others can exhale after New Jersey enacted a law requiring employers to offer workers paid sick leave. New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy signed the bill Wednesday in Trenton at the War Memorial theater alongside lawmakers, first lady Tammy Murphy and Muhammad, a mother and grandmother. "This law demonstrates a responsible, holistic inclusive approach to building and improving the great state of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Saving New Jersey's Nuclear Plants Came At A Hefty Price - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/energysource/2018/04/12/saving-new-jerseys-nuclear-plants-came-at-a-hefty-price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBO2btdduc3kB1NCNP-bwfYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 01:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/energysource/2018/04/12/saving-new-jerseys-nuclear-plants-came-at-a-hefty-price/" target="_blank"&gt;Saving New Jersey's Nuclear Plants Came At A Hefty Price&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Hope Creek Nuclear Generating Station and cooling tower seen in the distance behind a farmhouse in Lower Alloways Township, New Jersey. (STAN HONDA/AFP/Getty Images) New Jersey’s passage Thursday of legislation to prevent the premature closure of the state’s nuclear plants is another crucial victory to save America’s largest source of clean energy. Climate and environmental scientists organized by Environmental Progress urged New Jersey’s Governor Philip Murphy to pass the legislation, and I testified in support of the legislation last December. But the legislation’s passage came at a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>New Jersey's Liberal New Governor Is The Anti-Chris Christie - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-governor-phil-murphy-not-christie_us_5aa9923ee4b0004c0406ee63</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDi7Os1kQQAFtP466jDPadQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 13:54:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-governor-phil-murphy-not-christie_us_5aa9923ee4b0004c0406ee63" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey's Liberal New Governor Is The Anti-Chris Christie&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRENTON, N.J. ― New Jersey politics is a lot of things, but one thing it’s not is boring. There are the brusque, larger-than-life personalities; the shady real estate developers; the Godzilla vs. Megalon-level slugfests between entrenched interest groups; the random agencies whose existence you only learned about after indictments were unsealed (we’re looking at you, Passaic Valley Sewerage Commission); more shady real estate developers; and enough windbreaker-clad federal agents hauling boxes out of offices in cheerless strip malls to fill MetLife Stadium. And for most of the past decade, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Fiscal mess, tax hikes likely for New Jersey governor's first budget - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-new-jersey-budget/fiscal-mess-tax-hikes-likely-for-new-jersey-governors-first-budget-idUSKCN1GO2PZ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENvUSWc7RdFrqGCg38A2-TMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 21:41:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-new-jersey-budget/fiscal-mess-tax-hikes-likely-for-new-jersey-governors-first-budget-idUSKCN1GO2PZ" target="_blank"&gt;Fiscal mess, tax hikes likely for New Jersey governor's first budget&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Hilary Russ NEW YORK (Reuters) - New Jersey Governor Phil Murphy is expected to unveil tax hikes for businesses or millionaires and the green light for marijuana sales when he proposes his first state budget on Tuesday. But the state is still mired in fiscal problems left over from Republican Chris Christie's eight contentious years as governor, and the new Democrat governor's planned tax rises may not be enough to pay for the bold initiatives he will need to distinguish his new governorship. "The great cocktail party discussion in Trenton these days is - what's the budget going to look ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Democrats Offering Bill to Allow Prisoners To Vote - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-prisoners-to-vote_us_5a942b9be4b01f65f598c58e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYHbTL8Mi6ew6Ye5kYINJgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 18:01:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-jersey-prisoners-to-vote_us_5a942b9be4b01f65f598c58e" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Democrats Offering Bill to Allow Prisoners To Vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Jersey Democrats proposed legislation on Monday that would allow people to vote while they are in prison, a move that could expand the franchise to about 100,000 people in the state. New Jersey, like several other states, does not allow felons to vote after their conviction, including while they are on parole or probation. If the bill becomes law, New Jersey would join just two other states ― Maine and Vermont ― in allowing any felon, including murderers, to vote while they are in jail and after they have been released. The bill would allow prisoners to vote by mail-in ballot in the dis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Republican Governors Outpace Trump on Guns - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/republican-governors-outpace-trump-on-guns</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENHoXicBeSrm-JanYmIzQ-UqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 10:05:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/republican-governors-outpace-trump-on-guns" target="_blank"&gt;Republican Governors Outpace Trump on Guns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast After yet another confusing week of Twitter tirades, no one knows what, if any, changes to the nation’s gun laws President Donald Trump would actually support. But the lack of clear leadership from the top of the GOP isn’t stopping the momentum that seems to be building at the state level to re-examine the nation’s disparate gun laws—and this time, it’s not just Democrats leading the charge. Over the weekend, the majority of America’s governors descended on the nation’s swampy Capitol and gun control was on the top of many of their minds—lending an unus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Democrats eye decade-altering wins in governors' races - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/25/politics/governors-battlegrounds-2018-midterms/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKK3pkPyCdjzjfKnS16a0-0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 23:05:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/25/politics/governors-battlegrounds-2018-midterms/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Democrats eye decade-altering wins in governors' races&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Democrats, this year's governors' races present a once-in-a-decade opening. This year features 36 gubernatorial contests -- including 23 in Republican-held states -- starting in less than a month with the primary in Illinois to determine who will take on GOP Gov. Bruce Rauner, perhaps the nation's most vulnerable incumbent. It's the opposite of this year's Senate map, where Democrats are defending 10 seats in states President Donald Trump won in 2016. What's at stake in many of these races is an opportunity to have a direct hand in the congressional map-making process after the 2020 Cen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Governor wants states to form gun control coalition after lack of action by US Congress - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/phil-murphy-democrat-gun-control-legislation-new-jersey-trump-a8220126.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOjeKx2glZsBkBECSKYc1twqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/phil-murphy-democrat-gun-control-legislation-new-jersey-trump-a8220126.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Governor wants states to form gun control coalition after lack of action by US Congress&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democratic Governor Phil Murphy has said “we gotta die trying” to pass gun control laws, declaring he wants to form a coalition of like-minded governors to push for reform. Mr Murphy’s comments are part of a stream of rebellious moves by states to protest the policies of President Donald Trump. The fallout of last week’s mass shooting at a Florida high school has again demonstrated the divide between the US’s main political parties on gun control, with Republicans most offering their condolences while Democrats call for action. Armed with a legally purchased AR-15-style assault rifle, a gun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Democratic governors ready to take action on gun control - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/23/politics/governors-gun-control-coalition-new-day-cnntv/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJO07hjctH-RqFjHYjHJaQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 14:33:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/23/politics/governors-gun-control-coalition-new-day-cnntv/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Democratic governors ready to take action on gun control&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four Democratic governors from the Northeast have formed a coalition on gun control, saying they can't wait for Congress and the federal government to take action. Three of them appeared on CNN's "New Day" Friday morning to explain why. "We as governors are demanding action from the federal government and we need them to take action, but in the meantime, we've decided to take a regional approach," said Rhode Island Gov. Gina Raimondo. That approach includes "sharing information about guns across our state lines, sharing a database, and for the first time that I know of having a regional res...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>States band together to take action on gun violence - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/22/us/northeast-governors-gun-safety-coalition/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPw4ELNR662j1OXLgWo8cXEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 18:48:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/02/22/us/northeast-governors-gun-safety-coalition/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;States band together to take action on gun violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saying that states can't wait for the federal government to tighten gun control legislation, the governors of Connecticut, New Jersey, New York and Rhode Island announced the formation of a partnership to combat gun violence. The "States for Gun Safety Coalition" will initially only include the four neighboring states, but state leaders hope others will join the group in the future, the governors explained in a media conference call Thursday. New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo said he also hoped that in the aftermath of the massacre at Florida's Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School last week, the f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Federal prosecutors dismiss corruption charges against Senator Bob Menendez - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/feb/01/bob-menendez-federal-prosecutors-dismiss-corruption-charges</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKdNwipEPpKadZ-VjGCBAvYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:34:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/feb/01/bob-menendez-federal-prosecutors-dismiss-corruption-charges" target="_blank"&gt;Federal prosecutors dismiss corruption charges against Senator Bob Menendez&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal prosecutors decided on Wednesday not to retry Senator Bob Menendez on corruption charges that ended in a hung jury last fall, lifting the legal cloud hanging over the New Jersey Democrat as he gears up for re-election this year to the closely divided Senate. The move brings to an end a more than five-year investigation that began with never-substantiated allegations about consorting with prostitutes and eventually resulted in a bribery indictment. Menendez, 64, was charged with trading his political influence for gifts and campaign contributions from Florida eye doctor Salomon Melge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Stung by tax-law changes, Connecticut, New Jersey and New York plan to sue Washington - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stung-by-tax-law-changes-connecticut-new-jersey-and-new-york-plan-to-sue-washington-2018-01-26</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJdvII7mRcdlAOrD8FKZCwkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 19:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stung-by-tax-law-changes-connecticut-new-jersey-and-new-york-plan-to-sue-washington-2018-01-26" target="_blank"&gt;Stung by tax-law changes, Connecticut, New Jersey and New York plan to sue Washington&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Andrea Riquier It’s not just household finances that the states’ governors are worried about, but local housing markets and economies, too MarketWatch photo illustration/Getty Images Governors of three Northeastern states on Friday said they were forming a coalition to jointly sue the federal government over the recently passed tax-code changes, which they say unfairly target Democratic-leaning, higher-tax states by reducing the amount of state and local taxes residents can deduct on their federal returns. “This provision effectively pre-empts the states’ ability to govern by reducing th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>New York, New Jersey, Connecticut form coalition against tax bill - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-tax-states-coalition/new-york-new-jersey-connecticut-form-coalition-against-tax-bill-idUSKBN1FF273</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHh0PhOzkd6NA85r06n5rL0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 16:29:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-tax-states-coalition/new-york-new-jersey-connecticut-form-coalition-against-tax-bill-idUSKBN1FF273" target="_blank"&gt;New York, New Jersey, Connecticut form coalition against tax bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (Reuters) - The governors of New York, New Jersey and Connecticut said on Friday they are forming a multi-state coalition against a new federal tax bill and will file legal action challenging the constitutionality of the legislation signed in December. The bill unfairly impacts their states with its repeal of state and local tax deductibility, the first federal double taxation in U.S. history, the governors said during a call with reporters. New York Governor Andrew Cuomo said there were "very strong" arguments that the bill violates states' rights as well as the Equal Protection c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Judge narrows bribery case against New Jersey Democratic Senator Menendez - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-new-jersey-menendez/judge-narrows-bribery-case-against-new-jersey-democratic-senator-menendez-idUSKBN1FD355</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBsVpFQV1s_ICPxBSVQEz-oqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 22:19:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-new-jersey-menendez/judge-narrows-bribery-case-against-new-jersey-democratic-senator-menendez-idUSKBN1FD355" target="_blank"&gt;Judge narrows bribery case against New Jersey Democratic Senator Menendez&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Joseph Ax (Reuters) - A federal judge on Wednesday threw out several bribery charges against Democratic U.S. Senator Bob Menendez, five days after U.S. prosecutors announced they would seek to retry him after his first trial ended with a hung jury. The New Jersey politician, who is expected to run for reelection this year, is charged with accepting gifts, including luxury trips and campaign contributions, from wealthy ophthalmologist Salomon Melgen in exchange for official favors. U.S. District Judge William Walls, who presided over last year's corruption trial, said on Wednesday that pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>At the Women's March, New Jersey's First Lady shares her story of a sexual assault - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/01/22/us/new-jersey-first-lady-sexual-assault-trnd/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJt7M24hjjHeFxzHuN2Bo8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 17:38:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/01/22/us/new-jersey-first-lady-sexual-assault-trnd/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;At the Women's March, New Jersey's First Lady shares her story of a sexual assault&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the Women's March in New Jersey, the state's first lady Tammy Murphy shared something she'd kept private for decades "I was sexually assaulted," Murphy told the crowd in Morristown on Saturday. The attack took place when she was a sophomore at the University of Virginia, Murphy said. She was walking on campus one night to meet a group of friends, when a stranger pulled her into the bushes. "I was thrown on my back," she said. "I had a man on top of me. [He] pulled my shirt up, pulled my skirt up, and I started screaming." Murphy said there was a party going on "not more than six feet awa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Democratic administration faces challenges as Chris Christie era ends in New Jersey - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/democratic-administration-faces-challenges-as-chris-christie-era-ends-in-new-jersey-2018-01-16</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBsEriqosW6KgjVb3mdw6D8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 18:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/democratic-administration-faces-challenges-as-chris-christie-era-ends-in-new-jersey-2018-01-16" target="_blank"&gt;Democratic administration faces challenges as Chris Christie era ends in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WALL STREET JOURNAL By Kate King Outgoing New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie and his wife, Mary Pat, listen to the newly sworn-in governor, Phil Murphy, speaking after taking the oath of office Tuesday in Trenton, N.J. Reuters New Jersey Democrats are gearing up to take over Trenton but face a tight budget as they look to enact far-reaching policy changes. Phil Murphy took the oath of office to become governor on Tuesday, ending eight years of Republican control of the top office in the Garden State. But Murphy, a former Goldman Sachs executive, faces the tricky task of implementing his pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Christie ends term as first New Jersey governor to not break a leg in 25 years - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jan/17/chris-christie-leaves-nj-governors-office</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECufAiX34jNyEHkZnvaV7EoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 16:36:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jan/17/chris-christie-leaves-nj-governors-office" target="_blank"&gt;Christie ends term as first New Jersey governor to not break a leg in 25 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican Chris Christie left the New Jersey governor’s office with his popularity in tatters, but at least he didn’t break a leg. Christie is the first elected New Jersey governor in nearly 25 years to serve without breaking a leg. Christie’s predecessor, Jon Corzine, a Democrat, broke his leg during a serious vehicle accident on the Garden State Parkway in 2007. Related: 'You're a bum': Chris Christie battles with callers in sports radio host tryout Democrat Jim McGreevey broke his leg during a walk on the beach in Cape May in 2002. Christine Todd Whitman, a Republican, fractured her leg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Drunk droning now illegal in New Jersey - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-drones-drunken/drunk-droning-now-illegal-in-new-jersey-idUSKBN1F42OV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBSw2xbzwVBScI_MReJgmM0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 22:33:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-drones-drunken/drunk-droning-now-illegal-in-new-jersey-idUSKBN1F42OV" target="_blank"&gt;Drunk droning now illegal in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Reuters) - New Jersey Governor Chris Christie signed a law on Monday making it illegal to fly an unmanned drone aircraft after too many drinks, a spokesman said on the Republican's last day in office. The law prohibits flying a drone with a blood alcohol content of 0.08 percent or higher, the same as for driving a vehicle, or while drugged. Violators face up to six months in jail, a $1,000 fine or both. The measure, which passed the Democratic-controlled state legislature earlier this month, also bars flying a drone near a prison or in pursuit of wildlife. The drone measure was among 109 b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>