<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Caesarean section - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNR051T0djU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-SG&amp;gl=SG&amp;ceid=SG:en</link><language>en-SG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:58:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Doctors make man choose: Surgery to save wife or C-section to save baby - AsiaOne</title><link>http://www.asiaone.com/world/doctors-make-man-choose-surgery-save-wife-or-c-section-save-baby</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiXWh0dHA6Ly93d3cuYXNpYW9uZS5jb20vd29ybGQvZG9jdG9ycy1tYWtlLW1hbi1jaG9vc2Utc3VyZ2VyeS1zYXZlLXdpZmUtb3ItYy1zZWN0aW9uLXNhdmUtYmFiedIBqAFodHRwczovL3d3dy1hc2lhb25lLWNvbS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi93d3cuYXNpYW9uZS5jb20vd29ybGQvZG9jdG9ycy1tYWtlLW1hbi1jaG9vc2Utc3VyZ2VyeS1zYXZlLXdpZmUtb3ItYy1zZWN0aW9uLXNhdmUtYmFieT9hbXAmYW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:24:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.asiaone.com/world/doctors-make-man-choose-surgery-save-wife-or-c-section-save-baby" target="_blank"&gt;Doctors make man choose: Surgery to save wife or C-section to save baby&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;AsiaOne&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man in Colorado, United States recently went through great sorrow and joy in one day, as he welcomed a baby girl but lost his wife from childbirth. Frederick ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.asiaone.com">AsiaOne</source></item><item><title>Indian mother and newborn die in botched C-section delivery by drunken doctor - The Straits Times</title><link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/south-asia/indian-mother-and-newborn-die-in-botched-c-section-delivery-by-drunk-doctor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMieGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnN0cmFpdHN0aW1lcy5jb20vYXNpYS9zb3V0aC1hc2lhL2luZGlhbi1tb3RoZXItYW5kLW5ld2Jvcm4tZGllLWluLWJvdGNoZWQtYy1zZWN0aW9uLWRlbGl2ZXJ5LWJ5LWRydW5rLWRvY3RvctIBAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 04:57:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/south-asia/indian-mother-and-newborn-die-in-botched-c-section-delivery-by-drunk-doctor" target="_blank"&gt;Indian mother and newborn die in botched C-section delivery by drunken doctor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A doctor from the western Indian state of Gujarat was arrested on Tuesday (Nov 27) for allegedly performing a caesarean delivery on a 22-year-old woman while ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.straitstimes.com">The Straits Times</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/Yzzlq8olyqxo-zYlaq0W8oTOwyGvjwz8xLdT7q5XrCWZwBdULpRyauCWu1Es7x9nN39VTOjU4broZZ8Aw7GeHQ0GJVajNeo7rm7p2CTjk91-ncY7OC_XK-MKtE570N5Smys9Rs2JXmR1eWwFjZqAm4YwxLZViM2PNn0ZpMxkRYPDWOO1pAjln3KUf_c=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Elective caesareans tied to higher risk of overweight babies: Singapore study - Channel NewsAsia</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/singapore/elective-caesareans-c-section-risk-overweight-babies-singapore-10982812</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMidmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNoYW5uZWxuZXdzYXNpYS5jb20vbmV3cy9zaW5nYXBvcmUvZWxlY3RpdmUtY2Flc2FyZWFucy1jLXNlY3Rpb24tcmlzay1vdmVyd2VpZ2h0LWJhYmllcy1zaW5nYXBvcmUtMTA5ODI4MTLSAQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:45:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/singapore/elective-caesareans-c-section-risk-overweight-babies-singapore-10982812" target="_blank"&gt;Elective caesareans tied to higher risk of overweight babies: Singapore study&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Channel NewsAsia&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINGAPORE: Pregnant women who opt for surgical caesarean deliveries may be more likely than those who have vaginal deliveries to have a child that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.channelnewsasia.com">Channel NewsAsia</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/bHKEitou4n_L2hBjg7GghGMn748i4PBSRzCoHSkX1CaZNpNzIxS2Zn0LIawVTdgtMkA_5_kFufcTo0tp9wjLzgOSnUctuz1WNIkfLL2p-NV-YINl_ANcgwBh-CnrBcOuOno3DKveLRbY_wPfv9a8VQLuKueTPzZOjrJTONU2HHmdUPHi8Cut2M6TIJU=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>C-sections to be performed by healthcare assistants, report predicts - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/07/c-sections-performed-healthcare-assistants-report-predicts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBct0GPWVq8LxX_sPn_HtxwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/07/c-sections-performed-healthcare-assistants-report-predicts/" target="_blank"&gt;C-sections to be performed by healthcare assistants, report predicts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rise in robotic surgery could see caesarean sections performed by healthcare assistants rather than surgeons in five years time, medical leaders have said. A report by the Royal College of Surgeons predicts that healthcare assistants, who sit below nurses in the clinical pecking order, will be responsible for carrying out key parts of the major procedure undergone by roughly one in four mothers. Specialist obstetricians and surgeons will remain in charge, although they will not necessarily be present in the operating theatre all the time. The Future of Surgery report - the product of th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>World's first baby born via womb transplant from dead donor - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-womb-transplant/worlds-first-baby-born-via-womb-transplant-from-dead-donor-idUSKBN1O32WS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELN6LXT8NtRJjDbiXPEO5FQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMPT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:38:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-womb-transplant/worlds-first-baby-born-via-womb-transplant-from-dead-donor-idUSKBN1O32WS" target="_blank"&gt;World's first baby born via womb transplant from dead donor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman in Brazil who received a womb transplanted from a deceased donor has given birth to a baby girl in the first successful case of its kind, doctors reported. The case, published in The Lancet medical journal, involved connecting veins from the donor uterus with the recipient's veins, as well as linking arteries, ligaments and vaginal canals. It comes after 10 previously known cases of uterus transplants from deceased donors - in the United States, the Czech Republic and Turkey - failed to produce a live birth. The girl born in the Brazilian case was delivered via caesarean section at ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The live birth from a dead donor could change the definition of motherhood - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/live-birth-dead-donor-definition-motherhood-transplants-pregnancy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA7Ff-iP2bjGZJgddeBL_E0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/live-birth-dead-donor-definition-motherhood-transplants-pregnancy" target="_blank"&gt;The live birth from a dead donor could change the definition of motherhood&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A year ago, a baby girl was born by caesarean section in a hospital in São Paulo, Brazil, after being conceived by IVF. What made the birth unique was that the child had been gestated in a womb transplanted from a 45-year-old woman who had died. Births resulting from uterus transplants have been happening since 2014, but for all previous children conceived this way, the donor was alive. That, understandably, places severe limits on the availability of the organs. This demonstration, reported in the Lancet – that a uterus can be successfully preserved and transplanted from a deceased person ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Baby Girl Born After Womb Transplant - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/baby-girl-born-after-womb-transplant</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECyzZV0U8vPzZIgZCLpgBjEqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 08:05:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/baby-girl-born-after-womb-transplant" target="_blank"&gt;Baby Girl Born After Womb Transplant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FREDERICK FLORIN, A woman in Brazil has become the first to successfully give birth after receiving a womb transplant from a dead donor. Writing in The Lancet, the medical team say they removed a womb from a 45-year-old woman who had died from a burst blood vessel in the brain and who had previously given birth three times. The recipient was a 32-year-old woman who was born without a womb. Just over a month after the transplant, the woman’s periods started, and seven months after the operation the team transferred an embryo into her womb. The pregnancy went smoothly and a baby girl was deli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Woman gives birth using womb transplanted from dead donor - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/04/woman-gives-birth-using-womb-transplanted-from-dead-donor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdFWm_G0fGgEXMeL0_WuOsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 23:30:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/04/woman-gives-birth-using-womb-transplanted-from-dead-donor" target="_blank"&gt;Woman gives birth using womb transplanted from dead donor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman in Brazil has successfully given birth after receiving a womb from a dead donor, the first time such a procedure has been successful. While researchers in countries including Sweden and the US have previously succeeded in transplanting wombs from living donors into women who have gone on to give birth, experts said the latest development was a significant advance. “With a deceased donor, you reduce the risk because you don’t have the risk to the donor – and you reduce the costs, too, because you don’t have the hospitalisation and the very long surgery of the donor,” said Dr Dani Ejz...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Circle of life: World’s first baby ‘miraculously’ born using womb transplanted from dead woman - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445644-baby-born-womb-deceased/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZj-QmOsSgtaClnuoqlPcAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:06:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445644-baby-born-womb-deceased/" target="_blank"&gt;Circle of life: World’s first baby ‘miraculously’ born using womb transplanted from dead woman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A baby girl was born from the womb of a deceased woman in the Brazilian city of São Paulo, in a world-first which could bring hope to countless infertile women. The 32-year-old mum was born without a womb due to the rare Mayer-Rokitansky-Küster-Hauser syndrome, which doesn’t allow the vagina and uterus to form properly. Desperate for a child but with little hope of having one, the woman got a womb transplant from a 45-year-old mum-of-three who had died of a stroke. Au Brésil, première naissance issue d'une greffe de l'utérus d'une donneuse morte pic.twitter.com/2kak9El61h — BFMTV (@BFMTV) D...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>A woman born without a womb became a mother, thanks to a uterus transplant - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90277040/a-woman-born-without-a-womb-became-a-mother-thanks-to-a-uterus-transplant</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN2MPZx_jNj4iN3rDRpie-4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:43:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90277040/a-woman-born-without-a-womb-became-a-mother-thanks-to-a-uterus-transplant" target="_blank"&gt;A woman born without a womb became a mother, thanks to a uterus transplant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a medical first, a woman born without a womb was able to become a mother, thanks to an organ transplant from a deceased donor. While there have been 39 womb transplants using live donors—including mothers donating their wombs to their daughters, which have resulted in 11 babies—the success rate for wombs donated from deceased donors has been far less successful. Ten previous transplants from dead donors have either failed or resulted in miscarriage. This case, reported in The Lancet, is the first time a womb transplant via a deceased donor has led to the birth of a healthy baby. The tran...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Doctors claim world-first with baby born from dead donor's uterus - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-05/first-baby-born-using-uterus-transplanted-from-deceased-donor/10584288</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAEpPsMSvPiLweSL0oWM8KkqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-05/first-baby-born-using-uterus-transplanted-from-deceased-donor/10584288" target="_blank"&gt;Doctors claim world-first with baby born from dead donor's uterus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brazilian doctors are reporting the world's first baby born to a woman with a uterus transplanted from a deceased donor. Eleven previous births have used a transplanted womb but from a living donor, usually a relative or friend. The baby girl was delivered last December by a woman born without a uterus because of a rare syndrome. The woman — a 32-year-old psychologist — was initially apprehensive about the transplant, said Dr Dani Ejzenberg, the transplant team's lead doctor at the University of Sao Paulo School of Medicine. "This was the most important thing in her life," he said. "Now she...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>1st baby born using uterus transplanted from deceased donor - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/8264196b755d4b5490434467c81ee9f0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECfHMdXo0jZqRbymTGd6N9IqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6udAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 23:35:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/8264196b755d4b5490434467c81ee9f0" target="_blank"&gt;1st baby born using uterus transplanted from deceased donor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON (AP) — Brazilian doctors are reporting the world's first baby born to a woman with a uterus transplanted from a deceased donor. Eleven previous births have used a transplanted womb but from a living donor, usually a relative or friend. Experts said using uteruses from women who have died could make more transplants possible. Ten previous attempts using deceased donors in the Czech Republic, Turkey and the U.S. have failed. The baby girl was delivered last December by a woman born without a uterus because of a rare syndrome. The woman — a 32-year-old psychologist — was initially appre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Elective cesareans tied to higher risk of overweight babies - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-csections-overweight-babies/elective-cesareans-tied-to-higher-risk-of-overweight-babies-idUSKCN1NY2SP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIqIMFvvY2GdvJBtgvpawqAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 21:56:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-csections-overweight-babies/elective-cesareans-tied-to-higher-risk-of-overweight-babies-idUSKCN1NY2SP" target="_blank"&gt;Elective cesareans tied to higher risk of overweight babies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Lisa Rapaport (Reuters Health) - Pregnant women who opt for surgical cesarean deliveries may be more likely than those who have vaginal deliveries to have a child that is overweight by its first birthday, a small study suggests. For the analysis, researchers examined data on 727 infants born at two major hospitals in Singapore. Overall, 222 deliveries were surgical, and 74 of these procedures were elective - not done because of medical issues with the mother or baby. The rest were emergency surgeries. By the time babies were 12 months old, about 12 percent of them were on the cusp of bei...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Staffing more doctors and midwives tied to lower C-section rates - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-childbirth-staffing/staffing-more-doctors-and-midwives-tied-to-lower-c-section-rates-idUSKCN1NX2RS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKY1S_hdthG5DVqgszjzMKkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 21:19:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-childbirth-staffing/staffing-more-doctors-and-midwives-tied-to-lower-c-section-rates-idUSKCN1NX2RS" target="_blank"&gt;Staffing more doctors and midwives tied to lower C-section rates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Lisa Rapaport (Reuters Health) - - Pregnant women may be less likely to have cesarean deliveries when they labor at a hospital with more obstetricians and midwives on staff, a French study suggests. At the 11 hospitals in the study, as the number of obstetricians per unit increased, the rate of cesareans, or "C-sections," performed after labor had begun decreased, said study leader Saad Zbiri of Versailles Saint Quentin University in Montigny-le-Bretonneux and Poissy Saint-Germain Hospital. And as the number of midwives per unit increased, fewer cesareans were done that had been planned ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Many in Rural US Find Fewer Maternity Care Options - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/many-in-rural-us-find-fewer-maternity-care-options/4672835.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELt8yTbxdGZb083NRJ3Y540qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 10:15:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/many-in-rural-us-find-fewer-maternity-care-options/4672835.html" target="_blank"&gt;Many in Rural US Find Fewer Maternity Care Options&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, Americans have migrated toward urban areas seeking opportunities, emptying out large swaths of countryside. In their wake, they have left shrinking communities that struggle to support multiple businesses, schools and hospitals. This is a common theme in the Midwestern state of Iowa, whose population has grown by less than a million people in the past century. As family farms have consolidated into megafarms run by large corporations, rural residents have moved to cities like Des Moines, the state capital, or left the state altogether. Mallard, Iowa, located in northwest Iowa, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Mothers should never have been made to feel like failures for shunning a 'natural birth' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/editorials/royal-college-of-midwives-childbirth-caesarean-section-natural-birth-stigma-a7890036.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGg4pgz0qbvLI5h7lcCcP80qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/editorials/royal-college-of-midwives-childbirth-caesarean-section-natural-birth-stigma-a7890036.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mothers should never have been made to feel like failures for shunning a 'natural birth'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The motives that lay behind the Royal College of Midwives’ 12 year campaign for “natural birth” were sincere. Indeed as a body of professionals dedicated to their vocation, and experts in their field, their advice to mothers was respected and often followed. It stemmed in turn from a desire to hold the line against an overmedicalised society generally, where medications and procedures are sometimes deployed unnecessarily and counterproductively, even. The over-lavish prescription of antibiotics is one example of overcautious medics having a perverse effect on health and resistance. Childbir...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Vaginal seeding: Doctors warn new mothers not to embrace dangerous ‘microbirthing’ trend - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/vaginal-seeding-microbirthing-mothers-caesarean-birth-trend-dangerous-infection-a7907936.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBnpMwQODg_QwF8uo0kX7msqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 09:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/vaginal-seeding-microbirthing-mothers-caesarean-birth-trend-dangerous-infection-a7907936.html" target="_blank"&gt;Vaginal seeding: Doctors warn new mothers not to embrace dangerous ‘microbirthing’ trend&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women are being warned not to follow a trend called “vaginal seeding” after giving birth, as it may put babies at risk of dangerous infection. The trend, also known as microbirthing, involves taking a swab of vaginal fluid and wiping it over the baby’s face, eyes and mouth after birth by caesarian section. It is believed to expose children born by c-section to bacteria that could have covered their bodies if they had been born vaginally. This is thought to help kick-start the immune system and lower the risk of allergies. But experts have warned that vaginal seeding could lead to infections...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Mom Who Had 3 C-Sections Explains Why Her Body Didn't 'Fail Her' - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mom-who-had-3-c-sections-explains-why-her-body-didnt-fail-her_us_599c4661e4b04c532f448add</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFbkNIB9vpfhSvYEDn2wdtUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 18:59:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mom-who-had-3-c-sections-explains-why-her-body-didnt-fail-her_us_599c4661e4b04c532f448add" target="_blank"&gt;Mom Who Had 3 C-Sections Explains Why Her Body Didn't 'Fail Her'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A series of photos is reminding mothers who gave birth via C-section that their bodies did not “fail” them. As part of her “Honest Body Project,” photographer Natalie McCain interviewed and took pictures of a mom named Jacqueline, who delivered three babies via C-section. She also struggles with aggressive endometriosis, which required multiple surgeries. “I have received so many messages from women about their C-section scars and how they struggle with their experience,” McCain told HuffPost. “I loved this mom’s perspective on her C-section scar, and I wanted her message to help reach othe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Don’t have oral sex while pregnant, warn experts - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/oral-sex-pregnant-not-safe-genital-herpes-unborn-child-experts-health-risk-a7931751.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFWPAYHoxqH0O-f5Z8yUms8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 09:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/oral-sex-pregnant-not-safe-genital-herpes-unborn-child-experts-health-risk-a7931751.html" target="_blank"&gt;Don’t have oral sex while pregnant, warn experts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s bad news for expecting couples, as experts reveal that there could be severe consequences for women who have oral sex whilst pregnant. Due to their compromised immune system, pregnant women are at a greater risk of contracting STIs, particularly in their third trimester. The biggest risks become apparent if the expecting mother or her partner contracts genital herpes, a nurse practitioner and author of The Good News About The Bad News: Herpes: Everything You Need to Know told Vice. - Read more Oral sex is making gonorrhoea harder to treat, warns WHO If an expecting mother contracts the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Kate Hudson faces backlash over 'lazy' C-section joke - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/13/kate-hudson-faces-backlash-lazy-c-section-joke/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDvWJ4EvCcUzHm-O6H_haOAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 20:41:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/13/kate-hudson-faces-backlash-lazy-c-section-joke/" target="_blank"&gt;Kate Hudson faces backlash over 'lazy' C-section joke&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kate Hudson, the Hollywood actress who won the hearts of audiences in a string of romantic comedies, has faced a backlash after saying the "laziest" thing she's ever done was to have a caesarean birth. In a cover interview for the October issue of Cosmopolitan the star was asked to fill out a questionnaire. Her answers were innocuous until she reached the question "What's the laziest thing you've ever done?" Hudson, a 38-year-old mother-of-two, scrawled "Have a C-Section!" It may have been a bad joke but the wrath from mothers on social media was swift and fierce. On Twitter Hudson was accu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Kate Hudson Is Getting Flak For Her C-Section Comment - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/kate-hudson-is-getting-flak-for-her-c-section-comment_us_59b69fb9e4b06e4604a1ec7d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKSnfTXe4NHQF0Q7X_gUOGwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 20:18:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/kate-hudson-is-getting-flak-for-her-c-section-comment_us_59b69fb9e4b06e4604a1ec7d" target="_blank"&gt;Kate Hudson Is Getting Flak For Her C-Section Comment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kate Hudson is facing criticism following an interview she gave for her cover story in Cosmopolitan. The actress, who appears on the October cover, filled out a questionnaire as part of her feature. A post shared by Kate Hudson (@katehudson) on Aug 31, 2017 at 9:42am PDT The prompts included “the last photo I took on my phone,” “my me-time rituals,” and “my biggest source of anxiety.” Hudson’s answers were pretty innocuous for the most part, but her response to “the laziest thing I’ve ever done” rubbed many people the wrong way. Her response? “Have a C-section.” Dear #KateHudson Having a C-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Pregnant woman in excruciating pain kills herself after being denied a caesarean section - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/pregnant-woman-suicide-caesarean-section-kill-herself-pain-ma-shaanzi-province-a7933876.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPlmf41Sre2XNOvBbI3HLZkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 10:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/pregnant-woman-suicide-caesarean-section-kill-herself-pain-ma-shaanzi-province-a7933876.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pregnant woman in excruciating pain kills herself after being denied a caesarean section&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A pregnant Chinese woman killed herself after being denied a caesarean section, prompting an outpouring of condemnation of the country's strict surgical laws. The 27-year-old woman, identified only as Ma, was suffering from excruciating pain after going into labour. Ms Ma was 41 weeks pregnant when she jumped from a hospital room in the northern Shaanzi province on 31 August, killing herself and her unborn child. Read more - India 'preparing for war with China and Pakistan' - Taking antidepressants while pregnant 'can raise psychiatric risks' - Pregnant woman thrown out of restaurant for we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Should you use ‘vaginal seeding’ if your baby is born by caesarean? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/shortcuts/2017/aug/23/should-you-use-vaginal-seeding-if-your-baby-is-born-by-caesarean</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGxUvjSuhdiVXySIZwCuIpIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCcwRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 16:17:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/shortcuts/2017/aug/23/should-you-use-vaginal-seeding-if-your-baby-is-born-by-caesarean" target="_blank"&gt;Should you use ‘vaginal seeding’ if your baby is born by caesarean?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There has been an emerging trend among mothers who have a caesarean section for “vaginal seeding”, a process that exposes newborn babies to the micro-organisms they would normally encounter during vaginal birth. This week, though, Danish obstetricians writing in the international journal BJOG said that it “could do more harm than good”. Doctors at the UK’s Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists also warned against it. Although the research is new and untested, experts in award-winning documentary Microbirth suggest a link between the health of our microbiome and the “epidemic” of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The One Thing Businesses Want From This Week's Senate Health Care Hearings - Forbes Now</title><link>//www.forbes.com/sites/leahbinder/2017/09/07/the-one-thing-businesses-want-from-this-weeks-senate-health-care-hearings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBgKaZnIEfw11JrD1kK2XiIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 15:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="//www.forbes.com/sites/leahbinder/2017/09/07/the-one-thing-businesses-want-from-this-weeks-senate-health-care-hearings/" target="_blank"&gt;The One Thing Businesses Want From This Week's Senate Health Care Hearings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hearings began in the Senate this week on fixing emerging issues with the Obamacare exchange plans. These days, even the decidedly unsexy goal of stabilizing insurance markets passes for a major achievement when it prompts bipartisan consensus. But even the miracles of two parties talking may prove inadequate in the long run, because health care is not only a public policy issue. It’s also a business issue. Employers and other purchasers invest hundreds of billions of dollars in U.S. health care, paying for more than 20% of all health costs. Without that private-sector involvement, our heal...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Denied Abortion, Indian Rape Victim, 10, Gives Birth - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/india-child-rape-victim-ten-years-old-gives-birth/3990162.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEINVkM42DID9TO-FpbrmzG8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 21:00:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/india-child-rape-victim-ten-years-old-gives-birth/3990162.html" target="_blank"&gt;Denied Abortion, Indian Rape Victim, 10, Gives Birth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 10-year-old rape victim in India, who was denied permission to have an abortion, has given birth to a girl. The baby, weighing 2.5 kilograms (5.5 pounds), was delivered by Caesarean section in the northern city of Chandigarh on Thursday, a month after the Indian Supreme Court denied an abortion request. The ruling was made after medical determinations concluded an abortion was "too risky" for the girl and the fetus. The child was allegedly repeatedly raped by her uncle over several months. The uncle has been arrested. The suspected crime came to light when she was taken to a hospital comp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Natural childbirth: Royal College of Midwives to end 12-year campaign against caesarians, epidurals, inductions and use of instruments - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/normal-birth-royal-college-of-midwives-professor-cathy-warwick-caesarean-induction-instruments-a7889411.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ-g166QOMtjvJxUZwox628qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 08:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/normal-birth-royal-college-of-midwives-professor-cathy-warwick-caesarean-induction-instruments-a7889411.html" target="_blank"&gt;Natural childbirth: Royal College of Midwives to end 12-year campaign against caesarians, epidurals, inductions and use of instruments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Midwives have dropped their "campaign for normal birth", admitting it made some women feel like failures, it has been reported. The Royal College of Midwives (RCM) has said women will no longer be told that they should have babies without medical intervention. Professor Cathy Warwick, chief executive of the college, denied the campaign, which has run since 2005, had compromised safety, but told The Times it would be ended. Read more - Midwives warn about new mothers' mental health after death - More NHS nurses and midwives leaving than joining, new figures show - Half of all midwives 'could...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>10 most expensive cities in America to have a child - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/10-most-expensive-cities-in-america-to-have-a-child-2016-07-06</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMD1sWaaWhvqUPGl2bDQ3p0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 15:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/10-most-expensive-cities-in-america-to-have-a-child-2016-07-06" target="_blank"&gt;10 most expensive cities in America to have a child&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE BALANCE By Catey Hill The cost of giving a birth varies by thousands depending on where you do it For some people, it’s cheaper in bulk. 20thCentFox/Courtesy Everett Collection Where you live has a huge impact on what it will cost to give birth. In cities across the nation, the cost for giving birth averages $8,775 for a routine vaginal delivery and $11,525 for a cesarean section, according to a report released by health care technology firm Castlight Health, which examined millions of medical claims, as well as information from insurance providers. These costs include prenatal office v...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>COPY OF Record NHS negligence payouts, fuelled by maternity blunders - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/19/copy-record-nhs-negligence-payouts-fuelled-maternity-blunders/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOMy2VGWdLs4fq96YQbqPNkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 15:57:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/19/copy-record-nhs-negligence-payouts-fuelled-maternity-blunders/" target="_blank"&gt;COPY OF Record NHS negligence payouts, fuelled by maternity blunders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NHS is facing record negligence bills for brain-damaged babies because midwives fail to carry out the right checks in two in three such cases, a major report shows. The review of compensation claims shows the costs of catastrophic birth injury have almost doubled in the last five years, reaching almost £2bn. The study by NHS litigation authorities examined 50 cases which between in depth. It found that in 64 per cent of cases, devastating harm - leaving children in need of life-long, round-the-clock care - followed failures to monitor babies’ hearts, or to interpret the results of check...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Caesarean section late in labour increases risk of preterm birth next time - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2017/sep/28/caesarean-section-late-in-labour-increases-risk-of-preterm-birth-next-time</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJgQRVyqcl5SpjtWyiiFBpYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 06:16:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2017/sep/28/caesarean-section-late-in-labour-increases-risk-of-preterm-birth-next-time" target="_blank"&gt;Caesarean section late in labour increases risk of preterm birth next time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Undergoing an emergency caesarean section during the final stage of labour should be added to the list of risk factors for experiencing a premature birth in subsequent pregnancies, a study published on Thursday suggests. In one of the largest Australian studies into the link between caesarean sections and premature birth, researchers from Sydney’s Royal Prince Alfred hospital and the University of Sydney studied 2,672 women who either had a caesarean section during the first stage of labour, or at a late stage once their cervix was fully dilated. Related: Pregnancy and mental health should ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>My nephew is disabled and it’s all his mother’s fault - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2017/sep/03/my-nephew-is-disabled-and-its-all-his-mothers-fault-mariella-frostrup</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHyB2EQbTObS2pxvYXybiWoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCcwRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 05:00:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2017/sep/03/my-nephew-is-disabled-and-its-all-his-mothers-fault-mariella-frostrup" target="_blank"&gt;My nephew is disabled and it’s all his mother’s fault&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The dilemma I have huge anger at my brother’s wife for her actions, which I feel are directly responsible for my nephew being handicapped. For her first birth she had an emergency C-section, but she then chose to have a Vbac (vaginal birth after ceasarean) home birth for her second child – against all recommendations from her doctor. The home birth went terribly wrong and my nephew has been left permanently damaged. It’s a tragedy almost Shakespearean in its proportions. I knew my brother was browbeaten, but not to the extent he would let his wife harm their child. It’s caused major rifts i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Teens Are Shocked When Mom Surprises Them With New Baby Sister - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/leanne-allen-surprise-baby_us_598c9617e4b0a66b8bb1d728</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELvyErUbXPo4woSuTsAIv28qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 21:46:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/leanne-allen-surprise-baby_us_598c9617e4b0a66b8bb1d728" target="_blank"&gt;Teens Are Shocked When Mom Surprises Them With New Baby Sister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Leanne Allen went to the doctors for kidney problems, she suspected they might have to remove something. She never expected it would be a baby girl. The 37-year-old mom from Gosport, in southern England, went to doctors after experiencing fatigue, swollen legs and kidney problems. An MRI discovered Allen was 31 weeks pregnant ― something the mother of two teenagers never suspected. ″[The doctor] said she had found something on the scan that she needed to tell me. Straight away I was panicked, thinking she had found a tumor,” Allen said, according to Inside Edition. “When she then told ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Donald Trump's racist comments are to blame for the white supremacists' violence - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/donald-trumop-virginia-charlottesville-white-supremacists-north-korea-kim-jong-un-a7891326.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGBgJXkGnnJ7GbounpHslrIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 16:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/donald-trumop-virginia-charlottesville-white-supremacists-north-korea-kim-jong-un-a7891326.html" target="_blank"&gt;Donald Trump's racist comments are to blame for the white supremacists' violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One interesting part of the horrific footage of events from Virginia has largely been un-commented on. The riot footage revealed paramilitary neo-Nazis in crash helmets, armed with home-made body armour, shields and batons using pre-rehersed Roman phalanx tactics to lay waste to anti-racist protestors. This raises a number of questions. Given we have seen violent intolerance from US police forces of even peaceful Black Lives Matter activists, in what circumstances in recent years can we imagine police services allowing similarly armed black paramilitaries into enclosed public spaces where p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>American surgeons poorly prepared for humanitarian operations - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-surgeons-humanitarian-assignments-idUSKCN1B12AN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMirK7pco6VPLtYqnB6kHEYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 20:39:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-surgeons-humanitarian-assignments-idUSKCN1B12AN" target="_blank"&gt;American surgeons poorly prepared for humanitarian operations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Ronnie Cohen (Reuters Health) - A Haitian physician taught American-trained vascular surgeon Dr. David Kuwayama how to perform C-sections in a Caribbean clinic, and a Congolese surgeon taught him other basic surgical procedures in an African war zone. “It is the norm - not the exception - that when we go abroad, the non-American surgeons are teaching the American surgeons how to do numerous things,” said Kuwayama, who regularly serves on humanitarian missions for the medical aid group Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF), known in the U.S. as Doctors Without Borders. Kuwayama and other America...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Midwives agree to drop 'normal births' campaign as it makes women 'feel like failures' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/08/12/midwives-agree-drop-normal-births-campaign-makes-women-feel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENU0nKX2AtF32xiyaUwOqB8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 08:24:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/08/12/midwives-agree-drop-normal-births-campaign-makes-women-feel/" target="_blank"&gt;Midwives agree to drop 'normal births' campaign as it makes women 'feel like failures'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Midwives have dropped a campaign to encourage "normal births" and will no longer urge women to have babies without medical intervention. The 12-year long campaign has been dropped by the Royal College of Midwives after it "made women feel like failures". In an overhaul of its guidance to professionals, it is seeking to dispel the myth that caesareans and epidurals are abnormal. Prof Cathy Warwick, chief executive of the college, last night conceded that the campaign had "created the wrong idea" and would be ended. Chief Executive of the Royal College of Midwives Cathy Warwick Credit: John ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Katherine Heigl On The 'Glorious Imperfections' Of Her Postpartum Body - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/katherine-heigl-on-the-glorious-imperfections-of-her-postpartum-body_us_598c5e49e4b0d793738cfbae</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECvyJuMVnj9kZvVw3_2R8wUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 14:18:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/katherine-heigl-on-the-glorious-imperfections-of-her-postpartum-body_us_598c5e49e4b0d793738cfbae" target="_blank"&gt;Katherine Heigl On The 'Glorious Imperfections' Of Her Postpartum Body&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Katherine Heigl is getting real about her postpartum body ― “glorious imperfections” and all. In a post on her blog, “Those Heavenly Days,” the actress offered advice on how she’s learned to embrace her body after giving birth to her youngest, Joshua Jr. Heigl, who also has two daughters, wrote that she gained 50 pounds while pregnant with her son. While she quickly lost 30 after giving birth, the last 20 have proved more difficult to lose. Over time, Heigl has lost some of those pounds, but has learned not to obsess over them. Instead, she has chosen to appreciate her body, including her C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>62-yr-old single mother gives birth - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/general_news/2018/11/14/62-yr-old-single-mother-gives-birth_d9e45831-8853-4ef8-a47d-9b5b351f6a35.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFvtEynJPZz8R5sW2FnMiuYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 16:34:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/general_news/2018/11/14/62-yr-old-single-mother-gives-birth_d9e45831-8853-4ef8-a47d-9b5b351f6a35.html" target="_blank"&gt;62-yr-old single mother gives birth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, November 14 - A 62-year-old woman gave birth to a healthy girl on Wednesday in the Italian capital. The baby was born through a planned Caesarean section without complications. The mother, a nurse, had had the embryo implanted in Tirana, Albania, since she does not have a partner. The director of Obstetric Anesthesia at San Giovanni hospital, where the baby was born, Marco Traversa said that "what the data shows us is that those in obstetrics wards in the Lazio region are ever older. Especially from our experience, it has become clear that in the metropolitan area, on aver...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Why the outrage over a 50-year-old woman having quadruplets? The only scandal is that she couldn't get IVF on the NHS - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/quadruplets-grandmother-gives-birth-tracey-britten-ivf-nhs-hospital-cyprus-a8626081.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_VG7DV_oZza8Z8uLye79QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/quadruplets-grandmother-gives-birth-tracey-britten-ivf-nhs-hospital-cyprus-a8626081.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why the outrage over a 50-year-old woman having quadruplets? The only scandal is that she couldn't get IVF on the NHS&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 50, Tracey Britten has become the UK’s oldest mother of quads – she’s hoping to bring her three new daughters and son home in time for her 51st birthday next month. Instead of celebrating this remarkable achievement, social media is full of snotty condemnations. The reason? It took a team of 35 NHS staff to deliver Tracey’s babies by Caesarean section at a London hospital, at a time when OAPs can’t get a flu jab and even some essential operations like joint replacements are being cancelled. The NHS seems to be at breaking point, so should older mums who go abroad for IVF treatment and th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>U.S. companies team up with hospitals to reduce employee maternity costs - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-world-work-maternity/u-s-companies-team-up-with-hospitals-to-reduce-employee-maternity-costs-idUSKCN1NC1EQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGlsg0tENsr_rtBiGhwZd9MqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 11:06:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-world-work-maternity/u-s-companies-team-up-with-hospitals-to-reduce-employee-maternity-costs-idUSKCN1NC1EQ" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. companies team up with hospitals to reduce employee maternity costs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;General Electric Co (GE.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) and other large companies are trying to chip away at rising childbirth costs for U.S. employees, working directly with hospitals to reduce cesarean sections and related complications. The efforts are in very early stages, with few details on their impact outside of cost savings of a few million dollars so far. But they illustrate yet another path companies are taking to bring down U.S. medical costs by working with doctors and hospitals to set health goals. GE's maternity strategy is designed to steer its employees to hospital...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Conjoined Bhutanese twins separated after six-hour surgery - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/09/health/bhutan-conjoined-twins-success-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECIva3cGxDxO7YkmLZXbHfgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 18:15:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/09/health/bhutan-conjoined-twins-success-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Conjoined Bhutanese twins separated after six-hour surgery&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conjoined twins who flew nearly 6,000 miles for a life-changing operation have been separated by doctors in Australia. The 15-month-old twin girls, Nima and Dawa Pelden, were joined at the stomach and had grown up facing each other, unable to move independently. Dr. Joe Crameri, head of pediatric surgery at Melbourne Royal Children's Hospital, said Friday that the surgery was a "relief" and a "joy." "There is nothing better in any operation than to be able to go to the parents and say, 'we've been able to look after your child,' " he said. "I feel confident that they will be able to recover...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>She Wanted a ‘Freebirth’ at Home. When the Baby Died, the Attacks Began - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/she-wanted-a-freebirth-at-home-when-the-baby-died-the-attacks-began</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENnO5OBtt9DYxzZeKtz5jvgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 01:14:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/she-wanted-a-freebirth-at-home-when-the-baby-died-the-attacks-began" target="_blank"&gt;She Wanted a ‘Freebirth’ at Home. When the Baby Died, the Attacks Began&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the photos, Journey Moon looks peaceful. Her eyes are closed, her tiny body swaddled in blankets. She rests on her mother's chest, the slight bruising around her face the only indication of what happened: that she was born dead, at 42 weeks, after six days of painful labor. This was no ordinary stillbirth. Journey Moon’s mother, Lisa*, spent those six excruciating days in a remote desert home, laboring entirely alone—aside from her husband and the virtual company of more than 6,000 members of a private Facebook group. Lisa was a member of the now-defunct Free Birth Society, an online com...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>A few interventions may work to reduce C-sections - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-childbirth-c-sections/a-few-interventions-may-work-to-reduce-c-sections-idUSKCN1N52RZ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMeJFnToOhzGPs9ca6BKYdgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 19:53:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-childbirth-c-sections/a-few-interventions-may-work-to-reduce-c-sections-idUSKCN1N52RZ" target="_blank"&gt;A few interventions may work to reduce C-sections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Will Boggs MD (Reuters Health) - Unnecessary cesarean-section deliveries (C-sections) might decline if a variety of interventions targeting patients, healthcare professionals and hospitals were implemented, suggests an updated review of existing research. "For women, targeted prenatal educational support programs may help reduce unnecessary caesarean section, and this supports the notion that women benefit from having adequate information to make an informed choice," lead author Dr. Innie Chen from the University of Ottawa in Canada told Reuters Health. "Ongoing communication with the he...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Spina bifida surgery performed on two babies in the womb in UK first - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/health/spina-bifida-surgery-on-unborn-babies-uk-first-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF3Yks8mYp8E1H-4HDqIsW0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 12:48:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/24/health/spina-bifida-surgery-on-unborn-babies-uk-first-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Spina bifida surgery performed on two babies in the womb in UK first&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a UK first, a team of international surgeons successfully operated on the abnormally developed spines of two unborn babies with spina bifida. Until now, British mothers had to choose between traveling abroad to complete this surgery or waiting for their child to be born. The 30-strong team was completed with two surgeries this summer by researchers from University College London (UCL), clinicians from UCL Hospital, UCL and Great Ormond Street Hospital (GOSH) and University Hospital Leuven in Belgium, Treatment for spina bifida -- a problem with the development of the spinal cord leaving ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Mother of triplets shares progress photo of her post-baby body - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/baby-body-pregnancy-post-birth-mother-triplets-photos-maria-nordo-jorstad-denmark-a8598406.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFiVxWRE1lE0KkOsycfaXy8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 20:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/baby-body-pregnancy-post-birth-mother-triplets-photos-maria-nordo-jorstad-denmark-a8598406.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mother of triplets shares progress photo of her post-baby body&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mother of newborn triplets is being applauded for sharing refreshingly “real” photos of her post-baby body on Instagram. Maria Nordø Jørstad, from Copenhagen, Denmark, gave birth by Caesarean section on September 12 to triplets Iben, Filip, and Agnes. Following the birth of the “spontaneous” triplets - the term given to triplets conceived without the aid of fertility drugs - the mum posted a candid photo of her body one week post-pregnancy, and another after four weeks. - Read more The best reactions to Meghan Markle's pregnancy announcement In her latest unfiltered update to her more tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The stress pregnant immigrants face in America - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/23/health/pregnant-immigrant-women-every-mother-counts/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJLBYucNvWFqmOYtSIx2viIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 12:20:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/23/health/pregnant-immigrant-women-every-mother-counts/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The stress pregnant immigrants face in America&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The documentary series "Giving Birth in America" is produced by Every Mother Counts, a nonprofit organization that seeks to raise the profile and issues of maternal health in the United States. She became a doctor to serve communities like the one she grew up in. Her patient suffered a high-risk pregnancy and faced a serious complication. The experiences of these two women, doctor and patient, shed light on the state of maternal health care impacting immigrant women in the United States. Earlier this year, the patient's blood pressure inched higher and higher. Her pregnant body felt "strang...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Drama Of Pregnant Women In Prison - And The Woman On A Mission To Fix It - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ashoka/2018/10/25/the-drama-of-pregnant-women-in-prison-and-the-woman-on-a-mission-to-fix-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIbrPtYh4Dvxu0jZmlufLnoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ashoka/2018/10/25/the-drama-of-pregnant-women-in-prison-and-the-woman-on-a-mission-to-fix-it/" target="_blank"&gt;The Drama Of Pregnant Women In Prison - And The Woman On A Mission To Fix It&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Erica Gerrity, a Minnesota doula and social entrepreneur, wants to transform the experience of expecting mothers in American prisons. Erica Gerrity is the founder of Ostara Initiative, a new national effort that pairs expecting mothers who are incarcerated with doulas. With deep roots in Minnesota, the effort is expanding now to Alabama and beyond. Ashoka’s Konstanze Frischen caught up with Gerrity to learn more. Q: How many women are incarcerated? A: In 1980 it was 13,000 women. Now it’s more than 250,000. This makes women the fastest growing segment in our criminal justice system, a more ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Which Countries Conduct The Most Caesarean Sections? [Infographic] - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/niallmccarthy/2018/10/15/which-countries-conduct-the-most-caesarean-sections-infographic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJwswPOwkl9BxBc4peEIv4gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/niallmccarthy/2018/10/15/which-countries-conduct-the-most-caesarean-sections-infographic/" target="_blank"&gt;Which Countries Conduct The Most Caesarean Sections? [Infographic]&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, a study published in the Lancet found that the use of caesarean sections is rising rapidly worldwide with experts saying the procedure is growing at an “alarming” rate. While the share of caesarean births was 12% at the turn of the century, it was over 21% in 2015. Doctors have said that in many cases, these procedures have been unjustified. The World Health Organization estimates that around 10 to 15% of births require a C-section due to complications and it has suggested that rates higher than that are excessive. Even though a C-section can be a life-saving procedure for both m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The countries where more than half of babies are delivered via C-section - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/science/2018-10-15/countries-where-more-than-half-babies-born-by-c-section/10370302</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC1bboHeNgpbFQ9HolQBABMqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 20:15:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/science/2018-10-15/countries-where-more-than-half-babies-born-by-c-section/10370302" target="_blank"&gt;The countries where more than half of babies are delivered via C-section&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Genelle Weule Globally, 21 per cent of babies are born via C-section — an almost two-fold rise in 15 years. Globally, 21 per cent of babies are born via C-section — an almost two-fold rise in 15 years. Caesarean section is one of the most common medical procedures in many countries around the world. It can be a lifesaving intervention for women with complicated pregnancies and births, but it is not without risk. The World Health Organisation estimates that around 10–15 per cent of births require a C-section due to complications. But worldwide there has been "alarming increase" in the use...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Use of caesarean sections growing at 'alarming' rate - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/oct/11/use-of-caesarean-sections-growing-at-alarming-rate</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO8ckeFoZTshD676x7odDa4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 22:30:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/oct/11/use-of-caesarean-sections-growing-at-alarming-rate" target="_blank"&gt;Use of caesarean sections growing at 'alarming' rate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The use of caesarean sections to deliver babies has reached epidemic proportions, say experts, with the procedure growing in use at an “alarming” rate. While caesarean sections can be a crucial intervention for the safety of the mother and child, for example if the baby is showing distress or if the mother is bleeding before birth, experts say the procedure would account for about 10-15% of births if only used when medically necessary. But in a new series of studies and commentaries published in the Lancet, a team of researchers have revealed that in many countries caesarean sections are ri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Caesareans now used in one in four UK births, major new report reveals - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/11/caesareans-now-used-one-four-uk-births-major-new-report-reveals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENrQmha5idXMv6RoM_BFrlgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 22:38:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/11/caesareans-now-used-one-four-uk-births-major-new-report-reveals/" target="_blank"&gt;Caesareans now used in one in four UK births, major new report reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One in four UK babies is now delivered by caesarean section, new figures reveal as experts say women are increasingly scared of natural birth. A major international study, published in the Lancet, shows rates of C-section delivery have increased from 19.7 per cent in 2000 to 26.2 per cent in 2015, putting Britain among the highest in Western Europe for use of the procedure. The 33 per cent increase comes despite years of a natural birth campaign in many NHS hospitals, which still sees women occasionally denied the treatment at three-quarters of maternity units. As well as “fear” of natural ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>C-section births rise rapidly to more than 20 percent worldwide - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-childbirth-caesarean/c-section-births-rise-rapidly-to-more-than-20-percent-worldwide-idUSKCN1ML32J</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECTb7jWxz3ceCgdldu-mHQsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 22:40:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-childbirth-caesarean/c-section-births-rise-rapidly-to-more-than-20-percent-worldwide-idUSKCN1ML32J" target="_blank"&gt;C-section births rise rapidly to more than 20 percent worldwide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rates of caesarean section births almost doubled between 2000 and 2015 – from 12 to 21 percent worldwide - new research has found, with the life-saving surgery unavailable to many women in poor countries while often over-used in richer ones. The research, published in The Lancet medical journal on Thursday, found that 60 percent of countries overuse C-sections and 25 percent under-use them, suggesting that recommendations for their use in cases of medical need are widely ignored. In at least 15 countries, more than 40 percent of all babies born are delivered by C-section. The highest rate, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>'Medically unnecessary' c-sections double in UK as major study warns of global overuse - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/c-section-birth-caesarean-pregnancy-complications-risk-maternity-baby-lancet-incontinence-pelvic-a8579821.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKpfRWZd97mgc8x0FrCbeiUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 22:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/c-section-birth-caesarean-pregnancy-complications-risk-maternity-baby-lancet-incontinence-pelvic-a8579821.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Medically unnecessary' c-sections double in UK as major study warns of global overuse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medically unnecessary caesarean births have more than doubled in the UK in the past 15 years, according to an international study which warns mothers are being put at risk by over use. While women in low income or more isolated regions are still unable to access this life-saving intervention, it is increasingly being used without robust medical justification in wealthier parts of the world, the experts warned. Since 2000 the proportion of births by C-section has doubled globally, rising from 12 per cent to 21 per cent of all births, according to the new research published in The Lancet medi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>IUD risk for new mothers depends on timing - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-contraception-iud/iud-risk-for-new-mothers-depends-on-timing-idUSKCN1MR33B</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAyolFvkytWWHV8C06rl7aYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 21:23:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-contraception-iud/iud-risk-for-new-mothers-depends-on-timing-idUSKCN1MR33B" target="_blank"&gt;IUD risk for new mothers depends on timing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Lisa Rapaport (Reuters Health) - New mothers who want intrauterine devices (IUDs) for long-acting contraception after giving birth should know the risk of the implant being expelled is tied to how soon after delivery it is inserted, researchers say. The best option is either to place the IUD immediately after delivery, when there is only a 10 percent risk of the uterus expelling the device, or to wait at least four weeks afterward, when the risk drops to 4 percent, an analysis of existing research found. When women get an IUD implanted in the uterus more than 10 minutes after delivery bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Asthma during pregnancy tied to postpartum depression risk - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-pregnancy-asthma-depression/asthma-during-pregnancy-tied-to-postpartum-depression-risk-idUSKCN1ML2LR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEEIlcXENHfaTWibi_CjzG8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 17:57:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-pregnancy-asthma-depression/asthma-during-pregnancy-tied-to-postpartum-depression-risk-idUSKCN1ML2LR" target="_blank"&gt;Asthma during pregnancy tied to postpartum depression risk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Shereen Lehman (Reuters Health) - Women who have asthma during their pregnancies are more likely to experience postpartum depression after delivery, a large Canadian study suggests. Physicians should watch for signs of depression in their pregnant patients with asthma so treatment and coping strategies can start early, the authors write in The Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology: In Practice. "We knew asthma in general (outside of pregnancy) is associated with an increased risk of depression, so we suspected that asthma during pregnancy could increase the risk of postpartum depres...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>GPs could start performing caesarean births under proposals for stretched maternity unit - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/caesarean-gp-c-section-birth-maternity-unit-csection-nhs-workforce-shortage-oxfordshire-a8562151.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOqknRp7Q_nhftZiGMWiQXIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 20:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/caesarean-gp-c-section-birth-maternity-unit-csection-nhs-workforce-shortage-oxfordshire-a8562151.html" target="_blank"&gt;GPs could start performing caesarean births under proposals for stretched maternity unit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GPs should be given extra training on performing caesarean sections, according to a proposal being considered by managers of a health trust for staffing a local maternity unit. One of nine options being considered by Oxfordshire health chiefs, the proposal is modelled on a rural or remote maternity service where women may not be able to access a dedicated obstetrician at short notice. It is hoped that this could address a serious shortage of obstetricians that led to caesarean births and other procedures at Horton General Hospital, Banbury, being suspended over safety concerns. - Read more ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Conjoined twins flown from Bhutan to Australia for separation operation - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/02/health/australia-bhutan-conjoined-twins-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANrH0RRAvQPxMxskQ3m3ywqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 06:58:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/02/health/australia-bhutan-conjoined-twins-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Conjoined twins flown from Bhutan to Australia for separation operation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A pair of conjoined twins have been flown from Bhutan to Australia, where doctors hope they will be able to operate on the 14-month-old girls, who have grown up facing each other, unable to move independently. Joe Crameri, a doctor at Melbourne Royal Children's Hospital, said staff were examining the twins, Dawa and Nima Pelden, who are joined at the stomach, with the hopes they will be able to carry out of a life-changing operation to separate them. "Once we've got that information, then we'll be able to formulate a more correct plan for how we can separate these twins but at the moment we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Sister of UK woman who died in botched caesarean makes justice plea - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/26/british-woman-xynthia-hawke-died-france-botched-c-section</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF6W9mR79rZWB2r9o7QBVFsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 17:29:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/26/british-woman-xynthia-hawke-died-france-botched-c-section" target="_blank"&gt;Sister of UK woman who died in botched caesarean makes justice plea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xynthia Hawke was 28 and expecting her first child, with all the excitement and delight of a new mother to be. She and her French partner, Yannick Balthazar, had planned everything down to the last detail in what they hoped would be as natural a birth as possible in a specially chosen clinic. “Xynthia liked to be prepared for things and this was just the most exciting thing ever to prepare for,” says her sister, Iris Hawke. “She sailed through the pregnancy; she had none of the sickness, just the good things and lots of mental clarity. She was swimming, doing yoga and eating well and she an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Vanessa Fernandez Arango death: Fertility blogger dies during emergency Caesarean section - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/vanessa-fernandez-arango-death-blog-fertility-birth-emergency-caesarean-section-a8542191.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOmIhMcfNHwUo37W0eU9F-UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 21:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/vanessa-fernandez-arango-death-blog-fertility-birth-emergency-caesarean-section-a8542191.html" target="_blank"&gt;Vanessa Fernandez Arango death: Fertility blogger dies during emergency Caesarean section&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The husband of a fertility blogger who died giving birth to the couple’s son has shared an emotional tribute to his late wife. Vanessa Fernandez Arango recently passed away from complications arising from an emergency Caesarean section that saved her son’s life. To honour her memory, Arango’s husband Jonathan Garcia has decided to continue updating his wife’s 8,000 followers with news of their son’s life. - Read more Photo of newborn surrounded by IVF needles captures fertility struggle Following his wife’s death, the new dad wrote on Instagram: “You have helped me as much as I hope that sh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>‘Yes he’s alive but I’m not OK’: the bloody truth about childbirth - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/sep/19/yes-hes-alive-but-im-not-ok-the-bloody-truth-about-childbirth</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAneJVlAaNYa5SMKD4QqBtkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCcwRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 05:00:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/sep/19/yes-hes-alive-but-im-not-ok-the-bloody-truth-about-childbirth" target="_blank"&gt;‘Yes he’s alive but I’m not OK’: the bloody truth about childbirth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clare Cashion was 28 weeks pregnant and just about to board a plane home from a family Christmas in Ireland when her waters broke. She was rushed to hospital in Dublin, where doctors managed temporarily to halt the birth. But there was no longer any question of her safely leaving the country, so while her partner and three older children flew back home to England, Clare stayed behind in hospital. Her son Cullan was eventually born on New Year’s Day by emergency caesarean section, after a labour that was traumatic from the beginning. It was only when surgeons began operating, says Clare, tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Hudson's mum blames her obstetrician and hospital for his cerebral palsy. Now she's suing them for $20m - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-16/qld-mother-sues-queensland-hospital-and-obstetrician-for-2420-/10250964</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGK9s4yM4w8mHQ1hwtUquN8qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 20:19:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-16/qld-mother-sues-queensland-hospital-and-obstetrician-for-2420-/10250964" target="_blank"&gt;Hudson's mum blames her obstetrician and hospital for his cerebral palsy. Now she's suing them for $20m&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Rachel Riga A mother has lodged a $20 million medical negligence claim in the Supreme Court in Brisbane against an obstetrician and the Mater Mothers' Private Hospital on behalf of her son for allegedly causing his cerebral palsy. Petrea Aslett, 43, claims she shouldn't have been prescribed penicillin when she presented to the Mater Mothers' Private Hospital in Brisbane with irregular pelvic and abdominal pain in March 2012, which caused her to suffer a severe anaphylactic reaction and for her son Hudson, now six, to be born prematurely. Court documents allege Ms Aslett was 30 weeks preg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>First evidence of soot air pollution reaching the placenta found in London mothers, new study says - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/air-pollution-pregnant-women-london-study-placenta-first-evidence-a8539861.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHGW7Q75Iy2LqVnqoWa11J0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 09:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/air-pollution-pregnant-women-london-study-placenta-first-evidence-a8539861.html" target="_blank"&gt;First evidence of soot air pollution reaching the placenta found in London mothers, new study says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evidence that air pollution passes from pregnant women's lungs to the placenta has been found for the first time, according to a new UK study. Researchers detected what they believe are tiny particles of carbon, typically created by burning fossil fuels, after five non-smoking mothers living in London underwent planned Caesarean section births. The study adds to existing evidence on the dangers of pollution for unborn babies and suggests that when pregnant women breathe polluted air, sooty particles are able to reach the placenta via the bloodstream. Read more - Air pollution now 'biggest e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Mumsnet and Facebook putting women off natural birth with 'tsunami of horror stories' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/mumsnet-childbirth-mumsnet-caesarean-instagram-catriona-jones-social-media-a8535526.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHP3Ju1a9gam82IPFgE1u4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 09:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/mumsnet-childbirth-mumsnet-caesarean-instagram-catriona-jones-social-media-a8535526.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mumsnet and Facebook putting women off natural birth with 'tsunami of horror stories'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In today’s social media age, oversharing has become the norm, but where does this leave us when it comes to childbirth? Once an experience shared only between parents and midwives, giving birth has become a trending topic online, as women divulge their stories across a range of platforms with a no holds barred approach to detail. While anecdotes of the labour process may provide feelings of comfort and camaraderie among new and expecting mothers, one midwifery lecturer has claimed that they may be traumatising pregnant women and putting some people off childbirth altogether. - Read more New...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Don’t tell women to shut up about childbirth. Sharing stories saves lives - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/13/women-childbirth-stories-giving-birth-painful</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECgLwPXUHJLIEERTptXalHIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 12:16:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/13/women-childbirth-stories-giving-birth-painful" target="_blank"&gt;Don’t tell women to shut up about childbirth. Sharing stories saves lives&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mumsnet may be responsible for a lot of questionable things – penis beaker, anyone? – but will it actually end the human race? Will it stop us reproducing? This seems a tad excessive but apparently by sharing stories about childbirth there, women are scaring other women into “a pathological terror of childbirth”, says an expert. Catriona Jones is a lecturer in midwifery at the University of Hull who studies “tocophopbia”. She suggests social media is partly to blame for this fear-with-no-name (which, of course, now has one). Let’s break this down, shall we? Women fear childbirth because pus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Poor maternal care leads to hysterectomies, antibiotic resistance - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/poor-maternal-care-leads-hysterectomies-antibiotic-resistance-180907092450035.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOwlcvDN0FvEYRiVcGg2eM8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 10:53:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/poor-maternal-care-leads-hysterectomies-antibiotic-resistance-180907092450035.html" target="_blank"&gt;Poor maternal care leads to hysterectomies, antibiotic resistance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thyolo, Malawi - In a hospital room in Thyolo, a southern Malawian town among tea plantations, Ngellina Chikopa unwraps her sarong to reveal a long wound filled with pus. The cut stretches from her lower abdomen through her belly button and up past her stomach. The 18-year-old gave birth by caesarean section in April 2018, but the baby died of asphyxia after becoming stuck and suffering brain damage from lack of oxygen. While she was grieving, the wound became infected. She was given IV antibiotics but it started to release foul-smelling pus. The infection spread to her uterus. Doctors gave...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Fat-Shaming The Pregnant: How The Medical Community Fails Overweight Moms - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/fat-shaming-pregnant-overweight-moms_us_5b89a872e4b0511db3d872a9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG5IANlAKm3TQ8-PrNkhOFEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 09:45:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/fat-shaming-pregnant-overweight-moms_us_5b89a872e4b0511db3d872a9" target="_blank"&gt;Fat-Shaming The Pregnant: How The Medical Community Fails Overweight Moms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hilary was 23 years old and newly married when her doctor confirmed she was pregnant with her first baby. As soon as she heard the good news, the doctor hit her with some bad news: He said her weight ― 211 pounds at 5 feet, 1 inch ― would be a problem. She was less than six weeks’ pregnant, but her doctor started talking about labor. He announced she was “too obese” to give birth vaginally and would have to have a cesarean section. He didn’t elaborate and Hilary, caught off-guard, didn’t ask questions. “I was stunned,” she said. Hearing that her weight was already limiting her and her baby’...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>California actions to lower dangerous maternal death rate may help rest of US - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/sep/04/california-actions-to-lower-dangerous-maternal-death-rate-may-help-rest-of-us</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI4zeB9DI_2Xv68yOYLudJ4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 20:59:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/sep/04/california-actions-to-lower-dangerous-maternal-death-rate-may-help-rest-of-us" target="_blank"&gt;California actions to lower dangerous maternal death rate may help rest of US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alisha Berry was at the doctor for what she thought was a normal check-up at 18 weeks pregnant. But she gradually realized that it wasn’t normal at all. “I could tell something was wrong,” she said. “They were looking through the scans and whispering.” The doctors didn’t immediately tell her what was going on. She recalled later: “Like a lot of situations, they treat women with delicate words, when in reality we just want to know the truth.” Eventually, they did tell her what the problem was. Related: Gifting moms vacation days is cute - but could we give them rights instead? “They mentione...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Inducing labour lowers a woman's chance of c-section - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/health/2018-08-31/women-at-lower-risk-of-caesarean-section-when-theyre-induced/10178692</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMn0AOnRToNbt87-p1Xk2G8qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 19:02:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/health/2018-08-31/women-at-lower-risk-of-caesarean-section-when-theyre-induced/10178692" target="_blank"&gt;Inducing labour lowers a woman's chance of c-section&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By James Bullen for the Health Report It's a debate that's vexed doctors for decades — are pregnant women better off being induced into labour or waiting for it to come naturally? The long-held belief has been that women who were induced early were more likely to need a caesarean section. But new research published this month in the New England Journal of Medicine says that isn't the case. "For many years there has been a belief, really deeply ingrained, that labour induction leads to a greater chance of caesarean delivery," said the study's lead author Bill Grobman, an obstetrician-gynaeco...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Scandal-hit NHS Trust faces calls for wider investigation into deaths on maternity unit - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/31/scandal-hit-nhs-trust-faces-calls-wider-investigation-deaths/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHU-yz4aIICQJ2VTHUX7zhYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/31/scandal-hit-nhs-trust-faces-calls-wider-investigation-deaths/" target="_blank"&gt;Scandal-hit NHS Trust faces calls for wider investigation into deaths on maternity unit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dozens of families have come forward with concerns their babies may have been killed or seriously injured at a “toxic” NHS maternity unit accused of being obsessed with natural births. A Government-ordered review into 23 incidents at the Shrewsbury and Telford NHS Trust (SaTH) may be expanded after it emerged an extra 40 cases have been flagged. The extent of alleged malpractice between 1998 and 2017 threatens a scandal bigger than that of Morecambe Bay, which saw the avoidable deaths of 11 babies and one mother. The latest deaths, those a mother and two babies, occurred as recently as Dece...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>What The Rest Of The U.S. Can Learn From A Small North Carolina Maternal Health Program - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/maternal-mortality-rate-social-causes_us_5b87276ae4b0511db3d47c1c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN2TNjHxry4GRm5_ZcX-nCMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 09:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/maternal-mortality-rate-social-causes_us_5b87276ae4b0511db3d47c1c" target="_blank"&gt;What The Rest Of The U.S. Can Learn From A Small North Carolina Maternal Health Program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Efforts to drive down the rates of maternal mortality in the U.S. tend to focus on how doctors and hospitals can change the way they administer medical care. Yet research shows that things like loving relationships, safe homes and being part of a fair and equitable community also play an important role in whether a woman has a positive experience with pregnancy and giving birth. So experts were heartened by a pair of complementary bills, announced over the past week, that tackle this problem from both sides. The most recent national proposal, a billfrom Sen. Kirsten Gillibrand (D-N.Y.) anno...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Women being denied Caesarean births - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/21/women-denied-caesarean-births/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMtUKJc4dWd0TE4TynSHg5wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 11:52:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/21/women-denied-caesarean-births/" target="_blank"&gt;Women being denied Caesarean births&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women at three quarters of maternity units are being denied the right to choose a Caesarean birth, research suggests. Guidelines from the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (Nice) state women who ask for a caesarean should be offered one if, after support and discussion with a doctor, they feel it is best for them. But a report by childbirth charity Birthrights found that only 26 per cent of trusts were abiding by the guidelines and many women faced delays and difficulties in requesting a caesarean on non-medical grounds. Experts raised concerns that women who had previously ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Pregnant women being denied choice of caesarians at a number of UK hospitals, report finds - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/uk-hospitals-caesareans-elective-refuse-perform-mothers-rights-nice-birthrights-a8500621.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELMX11Q5ljQ1rEfdP6QawgcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 12:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/uk-hospitals-caesareans-elective-refuse-perform-mothers-rights-nice-birthrights-a8500621.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pregnant women being denied choice of caesarians at a number of UK hospitals, report finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A number of hospitals across the UK are routinely refusing to perform caesarean sections on expectant mothers, unless they have a medical reason for doing so, an investigation has revealed. Birthrights, a charity dedicated to protecting human rights in childbirth, conducted a nationwide Freedom of Information request to 153 trusts about how they adhered to NICE guidelines. Under the guidelines, women requesting a caesarean for whatever reason “should be offered appropriate discussion and support - but ultimately, if they are making an informed choice, a caesarean should be offered." - Read ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item></channel></rss>