<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Can Dündar - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNR0o1YmpsekVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-SG&amp;gl=SG&amp;ceid=SG:en</link><language>en-SG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:04:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Turkish authorities seek arrest of journalist Dundar over 2013 protests - Yahoo Singapore News</title><link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/turkish-authorities-seek-arrest-journalist-dundar-over-2013-213836142.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiZGh0dHBzOi8vc2cubmV3cy55YWhvby5jb20vdHVya2lzaC1hdXRob3JpdGllcy1zZWVrLWFycmVzdC1qb3VybmFsaXN0LWR1bmRhci1vdmVyLTIwMTMtMjEzODM2MTQyLmh0bWzSAbYBaHR0cHM6Ly9zZy1uZXdzLXlhaG9vLWNvbS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3NnLm5ld3MueWFob28uY29tL2FtcGh0bWwvdHVya2lzaC1hdXRob3JpdGllcy1zZWVrLWFycmVzdC1qb3VybmFsaXN0LWR1bmRhci1vdmVyLTIwMTMtMjEzODM2MTQyLmh0bWw_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://sg.news.yahoo.com/turkish-authorities-seek-arrest-journalist-dundar-over-2013-213836142.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish authorities seek arrest of journalist Dundar over 2013 protests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Yahoo Singapore News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkish authorities have issued an arrest warrant for journalist Can Dundar as part of an investigation into protests in Istanbul in 2013 against President Tayyip ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://sg.news.yahoo.com">Yahoo Singapore News</source></item><item><title>Turkish authorities seek arrest of journalist Dundar over 2013 protests - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-journalist/turkish-authorities-seek-arrest-of-journalist-dundar-over-2013-protests-idUSKBN1O42MR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKzBF0Ywjn3na2zj4o0X16YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 20:46:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-journalist/turkish-authorities-seek-arrest-of-journalist-dundar-over-2013-protests-idUSKBN1O42MR" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish authorities seek arrest of journalist Dundar over 2013 protests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkish authorities have issued an arrest warrant for journalist Can Dundar as part of an investigation into protests in Istanbul in 2013 against President Tayyip Erdogan's rule, state-run Anadolu agency said on Wednesday. Prosecutors said he played an active role in the protests and provoked public unrest through social media. They also said he supported members of a terrorist organization against the police, the news agency said. It is not clear how the warrant can be served because Dundar has left the country. Dundar, a former editor of opposition newspaper Cumhuriyet, was sentenced in 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Journalist released from Turkish jail in press freedom case - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cfa01768-a2a7-11e7-9e4f-7f5e6a7c98a2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEODwdS9us2TNr1_lJtExA7cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 12:33:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cfa01768-a2a7-11e7-9e4f-7f5e6a7c98a2" target="_blank"&gt;Journalist released from Turkish jail in press freedom case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Turkey’s most prominent journalists has been freed on bail after being held for 330 days in a case that has focused attention on President Recep Tayyip Erdogan’s crackdown on dissent. Kadri Gursel, who worked as a columnist for the Cumhuriyet newspaper, left Turkey’s Silivri prison late on Monday night. He remains charged with “helping a terrorist organisation without being a member”, alongside 17 of his former colleagues at the paper, including a cartoonist and an accountant. Four of the people charged, including the editor-in-chief of Cumhuriyet, one of Turkey’s oldest media outlet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Turkish opposition politician jailed for 25 years on spying charges - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jun/14/turkish-opposition-politician-jailed-spying-charges-enis-berberoglu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBIRcu1wiOHeYS2VeQ9rDIEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 15:45:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jun/14/turkish-opposition-politician-jailed-spying-charges-enis-berberoglu" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish opposition politician jailed for 25 years on spying charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Turkish court has sentenced the opposition Republican People’s party (CHP) lawmaker Enis Berberoğlu to 25 years in prison over spying charges. Berberoğlu, the first CHP lawmaker to be handed prison time since the lifting of parliamentary immunities last year, was accused of providing an opposition newspaper with video purporting to show Turkey’s intelligence agency trucking weapons into Syria. A report in the secular Cumhuriyet newspaper in May 2015 said trucks allegedly owned by Turkey’s state intelligence service had been found to contain weapons and ammunition that were headed for Syri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Turkey opposition marches against MP's imprisonment - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/turkey-opposition-marches-mp-imprisonment-170615090051447.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4z8z8VDIDu89acgKSk-YwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 11:05:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/turkey-opposition-marches-mp-imprisonment-170615090051447.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey opposition marches against MP's imprisonment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey's main opposition party is holding a protest march from Ankara, to Istanbul after an MP was sentenced to 25 years in prison on spying charges. Enis Berberoglu, the first Republican People's Party (CHP) MP to be handed prison time since the lifting of parliamentary immunities last year, was accused of giving an opposition newspaper video footage purporting to show Turkey's intelligence agency trucking weapons into Syria. CHP supporters gathered at an Ankara park on Thursday after party leader Kemal Kilicdaroglu announced the march in protest against the conviction a day ago, which the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Turkish opposition MP jailed for 25 years as part of Erdogan's ongoing political crackdown - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/06/14/turkish-opposition-mp-jailed-25-years-latest-political-crackdown/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK8F3egI0eNa6r7r8PlqMaEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 15:23:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/06/14/turkish-opposition-mp-jailed-25-years-latest-political-crackdown/" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish opposition MP jailed for 25 years as part of Erdogan's ongoing political crackdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Turkish court on Wednesday sentenced a Republican People's Party (CHP) politician to 25 years jail for leaking classified material to the press, the first time a main opposition party deputy has been arrested in an ongoing crackdown. Enis Berberoglu had not been detained during his trial but after the verdict was announced he was immediately placed under arrest at the Istanbul criminal court, state-run Anadolu news agency said. A dozen lawmakers from the pro-Kurdish Peoples' Democratic Party (HDP) have been arrested under the state of emergency that followed last year's failed coup. But t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Turkish Prosecutors Accuse Newspaper of ‘Asymmetric War' on Erdogan - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3798464.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPPH3dWD_tXmUjxAmB3Cq4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 00:20:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3798464.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish Prosecutors Accuse Newspaper of ‘Asymmetric War' on Erdogan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkish prosecutors are seeking up to 43 years in jail for journalists from a leading opposition newspaper on charges of supporting a terrorist organization and targeting President Tayyip Erdogan through “asymmetric war methods.” An indictment seen by Reuters on Wednesday said Cumhuriyet had effectively been “taken over” by the network of U.S.-based cleric Fethullah Gulen, blamed for a failed coup last July, and used to “veil the actions of terrorist groups.” Turkey has purged more than 113,000 people from the police, judiciary, military and elsewhere since the coup attempt, and has closed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Turkey Detains Editor, Staff at Opposition Newspaper - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/turkey-detains-editor-staff-at-opposition-paper/3572727.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG7gYYb_d_9Oi82NFN79ApMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 10:01:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/turkey-detains-editor-staff-at-opposition-paper/3572727.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey Detains Editor, Staff at Opposition Newspaper&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkish police detained the editor and a dozen senior staff from the main secularist opposition newspaper on Monday, a day after 10,000 more civil servants were sacked over suspected links to a failed July coup. Turkey's crackdown since rogue soldiers tried to seize power on July 15 has alarmed Western allies and rights groups, who fear President Tayyip Erdogan is using the coup attempt to crush dissent. More than 100,000 people have been sacked or suspended and 37,000 arrested over the past three and a half months. The Istanbul prosecutor's office said the staff from the Cumhuriyet daily, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Cafeteria manager jailed for insulting Turkey's Erdogan, lawyer says - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-detentions-idUSKBN14F0S6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDfyONS3Vf6BgAiPn3HCeI8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:49:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-detentions-idUSKBN14F0S6" target="_blank"&gt;Cafeteria manager jailed for insulting Turkey's Erdogan, lawyer says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Humeyra Pamuk ISTANBUL (Reuters) - Turkish authorities have arrested the cafeteria manager of the opposition Cumhuriyet newspaper for insulting the president after he said he would not serve tea to Tayyip Erdogan, one of the manager's lawyers told Reuters on Monday. Senol Buran, who runs the cafeteria at the Istanbul office of Cumhuriyet, was taken into custody after police raided his home late on Saturday, lawyer Ozgur Urfa said. The newspaper is among the few still critical of the government. Insulting the president is a crime punishable by up to four years in prison in Turkey. Lawyers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Turkey detains editor of secular opposition newspaper Cumhuriyet - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/turkey-detains-editor-opposition-newspaper-cumhuriyet-murat-sabuncu-can-dundar-a7388471.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDA2sEI-fPtbQwMGNz__nsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 07:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/turkey-detains-editor-opposition-newspaper-cumhuriyet-murat-sabuncu-can-dundar-a7388471.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey detains editor of secular opposition newspaper Cumhuriyet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkish police have detained the editor-in-chief of the secularist opposition newspaper Cumhuriyet and have issued detention warrants for 13 of the paper's journalists and executives, state media and CNN Turk reported. Murat Sabuncu was detained while authorities searched for executive board chairman Akin Atalay and writer Guray Oz, the official news agency Anadolu said. Police were searching the homes of Mr Atalay and Mr Oz, the agency added. In pictures: Turkey coup attempt - 17 show all In pictures: Turkey coup attempt - 1/17 Turkish President Erdogan attends the funeral service...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Turkish court sentences opposition MP to 25 years on spy charges - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/08ee7db0-5114-11e7-bfb8-997009366969</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMm9QzCFd9xKDL7YtWWKLSYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 18:02:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/08ee7db0-5114-11e7-bfb8-997009366969" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish court sentences opposition MP to 25 years on spy charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Turkish court sentenced an opposition lawmaker to 25 years in prison for espionage on Wednesday in a sensational case that has vexed President Recep Tayyip Erdogan for two years. Enis Berberoglu, an MP the Republican People’s party (CHP), the largest opposition, was accused of leaking videos of intelligence agency trucks carrying weapons that were purportedly heading into Syria, to an opposition newspaper in 2015. The videos were genuine, Turkish officials have said, but were collected and shared by people loyal to Fethullah Gulen, a shadowy cleric, whom Mr Erdogan blames for last year’s ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>In an age of autocracy, meet the dissidents speaking truth to power - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/feb/22/age-of-autocracy-dissidents-speaking-truth-to-power</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEODtbgQ-Q0dJh19mh5jLAykqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 12:14:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/feb/22/age-of-autocracy-dissidents-speaking-truth-to-power" target="_blank"&gt;In an age of autocracy, meet the dissidents speaking truth to power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are trying times. We live in an age of autocracy when strongmen (they are almost always men) abuse their power to silence their critics, use brute force to stop people championing the vulnerable and rob people of their agency in the pursuit of power. In a world flooded with triumphant nationalist statements and declarations of war, who speaks for the other side? Who is willing to risk solitary confinement and be torn from loved ones to speak for the voiceless? We caught up with six dissidents, who have been been imprisoned for a total of 26 years and three months, to understand what i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Turkish Court Rules Opposition Newspaper Journalists Must Remain in Custody - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/turkish-court-rules-opposition-newspaper-journalists-must-remain-in-custody-/4024912.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKf-DEA7F279R848Li2_AEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 02:45:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/turkish-court-rules-opposition-newspaper-journalists-must-remain-in-custody-/4024912.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish Court Rules Opposition Newspaper Journalists Must Remain in Custody&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Turkish court remanded five prominent staff from the opposition Cumhuriyet newspaper in custody on Monday in a trial which President Tayyip Erdogan's critics have condemned as an attack on free speech. The court said the newspaper correspondents and executives, some of whom have already been detained for 10 months, should remain in detention until more evidence was presented. "The court has decided to keep the arrested until witnesses are heard," chief judge Abdurrahman Orkun Dag said after a 13-hour session, adjourning the case for two weeks. "After hearing the witnesses, we think a more...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Ferrara Internazionale Fest set to start - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/lifestyle/arts/2017/09/15/ferrara-internazionale-fest-set-to-start_655e956a-7938-44b6-9b7e-186ee8fb2a95.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJrTj2zamMbEXZjyDBaHQgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 15:52:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/lifestyle/arts/2017/09/15/ferrara-internazionale-fest-set-to-start_655e956a-7938-44b6-9b7e-186ee8fb2a95.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ferrara Internazionale Fest set to start&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, September 15 - Italian weekly newsmagazine Internazionale will host its 11th annual festival, "Internazionale in Ferrara", from September 29 to October 1, featuring guests including former Greek Finance Minister Yanis Varoufakis, activist and writer Angela Davis, and U.S. Representative John Lewis, who participated in the 1963 March on Washington with Martin Luther King, Jr. Other guests among the 270 scheduled to participate at the festival, from 40 countries including journalists from 40 publications, include former Italian Premier Romano Prodi, former French Justice ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>How to survive tyranny: 10 pieces of advice from Turkey - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/mar/24/how-to-survive-tyranny-10-pieces-of-advice-from-turkey</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELIB75hbHNaOCNojbUCvZX0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 07:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/mar/24/how-to-survive-tyranny-10-pieces-of-advice-from-turkey" target="_blank"&gt;How to survive tyranny: 10 pieces of advice from Turkey&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rise of autocracy can be insidious, and doesn’t come with an instruction manual on how to survive, said one of hundreds of people who got in touch to tell us what life is like in Turkey. Over the past few years the president, Recep Tayyip Erdoğan, has slowly tightened his grip on power, imprisoning journalists who criticise him and intimidating citizens who may not agree with him. How do you fight back? Here are 10 pieces of advice from people inside Turkey, and from the diaspora. Names have been withheld because of the danger of speaking out. Head off the threat at the onset When it co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Germany summons Turkish ambassador, seeks release of jailed journalist - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-germany-gabriel-idUSKBN16722S</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEITl_WhoKf2JidXki7D6Nv8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 18:54:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-germany-gabriel-idUSKBN16722S" target="_blank"&gt;Germany summons Turkish ambassador, seeks release of jailed journalist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Andrea Shalal and Ece Toksabay BERLIN/ANKARA (Reuters) - Berlin summoned Ankara's ambassador on Tuesday to protest the arrest in Turkey of a correspondent for a German newspaper, further fuelling tensions between the two NATO allies as demonstrations took place across German-speaking Europe. Deniz Yucel, a German-Turkish dual national with Die Welt, faces up to 10-1/2 years in prison after being arrested on charges of propaganda in support of a terrorist organization and inciting public violence, his lawyer Veysel Ok told Reuters on Tuesday. "German-Turkey relations are facing one of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Turkey detains Cumhuriyet editor in chief Murat Sabuncu - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/10/turkey-detains-cumhuriyet-editor-chief-murat-sabuncu-161031052448605.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE1tARc6G7ahkiltyqcFOXIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 09:20:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/10/turkey-detains-cumhuriyet-editor-chief-murat-sabuncu-161031052448605.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey detains Cumhuriyet editor in chief Murat Sabuncu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkish police have detained the editor-in-chief of Cumhuriyet, an opposition newspaper, according to media reports. The reports say that along with Murat Sabuncu, nine other employees of the paper, including writers, were detained on Monday morning. Their residences were being searched, the reports said. Prosecutors have issued detention warrants for a total of 13 executives and writers at the newspaper, including the publication's chairman, who is abroad, media reports said. The detentions come as authorities cracks down on anyone suspected of links to Fethullah Gulen, the US-based religi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Turkish court remands four opposition newspaper staff in custody, releases seven - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-newspaper-idUSKBN1AD2I5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECmTEkIWEMmV2AVLovbY9gAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 19:20:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-newspaper-idUSKBN1AD2I5" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish court remands four opposition newspaper staff in custody, releases seven&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Can Sezer ISTANBUL (Reuters) - A Turkish court ruled on Friday that four prominent members of an opposition newspaper must remain in detention but freed seven others for the duration of the trial, in a case seen by critics of President Tayyip Erdogan as an attack on free speech. Since the first hearing in the case on Monday, hundreds of people have protested outside the central Istanbul court against the prosecution of 17 writers, executives and lawyers of the secularist Cumhuriyet newspaper. The court remanded in custody the chairman of Cumhuriyet's executive committee Akin Atalay, its ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>President Erdoğan is now targeting anyone who doesn’t support him - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/nov/07/president-erdogan-turkey-leader-crackdown-media-internet-kurdish</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBejn7B9AMKlOw3cvxYcSfQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 10:00:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/nov/07/president-erdogan-turkey-leader-crackdown-media-internet-kurdish" target="_blank"&gt;President Erdoğan is now targeting anyone who doesn’t support him&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freedom of expression and the free press are under threat in Turkey. Last Saturday, the government closed down Tîroj, a Kurdish and Turkish literary magazine I had been due to contribute to. Tîroj (“light beam” in Kurdish) was special to me as it is published in Kurdish, my mother tongue, and a language which has been forbidden in schools and government institutions for 100 years. Related: Turkey shuts 15 media outlets and arrests opposition editor But it was not alone. Fourteen other media outlets, including Jinha, an all-female Kurdish news agency, and Evrensel Kültür, a socialist cultura...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Turkish newspaper chairman detained at Istanbul airport - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/nov/11/turkish-newspaper-chairman-detained-at-istanbul-airport</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOFRvEVDzo6DbfUFGgUUuS0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 10:42:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/nov/11/turkish-newspaper-chairman-detained-at-istanbul-airport" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish newspaper chairman detained at Istanbul airport&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey has detained the chairman of the opposition newspaper Cumhuriyet, which has been the target of an intensifying crackdown since July’s failed coup. Akın Atalay was taken into custody at Istanbul’s airport after arriving from Germany, said Cumhuriyet, which also saw nine of its staff arrested last week. The paper has in recent years taken a strong line against President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan’s ruling Islamic-rooted Justice and Development party (AKP). Related: President Erdoğan is now targeting anyone who doesn’t support him | Burhan Sönmez Atalay was targeted by a warrant that was part...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Turkish PM urges opposition head to call off 20-day protest march - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-march-idUSKBN19722J</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE9LF2WB8ulsJ0XOuMdKMdUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 15:49:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-march-idUSKBN19722J" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish PM urges opposition head to call off 20-day protest march&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Daren Butler and Tuvan Gumrukcu ISTANBUL/ANKARA (Reuters) - Turkey's prime minister urged the head of the main opposition party on Friday to end a 425 kilometer (265 mile) march from Ankara to Istanbul in protest over the jailing of one of his lawmakers, saying justice "cannot be sought on the streets". Kemal Kilicdaroglu, 68, head of the secularist Republican People's Party (CHP), set out on the march on Thursday after Enis Berberoglu was jailed for 25 years on spying charges. He was seen off by thousands of supporters and has garnered much attention in a country where government domina...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Turkey's opposition begins protest march over MP's imprisonment - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jun/15/turkeys-opposition-begins-protest-march-over-mps-imprisonment-enis-berberoglu</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGMVDvqXHttbv-4Du2iEQzkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:57:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jun/15/turkeys-opposition-begins-protest-march-over-mps-imprisonment-enis-berberoglu" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey's opposition begins protest march over MP's imprisonment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey’s main opposition party has begun a march from the country’s capital, Ankara, to its largest city, Istanbul, to protest against the imprisonment of an MP who was sentenced to 25 years in jail for allegedly leaking information to the press. “We are facing dictatorial rule,” said Kemal Kılıçdaroğlu, the leader of the Republican People’s party (CHP), as he set out on the march. “We don’t want to live in a country where there is no justice. We are saying enough is enough.” Hundreds of protesters appeared to have joined the march, carrying banners that said “adalet” or “justice” as they s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Turkey Detains Head of Opposition Newspaper - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/turkey-detains-head-of-opposition-newspaper/3592168.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKcTLJETd13ut0w8D8mAOPQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 14:56:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/turkey-detains-head-of-opposition-newspaper/3592168.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey Detains Head of Opposition Newspaper&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey on Friday detained the board chairman of the opposition daily Cumhuriyet, following the arrests of nine staff members last week, the newspaper reported. Police stopped Akin Atalay at Istanbul's airport on his arrival from Germany, said Cumhuriyet, which has been a strong critic of President Recep Tayyip Erdogan's ruling Justice and Development Party (AKP). Atalay was held for a while at the airport and later was ushered into a police vehicle, which took him to the Istanbul Security Directorate. Cumhuriyet said he is being held in connection with an investigation into "terrorist activ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Turkey hands opposition lawmaker 25 years jail time in espionage case - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-lawmaker-idUSKBN19521W</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOaRYS8IlkrkSVb97tLQ4EEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 14:09:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-lawmaker-idUSKBN19521W" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey hands opposition lawmaker 25 years jail time in espionage case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANKARA (Reuters) - A Turkish court on Wednesday sentenced opposition Republican People's Party (CHP) lawmaker Enis Berberoglu to 25 years in prison over spying charges. Berberoglu, the first CHP lawmaker to be handed prison time since the lifting of parliamentary immunities last year, was accused of providing an opposition newspaper with video purporting to show Turkey's intelligence agency trucking weapons into Syria. A report in the secular Cumhuriyet newspaper in May 2015 said that trucks allegedly owned by Turkey's state intelligence service were found to contain weapons and ammunition ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Turkish journalists go on trial accused of waging 'asymmetric war' - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/turkey-security-newspaper-idUSL5N1KF0KQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBV6DsWtNZtaRDudSuiYXl4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 09:44:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/turkey-security-newspaper-idUSL5N1KF0KQ" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish journalists go on trial accused of waging 'asymmetric war'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Can Sezer ISTANBUL (Reuters) - Seventeen employees of a Turkish opposition newspaper went on trial on Monday accused of supporting a terrorist group, a case seen by government critics as a further sign that freedom of expression is under attack. "Journalism is not a crime," chanted several hundred people gathered outside the central Istanbul court to protest against the prosecution of writers, executives and lawyers of the staunchly secularist Cumhuriyet newspaper. The hearing coincides with an escalating dispute with Germany over the arrest in Turkey of 10 rights activists, including on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Thousands rally in Turkey after opposition lawmaker jailed - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-lawmaker-idUSKBN1960VE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdhNqTnawuYrdidFU8ryroqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 10:53:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-lawmaker-idUSKBN1960VE" target="_blank"&gt;Thousands rally in Turkey after opposition lawmaker jailed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Ece Toksabay and Gulsen Solaker ANKARA (Reuters) - Several thousand people took to the streets of Turkey's two biggest cities on Thursday to protest against a 25-year prison sentence handed down to an opposition lawmaker on spying charges. A court sentenced Enis Berberoglu, a lawmaker from the main opposition Republican People's Party (CHP), on charges of military espionage on Wednesday. It alleged he gave an opposition newspaper a video purporting to show Turkey's intelligence agency trucking weapons into Syria. He is the first lawmaker from the secular CHP to be jailed in a government ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Interpol Helps Dictators Hunt Down Dissidents—and Me - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/interpol-helps-dictators-hunt-down-dissidentsand-me</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGKtis0HY9o-ILPHPsyveKgqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLzdlwI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 09:49:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/interpol-helps-dictators-hunt-down-dissidentsand-me" target="_blank"&gt;Interpol Helps Dictators Hunt Down Dissidents—and Me&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast In September, I applied for a visa for Iraq, a country I travel to fairly frequently for work. It wasn’t granted initially and after some digging I learned that there was an Interpol notice attached to my name. Interpol, the International Criminal Police Organization, has 192 member countries. And one of them apparently was seeking my arrest and extradition. In 2016, shortly after the failed coup in Turkey, I was arrested and imprisoned there. I was accused of being a CIA agent, an allegation made against countless people, and eventually I was released,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Turkey pledges accountability in Saudi probe; critics wonder - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/cb543e09ec1c48df83d67857e7c8e451</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQR1s9EWX1VW0x-cGaPYs4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 13:54:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/cb543e09ec1c48df83d67857e7c8e451" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey pledges accountability in Saudi probe; critics wonder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under global scrutiny, Turkey vows to get to the bottom of the alleged killing of a Saudi journalist at the kingdom's consulate in Istanbul. But some observers see a double standard in promises of transparency from a government accused of stifling freedom of expression. Since an attempted coup in 2016, critics say President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has turned Turkey into an increasingly authoritarian state, using emergency powers to arrest tens of thousands of suspects, purging many more from state institutions and jailing dozens of journalists. Officials have even admitted that they seized doz...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Erdogan: Turkish journalist should be extradited - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/6e60cc6619554673be81c1eb75c6da5e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPP8WYhSam_YLegvD_JENqAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 11:51:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/6e60cc6619554673be81c1eb75c6da5e" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Erdogan: Turkish journalist should be extradited&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The Latest on the Turkish president's visit to Germany (all times local): 1:45 p.m. Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan says prominent Turkish journalist Can Dundar, who is in exile in Germany, is a convicted spy and should be extradited to Turkey. Erdogan told reporters Friday: "At this moment this person is, according to Turkish law, a convict, a spy (who has) revealed state secrets." He was speaking at a joint news conference with German Chancellor Angela Merkel. Dundar was convicted in 2016 of revealing state secrets after his newspaper published photographs suggesting ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Journalist calling for press freedom ejected from Berlin news conference - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/28/europe/erdogan-germany-visit-grm-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAMDF8PuznX2X_mM4HR-6ZoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 19:46:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/28/europe/erdogan-germany-visit-grm-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Journalist calling for press freedom ejected from Berlin news conference&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man calling for freedom of the press and the release of journalists held in Turkey was removed by security from a news conference between Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan and German Chancellor Angela Merkel in Berlin on Friday. He was later identified as Turkish journalist and general secretary of the European Turkish Journalists' Association Adil Yigit, who lives in Germany and is a staunch critic of Erdogan. The news conference, held on the second day of a controversial state visit by the Turkish leader, was well underway when Yigit, sitting on one of the front rows with a camera,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Germany, Turkey seek better ties but concede little ground - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/9ac7935a4cca4d1ea79e88960a7ab91d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIXnuvjcI9qKbClsaSiy5ZYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 19:49:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/9ac7935a4cca4d1ea79e88960a7ab91d" target="_blank"&gt;Germany, Turkey seek better ties but concede little ground&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German Chancellor Angela Merkel and Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan conceded little ground on issues dividing their countries after meeting Friday, but stressed the importance of the two NATO allies working together as they sought to improve acrimonious relations. The two nations have clashed over numerous issues in recent years, including Turkey's jailing of German journalists and a German parliament resolution labeling the early-20th century killing of Armenians in Turkey as genocide. Turkey vehemently denies that the massacre was genocide and insists it was part of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Turkey's Erdogan, in Berlin, pledges EU visa push - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-turkey/turkeys-erdogan-in-berlin-pledges-eu-visa-push-idUSKCN1M8296</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDlYzqzquUoBbmus5SjjsvcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 19:29:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-turkey/turkeys-erdogan-in-berlin-pledges-eu-visa-push-idUSKCN1M8296" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey's Erdogan, in Berlin, pledges EU visa push&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey aims to win easier access to the European Union for its citizens, President Tayyip Erdogan said in Berlin on Friday during a state visit that aims to repair relations with Germany after bitter disputes. Turkey would move to meet the EU's criteria for achieving visa liberalization, he said on the second day of a visit also intended to improve ties with the European Union after the freeze that followed a failed coup in 2016. Facing an economic crisis aggravated by U.S. sanctions, Erdogan is hoping to attract more private investment from the economic superpower on Turkey's doorstep. "Vi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Turkish court orders release of jailed opposition lawmaker: Anadolu - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-court-lawmaker/turkish-court-orders-release-of-jailed-opposition-lawmaker-anadolu-idUSKCN1M02CS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPV8P7iZonOTNQ6drtO1tA4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 22:08:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-court-lawmaker/turkish-court-orders-release-of-jailed-opposition-lawmaker-anadolu-idUSKCN1M02CS" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish court orders release of jailed opposition lawmaker: Anadolu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Turkish court ordered the release of a jailed opposition lawmaker on Thursday who had been sentenced to more than five years for disclosing government secrets, the state-run Anadolu news agency said. Enis Berberoglu was the first lawmaker from the main opposition Republican People's Party (CHP) to be jailed amid government purges following a failed military coup in 2016. Berberoglu was initially sentenced in June 2017, to 25 years for espionage on charges that he gave an opposition newspaper a video purporting to show Turkey's intelligence agency trucking weapons into Syria. He denied the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Merkel gives cool reception to Erdogan’s call for detente - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ded204f4-c307-11e8-95b1-d36dfef1b89a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEMgWPS9hT1aWlnhoXLkhfIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 15:41:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ded204f4-c307-11e8-95b1-d36dfef1b89a" target="_blank"&gt;Merkel gives cool reception to Erdogan’s call for detente&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angela Merkel offered a cool reception to Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan’s call for a new detente with Germany, stressing the “far-reaching differences” between Berlin and Ankara on issues such as press freedom and human rights. The German chancellor also firmly rebuffed Mr Erdogan’s demand that the movement of the Muslim cleric Fethullah Gulen, which he blames for the attempted coup in 2016 that left 250 dead, be designated a terrorist organisation. But she also said that there was “much that unites us”, stressing Turkey’s status as a Nato ally and its role in helping to stem refug...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>#WeAreArrested / Day of the Living review – voices from the dungeon and of the disappeared - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/stage/2018/jun/06/wearearrested-day-living-review-other-place-stratford-avon</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEuKX-LqOctt6OoDaOET90oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 19:00:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/stage/2018/jun/06/wearearrested-day-living-review-other-place-stratford-avon" target="_blank"&gt;#WeAreArrested / Day of the Living review – voices from the dungeon and of the disappeared&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Newspaper editor Can Dündar was arrested in November 2015 and imprisoned in Silivri prison in Turkey for his role in exposing state intelligence involvement in arming Islamist militants in Syria. During 92 days of solitary confinement, he wrote a memoir longhand. In its preface, he states: “This book is the product of a collective act of solidarity.” That collective defiance continues in Pippa Hill and Sophie Ivatts’s excellent adaptation of We Are Arrested. The play is both a relatively faithful dramatisation of the book and an audacious attempt to interrogate where else its story could ta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>#WeAreArrested/Day of the Living, The Other Place, Stratford-upon-Avon - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d87f7c86-696a-11e8-b6eb-4acfcfb08c11</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOIK8xACF8ZAT5WXd-ZW7r4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 13:57:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d87f7c86-696a-11e8-b6eb-4acfcfb08c11" target="_blank"&gt;#WeAreArrested/Day of the Living, The Other Place, Stratford-upon-Avon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The re-opening in 2016 of the Royal Shakespeare Company’s The Other Place was intended consciously to plug into the spirit of radicalism of its first director, Buzz Goodbody, in the 1970s. Unfortunately, “self-consciously” might be a better adverb. TOP has largely been restricted to periodic “Mischief” mini-festivals, presenting work that often toils to be provocative, as with this latest double-bill. #WeAreArrested is an adaptation from Can Dündar’s account of his imprisonment without trial in Turkey for alleged espionage in printing, as editor of the newspaper Cumhuriyet, details of his g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Berlin and Ankara trade barbs over Ozil-Gundogan-Erdogan meeting - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/05/berlin-ankara-trade-barbs-ozil-gundogan-erdogan-meeting-180515125455763.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENXYMDAqfcklpXBn2y_l0rEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw4r4I</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 17:47:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/05/berlin-ankara-trade-barbs-ozil-gundogan-erdogan-meeting-180515125455763.html" target="_blank"&gt;Berlin and Ankara trade barbs over Ozil-Gundogan-Erdogan meeting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior Turkish official has slammed the German football federation, media and several politicians after they criticised two German players of Turkish descent who met Turkey's President Recep Tayyip Erdogan as he seeks re-election. Erdogan met Arsenal's Mesut Ozil and Manchester City's Ilkay Gundogan during an official visit to the United Kingdom. Both also play for the German national team. Turkey's striker Cenk Tosun was also at the gathering. Photos taken in London show the players handing jerseys to the Turkish president and were published on social media on Monday by Erdogan's ruling ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Turkey: 14 Cumhuriyet staff sentenced on 'terror' charges - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/04/turkey-14-cumhuriyet-staff-sentenced-terror-charges-180425190539778.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOl0K35MV8MMWDnAgohLv7AqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 21:26:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/04/turkey-14-cumhuriyet-staff-sentenced-terror-charges-180425190539778.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey: 14 Cumhuriyet staff sentenced on 'terror' charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Turkish court has handed prison sentences to 14 staff of the Cumhuriyet opposition newspaper on "terrorism" charges, and acquitted three others, according to state media. The sentences for those convicted on Wednesday by the Istanbul-based court ranged from two-and-a-half years to seven-and-a-half years. Among them are renowned journalists, including investigative reporter Ahmet Sik, who was sentenced to seven years and six months. Journalist and columnist Kadri Gursel was sentenced to 30 months. The court handed cartoonist Musa Kart a three-year-and-nine-month sentence, while Cumhuriyet ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Turkish court jails 14 staff from opposition newspaper - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/04/25/turkish-court-jails-14-staff-opposition-newspaper/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL16VcW5ljt2njQA8LAKMEsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 20:04:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/04/25/turkish-court-jails-14-staff-opposition-newspaper/" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish court jails 14 staff from opposition newspaper&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Turkish court sentenced 14 staff of the country’s leading opposition newspaper to up to seven years in prison on terrorism charges on Wednesday, according to the newspaper. Cumhuriyet Editor-in-chief Murat Sabuncu and investigative reporter Ahmet Sik were sentenced to seven years and six months in prison, according to Turkey’s state news agency. The journalists remain free pending appeal. Three of 17 defendants were acquitted. Chairman Akin Atalay was convicted but will be released after already spending more than 500 days in jail. The journalists were accused of supporting US-based cler...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Turkish court sentences more than dozen Cumhuriyet staff to prison on terrorism charges - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-newspaper/turkish-court-sentences-15-of-cumhuriyet-staff-to-prison-on-terrorism-charges-idUSKBN1HW2PK</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFJmwSOu98iIfj5iuDh5S8kqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 20:29:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-newspaper/turkish-court-sentences-15-of-cumhuriyet-staff-to-prison-on-terrorism-charges-idUSKBN1HW2PK" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish court sentences more than dozen Cumhuriyet staff to prison on terrorism charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Ali Kucukgocmen ISTANBUL (Reuters) - A Turkish court on Wednesday sentenced 14 staff of the opposition Cumhuriyet newspaper to prison on terrorism charges and acquitted three, one of their lawyers said, in a case that has sparked global outrage over press freedom under Tayyip Erdogan. The court handed down sentences ranging from 2 1/2 to 7 1/2 years to the Cumhuriyet staff, lawyer Ozden Ozdemir told Reuters. Another defendant in the case, who was not employed by the paper and had been charged for his activities on Twitter, got the stiffest sentence, 10 years, Ozdemir said. Ahmet Sik, a w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The agonies of writing from exile - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2168d1da-31d6-11e8-b5bf-23cb17fd1498</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL92GYaCuhSTqrvCfj5SXx4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 11:26:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2168d1da-31d6-11e8-b5bf-23cb17fd1498" target="_blank"&gt;The agonies of writing from exile&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I first met Can Dündar in 2016, just before he was sentenced to nearly six years in jail. His crime was reporting on the Turkish government’s arming of Syrian rebels for Cumhuriyet, the popular leftist news­paper he edited at the time. In the moments before his sentencing, he narrowly escaped an assassination attempt outside the courthouse when his wife Dilek tackled the gunman. Dündar was abroad at the time of the 2016 coup attempt against President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan, awaiting his appeal, and was advised by his lawyer not to return to Turkey. He has been in Berlin ever since on a “Write...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Turkish Court Orders Release of Journalists During Their Trial - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/turkish-court-orders-release-journalists-during-their-trial/4288389.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAl3OZNgadYp9DW7ubMW1CYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 22:45:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/turkish-court-orders-release-journalists-during-their-trial/4288389.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish Court Orders Release of Journalists During Their Trial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Turkish court ruled on Friday that two journalists should be released for the duration of their trial for subversion, a lawyer at the courthouse said. Murat Sabuncu, editor-in-chief of the newspaper Cumhuriyet, and writer Ahmet Sik were ordered released, the lawyer said. However, Cumhuriyet said that its attorney, Akin Atalay, was remanded in custody until the next hearing, on March 16. Prosecutors charge that Cumhuriyet was effectively taken over by supporters of Fethullah Gulen, a U.S.-based cleric blamed by the government for a 2016 failed coup. The newspaper and staff deny the charges...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Turkey releases two more journalists on bail - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/mar/10/turkey-releases-two-more-journalists-on-bail</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI7IRPPE7wDEZkYJVmz3mosqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 03:13:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/mar/10/turkey-releases-two-more-journalists-on-bail" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey releases two more journalists on bail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two Turkish journalists have been freed on bail after over a year behind bars in the trial on terror-related charges of staff from the opposition Cumhuriyet newspaper. The case is seen as a test of press freedom under President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan. Cumhuriyet’s editor-in-chief Murat Sabuncu and investigative reporter Ahmet Şik were ordered to be freed by the judge after a day-long hearing. However they remain under charge and on trial. One more detained suspect, the paper’s chairman Akin Atalay, was ordered to stay in jail. The three were the last remaining suspects in the case to be held ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>RSC to explore press freedom in play about exiled Turkish editor - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/stage/2018/jan/18/rsc-explores-press-freedom-in-wearearrested-play-about-turkish-editor-can-dundar</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPCyssiLTCYSQAg5fxEqlTcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 07:00:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/stage/2018/jan/18/rsc-explores-press-freedom-in-wearearrested-play-about-turkish-editor-can-dundar" target="_blank"&gt;RSC to explore press freedom in play about exiled Turkish editor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The dangers posed to a free and independent press by governments are to be explored in a play commissioned by the Royal Shakespeare Company. The play is based on the true story of Can Dündar, a Turkish newspaper editor sentenced to jail and now in exile after exposing covert state arms deals with Islamic fundamentalists in Syria. However, the RSC’s deputy artistic director said it would be more than a biography. It felt like a universal story, one that could happen anywhere, including the UK, Erica Whyman said. “It is also our world, it is about things which could be taken away from us toda...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item></channel></rss>