<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Trade agreement - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZtYzJzMUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-SG&amp;gl=SG&amp;ceid=SG:en</link><language>en-SG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:06:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Singapore, China sign several agreements, including free trade agreement upgrade - Channel NewsAsia</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/singapore-china-sign-free-trade-agreement-upgrade-10922790</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiZGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNoYW5uZWxuZXdzYXNpYS5jb20vbmV3cy9hc2lhL3NpbmdhcG9yZS1jaGluYS1zaWduLWZyZWUtdHJhZGUtYWdyZWVtZW50LXVwZ3JhZGUtMTA5MjI3OTDSAQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/singapore-china-sign-free-trade-agreement-upgrade-10922790" target="_blank"&gt;Singapore, China sign several agreements, including free trade agreement upgrade&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Channel NewsAsia&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China and Singapore have signed a slew of agreements, including the upgrade of a bilateral free trade pact, which will allow greater market access for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.channelnewsasia.com">Channel NewsAsia</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/IEES513EBE0I0vubaOP3lExBtyGrVZLGa9YbMKO-7IsmtC5bzocsxJhDbSuE0YPkORvIsoi300LF-mD3Oa0ZVxm_cAHP5uwTTFiE6vc4rGgGBkCzG7VBXl60Ag6Xc9oQx8lAa6J_1tQvjMtxka8WxmLV7EO-zmKV68Hew5smuzfFDv_S-elVrgr54vVEW0m2G58Bh9nYj9EU_Q=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Everything that is wrong with the prime minister’s proposed Brexit deal is also wrong with Norway Plus - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/norway-plus-brexit-deal-eea-customs-union-details-vote-latest-a8672836.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEADj3I4oldOmYEcxk6pZC84qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/norway-plus-brexit-deal-eea-customs-union-details-vote-latest-a8672836.html" target="_blank"&gt;Everything that is wrong with the prime minister’s proposed Brexit deal is also wrong with Norway Plus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As undeliverable promises collide with improbable parliamentary arithmetic, MPs are searching frantically for a way out of Brexit’s burning building. For some, the idea of “Norway Plus” now looks like a potential bolthole. As an example of a country which is not a member of the European Union but which, as part of the European Economic Area (EEA), clings closely to its economic structures, some politicians see Norway – with the addition of a customs union – as a compromise between Leavers and Remainers. But, as is spelled out in a new report by the People’s Vote campaign, MPs would be makin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Norwegian politicians reject UK's Norway-plus Brexit plan - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/dec/07/norwegian-politicians-reject-uks-norway-plus-brexit-plan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAhGp4nVEIy8GRp_3I54JGkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:33:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/dec/07/norwegian-politicians-reject-uks-norway-plus-brexit-plan" target="_blank"&gt;Norwegian politicians reject UK's Norway-plus Brexit plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senior Norwegian politicians and business figures have rejected Norway-plus, the increasingly touted British cross-party plan for the UK to leave the EU but join Norway in a free trade trade area inside the EU single market. They attacked the idea as “neither in Norway nor the UK’s interest”. The UK would need Norway’s permission to join its Efta club. The rejection is a blow to an influential cross-party group led by the Tory MP Nick Boles, with private cabinet support, that is looking for a plan B if, as expected, MPs reject Theresa May’s deal next Tuesday. Related: Brexit: Hancock confir...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>It’s about services, stupid - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ec600b6c-f9e3-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYopi5DQCXC0fSHQXUSTMYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:32:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ec600b6c-f9e3-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;It’s about services, stupid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FT subscribers can click here to receive Brussels Briefing every day by email. The endless talk of backstops in the Brexit debate has somewhat overshadowed the fact that the UK is a service-based economy, and for a big chunk of its exports, customs borders are not really the point. Services trade has been relatively absent for much of the discussion about Britain’s relationship with the EU, most likely for several interconnected reasons. One, the UK’s service industries have been comparatively reticent about lobbying, or at least grousing in public. Two, the inability of accountants to sell...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Financial services exports to EU face 59% fall, warns think-tank - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b5fc4a56-f978-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPB-yhlWm6EVeoZtJpFFQSMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:01:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b5fc4a56-f978-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Financial services exports to EU face 59% fall, warns think-tank&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain’s exports of financial services to the EU could fall by almost 60 per cent as a result of leaving the single market, marking a “sea change” in the services sector that drives the UK economy, according to new research by the Centre for European Reform. The think-tank sought to assess the impact of new trading barriers on the key areas of services where Britain currently has a comparative advantage — finance, insurance, law and accountancy. It estimates, in a paper published on Tuesday, that exports of financial services, minus insurance and pensions, would drop from their level of £2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Labour could do a better Brexit deal. Give us the chance - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/jeremy-corbyn-general-election-brexit-labour-theresa-may</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFxXDusU-LvKrMItWuWiWP8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:53:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/jeremy-corbyn-general-election-brexit-labour-theresa-may" target="_blank"&gt;Labour could do a better Brexit deal. Give us the chance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The botched Brexit deal that Theresa May has put to parliament this week is a monumental and damaging failure for our country. Instead of the sensible agreement the prime minister could have negotiated, it is a worst-of-all-worlds deal that works for nobody, whether they voted leave or remain. Instead of taking back control, it gives up control. Instead of protecting jobs and living standards, it puts them at risk by failing to put in place the basis for frictionless trade. For two and a half years the Conservatives have been negotiating with themselves, rather than the European Union. The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>China promises prompt action on US trade pact - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/40c07a98e6f243dea5f275ca39640224</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOL_KVbb1yUzjnpaV7JvqHgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:05:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/40c07a98e6f243dea5f275ca39640224" target="_blank"&gt;China promises prompt action on US trade pact&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China's government said Thursday it will promptly carry out a tariff cease-fire with Washington and is confident they can reach a trade agreement, suggesting Beijing wants to avoid disruptions due to the arrest of a tech executive. Talks during the 90 day period during which President Donald Trump has agreed to suspend U.S. tariff hikes will start by focusing on farm goods, energy and automobiles, said a Ministry of Commerce spokesman, Gao Feng. Asked to confirm whether Beijing promised to buy American goods immediately, Gao said China will "immediately implement the consensu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trade deficit hits 10-year high as Americans snap up imports and China shuns soybeans - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-trade-deficit-climbs-to-10-year-high-despite-tariffs-tough-trump-stance-2018-12-06</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQmFcNZOyqt_PiDVkbLGIcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-trade-deficit-climbs-to-10-year-high-despite-tariffs-tough-trump-stance-2018-12-06" target="_blank"&gt;Trade deficit hits 10-year high as Americans snap up imports and China shuns soybeans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ECONOMIC REPORT By Jeffry Bartash Trade deficit rises to $55.5 billion in October, which is highest since 2008 U.S. imports from China, ranging from clothes to Apple iPhones, rose to a record high in October. STR/AFP/Getty Images The numbers: The trade deficit rose in October to a 10-year high amid a record shortfall with China, keeping the U.S. on pace to record the largest annual gap in a decade. The deficit edged up 1.7% to $55.5 billion from a revised $54.6 billion in September, the Commerce Department said Thursday. That’s the biggest shortfall since October 2008, and ironically, it st...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Disagree with May’s Brexit deal? Fine, but be honest about the alternatives - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/brexit-deal-better-theresa-may-europe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHqt3VVG0wdmb-jOcp6goNYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:23:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/brexit-deal-better-theresa-may-europe" target="_blank"&gt;Disagree with May’s Brexit deal? Fine, but be honest about the alternatives&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heaven knows, there are myriad problems with the deal negotiated by the prime minister. A compromise intended to reconcile a badly divided parliament ended up alienating most MPs. Yet what would these opponents of the deal suggest as an alternative? Pose this question, and the crass dishonesty of much of the Brexit debate becomes all too apparent. It’s only fair to start by saying that there are opponents of the deal with more or less credible (let’s leave desirable to one side) alternatives in mind. At one extreme are the no-dealers, happy to take the plunge and then, once the initial conf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Trump: Trade Talks With China Underway - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-if-no-china-trade-deal-possible-i-am-a-tariff-man-/4686228.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBE7HOLs6EdGLuWZG5z9FnsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 16:49:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-if-no-china-trade-deal-possible-i-am-a-tariff-man-/4686228.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump: Trade Talks With China Underway&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump said in a series of tweets Tuesday that talks to secure a trade deal with China "have already started" and if a "fair deal" is reached, "I will happily sign it." Trump's comments come after leaders of the world's two biggest economies agreed Saturday in Argentina to not impose any new tariffs on each other's exports for the next 90 days while they negotiate a detailed trade agreement. Trump declared himself Tuesday "a Tariff Man" who wants "people or countries" with intentions to "raid the great wealth" of the U.S. "to pay for the privilege of doing so." White Ho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Factbox: What happens if the U.S. terminates NAFTA - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-nafta-factbox/factbox-what-happens-if-the-us-terminates-nafta-idUSKBN1O41SW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKlxOz4GmdsRh6UQ_TFkREQqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:10:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-nafta-factbox/factbox-what-happens-if-the-us-terminates-nafta-idUSKBN1O41SW" target="_blank"&gt;Factbox: What happens if the U.S. terminates NAFTA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump said on Saturday he would soon give formal notice to the U.S. Congress to terminate the North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), giving lawmakers six months to approve a new trade deal between the United States, Mexico and Canada to replace it. Trump said that if U.S. lawmakers don't approve the new agreement, then the three countries would revert to the rules of trade that existed before NAFTA came into effect in 1994. It is unclear if Trump has the legal power to terminate NAFTA in the way he has threatened. The opposition Democratic party will soon have a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Record imports push US trade gap to $55.5 billion in October - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/73e93b30c49a4349aea32f2f42249cc5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4O6ulTjITdZxAcKp9SW80qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:58:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/73e93b30c49a4349aea32f2f42249cc5" target="_blank"&gt;Record imports push US trade gap to $55.5 billion in October&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Record imports in October drove the U.S. trade deficit to the highest level in a decade. The Commerce Department said Thursday that the gap between the United States sells and what it buys from foreign countries hit $55.5 billion in October, the fifth straight increase and highest since October 2008. The politically sensitive deficit in the trade of goods with China rose 7.1% to a record $43.1 billion. The goods gap with the European Union widened 65.5% to a record $17.6 billion. Led by shipments of medicine and cars, overall imports rose 0.2% to a record $266.5 billion. E...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Ignore the Brexit scare stories - they have no basis in sound economics - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/comment/brexit-scare-stories-ashoka-mody-imf-bank-of-england-mervyn-king-economics-trade-a8670416.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZL__b5Irc2cbPjcsKrNkkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/comment/brexit-scare-stories-ashoka-mody-imf-bank-of-england-mervyn-king-economics-trade-a8670416.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ignore the Brexit scare stories - they have no basis in sound economics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Bank of England’s prediction that civilization will end with Brexit is merely an effort to outdo in shrillness similar analyses by the UK Treasury and the IMF. All official agencies, trapped in an echo chamber, are competing to paint the grimmest economic consequences of a British exit from the European Union. They are straining so hard because their projected costs of exit have no basis in economic theory or empirical findings. “I don’t understand how you can get that kind of cost without making some big ad hoc assumptions,” tweeted Nobel laureate Paul Krugman. When he uses the express...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Arrest triggers fresh doubts about Trump's ability to deliver on China deal - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/trump-huawei-china-trade/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEORNMRZOtldMNWx23SvdnL4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:27:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/trump-huawei-china-trade/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Arrest triggers fresh doubts about Trump's ability to deliver on China deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The arrest of a top Chinese technology executive should have been a triumphant moment for the Trump administration. Instead, the detention of Chinese tech giant Huawei's chief financial officer, Meng Wanzhou, in Vancouver, British Columbia, triggered a market meltdown Thursday amid uncertainty about whether President Donald Trump can strike a lasting trade deal with Beijing. The volatility put a spotlight on doubts about Trump's ability to deliver on his promises with China -- and exposed a clash between his policy goals in China and his efforts to crack down on technology companies and oth...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Hammond tells MPs Brexit a price worth paying - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0ea57450-f890-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFcg3zJkrwrCSM2h5U7q9BcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:24:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0ea57450-f890-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Hammond tells MPs Brexit a price worth paying&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philip Hammond told MPs on Wednesday that the economic costs of Brexit were a price worth paying to ensure those who voted for Brexit did not feel betrayed in the years ahead. Reflecting on his long-held view that people did not vote for Brexit “to become poorer”, the chancellor said he now thought he had to balance that view against any political backlash from Brexiters in a deeply polarised society. Mr Hammond said a successful Brexit that healed divisions “depends on us executing the instructions of the people from the referendum — leaving the EU — but doing so in a way that minimises th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Trump Tries to Calm Global Markets After Stocks Drop Sharply - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-tries-to-calm-global-markets-after-stocks-drop-sharply-in-response-to-us-china-trade-war/4687911.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECLDCnqp6TX5y_rfTNGYaJAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:43:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-tries-to-calm-global-markets-after-stocks-drop-sharply-in-response-to-us-china-trade-war/4687911.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Tries to Calm Global Markets After Stocks Drop Sharply&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump, who rattled global markets Tuesday after declaring himself "a Tariff Man," predicted in a series of tweets Wednesday the United States and China would negotiate a new trade deal. Trump said China is planning to resume buying U.S. soybeans and natural gas, which he said confirms his claims that China had agreed to start "immediately" buying U.S. products." Trump said he believes "President Xi (Jinping) meant every word of what he said" at their meeting recently in Argentina, including "his promise to me to criminalize the sale of deadly Fentanyl coming into the U...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Backstop bargaining: How the EU could renegotiate the Brexit deal - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/81abb792-f8aa-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP0Qp2xWJOB1UppjyDp9Tm4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 04:00:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/81abb792-f8aa-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Backstop bargaining: How the EU could renegotiate the Brexit deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through gritted teeth, EU negotiators may soon be mounting a rescue operation for Britain’s Brexit deal. If the House of Commons rejects the proposed agreement next week — as many in Westminster expect — a package that German chancellor Angela Merkel lauded as a “masterpiece of diplomacy” will suddenly be placed on Brussels’ life support. Depending on the scale of the defeat, British and EU diplomats will begin exploring ways to salvage the deal without resorting to a big renegotiation or inviting a host of new demands from interested parties. Brussels has time-tested techniques to give a n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Trump poised to make NAFTA ultimatum to congressional Democrats - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/trump-nafta-threat/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAWmbKxIrqQ2YX29dRZ7d-QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:43:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/politics/trump-nafta-threat/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump poised to make NAFTA ultimatum to congressional Democrats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid market turmoil over the status of President Donald Trump's trade deal with the Chinese, many American businesses are focused on a different threat: his promise to unilaterally cancel the North American Free Trade Agreement. Trump said on his way home from Argentina that he would give Congress a choice between his US-Mexico-Canada Agreement or USMCA, or none at all. Killing the 1994 trade deal without a successor in placewould invite Mexico and Canada -- both leading importers of US goods -- to put tariffs on items coming from the United States, risking a severe economic shock. "We have...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>China confident on U.S. trade pact, Trump cites Xi's 'strong signals' - Reuters</title><link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-deal/china-says-confident-it-can-implement-trade-deal-with-u-s-idUKKBN1O401H</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKweXIOXpNlMmYSxgnQLLowqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:36:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-deal/china-says-confident-it-can-implement-trade-deal-with-u-s-idUKKBN1O401H" target="_blank"&gt;China confident on U.S. trade pact, Trump cites Xi's 'strong signals'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China expressed confidence on Wednesday that it can reach a trade deal with the United States, a sentiment echoed by U.S. President Donald Trump a day after he warned of more tariffs if the two sides could not resolve their differences. The remarks, by the Chinese Commerce Ministry, follow a period of relative quiet from Beijing after Trump and Chinese leader Xi Jinping reached a temporary truce in their trade war at a meeting over dinner in Argentina on Saturday. In a brief statement, the ministry said China would try to work quickly to implement specific items already agreed upon, as both...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://uk.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump-Xi meeting improves odds for trade deal between U.S. and China, Kudlow says - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-xi-meeting-raises-odds-for-trade-deal-between-us-and-china-kudlow-says-2018-12-03</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC4cJKEbEHa3881je_CXyC0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 20:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-xi-meeting-raises-odds-for-trade-deal-between-us-and-china-kudlow-says-2018-12-03" target="_blank"&gt;Trump-Xi meeting improves odds for trade deal between U.S. and China, Kudlow says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Jeffry Bartash Yet top White House economic adviser says significant hurdles remain Larry Kudlow says President’s Trump face-to-face meeting with Chinese President Xi Jinping could help lead the way to a major trade deal. Kudlow is director of the U.S. National Economic Council and one of the president’s top economic advisers. Bloomberg News Top White House economic counselor Larry Kudlow said there are still lots of hurdles to a broad trade deal with China, but he’s “cautiously optimistic” after a face-to-face meeting between President Trump and China’s leader lead to a t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Is Spain’s threat to ‘veto Brexit’ over Gibraltar just an empty one? - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/brexit-spain-gibraltar-veto-pedro-sanchez-withdrawal-agreement-trade-deal-a8649021.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEXcAp4ph9T0uoXRFzMwwmwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDyxv0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 10:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/brexit-spain-gibraltar-veto-pedro-sanchez-withdrawal-agreement-trade-deal-a8649021.html" target="_blank"&gt;Is Spain’s threat to ‘veto Brexit’ over Gibraltar just an empty one?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I understand Pedro Sanchez’s threat to “veto Brexit” was met with some mirth in Westminster. The Spanish prime minister, of course, cannot singlehandedly stop the UK’s exit from the bloc – and he doesn’t even have a veto on signing the withdrawal agreement. With those facts in mind there is a temptation to think Mr Sanchez has overplayed his hand, and looks silly. Spain will inevitably have to climb down at some point before or during Sunday’s summit – or slink away. Seen from Brussels, though, it feels too early for the Brits to start laughing just yet. Spain, like every other European Uni...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Taking A Second Look: Worries Over Trade Deal Appear To Give Market A Pause - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jjkinahan/2018/12/04/taking-a-second-look-worries-over-trade-deal-appear-to-give-market-a-pause/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKM1qEIyQ1-17eNyFs4RmsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jjkinahan/2018/12/04/taking-a-second-look-worries-over-trade-deal-appear-to-give-market-a-pause/" target="_blank"&gt;Taking A Second Look: Worries Over Trade Deal Appear To Give Market A Pause&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qilai Shen/Bloomberg It looks like “second thoughts” time. Markets around the world fell overnight and pressure seemed to spill into the U.S. as investors considered the U.S. trade deal with China and started worrying about details. Before diving back into the deal and its possible market ramifications for Tuesday, a reminder that U.S. financial markets are closed tomorrow in honor of the late President George H.W. Bush. Trading could be thin today, with some market participants maybe feeling hesitant to take on big new positions with an off-day immediately ahead. Of course, foreign markets...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>China confident of agreeing US trade deal despite Trump's combative stance - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/china-us-trade-deal-trump-tariff-beijing</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL89FZDMK8LerNwm0EKsG9AqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 02:27:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/china-us-trade-deal-trump-tariff-beijing" target="_blank"&gt;China confident of agreeing US trade deal despite Trump's combative stance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China has said that Beijing and Washington will push forward with trade negotiations in the next 90 days and it is confident that an agreement can be reached but doubts remain over whether the two sides can resolve their deep differences. The commerce ministry, in a brief statement on its website, also said China would work to implement specific issues already agreed upon as quickly as possible. The ministry’s statement came after the US president, Donald Trump, called himself “a Tariff Man” on Twitter and warned more levies could be imposed on China. The slew of Trump tweets prompted marke...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'A better future': May's arguments for Brexit deal – and the reality - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/dec/04/a-better-future-mays-arguments-for-brexit-deal-and-the-reality</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOidxxuYDdu6rk4GaI84FrEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDHmu8F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 19:51:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/dec/04/a-better-future-mays-arguments-for-brexit-deal-and-the-reality" target="_blank"&gt;'A better future': May's arguments for Brexit deal – and the reality&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the start of five days of debate that the prime minister said would “set the course” for the country for decades to come, Theresa May made a series of claims about the deal she struck with Brussels that will be put to a vote in parliament on 11 December. Here are the main pillars of the argument May made in the House of Commons at the start of the debate, and analysis of whether they stand up. A better future May said there could be a “better future outside the EU”. But according to Treasury figures, the UK economy will be at best up to 3.9% smaller after 15 years under her Brexit plan, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Trump Boasts of Relations with Xi, New Trade Deal with China - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-boasts-of-relations-with-xi-and-new-trade-deal-with-china/4684511.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF9b4ViYVWvPTIWvhKcNvmsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:13:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-boasts-of-relations-with-xi-and-new-trade-deal-with-china/4684511.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Boasts of Relations with Xi, New Trade Deal with China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump boasted Monday of his "very strong and personal relationship" with Chinese President Xi Jinping, declaring a new U.S.-China trade deal would immediately allow American farmers to sell more of their products to Beijing. Stock markets in Asia and Europe jumped sharply after Trump and Xi, as leaders of the world's two biggest economies, agreed Saturday in Argentina to not impose any new tariffs on each other's exports for the next 90 days while they negotiate a detailed trade agreement. People stand by an electronic stock board of a securities firm in Tokyo, Monday,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Who is behind the push for a post-Brexit free trade deal with the US? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/04/post-brexit-free-trade-deal-us-rightwing-thinktanks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGVyXAUppqD9U0dOafABMS4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 06:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/04/post-brexit-free-trade-deal-us-rightwing-thinktanks" target="_blank"&gt;Who is behind the push for a post-Brexit free trade deal with the US?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is it that hard Brexiters and Donald Trump want so much in a free trade agreement between Britain and the US that they are adamant only a complete break with the EU could achieve it, while Theresa May’s deal scuppers it? The sort of deal they have held up as the Brexit prize is contained in a blueprint published by rightwing thinktank the Institute of Economic Affairs, called Plan A+. Last week it was told to remove Plan A+ from its website by the Charity Commission, for breaking rules on political campaigning. Boris Johnson, David Davis and hard-Brexit European Research Group members ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>China ‘confident’ of US trade deal ‘within 90 days’ - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/25952ec0-f869-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDyAe6AeazSldghs62uviVMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:16:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/25952ec0-f869-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;China ‘confident’ of US trade deal ‘within 90 days’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chinese government said that it was working towards an agreement that could end its trade war with the US by March 1 — Beijing’s first comment on the issue since Donald Trump said he had set a 90-day truce before raising tariffs on Chinese imports. In a brief statement on Wednesday attributed to an unidentified spokesperson and posted on its website, China’s commerce ministry said it was “confident” a trade agreement with the US could be reached “within 90 days”. The comments, however, did nothing to halt a sell-off on Asian and European stock exchanges. US shares had tumbled on Tuesday...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Markets Are Demanding A Trade War Cease-Fire At G20 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kenrapoza/2018/11/30/markets-are-demanding-a-trade-war-cease-fire-at-g20/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEON5JvOReGzTHQHvjZ8A3iYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 18:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kenrapoza/2018/11/30/markets-are-demanding-a-trade-war-cease-fire-at-g20/" target="_blank"&gt;Markets Are Demanding A Trade War Cease-Fire At G20&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump and others eact to Mexico’s President Enrique Peña Neto as he arrives late for a photo at the G20 summit on November 30, 2018, in Buenos Aires. Trump got a new NAFTA deal. The market wants a bilateral trade agreement with China. Or at least no new tariffs. Or else …. (AP Photo/Pablo Martinez Monsivais) Big investors honestly do not know what to make of the U.S.-China trade war. The U.S. economy is up, largely thanks to fiscal stimulus, and the Chinese economy is slowing. Mainland China equities have been in a bear market since Trump announced tariffs on around $50 bil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>‘Trump’s pulling back in trade war with China is political propaganda move’ - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445670-china-trade-war-trump/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAvgd2b7wVJJptTuyZNicZ8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445670-china-trade-war-trump/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Trump’s pulling back in trade war with China is political propaganda move’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going into the holiday season, Trump wanted to see some optimism and pulled back on his aggressive stance with China, but in 90 days it could be back, Jeffrey Tucker from American Institute for Economic Research told RT. President Donald Trump took to Twitter on Tuesday to say that the US has begun negotiating a new trade deal with China, adding that both he and Xi Jinping want the talks to be a success. It came two days after the leaders met in Buenos Aires where they attempted to put an end to their countries' ongoing trade war. RT: Judging by what both American and Chinese officials have...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Trump to notify Congress in 'near future' he will terminate NAFTA - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-budget/trump-likely-to-agree-to-two-week-government-funding-extension-idUSKCN1O103M</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECv1yHfQ9HOXHmiBTziyQYgqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 05:16:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-budget/trump-likely-to-agree-to-two-week-government-funding-extension-idUSKCN1O103M" target="_blank"&gt;Trump to notify Congress in 'near future' he will terminate NAFTA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump said on Saturday he will give formal notice to the U.S. Congress in the near future to terminate the North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), giving six months for lawmakers to approve a new trade deal signed on Friday. "I will be formally terminating NAFTA shortly," Trump told reporters aboard Air Force One on his way home from Argentina. "Just so you understand, when I do that - if for any reason we're unable to make a deal because of Congress then Congress will have a choice" of the new deal or returning to trade rules from before 1994 when NAFTA took effe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>U.S. expects immediate action from China on trade commitments - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china/u-s-expects-immediate-action-from-china-on-trade-commitments-idUSKBN1O201A</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBRHYoR4SH3dIfKeQ37PV6AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 08:00:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china/u-s-expects-immediate-action-from-china-on-trade-commitments-idUSKBN1O201A" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. expects immediate action from China on trade commitments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States expects China to take immediate action to cut tariffs on U.S. car imports and end intellectual property theft and forced technology transfers as the two countries move toward a broader trade deal, a White House official said on Monday. President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping on Saturday agreed to a ceasefire in a trade war that has seen the flow of hundreds of billions of dollars worth of goods between the world's two largest economies disrupted by tariffs. The two leaders agreed to hold off on imposing more tariffs for 90 days starting Dec. 1 while they ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Brexit jargon: From backstop to no deal, 17 key terms explained - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/brexit-jargon-backstop-deal-17-key-terms-explained-181201182945771.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB5hmNbGnSgfHkasKh2DsZAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 13:42:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/brexit-jargon-backstop-deal-17-key-terms-explained-181201182945771.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit jargon: From backstop to no deal, 17 key terms explained&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much like the questions around the UK's future relationship with the European Union, the terminology thrown up by Brexit is complex, confusing and contentious. Here is your brief guide to Brexit jargon, with an approximate reading time of five minutes: Article 50 The exit clause within the Lisbon Treaty, the terms of which form the constitutional basis of the European Union. A member state must invoke the treaty before it can formally and legally leave the bloc. The UK triggered Article 50 on 29 March 2017, becoming the first EU member to do so. Backstop A safety net provision within the wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>US, Canada and Mexico formally sign USMCA trade deal - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e84a6ec2-f4a3-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECF-7JQRQnrO4qIf_74T3R0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 13:35:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e84a6ec2-f4a3-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;US, Canada and Mexico formally sign USMCA trade deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The leaders of the US, Canada and Mexico on Friday formally signed the agreement to replace Nafta on the sidelines of the G20 summit in Argentina. President Donald Trump, Canadian prime minister Justin Trudeau, and outgoing Mexican president Enrique Peña Nieto inked a new trade deal dubbed USMCA (although some Canadians are calling it CUSMA), which was agreed to early last month following months of tough negotiations. It has been estimated that it will rule over $1trn of trade. After protesters launched the ‘Trump baby’ balloon in central Buenos Aires, the US president called the trade deal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Britain should have no fear in pursuing a WTO Brexit - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/82902f9e-f4a4-11e8-938a-543765795f99</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENNa-v4QCkfT-KnZLEEC0qEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 18:00:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/82902f9e-f4a4-11e8-938a-543765795f99" target="_blank"&gt;Britain should have no fear in pursuing a WTO Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The very fact that the entire machinery of the British government is devoted to re-hashing “ Project Fear” tells you everything you need to know about Theresa May’s proposed withdrawal agreement. It is not Brexit. Whether through weakness or design, it is a thinly disguised attempt to pull the wool over people’s eyes — led by a set of people who are wedded to the idea of staying in the EU. Remember when the prime minister spoke of a “Brexit prize”? Mrs May recognised then, as many of us still do, that one of the main reasons people voted to Leave was to take back control of our trade and re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Macron warns EU-Mercosur deal hangs on Bolsonaro - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/da19561c-f41f-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO52E7P_CIw0oFq4Na2M218qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 21:53:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/da19561c-f41f-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;Macron warns EU-Mercosur deal hangs on Bolsonaro&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;French president Emmanuel Macron threw cold water over the prospects of a long-awaited trade accord between Mercosur and the EU. On Thursday in Argentina, Macron said he is unwilling to sign a “broad trade” deal if Brazil’s incoming far-right leader, Jair Bolsonaro, pulls his country out of the Paris climate accord. “There has been a major political shift in Brazil recently, so Mercosur has to consider the impact of this change,” Mr Macron said, referring to the election of Mr Bolsonaro, during a joint press conference with Argentina’s President Mauricio Macri, who is hosting the G20 summit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Argentina, China Sign Deals Strengthening Ties After G-20 - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/argentina-china-sign-deals-strengthening-ties-after-g-20/4684120.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGnN1u7IdA1iILH236iMI-gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 02:31:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/argentina-china-sign-deals-strengthening-ties-after-g-20/4684120.html" target="_blank"&gt;Argentina, China Sign Deals Strengthening Ties After G-20&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China's president on Sunday signed new trade deals with Argentina as the Asian giant expands its growing role in Latin American economies. Presidents Mauricio Macri of Argentina and Xi Jinping of China announced the more than 30 agriculture and investment deals during a state visit following the Group of 20 summit of leaders in Buenos Aires. The deals include an agreement to export Argentine cherries to China and an expansion of a currency swap. China is among Argentina's top export markets, especially for agricultural commodities that are the engine of its economy. It is also one of Argent...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The agenda for the Economic G20: bilateral, trade agreements and VIP dinners - infobae</title><link>https://www.infobae.com/america/g20-summit-2018/2018/11/28/the-agenda-for-the-economic-g20-bilateral-trade-agreements-and-vip-dinners/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPyiV9X9EECZ9dOyTaaDHMcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowyPhzMO2BDDDCt60D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 22:46:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.infobae.com/america/g20-summit-2018/2018/11/28/the-agenda-for-the-economic-g20-bilateral-trade-agreements-and-vip-dinners/" target="_blank"&gt;The agenda for the Economic G20: bilateral, trade agreements and VIP dinners&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;infobae&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year, the Argentine presidency of the G20 will be marked by the economic definitions that emerge from the thousands of meetings that took place throughout the year in all official and unofficial peer groups. The formal announcement of each Leaders Summit has a long-term impact on economic policies, and the finance track is one of the most important because of the suggested guidelines on international trade and economic development. The consequences of the economic meetings during the next few days are not to be dismissed: the G20 members represent 85% of the global gross product, 66% o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.infobae.com">infobae</source></item><item><title>Trump to give Congress formal notice he will 'shortly' terminate Nafta - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/02/trump-terminate-nafta-formal-notice-congress</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0BiEogQds3tv7e25WpZm8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 15:04:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/02/trump-terminate-nafta-formal-notice-congress" target="_blank"&gt;Trump to give Congress formal notice he will 'shortly' terminate Nafta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump said on Saturday he will give formal notice to Congress in the near future to terminate the North American Free Trade Agreement (Nafta), giving six months for lawmakers to approve a new trade deal signed on Friday. Related: Donald Trump and Xi Jinping declare trade truce at G20 “I will be formally terminating Nafta shortly,” Trump told reporters aboard Air Force One on his way home from the G20 summit in Argentina. “Just so you understand, when I do that – if for any reason we’re unable to make a deal because of Congress then Congress will have a choice” of the new deal or retu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>North Korea Studies Vietnam for Development Ideas - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/vietnam-north-korea/4684191.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI2MyY3-pmimbkZGzLNjIeIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 06:15:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/vietnam-north-korea/4684191.html" target="_blank"&gt;North Korea Studies Vietnam for Development Ideas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vietnam, a fast-growing country that’s liberal on trade and has friends in multiple countries, is offering to help advance North Korea, a fellow communist state that’s impoverished as well as distrusted by the West. Vietnamese deputy Prime Minister Pham Binh Minh said his country was "ready to share" with North Korea its socio-economic development and nation-building experience, Viet Nam News reported Friday. North Korean Foreign Minister Ri Yong Ho visited the Southeast Asian country from Thursday to Sunday. The host's offer probably means teaching North Korea to prosper economically under...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>U.S., Canada, Mexico sign trade deal, Trump shrugs off Congress hurdle - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-g20-argentina-usmca/us-canada-mexico-sign-trade-deal-trump-shrugs-off-congress-hurdle-idUSKCN1NZ0HE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECuk4JlxNcpgLX6P-pAQG6cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:23:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-g20-argentina-usmca/us-canada-mexico-sign-trade-deal-trump-shrugs-off-congress-hurdle-idUSKCN1NZ0HE" target="_blank"&gt;U.S., Canada, Mexico sign trade deal, Trump shrugs off Congress hurdle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States, Canada and Mexico signed a North American trade pact on Friday, with President Donald Trump brushing aside concerns that he could face difficulties getting the deal through the U.S. Congress. The leaders of the three countries agreed on a deal in principle to replace the North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), which governs more than $1.2 trillion of mutual trade, after acrimonious negotiations concluded on Sept. 30. Friday's signing potentially ends a big source of irritation for the U.S. administration as it pivots to a much bigger trade fight with China that threa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Brexit backstop would be 'practical barrier' to trade deal, leaked paper says - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/dec/02/theresa-may-in-battle-over-brexit-legal-advice-as-charm-offensive-begins</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMlqmePkwYHPYS5a58L0KIoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 17:12:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/dec/02/theresa-may-in-battle-over-brexit-legal-advice-as-charm-offensive-begins" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit backstop would be 'practical barrier' to trade deal, leaked paper says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A leaked draft legal analysis produced for the European scrutiny committee by in-house lawyers warns that the UK will face “a practical barrier” to striking a trade deal with the US or other non-EU countries if the country falls into the backstop customs arrangements. The remarks, contained within a draft paper that leaked on Monday morning, emerged hours before the attorney general, Geoffrey Cox, was scheduled to brief the Commons about his advice on the Brexit deal negotiated by May. The 27-page document, dated 26 November, says the UK would conform to EU customs rules if it entered the b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>US, Mexico, and Canada sign new USMCA trade deal - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/mexico-canada-sign-usmca-trade-deal-181130130126984.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBMfitblSQvjw5sKKvBJq54qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/mexico-canada-sign-usmca-trade-deal-181130130126984.html" target="_blank"&gt;US, Mexico, and Canada sign new USMCA trade deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US President Donald Trump, Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, and outgoing Mexican President Enrique Pena Nieto have signed an updated free trade agreement, aimed at replacing NAFTA, on the sidelines of the G20 summit in Argentina. Trump said on Friday that the trade pact was "model agreement that changes the trade landscape forever." The US has spent more than a year pushing the leaders of Canada and Mexico into agreeing to a rewrite of North American trade rules. Trump had vowed to revamp NAFTA during his 2016 presidential election campaign. He threatened to tear it up and withdraw t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>May suggests UK has 'already negotiated a good trade deal with EU' despite lack of concrete details - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/brexit-uk-eu-trade-deal-theresa-may-g20-agreement-a8660241.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG83arG9S1dsO90HQ4c7tkEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 04:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/brexit-uk-eu-trade-deal-theresa-may-g20-agreement-a8660241.html" target="_blank"&gt;May suggests UK has 'already negotiated a good trade deal with EU' despite lack of concrete details&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK has already “negotiated a good trade deal with the EU”, Theresa May has claimed – despite the document having no agreed trading arrangements and no legal force. The long-term trade aspects of the withdrawal package are contained within the slim “political declaration” that accompanied the divorce deal, which is not a legal treaty. The EU has insisted trade talks cannot start until after Brexit day next March – and the prime minister herself has previously acknowledged the document offers a “spectrum” of future options. - Read more Theresa May won't rule out resigning if MPs vote for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>China: trade deal possible at G20 if US is 'fair minded' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/11/30/china-trade-deal-possible-g20-us-fair-minded/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOXXQeS6V6a_1Fw2uAdagDIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:25:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2018/11/30/china-trade-deal-possible-g20-us-fair-minded/" target="_blank"&gt;China: trade deal possible at G20 if US is 'fair minded'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China and the United States can reach a trade agreement at the G20 meeting in Argentina this week, the state-run China Daily newspaper said in an editorial on Friday, but Washington must be "fair minded" if it wants to defuse spiralling tensions. "Beijing wants a deal, just as Washington does. And it is willing to cooperate with Washington in dealing with concerns about trade if they are fair-minded," the paper said. "Should there be any other aspirations, such as taking advantage of the trade spat to throttle Chinese growth, then an agreement is unlikely to be reached." World leaders start...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Republican senators urge vote on new NAFTA deal this year - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-nafta-idUSKCN1NQ2CJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJpjj_jvntb4y5y4Oj8dYBwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 18:44:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-nafta-idUSKCN1NQ2CJ" target="_blank"&gt;Republican senators urge vote on new NAFTA deal this year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twelve U.S. Republican Senators on Wednesday urged President Donald Trump to submit the deal to update the North American Free Trade Agreement to Congress for passage by year-end, before Democrats assume control of the House of Representatives. "We are concerned that if the administration waits until next year to send to Congress a draft implementing bill, passage of the USMCA as negotiated will become significantly more difficult," the senators, led by Pat Toomey of Pennsylvania, wrote. The new U.S.-Canada-Mexico Agreement, forged in September after tense negotiations and intended as an up...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump says he'll force a 6-month deadline on Congress for NAFTA replacement - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/politics/trump-terminate-nafta/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDAm1IP4xSe6Y0EB2yRDWAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 17:13:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/politics/trump-terminate-nafta/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says he'll force a 6-month deadline on Congress for NAFTA replacement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump put pressure on Congress to approve his new trade deal with Canada and Mexico, saying late Saturday he intends to terminate the original North American Free Trade Agreement. That would leave Congress with two options: approve the United States-Mexico-Canada Agreement, or risk having no trade deal in place. "I will be formally terminating NAFTA shortly," Trump told reporters aboard Air Force One on his way home from the G20 summit in Argentina. "We get rid of NAFTA. It's been a disaster for the United States. It's caused us tremendous amounts of unemployment and loss a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The UK government says its Brexit deal will hurt the economy - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/economy/brexit-economic-impact/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK1jqwX1Hsb85nM2vXqWgJ8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 18:15:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/economy/brexit-economic-impact/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The UK government says its Brexit deal will hurt the economy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's official: The British government's plan for leaving the European Union will be bad for the economy. The government published a report Wednesday that outlines the economic costs associated with a range of Brexit scenarios. The Bank of England followed later in the day with its own assessment. The United Kingdom would be worse off under all scenarios studied by the government. Officials did not estimate the precise impact of the deal Prime Minister Theresa May has negotiated with the European Union, but even in the best case it too will mean a weaker economy than remaining in the bloc. "...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Tariff tensions shadow US, Canada, Mexico trade pact signing - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/058fa4676b4d40948055cfae877d4e7c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI3d50iXNqrSh0q4P4k6wxkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 23:20:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/058fa4676b4d40948055cfae877d4e7c" target="_blank"&gt;Tariff tensions shadow US, Canada, Mexico trade pact signing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BUENOS AIRES, Argentina (AP) — President Donald Trump signed a revised North American trade pact with the leaders of Canada and Mexico on Friday, declaring the deal a major victory for workers. But tensions over tariffs, looming GM layoffs and questions about the pact's prospects in Congress clouded the celebratory moment. The U.S.-Mexico-Canada Agreement is meant to replace the 24-year-old North American Free Trade Agreement, which Trump has long denigrated as a "disaster." The leaders signed the new deal on the sidelines of the Group of 20 summit in Buenos Aires after two years of frequen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Theresa May rules out Norway-style Brexit compromise with Labour - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/nov/30/theresa-may-rules-out-norway-style-brexit-compromise-with-labour</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHbUI9XjgDWo5ii6OkjzkSwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 04:24:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/nov/30/theresa-may-rules-out-norway-style-brexit-compromise-with-labour" target="_blank"&gt;Theresa May rules out Norway-style Brexit compromise with Labour&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May has ruled out any plan B involving a Norway-style compromise deal with the Labour party in order to deliver a parliamentary consensus on Brexit, saying the opposition party’s refusal to accept the backstop arrangement put the UK on a course for no deal. Influential backbenchers, including former Tory minister Nick Boles and Labour’s Stephen Kinnock, have been developing a compromise proposal based on membership of the European Economic Area plus a negotiated customs union, believing it is the only version of Brexit that could attract enough Labour and Tory votes to deliver a par...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>May defends Brexit deal as Trump casts doubt on UK ability to trade with US - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/27/politics/trump-brexit-deal-claims-gbr-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC_24zsyNBT35Yje0fT4jMIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:12:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/27/politics/trump-brexit-deal-claims-gbr-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;May defends Brexit deal as Trump casts doubt on UK ability to trade with US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May has defended her Brexit plan and insisted that the UK will be able to strike new trade agreements with the rest of the world after it leaves the European Union. May's comments come after US President Donald Trump added himself to the chorus of skeptics doubting her proposal -- saying it isn't clear if the agreement will allow a US-UK trading partnership. "I think we have to take a look at seriously whether or not the UK is allowed to trade. Because you know, right now, if you look at the deal, they may not be able to trade with us," Trump said on the White...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Report reveals Foreign Office shortage of trained Brexit trade negotiators - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/nov/28/uk-only-30-expert-trade-negotiators-brexit-foreign-affairs-committee-report</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA_lG5OPqXwDNEmn021Kg6MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDHmu8F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 00:01:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/nov/28/uk-only-30-expert-trade-negotiators-brexit-foreign-affairs-committee-report" target="_blank"&gt;Report reveals Foreign Office shortage of trained Brexit trade negotiators&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK’s capacity to secure the best free trade deals after Brexit has been thrown into doubt by figures showing only around 30 civil servants attended a session on how to negotiate a trade agreement. The revelation came in a report by MPs on the foreign affairs select committee, in which the body responsible for training free trade negotiators said it had intended to train 240 staff up to expert standard by Brexit day on March next year, but so far only 90 were at that level. The head of the Diplomatic Academy, Jon Benjamin, told the committee the targets were challenging, adding: “We will...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Trump open to 2nd meeting with North Korea's Kim - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/092528aa2a074d9ea7166c1fae68235e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPYOlBoKFTxWifaxwDapaaUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 01:59:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/092528aa2a074d9ea7166c1fae68235e" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Trump open to 2nd meeting with North Korea's Kim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BUENOS AIRES, Argentina (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump at the Group of 20 summit (all times local): 8 p.m. South Korea's presidential office says U.S. President Donald Trump has reaffirmed a willingness to hold his second summit with North Korean leader Kim Jong Un early next year. Spokesman Yoon Young-chan says Trump made the comments in a meeting Friday with South Korean President Moon Jae-in on the sidelines of the Group of 20 meeting in Buenos Aires, Argentina. Yoon says Trump also said a planned visit by Kim to Seoul for his fourth summit with Moon would create momentum fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump's NAFTA replacement will be signed this week, Kudlow says - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/27/politics/usmca-nafta-signed/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBj59fILyXhyd7NqV9j9OQQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 20:50:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/27/politics/usmca-nafta-signed/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's NAFTA replacement will be signed this week, Kudlow says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A replacement for the North American Free Trade Agreement will be signed this week when US, Canadian and Mexican officials gather in Argentina for the G20 summit, White House economic adviser Larry Kudlow said Tuesday. President Donald Trump announced the trilateral deal, known as the United States-Mexico-Canada Agreement, or USMCA, at the end of September and wants it signed before Mexican President Enrique Peña Nieto leaves office on Saturday. The deal must still be approved by all three countries' legislative bodies. Rules on trade policy in the United States make it unlikely the pact wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Theresa May rules out compromise on her Brexit plan - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8d05e3a4-f44c-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEByKujhFBx4jZxuyaQOaoI8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 03:46:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8d05e3a4-f44c-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Theresa May rules out compromise on her Brexit plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May has ruled out a possible compromise on her Brexit plan, insisting that she can still win a crucial parliamentary vote scheduled for December 11. MPs, including cabinet ministers, have started discussing possible Plan Bs, including a Norway-style relationship with the EU. But speaking en route to a G20 summit in Argentina, the UK prime minister again underlined her fundamental objection that the Norway model — featuring membership of the European single market — would not end free movement of workers. Mrs May also dismissed the opposition Labour party’s proposal for the UK to rem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Brexit: Trump 'speaking the truth' when he warns Theresa May's deal will wreck US trade agreement, expert says - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/brexit-trump-trade-deal-us-theresa-may-andrew-cahn-withdrawal-agreement-eu-a8653696.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECLiPnXp3PSVBBPeJex0cKUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDyxv0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 09:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/brexit-trump-trade-deal-us-theresa-may-andrew-cahn-withdrawal-agreement-eu-a8653696.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit: Trump 'speaking the truth' when he warns Theresa May's deal will wreck US trade agreement, expert says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former UK trade chief says Donald Trump is “speaking the truth” when he warns Theresa May’s Brexit deal will wreck hopes of a trade agreement with the US. Sir Andrew Cahn backed the US president, undermining attempts by a furious Downing Street to fight back against the bombshell dropped in Washington. Michael Fallon, the former defence secretary – who will vote against a deal he branded “doomed” – also warned that “brushing off” Mr Trump’s embarrassing comments would not work. - Read more EU's top court considers whether Britain has power to cancel Brexit No 10 was thrown on the back foo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>White House Adviser: US, China Could Reach New Trade Deal - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/white-house-adviser-us-china-could-reach-new-trade-deal/4676981.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFrHJXTMJ0c-A9B-Cp2EAmsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 20:43:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/white-house-adviser-us-china-could-reach-new-trade-deal/4676981.html" target="_blank"&gt;White House Adviser: US, China Could Reach New Trade Deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping could reach a new trade deal between the world's two largest economies when they meet in Argentina this weekend, White House economic adviser Larry Kudlow said Tuesday. "The president said there is a good possibility that we can make a deal and he is open to it," he said of Trump. But he cautioned that obstacles remain. Kudlow said the two leaders must resolve the issues of "fairness and reciprocity" at the center of the dispute. "China should change its practices and come into the community of responsible trading nations," he sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Leaders Sign New NAFTA - Problems Postponed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/phillevy/2018/11/30/leaders-sign-new-nafta-problems-postponed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_JdRAid94fo9SxJfp7_PQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/phillevy/2018/11/30/leaders-sign-new-nafta-problems-postponed/" target="_blank"&gt;Leaders Sign New NAFTA - Problems Postponed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mexico’s President Enrique Pena Nieto (L) US President Donald Trump (C) and Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, sign a new free trade agreement in Buenos Aires, on November 30, 2018, on the sidelines of the G20 Leaders’ Summit. SAUL LOEB/AFP/Getty Images U.S. President Donald Trump, along with his Mexican and Canadian counterparts, signed the successor agreement to NAFTA in Buenos Aires, Argentina this morning, on the sidelines of the G20 meeting. The signing is a significant achievement, but it mostly defers some major problems with the deal. The ceremonial conclusion remained uncertai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Mexico to bestow top honor on Trump son-in-law, sparking Twitter outcry - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-politics-kushner-idUSKCN1NX071</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPZZb-nJtsI0vtlY49Gxl7YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 03:01:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-politics-kushner-idUSKCN1NX071" target="_blank"&gt;Mexico to bestow top honor on Trump son-in-law, sparking Twitter outcry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mexico's outgoing government said on Tuesday it would bestow the country's top honor for foreigners on Jared Kushner, U.S. President Donald Trump's son-in-law, a decision quickly met with derision by critics on social media. Kushner, who also serves as a senior White House adviser, will be admitted to the Order of the Aztec Eagle because of "his significant contributions" to a new North American trade pact agreed to in August, the government said in a statement. Kushner has often played a key diplomatic role in Trump's administration, meeting with Mexican and other foreign leaders and helpi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Yes, Donald Trump is talking perfect sense on May’s Brexit deal - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/27/donald-trump-theresa-may-brexit-deal-peter-mandelson</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGVRgNWkg3YP59i3jcmgvK8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 19:30:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/27/donald-trump-theresa-may-brexit-deal-peter-mandelson" target="_blank"&gt;Yes, Donald Trump is talking perfect sense on May’s Brexit deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The humiliations of Brexit continue to rain down upon us, but it took Donald Trump to remind the British government that negotiating trade deals is a long, painful and necessarily complex business that would only be made harder by Theresa May’s plan for leaving the European Union. Related: Theresa May rejects Donald Trump's criticism of Brexit deal For a long time, the most ardent Brexiters have done their best to maintain the pretence that some kind of magic kingdom will take shape post Brexit, in which we somehow make up for the loss of trade with the European Union by conjuring up a seri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Trump's Brexit comments aren't necessarily wrong, but they are unhelpful - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/27/uk/trump-brexit-gbr-analysis-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOCRJBbIWao32zN0PY1wdK0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:31:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/27/uk/trump-brexit-gbr-analysis-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's Brexit comments aren't necessarily wrong, but they are unhelpful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US President Donald Trump has kicked up quite a stink here in the UK, after suggesting that Prime Minister Theresa May's Brexit deal might put the brakes on a UK-US trade deal in the brave new world of post-Brexit Britain. He went on to suggest that it was a "great deal for the EU", thus implying it is not such a great deal for the UK. Many of May's Brexit-loving backbench MPs have already said that they cannot support her deal when it is put to a vote on December 11. Trump's words will have done nothing to calm those in the UK who think that May has given the EU way too much. Prior to the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Brexit deal to cost up to £1,100 per person per year - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a60a949c-ef3f-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIlXVdCfsxibfoxZkGyBs3gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 00:02:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a60a949c-ef3f-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit deal to cost up to £1,100 per person per year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May’s Brexit deal is likely to result in substantial long-term economic costs in a range of £700 to £1,100 per person each year compared with staying in the EU, according to the first detailed economic analysis. Produced by the National Institute of Economic and Social Research, an independent think-tank, the analysis shows the prime minister’s withdrawal agreement is less economically damaging than crashing out of the EU without a deal, but there would be a hit to national income from less trade, foreign investment, productivity and migration. Even if Mrs May’s agreement is ratifie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>President Trump, Canadian PM Justin Trudeau and Mexican President Enrique Peña Nieto signed the new U.S. Mexico Canada Agreement in Buenos Aires - infobae</title><link>https://www.infobae.com/america/g20-summit-2018/2018/11/30/president-trump-participates-in-signing-ceremony-for-north-american-trade-deal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMeMbXOGoSrvoOSdfokfPScqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowyPhzMO2BDDDCt60D</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 13:14:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.infobae.com/america/g20-summit-2018/2018/11/30/president-trump-participates-in-signing-ceremony-for-north-american-trade-deal/" target="_blank"&gt;President Trump, Canadian PM Justin Trudeau and Mexican President Enrique Peña Nieto signed the new U.S. Mexico Canada Agreement in Buenos Aires&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;infobae&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump says a new trade pact being signed by the United States, Mexico and Canada is a "model agreement that changes the trade landscape forever." Trump spent more than a year pushing the leaders of Canada and Mexico into agreeing to a rewrite of North American trade rules. Trump, Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau and Mexico's outgoing President Enrique Pena Nieto are signing the new pact Friday at the Group of 20 summit in Buenos Aires, Argentina. Trump now faces what could prove a more formidable foe: The U.S. Congress, which must ratify the agreement. He says the par...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.infobae.com">infobae</source></item><item><title>UK central bank warns of deep recession without Brexit deal - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/35c380dc79ee48fcbf62e74907cedd99</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOO-SuKgBYBr1vckQNgHFLsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 18:10:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/35c380dc79ee48fcbf62e74907cedd99" target="_blank"&gt;UK central bank warns of deep recession without Brexit deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON (AP) — Leaving the European Union without a divorce deal could plunge Britain into its deepest recession in nearly a century, with the economy shrinking 8 percent within months as unemployment and inflation soar, the Bank of England warned Wednesday. The stark projection came the same day the government's own economists said the country will be poorer after Brexit than if it had stayed in the EU, no matter what sort of trade deal it secures with the bloc. Britain and the EU have agreed on a deal for the U.K.'s smooth exit in March. But British lawmakers are threatening to derail it, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump open to making trade deal with China - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/27/trump-open-to-making-trade-deal-with-chi?videoId=486024396</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF6xn6MqPoyncsU3_Z6C8ugqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 20:12:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/27/trump-open-to-making-trade-deal-with-chi?videoId=486024396" target="_blank"&gt;Trump open to making trade deal with China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;White House Economic Adviser Larry Kudlow said Tuesday that President Trump is open to making a trade deal with China if certain conditions are met. Rough Cut (no reporter narration).&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>My Bet: Trump Gets Congressional Approval For 'New NAFTA,' USMCA - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kenroberts/2018/11/30/my-bet-trump-gets-congressional-approval-for-new-nafta-usmca/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBCsjkQlkEa0XkwYFjOQoQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kenroberts/2018/11/30/my-bet-trump-gets-congressional-approval-for-new-nafta-usmca/" target="_blank"&gt;My Bet: Trump Gets Congressional Approval For 'New NAFTA,' USMCA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Trump reaches out to Mexico’s President Enrique Pena Nieto, left, and Canada’s Prime Minister Justin Trudeau as they prepare to sign a new United States-Mexico-Canada Agreement that is replacing the NAFTA trade deal, during a ceremony at a hotel before the start of the G20 summit in Buenos Aires, Argentina, on Friday. The USMCA, as Trump refers to it, must still be approved by lawmakers in all three countries. (AP Photo/Martin Mejia) The ink barely dry on the new United States Mexico Canada Agreement, my bet is that President Trump finds the votes in Congress he needs to get appro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Side issues loom over G-20 summit as world leaders arrive - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/cdb0439ba68e4944867269328d5e8a5a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBr_9jn6QpdYYuo8JF6fk_MqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:27:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/cdb0439ba68e4944867269328d5e8a5a" target="_blank"&gt;Side issues loom over G-20 summit as world leaders arrive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BUENOS AIRES, Argentina (AP) — World leaders arrived Thursday in the Argentine capital for the Group of 20 summit of the globe's largest economies as issues such as a trade war between the United States and China, the killing of a Saudi journalist in the country's Istanbul Consulate and the conflict over Ukraine threatened to overshadow the gathering. The two-day summit beginning Friday is supposed to focus on development, infrastructure and food security, but those seemed largely an afterthought amid soured U.S.-European relations and as the United States, Mexico and Canada hammered out th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump says Brexit deal may damage UK-US trade - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ab25aa80-f1be-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ6fwAFiDQde1AKCSz4RsJoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 23:00:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ab25aa80-f1be-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says Brexit deal may damage UK-US trade&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has slammed the UK prime minister’s Brexit deal, saying it would benefit the EU while damaging the UK’s ability to trade with the US. The US president’s comments on Monday came hours after Theresa May encountered a hostile response in the House of Commons while briefing MPs on the compromise agreement approved by EU leaders on Sunday. Mr Trump appeared to suggest the Brexit deal would make it more difficult for the UK to reach a trade accord with the US. “Sounds like a great deal for the EU,” Mr Trump said to reporters. “Right now as the deal stands, they may not be able to tra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>At G-20, Possible 'Breakthrough' on WTO Seen After All-night Talks - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/at-g-20-possible-breakthrough-on-world-trade-organizatio-seen-after-all-night-talks/4682577.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENebp_NlxDP4XUCgRpXwtBQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 14:34:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/at-g-20-possible-breakthrough-on-world-trade-organizatio-seen-after-all-night-talks/4682577.html" target="_blank"&gt;At G-20, Possible 'Breakthrough' on WTO Seen After All-night Talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All-night talks at the Group of 20 summit have resulted in a possible "breakthrough'' on fixing the global trading system, European diplomats said Saturday as the gathering entered its crucial second and final day in the Argentine capital. Despite deep divisions going into the summit and resistance from the United States, European Union officials said countries also are making progress on a final statement that will acknowledge problems with the World Trade Organization but commit to reforming it. U.S. President Donald Trump has criticized the WTO and taken aggressive trade policies targeti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>IP is the G20 Issue - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/lorenzomontanari/2018/11/29/ip-is-the-g20-issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPiioOB0YhnwGD1BCc2cMJMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 10:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/lorenzomontanari/2018/11/29/ip-is-the-g20-issue/" target="_blank"&gt;IP is the G20 Issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was co-authored with Philip Thompson, Property Rights Alliance’s Policy Analyst for Intellectual Property and International Trade The official priorities at the G20 Summit in Argentina include worrying about soil erosion, mainstreaming public-private partnerships, and voicing anxiety over whether government run schools can equip kids with employable skills.While those certainly are complex issues, they miss the urgency of a real global crises that President Trump has brought to the table. The new agenda is intellectual property, intellectual property, and intellectual property. Pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Attention USMCA Leaders: Time Is Running Out - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyjsemotiuk/2018/11/23/attention-usmca-leaders-time-is-running-out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGnYSkf6LejJVCd_WKfHBu0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 15:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyjsemotiuk/2018/11/23/attention-usmca-leaders-time-is-running-out/" target="_blank"&gt;Attention USMCA Leaders: Time Is Running Out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert Lighthizer, U.S. trade representative, speaks on the U.S.-Mexico-Canada Agreement, or USMCA, in the Rose Garden of the White House in Washington, D.C., U.S., on Monday, Oct. 1, 2018. U.S. and Canadian negotiators worked around the clock to secure an agreement to enable leaders from those nations and Mexico to sign the accord on November 30th. There is doubt about meeting the signing deadline. Photographer: Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg Tick Tock! The clock is running and there is only one week left before the USMCA is supposed to be signed by country leaders. On September 30th 2018, after ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>