<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Atiku Abubakar - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNR013TWpScUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:23:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Nigeria election: Buhari battles body double rumours and economic woe - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/nigeria-election-buhari-battles-body-double-rumours-and-economic-woe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBoGVe_IzyxLWivSIUWigmQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:00:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/nigeria-election-buhari-battles-body-double-rumours-and-economic-woe" target="_blank"&gt;Nigeria election: Buhari battles body double rumours and economic woe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Returning to Nigeria after a long sick leave in London last year, President Muhammadu Buhari was greeted with a bizarre conspiracy theory. He had died and been replaced by “Jubril from Sudan”, a body double who had undergone extensive plastic surgery, said the Biafran secessionist leader Nnamdi Kanu. In October, just before campaigning began for February’s presidential election, the rumour went viral. For weeks now, prospective voters have been squinting at before-and-after pictures of the president’s hands and ears, trying to spot the difference – so much so that the normally-tightlipped B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Nigeria president Buhari denies rumours he was cloned - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/39d981ec-f6ed-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOYx8VXsPA-GWMHupgwpp9AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:15:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/39d981ec-f6ed-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Nigeria president Buhari denies rumours he was cloned&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigerian president Muhammadu Buhari would like voters to know that he is not dead — and has not even been cloned. At a roundtable with Nigerian expats in Poland, the Nigerian leader jokingly responded to a conspiracy theory that has circulated online for months that he had passed away and been replaced by a body-double. The rumours emerged after Mr Buhari, who has long been dogged by questions about his health, spent months in the UK last year seeking medical treatment for an undisclosed ailment. In a clip on Mr Buhari’s official Twitter account on Sunday, he addressed what he jokingly refe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Bring Back our Girls activist Oby Ezekwesili vows to disrupt 'Nigeria's politics of failure' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/22/africa/nigeria-oby-ezekwesili-politics/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJH9xrmzHTkX8WxA5xrFizoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 16:17:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/22/africa/nigeria-oby-ezekwesili-politics/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bring Back our Girls activist Oby Ezekwesili vows to disrupt 'Nigeria's politics of failure'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bring Back our Girls activist and former Nigerian minister Oby Ezekwesili has thrown her hat into the election ring for Nigeria's upcoming 2019 elections and says her candidacy will "disrupt the politics of failure" in Africa's most populous nation. Ezekwesili in an interview with Christiane Amanpour said bad governance had become endemic in Nigeria and citizens no longer hold leaders accountable for corruption or corrupt acts. "It [Nigerian politics] produced dismal results such that today Nigeria is the world's capital of extreme poverty," she said. "It's totally unacceptable. What I inte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ahead of Nigeria's election, opposition weaponizes soldier deaths - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-election-security/ahead-of-nigerias-election-opposition-weaponises-soldier-deaths-idUSKCN1NS1OI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEErkYfICh5Lyn3jcdmascPkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 22:53:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-election-security/ahead-of-nigerias-election-opposition-weaponises-soldier-deaths-idUSKCN1NS1OI" target="_blank"&gt;Ahead of Nigeria's election, opposition weaponizes soldier deaths&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of Nigerian soldiers have been killed in recent months by Islamist militants who the president vowed to defeat when voted into power in 2015 - and the bloodshed has become a useful weapon for opponents aiming to topple him in coming elections. Muhammadu Buhari's administration has been largely silent about the fighting in the northeast as, in battle after battle, soldiers have died. On Thursday Buhari's political opponents disclosed that 44 soldiers had been killed in an attack in the village of Metele, in the northeastern state of Borno, on Sunday. The move is calculated to underm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>'Get working again': Nigeria's Abubakar launches poll campaign - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/working-nigeria-abubakar-launches-poll-campaign-181119141314962.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMue_QGDeVKo5d7V08KsfoAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 18:47:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/working-nigeria-abubakar-launches-poll-campaign-181119141314962.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Get working again': Nigeria's Abubakar launches poll campaign&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abuja, Nigeria - Nigeria's main opposition leader Atiku Abubakar has vowed to get the country "working again" by reviving its economy as he launched his 2019 presidential elections campaign. In a Facebook Live address on Monday, the former vice president promised to create millions of jobs to tackle rising inequality and insecurity in Africa's top oil-producing country. "The sad fact today, as you know, is that too many of our people are not working and are living in poverty and insecurity," Abubakar said. "Almost all indices on socioeconomic and political development have plummeted, throwi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Deaths of Nigerian soldiers put pressure on president - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/75374ffe-f02f-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA8VbgTZWOdSb18V50HCLd8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 12:09:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/75374ffe-f02f-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Deaths of Nigerian soldiers put pressure on president&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The killings of scores of Nigerian soldiers by Boko Haram insurgents during the first week of the country’s presidential election campaign has put the administration of President Muhammadu Buhari under fire for its failure to deal with the insurgency. Boko Haram fighters killed about 100 soldiers last week at a base in northern Borno State, the heart of the jihadist insurgency, according to Reuters. Mr Buhari first acknowledged the deaths on Saturday night in a press release expressing “deep shock over the killing of military personnel” without confirming the number of casualties. On Friday...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Nigeria's Abubakar promises to boost oil investment, cut subsidies if elected - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-election/nigerias-abubakar-promises-to-boost-oil-investment-cut-subsidies-if-elected-idUSKCN1NO0UA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDUUkd2kzC2v03JlO96RwUEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 13:13:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-election/nigerias-abubakar-promises-to-boost-oil-investment-cut-subsidies-if-elected-idUSKCN1NO0UA" target="_blank"&gt;Nigeria's Abubakar promises to boost oil investment, cut subsidies if elected&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigeria's main opposition candidate Atiku Abubakar said on Monday he will boost oil sector investment, cut costly fuel subsidies and double the size of the economy by 2025 if he wins next year's presidential election. The businessman and former vice president portrayed himself as a champion of the private sector as he released his manifesto and set out his plans to stop incumbent Muhammadu Buhari securing a second term in February. There are few reliable opinion polls in Nigeria, Africa's largest oil producer. But Abubakar is seen as a substantial challenger to Buhari, a former military lea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nigeria's Buhari said he would not seek re-election in 2019: minister - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-politics/nigerias-buhari-said-he-would-not-seek-re-election-in-2019-minister-idUSKCN1BH2GT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAJK7LDggejkbGOs9A2mGagqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 17:26:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-politics/nigerias-buhari-said-he-would-not-seek-re-election-in-2019-minister-idUSKCN1BH2GT" target="_blank"&gt;Nigeria's Buhari said he would not seek re-election in 2019: minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Alexis Akwagyiram LAGOS (Reuters) - Nigeria's President Muhammadu Buhari told members of his party before he was first elected that he would only seek one term, implying he did not intend at that time to run in 2019, the minister of women's affairs told Reuters on Wednesday. The comments by Aisha Alhassan could heighten uncertainty over whether Buhari plans to contest the next election. Buhari took power in 2015 but has been absent for much of this year due to illness. He is yet to say if he will seek a second term. "In 2014/2015 he said he was going to run for only one time to clean up ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nigerian voters to choose between familiar faces - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/3a86b086-c71f-11e8-86e6-19f5b7134d1c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECsv_soThz96Lhpkdgx_t_cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 03:00:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3a86b086-c71f-11e8-86e6-19f5b7134d1c" target="_blank"&gt;Nigerian voters to choose between familiar faces&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Nigerians go to the polls in February, they will face a choice between two septuagenarian men they know well. Both are northern Muslims who have run for president multiple times, served at the highest levels of government and found success in their chosen fields. Besides that, President Muhammadu Buhari and former vice-president Atiku Abubakar— commonly known as Atiku — could not be more different. Mr Buhari, a former general who ruled the country in a military government briefly in the 1980s, is reserved and formal. Mr Abubakar, who served as vice-president from 1999 to 2007 to then p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Nigeria's Buhari Launches Re-Election Bid With Corruption Still in Focus - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/nigeria-buhari-launches-re-election-bid-with-corruption-still-in-focus/4663915.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECJ8lCbM-MvvFWkp4sTyIjMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 22:30:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/nigeria-buhari-launches-re-election-bid-with-corruption-still-in-focus/4663915.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nigeria's Buhari Launches Re-Election Bid With Corruption Still in Focus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigerian President Muhammadu Buhari launched his manifesto on Sunday, hoping his anti-corruption agenda can win him a second term at a February 16 election. Buhari, a military ruler in the early 1980s, in 2015 became the first opposition candidate to oust a president through the ballot box. His focus on corruption may be offset by Nigeria's slow growth. The country emerged from its first recession in a quarter of a century - largely caused by low crude prices – last year. In his first term, Buhari ordered government revenues and funds recovered in corruption investigations to be placed in a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Popular verdict looms for Nigerian leader Buhari - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e48b73f0-c701-11e8-86e6-19f5b7134d1c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFyaMH6-00f4O2YUudFf1BsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 03:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e48b73f0-c701-11e8-86e6-19f5b7134d1c" target="_blank"&gt;Popular verdict looms for Nigerian leader Buhari&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigeria’s election cycle is almost as fast-spinning as that of the US. It seems only yesterday that Muhammadu Buhari, a former general with a reputation for ascetic self-denial, scored a historic victory over former president Goodluck Jonathan to cement the country’s first democratic transition. That was 2015. After taking six months to pick a cabinet, Mr Buhari’s tenure has been punctuated by long absences for treatment of a mysterious illness in London. Now 75, he faces a battle for re-election in February after a first term that analysts rate as mediocre. Efforts to improve security, reb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Nigerian opposition candidate Abubakar picks 2019 election running mate - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-election-abubakar/nigerian-opposition-candidate-abubakar-picks-2019-election-running-mate-idUSKCN1MM2CF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDsNMOg_dWKxsYqqigjz9eEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 21:04:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-election-abubakar/nigerian-opposition-candidate-abubakar-picks-2019-election-running-mate-idUSKCN1MM2CF" target="_blank"&gt;Nigerian opposition candidate Abubakar picks 2019 election running mate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main opposition challenger to Nigerian President Muhammadu Buhari in next year's election has selected a former governor from the southeast of the country to be his running mate, the candidate's spokesman said on Friday. Atiku Abubakar, a former vice president who will stand as the candidate for the People's Democratic Party (PDP) in the February 2019 vote, chose Peter Obi, formerly governor of the southeastern state of Anambra. The choice points to a strategy to generate support in the southeast, where Buhari has polled badly in past elections and cracked down on secessionists by deplo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Ex-Nigerian president Obasanjo backs former deputy for 2019 election - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-election/ex-nigerian-president-obasanjo-backs-former-deputy-for-2019-election-idUSKCN1ML2OG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIPP5VFBQDw9eADR9FVRT0EqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 20:07:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-election/ex-nigerian-president-obasanjo-backs-former-deputy-for-2019-election-idUSKCN1ML2OG" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-Nigerian president Obasanjo backs former deputy for 2019 election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigerian ex-head of state Olusegun Obasanjo backed his former deputy on Thursday for next year's presidential election, ending a public feud that had threatened to undermine the main opposition candidate. Atiku Abubakar, who on Sunday won the race to be the candidate of the opposition People's Democratic Party (PDP), was vice president under Obasanjo from 1999-2007 but their relationship became strained at the time. Opposition to his candidacy by Obasanjo - a former military ruler who was democratically elected when Nigeria switched to civilian rule 19 years ago and remains influential - co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Abubakar to challenge Buhari in Nigeria's presidential race - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/abubakar-challenge-buhari-nigeria-presidential-race-181009175107509.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKpl_izF34aoRW2M3fFgYSgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 12:29:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/abubakar-challenge-buhari-nigeria-presidential-race-181009175107509.html" target="_blank"&gt;Abubakar to challenge Buhari in Nigeria's presidential race&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigeria's main opposition has chosen former Vice President Atiku Abubakar as its candidate for the 2019 elections as it seeks to oust President Muhammadu Buhari. The nomination of Abubakar, 71, by the People’s Democratic Party (PDP) sets the stage for what is expected to be a fiercely contested poll in Africa's largest economy. Abubakar hopes to replicate Buhari’s 2015 feat, when the latter became the first opposition candidate in Nigerian history to defeat a sitting president. Abubakar, who had been the country’s vice president between 1999 and 2007, left the ruling All Progressives Congre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Nigerian ex-minister and Chibok girls champion to run for president - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-politics-ezekwesili/nigerian-ex-minister-and-chibok-girls-champion-to-run-for-president-idUSKCN1MH01W</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP0j9NcYyhme_3P0_p61bpoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 20:40:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-politics-ezekwesili/nigerian-ex-minister-and-chibok-girls-champion-to-run-for-president-idUSKCN1MH01W" target="_blank"&gt;Nigerian ex-minister and Chibok girls champion to run for president&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Nigerian minister Obiageli Ezekwesili, co-founder of a group to raise awareness about more than 200 girls kidnapped by Boko Haram in 2014, announced on Sunday that she will run for president next year. Ezekwesili, 55, a former vice president for Africa at the World Bank, said she would run as the candidate of the Allied Congress Party of Nigeria (ACPN). Nigeria's presidential election is scheduled to take place in February 2019. She served in Nigeria's government between 2000 and 2007, first as minerals minister and later education minister. President Muhammadu Buhari, who took offic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Chibok girls activist aims to end Nigeria's political duopoly - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-politics-ezekwesili/chibok-girls-activist-aims-to-end-nigerias-political-duopoly-idUSKCN1MJ29B</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIRlHJqgZXI2YVm5Ocd3szYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 17:31:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-politics-ezekwesili/chibok-girls-activist-aims-to-end-nigerias-political-duopoly-idUSKCN1MJ29B" target="_blank"&gt;Chibok girls activist aims to end Nigeria's political duopoly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The co-founder of a group to raise awareness about schoolgirls kidnapped by jihadists said she aims to become Nigeria's first woman president by mobilizing first-time voters discouraged from going to the polls by the long domination of two main parties. Obiageli Ezekwesili, 55, also a former cabinet minister and senior World Bank official, announced on Sunday she would run as the candidate of the Allied Congress Party of Nigeria (ACPN) in the February 2019 vote to decide who runs Agrefrica's most populous country and top energy producer. [nL8N1WN113] "I am now fed up, like most Nigerians ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nigeria's opposition PDP selects Abubakar as 2019 presidential election - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-election-pdp/nigerias-opposition-pdp-selects-abubakar-as-2019-presidential-election-idUSKCN1MH0I6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENAYdop3enlx1PewR7U22M0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 12:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-election-pdp/nigerias-opposition-pdp-selects-abubakar-as-2019-presidential-election-idUSKCN1MH0I6" target="_blank"&gt;Nigeria's opposition PDP selects Abubakar as 2019 presidential election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Atiku Abubakar won on Sunday almost half the votes cast in a primary race to become the main opposition challenger to Nigerian President Muhammadu Buhari in next year's elections, party officials said. Abubakar, 71 and a former vice president, will stand as the People's Democratic Party (PDP) candidate. He scored 1,532 votes to defeat other candidates in the race, including the governor of the northwestern state of Sokoto, Aminu Tambuwal, and Nigeria's Senate President Bukola Saraki, the officials announced. "This is a victory for all of us. The task to get Nigeria working again starts now,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nigeria’s Atiku Abubakar to challenge Buhari for presidency - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/25d47548-ca2f-11e8-9fe5-24ad351828ab</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELItDc8XWIDmI2aJqwgiMZ8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 15:05:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/25d47548-ca2f-11e8-9fe5-24ad351828ab" target="_blank"&gt;Nigeria’s Atiku Abubakar to challenge Buhari for presidency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Atiku Abubakar, Nigeria’s former vice-president and a serial contender for the top job, has won the main opposition party’s nomination to challenge President Muhammadu Buhari in February’s elections. Over the next five months, the pair will battle for control of Africa’s largest crude producer and most populous nation amid rising oil prices and a sluggish economic recovery. Mr Buhari, a former military ruler with a cult-like following in the country’s predominately Muslim north, was thought all but unbeatable as recently as a few months ago. But recent state level elections have offered sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Nigerian women's minister becomes second cabinet member to resign this month - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-politics/nigerian-womens-minister-becomes-second-cabinet-member-to-resign-this-month-idUSKCN1M908Z</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKKBbo85jXqLfX-eFrJuoFoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 09:58:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-politics/nigerian-womens-minister-becomes-second-cabinet-member-to-resign-this-month-idUSKCN1M908Z" target="_blank"&gt;Nigerian women's minister becomes second cabinet member to resign this month&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigeria's women's affairs minister submitted her resignation in a letter to the president on Saturday, becoming the second cabinet member to step down this month and adding that she would leave the ruling party. Aisha Alhassan, a relatively junior cabinet member, resigned a little over two weeks after Kemi Adeosun, who had overseen finance, stepped down over allegations she had used a forged certificate to avoid mandatory national service. The resignations are the first in Buhari's cabinet since he came to power in 2015, and come in the run-up to early 2019 elections, typically a time where...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nigerian president faces election attacks on economic record - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2ec696f8-bb26-11e8-8274-55b72926558f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPfl1Ja4yf0zTAizvpF-KboqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 03:00:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2ec696f8-bb26-11e8-8274-55b72926558f" target="_blank"&gt;Nigerian president faces election attacks on economic record&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opposition candidates seeking to unseat Nigeria’s President Muhammadu Buhari are attacking his economic record and treatment of foreign investors as election season intensifies in Africa’s most populous country. Four members of Mr Buhari’s own party who have defected to the opposition to challenge him are pitching themselves as more business-minded candidates who can jump-start a sluggish economic recovery. Their criticisms in Africa’s biggest oil-producing nation, which is set to hold elections in February, come as two clashes highlight Mr Buhari’s vulnerability on economic policy, even as...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Nigeria's Buhari Officially Declares for Second Term - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/nigeria-s-buhari-officially-declares-for-second-term/4568776.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPYzbBQzKUlBm2ZMZWCB_mwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 17:46:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/nigeria-s-buhari-officially-declares-for-second-term/4568776.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nigeria's Buhari Officially Declares for Second Term&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigeria's President Muhammadu Buhari on Wednesday formally submitted his candidacy to stand for a second term of office at elections in February next year. The 75-year-old leader traveled to the headquarters of his ruling All Progressives Congress (APC) party in the capital Abuja to hand in his nomination form. He was accompanied by state governors, government ministers and party supporters. He said afterwards he was seeking the nomination "with all humility, sense of responsibility and an unquestionable desire to serve and protect the interest of all Nigerians." Well-wishers and supporters...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Hit by defections, Nigeria ruling party becomes a minority in Senate - Reuters</title><link>https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-politics/hit-by-defections-nigeria-ruling-party-becomes-a-minority-in-senate-idUSKBN1KE18Q?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI0pO9GE5b9JjpJFbQ8bFaQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 14:04:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-nigeria-politics/hit-by-defections-nigeria-ruling-party-becomes-a-minority-in-senate-idUSKBN1KE18Q?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" target="_blank"&gt;Hit by defections, Nigeria ruling party becomes a minority in Senate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fifteen Nigerian senators quit the ruling All Progressives Congress party on Tuesday, making it a minority in parliament's upper house and indicating worsening rifts in President Muhammadu Buhari's political camp months ahead of an election. Fourteen of the 15 lawmakers went to the opposition People's Democratic Party (PDP), a letter read on the Senate floor stated. Another senator later left the ruling party while parliament was in session. The PDP, which was in power from the start of civilian rule in 1999 until Buhari took office in 2015, said in a tweet that 32 lawmakers in the lower ho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://internal.www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nigeria: Opposition mounts against Buhari's re-election bid - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/nigeria-opposition-mounts-buhari-election-bid-180710160619931.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMFtrSeH2oOYPay5-1yGlPcqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:28:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/nigeria-opposition-mounts-buhari-election-bid-180710160619931.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nigeria: Opposition mounts against Buhari's re-election bid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opposition parties in Nigeria have come together to form a political coalition aimed at preventing President Muhammadu Buhari from winning a second consecutive term in next year's elections. Thirty-nine registered political forces, including the main opposition People's Democratic Party (PDP) and a splinter group from within the ruling party, signed an agreement late on Monday to form the Coalition of United Political Parties (CUPP). Kola Ologbondiyan, PDP spokesperson, described the parties' teaming up as a bold statement to demonstrate the "feelings of Nigerians" about Buhari's government...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item></channel></rss>