<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Ethiopian Airlines - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREl6TlRGNEVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:28:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Ethiopian Airlines ups Mogadishu flights - Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.ug/ethiopian-airlines-ups-mogadishu-flights/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiR2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmluZGVwZW5kZW50LmNvLnVnL2V0aGlvcGlhbi1haXJsaW5lcy11cHMtbW9nYWRpc2h1LWZsaWdodHMv0gEA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 02:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.ug/ethiopian-airlines-ups-mogadishu-flights/" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopian Airlines ups Mogadishu flights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kampala, Uganda | THE INDEPENDENT | Ethiopia's national carrier, Ethiopian Airlines, has announced plans to have daily flights between Addis Ababa and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.ug">Independent</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/VMaFBHVU8yLVRdYgLQA5OH3BmDWD6MorHTsJOL_AOIYJJRw4kukRn11X8w1nOX1brgjFNgTs9To2JHImBhglU4_RmJKTGCOn2LSJfAIieBpIKraWwYAx12Y1Bn36oRG3syc=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Ethiopian Airlines steps up hunt for African connections - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ethiopia-airlines-africa/ethiopian-airlines-steps-up-hunt-for-african-connections-idUSKCN1NS0X3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPEDk5p_EIuyLrKbjs5etdAqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 10:01:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ethiopia-airlines-africa/ethiopian-airlines-steps-up-hunt-for-african-connections-idUSKCN1NS0X3" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopian Airlines steps up hunt for African connections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethiopian Airlines is accelerating its strategy of weaving a patchwork of new African routes to soak up traffic on the continent and fly customers towards its more lucrative flights to rapidly expanding Asian markets. With a long-delayed African "open skies" revolution still mired in red tape, Ethiopian has been snapping up stakes in small carriers around the continent to pre-empt potential rivals and become the dominant pan-African airline. The carrier is in talks with Democratic Republic of Congo, Congo Republic and Djibouti about either launching airlines or securing landing spots, CEO T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nine Yemenis deported from U.S. to Ethiopia under Trump travel ban - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-immigration-ethiopia-idUSKBN15I1Z4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHyH_ikwy7NF-0z71GlJ_nQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 14:43:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-immigration-ethiopia-idUSKBN15I1Z4" target="_blank"&gt;Nine Yemenis deported from U.S. to Ethiopia under Trump travel ban&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ADDIS ABABA (Reuters) - Nine Yemenis deported from the United States in the wake of U.S. President Donald Trump's travel ban were flown to Ethiopia, then taken to neighboring Djibouti, an Ethiopian government official said on Friday. The Yemenis, blocked by Trump's executive orders barring travel to America by people from Yemen and six other Muslim-majority countries, had asked to go to Djibouti - just over the Red Sea from their home country - the official added. "The only reason they came to Addis Ababa was because Ethiopian Airlines has flights from Addis Ababa to Washington," government...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Viva Air Peru seen near $5 billion Airbus deal at Paris Airshow - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/airshow-paris-viva-idUSL8N1JF0U4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDwmhGKnw3dwbepsMWho_iAqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 19:45:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/airshow-paris-viva-idUSL8N1JF0U4" target="_blank"&gt;Viva Air Peru seen near $5 billion Airbus deal at Paris Airshow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Tim Hepher PARIS (Reuters) - Low-cost carrier Viva Air Peru looked close to reaching a roughly $5 billion deal with Airbus (AIR.PA: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) for medium-haul jets on Sunday, as Western planemakers seek to defy expectations of slow sales at this year's Paris Airshow. The Peruvian startup is set to order about 30 recently upgraded A320neo jets and 15 current-generation models known as A320ceo from Airbus, two industry sources told Reuters. A spokesman for Airbus had no comment. Viva Air Peru, which won an operating license earlier this year, is owned by Irelandi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Ethiopian Airlines plot takeover of Nigeria's flagship fleet - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/31/africa/ethiopia-arik-airlines/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBJDPcYsctP-1Gxnri8uJYgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 09:56:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/31/africa/ethiopia-arik-airlines/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopian Airlines plot takeover of Nigeria's flagship fleet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nigeria's leading airline could soon be under new management. Ethiopian Airlines has submitted a formal offer to take charge of troubled carrier Arik Air, which accounts for more than half of Nigerian air passenger traffic, according to official statistics. "We have outlined our terms and conditions to the Nigerian government and we are waiting to see if they agree," Esayas WoldeMariam, Ethiopian's managing director of international services, told CNN. "We are capable and desirous of handling the airline." WoldeMariam did not specify details of the offer, but added that he expects to face c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Boris Johnson 'should not leave Ethiopia' without freeing condemned man, rights group says - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/boris-johnson-andy-tsege-ethiopia-visit-reprieve-a7634396.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJaVTj_1zRosvm-NGcB2ZoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 01:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/boris-johnson-andy-tsege-ethiopia-visit-reprieve-a7634396.html" target="_blank"&gt;Boris Johnson 'should not leave Ethiopia' without freeing condemned man, rights group says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boris Johnson has visited Ethiopia as a father-of-three from London nears his 1,000th day on death row there, following his kidnapping by Ethiopian security forces. Andargachew Tsege, known as Andy, has been a vocal critic of the Ethiopian government. He was granted political asylum in the UK in 1979 and has lived in Britain ever since, though he continued to advocate for democratic reform in his home country. He was abducted in June 2014 while en route to Eritrea, and in July 2015 moved to the infamous Kality prison outside Addis Abiba, dubbed "Ethiopia's gulag". A death sentenced had been...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The world's best airlines have been announced – and it's bad news for BA - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/world-airline-awards-2017-qatar-british-airways/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHbk07tENcr8Gr5UFs_ELDUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 10:18:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/world-airline-awards-2017-qatar-british-airways/" target="_blank"&gt;The world's best airlines have been announced – and it's bad news for BA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar Airways has supplanted Emirates to claim the title of best carrier at the annual World Airline Awards. The gong will offer solace to the Doha-based airline, which has suffered in recent weeks thanks to a diplomatic crisis between Qatar and four of its Middle Eastern neighbours. It is currently banned from flying to the United Arab Emirates, Bahrain, Egypt and Saudi Arabia over allegations - denied by authorities in Doha - that Qatar has been funding terrorism in the region. It is the fourth time Qatar Airways as claimed the top prize, having won in 2011, 2012 and 2015Credit: REUTERS/E...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ethiopian Airlines has put in a bid to run Nigeria's new national carrier - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/14/africa/ethiopian-airlines-nigeria-investment-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFEWaVN5XEOLT92eXpHynRcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 14:11:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/14/africa/ethiopian-airlines-nigeria-investment-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopian Airlines has put in a bid to run Nigeria's new national carrier&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of Africa's air travel is conducted by airlines from outside of Africa. However the new initiative launched this year -- the Single African Air Transport Market (SAATM) -- by the African Union which aims to open up Africa's skies could pave the way for increased African air travel. Ethiopian Airlines is the country's state-owned carrier and leading carrier by number passengers. It serves over 120 passenger destinations. It's one of Africa's largest airlines and could be set to gain from the initiative. AFP/AFP/AFP/Getty Images With a fleet of 37, Kenya Airways flies over three million ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Eritrean Airlines starts regular flights to Addis, improving relations: minister - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ethiopia-eritrea-airlines/eritrean-airlines-starts-regular-flights-to-addis-improving-relations-minister-idUSKBN1KP0CX</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEYf1Max5XdGxwgkwNHBzZYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 11:33:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ethiopia-eritrea-airlines/eritrean-airlines-starts-regular-flights-to-addis-improving-relations-minister-idUSKBN1KP0CX" target="_blank"&gt;Eritrean Airlines starts regular flights to Addis, improving relations: minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eritrean Airlines has begun regular flights to Ethiopia's capital Addis Ababa, the Eritrean information minister said on Saturday, marking another step in improving relations between the Horn of African countries after a generation of hostility. Ethiopia's state-affiliated media confirmed that a plane carrying Eritrean transport and tourism ministers and other officials had landed at Addis Ababa's Bole international airport - the first time in two decades that such a flight had taken place, it said. "Upon arrival at Bole, Ethiopia’s State Minister for Foreign Affairs, Hirut Zemene and other...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Long-separated families reunite as Ethiopia and Eritrea resume flights after 20 years - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/19/africa/gallery/eritrea-ethiopia-first-flight/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOu-jsW_OuQXuFdKYzXlbEgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 15:32:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/19/africa/gallery/eritrea-ethiopia-first-flight/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Long-separated families reunite as Ethiopia and Eritrea resume flights after 20 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eritrean women hold up the flag of Eritrea as they welcome passengers of the flight from Ethiopian capital Addis Ababa upon their arrival at the Asmara International airport on Wednesday, July 18. MICHAEL TEWELDE/AFP/Getty Images Azmera Addisalem, second from left, and her family get emotional after meeting her father, an Ethiopian journalist, for the first time in twenty years upon his arrival at the Asmara International airport. MICHAEL TEWELDE/AFP/Getty Images Long-separated families are reunited on the tarmac of the Asmara International airport. MICHAEL TEWELDE/AFP/Getty Images Passenge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>First Ethiopian flight in 20 years lands to cheers in Eritrea - Reuters</title><link>https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-ethiopia-eritrea-arrival/first-ethiopian-flight-in-20-years-lands-to-cheers-in-eritrea-idUSKBN1K81FQ?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAVQFS0Vm1yAXdpCOU3rbEQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 11:41:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-ethiopia-eritrea-arrival/first-ethiopian-flight-in-20-years-lands-to-cheers-in-eritrea-idUSKBN1K81FQ?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" target="_blank"&gt;First Ethiopian flight in 20 years lands to cheers in Eritrea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first flight in 20 years from Ethiopia to Eritrea landed safely in Asmara on Wednesday, to be greeted by traditional dancers waving flags and flowers, cementing a stunning reconciliation between the Horn of Africa foes. Ethiopian Airlines Chief Executive Tewolde GebreMariam took to the on-board intercom as the flight crossed into Eritrean airspace. "This is the first time that this is happening in twenty years," he said, to applause from the 315 passengers on board. (Reporting by Aaron Maasho; Writing by Ed Cropley; Editing by Andrew Heavens)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://internal.www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Champagne and roses on first Ethiopia-Eritrea flights in two decades - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/18/champagne-and-roses-on-first-ethiopia-eritrea-flights-in-two-decades</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEINJ6FtFpVto3Pp-e_6_8wQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 10:05:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/18/champagne-and-roses-on-first-ethiopia-eritrea-flights-in-two-decades" target="_blank"&gt;Champagne and roses on first Ethiopia-Eritrea flights in two decades&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first commercial flight from Ethiopia to Eritrea in two decades has departed from Addis Ababa, after the two nations ended their bitter conflict in a whirlwind peace process. Ethiopian Airlines said flight ET0312 to Asmara had taken off from Bole international airport. To meet overwhelming demand it ran a second flight within 15 minutes of the first. Related: The shock of peace: Ethiopia and Eritrea embrace at last “This day marks a unique event in the history of Ethiopia and Eritrea,” the airline’s chief executive, Tewolde GebreMariam, said at a ceremony before the flight. “The fact th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Ethiopia Resumes Commercial Flights to Eritrea - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/ethiopia-resumes-commercial-flights-to-eritrea-/4487645.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAxvU9G34VBlh5dcxFT1kLEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 12:55:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/ethiopia-resumes-commercial-flights-to-eritrea-/4487645.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopia Resumes Commercial Flights to Eritrea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethiopia's main airline has resumed commercial flights to neighboring Eritrea, the latest sign of normalized ties between the longtime foes. Two Ethiopian Airlines planes landed in the Eritrean capital, Asmara, on Wednesday. One carried dignitaries and business leaders set to meet with Eritrean officials; the other was filled with ordinary people flying to visit family and friends. Tewelde Woldegebriel, a reporter for VOA's Horn of Africa service, said the mood at the Asmara airport was joyous, with people dressed in traditional clothes and singing traditional songs. The reporter said that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Eritrea's leader visits Ethiopia as dramatic thaw continues - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/e76cdb2ec08548ba98877d9d9dfbe835</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPqwpSqK7ujlMKygvILv4doqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 18:46:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/e76cdb2ec08548ba98877d9d9dfbe835" target="_blank"&gt;Eritrea's leader visits Ethiopia as dramatic thaw continues&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ADDIS ABABA, Ethiopia (AP) — To dancing and cheers, Eritrea's longtime president arrived in Ethiopia for his first visit in 22 years on Saturday amid a dramatic diplomatic thaw between the once-bitter rivals. "This is a historic day for all of us," President Isaias Afwerki said. "Anyone who thinks the people of Eritrea and Ethiopia are separated is considered as naïve from now on." Thousands turned out in Ethiopia's capital, Addis Ababa, under tight security to welcome Isaias, whose three-day visit is the latest step in ending a long state of war. "Welcome home President Isaias!!" the Ethio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Ethiopia, Eritrea leaders to meet 'soon' in surprising thaw - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/5503e7e935364c61abd40d9e9a101abc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIuXwSAOsQOgGdRY6uii4qcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 16:12:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/5503e7e935364c61abd40d9e9a101abc" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopia, Eritrea leaders to meet 'soon' in surprising thaw&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ADDIS ABABA, Ethiopia (AP) — The leaders of Ethiopia and Eritrea will meet "soon" amid a surprising diplomatic thaw between the rival nations, Ethiopia's top diplomat said Thursday, as an end to one of Africa's longest-running conflicts appeared to move closer. The meeting will "create a fertile ground to restore peace," Foreign Minister Workneh Gebeyehu told The Associated Press. "Details regarding the location and timing are under discussion." The minister spoke as an Eritrean delegation led by Foreign Minister Osman Saleh concluded a historic three-day visit to Ethiopia, the first in two...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Ethiopia welcomes 1st delegation from rival Eritrea in years - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/228cc2f2d21847689e9c3a3402e12e98</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDkzFMS_gY5g_cI_RiEOH6AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 19:28:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/228cc2f2d21847689e9c3a3402e12e98" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopia welcomes 1st delegation from rival Eritrea in years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ADDIS ABABA, Ethiopia (AP) — Ethiopia on Tuesday welcomed the first delegation of top officials from longtime rival Eritrea for the first time in two decades for peace talks, with Ethiopia's prime minister declaring that the separation between the neighbors "is shattered down." "We have tried war and found it useless," Prime Minister Abiy Ahmed told a dinner reception at the National Palace for Eritrea's foreign minister and others, after a day that began with draping the visitors on arrival at the Addis Ababa airport with strings of flowers. The two countries have not had diplomatic relati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Ethiopia to cede land at heart of bloody conflict with Eritrea - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4dddc09a-68ea-11e8-8cf3-0c230fa67aec</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDsgNCLFyjv_Nc1vlpAXysqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 19:46:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4dddc09a-68ea-11e8-8cf3-0c230fa67aec" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopia to cede land at heart of bloody conflict with Eritrea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethiopia announced on Tuesday it would implement a peace agreement ending a 1998-2000 war with Eritrea that requires it to cede disputed land it has occupied for almost two decades. The executive committee of the ruling Ethiopian People’s Revolutionary Democratic Front also said after a day-long meeting that the government would sell off minority stakes in state-owned enterprises, including Ethio Telecom and Ethiopian Airlines, and that foreigners would be allowed to invest in the lucrative businesses. The moves are part of a radical reform agenda initiated by Abiy Ahmed, who became Ethiopi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>What You Need to Know About Fifth Freedom Flights - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/geoffwhitmore/2018/05/30/what-you-need-to-know-about-fifth-freedom-flights/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPCAkpnodrBn_jkduGWADtYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 12:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/geoffwhitmore/2018/05/30/what-you-need-to-know-about-fifth-freedom-flights/" target="_blank"&gt;What You Need to Know About Fifth Freedom Flights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every once in a while you’ll notice an airline flying a route that seems kind of strange – like Air New Zealand from Los Angeles to London, or Singapore Airlines from New York to Frankfurt. These are called “fifth freedom” routes, referring to the “freedoms of the air,” a set of foundational principles for commercial aviation agreements between countries. The fifth freedom is the right for an airline to stop in a country other than its own and pick up passengers before continuing on to another destination (usually in a third country). Shutterstock Beyond the novelty of these flights, they c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Ethiopian Airlines positions itself to take over Africa's skies with ambitious plans - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/05/23/africa/ethiopian-airlines-africa-flight/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKeGJan_6dmdP5gi2D_L_esqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 08:17:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/05/23/africa/ethiopian-airlines-africa-flight/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopian Airlines positions itself to take over Africa's skies with ambitious plans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of Africa's air travel is conducted by airlines from outside of Africa. However the new initiative launched this year -- the Single African Air Transport Market (SAATM) -- by the African Union which aims to open up Africa's skies could pave the way for increased African air travel. Ethiopian Airlines is the country's state-owned carrier and leading carrier by number passengers. It serves over 120 passenger destinations. It's one of Africa's largest airlines and could be set to gain from the initiative. AFP/AFP/AFP/Getty Images With a fleet of 37, Kenya Airways flies over three million ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Africa's top airlines - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/01/31/africa/gallery/africa-top-airlines/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDdC6bQrGdat0Lb4nunISS4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 07:59:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/01/31/africa/gallery/africa-top-airlines/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Africa's top airlines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of Africa's air travel is conducted by airlines from outside of Africa. However the new initiative launched this year -- the Single African Air Transport Market (SAATM) -- by the African Union which aims to open up Africa's skies could pave the way for increased African air travel. Ethiopian Airlines is the country's state-owned carrier and leading carrier by number passengers. It serves over 120 passenger destinations. It's one of Africa's largest airlines and could be set to gain from the initiative. AFP/AFP/AFP/Getty Images With a fleet of 37, Kenya Airways flies over three million ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The ultimate guide to baggage limits by destination and airline - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/baggage-allowance-longhaul-flights-uk-delhi-dubai-new-york-hong-kong-sydney-nairobi-a8187766.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECYcZdhc9Etfs_EyLzxoVgwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 18:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/baggage-allowance-longhaul-flights-uk-delhi-dubai-new-york-hong-kong-sydney-nairobi-a8187766.html" target="_blank"&gt;The ultimate guide to baggage limits by destination and airline&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The amount of luggage you can carry on board a long-haul flight varies dramatically from one airline to another, and even between destinations on the same carrier. This guide to allowances for key locations is for passengers beginning their journey in the UK and buying the cheapest economy tickets. The weights are expressed in kilograms. Read more - Etihad halves baggage allowance for tens of thousands of UK passengers A combination of direct services and common indirect routings has been chosen. The figures do not take into account any charges for splitting the weight limit between more th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Sky's the limit as Africa makes major move towards aviation single market - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/01/31/africa/african-union-single-air-airline/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIWDip97OuGPtR2T7E8hXzMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 18:15:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/01/31/africa/african-union-single-air-airline/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sky's the limit as Africa makes major move towards aviation single market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of Africa's air travel is conducted by airlines from outside of Africa. However the new initiative -- the Single African Air Transport Market (SAATM) -- launched by the African Union which aims to open up Africa's skies could pave the way for increased African air travel. Ethiopian Airlines is the country's state-owned carrier. It serves a 122 passenger destinations. It's one of Africa's largest airlines and could be set to gain from the initiative. AFP/AFP/AFP/Getty Images With a fleet of 34, Kenya Airways flies over three million passengers to 53 destinations worldwide every year. It...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ethiopian Airlines to Re-launch Zambia's National Carrier - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/ethiopian-airlines-re-launch-zambia-national-carrier/4210180.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP1K1o6cnvXlH711S8Mhtt4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 17:22:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/ethiopian-airlines-re-launch-zambia-national-carrier/4210180.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopian Airlines to Re-launch Zambia's National Carrier&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethiopian Airlines says it has finalized an agreement with Zambia to re-launch the southern African country's national carrier. The partnership with Zambia comes as Ethiopian Airlines is opening new routes and hubs and is acquiring new aircraft. In a statement Tuesday, the airline said it will have a 45 percent stake in the Zambian carrier and it aims to make the Zambian capital, Lusaka, its newest aviation hub. The remaining 55 percent will be acquired by the Zambian government which is aiming to revive the country's aviation sector after Zambia Airways ceased operations on January 2009. "...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Revealed: The world's most (and least) punctual airlines - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/oag-most-punctual-airline-airports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENjxHJGTzAw3WW43Eu7IoxUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 17:28:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/oag-most-punctual-airline-airports/" target="_blank"&gt;Revealed: The world's most (and least) punctual airlines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan is a nation renowned for its punctuality. Last year one of its train operator, Tsukuba Express, even issued a grovelling apology after one of its services left the platform 20 seconds early, while in 2015 Kansai International Airport was praised for having not lost a single bag - not one - after 21 years in operation. So it should come as no surprise to learn that the world’s two most reliable large airlines are both based in the Far Eastern country. In its annual Punctuality Report, the aviation analysts OAG highlighted the airlines and airports, both large and small, doing the most ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ethiopian could buy 10-20 of Boeing's proposed mid-sized jet - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-emirates-airshow-ethiopian/ethiopian-could-buy-10-20-of-boeings-proposed-mid-sized-jet-idUSKBN1DE0UF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHi_csO9kKAYQmTgbFqWIcqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 08:12:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-emirates-airshow-ethiopian/ethiopian-could-buy-10-20-of-boeings-proposed-mid-sized-jet-idUSKBN1DE0UF" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopian could buy 10-20 of Boeing's proposed mid-sized jet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Alexander Cornwell DUBAI (Reuters) - Ethiopian Airlines would be interested in buying around 10 to 20 of the mid-sized jets that Boeing is studying whether to develop, the African airline's chief executive said on Tuesday. Boeing is looking at potentially filling a market gap between narrow and wide-body jets with a new aircraft that could seat 220 to 270 passengers. Ethiopian Chief Executive Tewolde Gebremariam said the airline was interested in a replacement for the out-of-production Boeing 757. "It is a very right size, and right range for the missions we have, especially (for) the al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Exploring Ethiopia: a Walking Tour from the Blue Nile to the Simien Mountains - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/tours/partners/kudu-travel/exploring-ethiopia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGHbHXpXTwtxbO6ZhB5nioqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 16:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/tours/partners/kudu-travel/exploring-ethiopia/" target="_blank"&gt;Exploring Ethiopia: a Walking Tour from the Blue Nile to the Simien Mountains&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview Ethiopia has acquired a mythical reputation through the stories of its unique culture, church, language, script and exotic traditional ceremonies. These traveller's tales can be realised on this fascinating two weeks of insight into an isolated society where a traditional way of life has endured for millennia. This tour will take you by road, aeroplane and foot to such sites as Lake Tana, source of the blue Nile, the ancient imperial capitals of Axum and Gondar and the captivating early-human museums in Addis Ababa. For nature lovers, there is the opportunity to walk in the Simien ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ethiopia is the hot new place in Africa -- here's why - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/travel/article/ethiopia-africa-travel-next-big-thing/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFFnYXo7sGhm6-Zsod8LvJgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 20:46:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/travel/article/ethiopia-africa-travel-next-big-thing/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ethiopia is the hot new place in Africa -- here's why&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethiopia's highest mountain range, the Simiens, nurture an incredible array of native flora and fauna including animals like the gelada baboon, Ethiopian wolf and walia ibex. Scheduled to open in early 2017, a new luxury tented camp will complement basic facilities already available in the national park. courtesy Ethiopia Tourism Organization A spectacular red-rock landscape reminiscent of the American Southwest provides a refuge for dozens of tiny rock-hewn monasteries scattered through the mountains. Trekking is the main activity, but the region also boasts some of Ethiopia's best wildern...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item></channel></rss>