<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Ali Bongo Ondimba - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRGgyYlhFMUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:28:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Gabon president Bongo 'doing well' in Morocco after illness: PM - Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.ug/gabon-president-bongo-doing-well-in-morocco-after-illness-pm/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiW2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmluZGVwZW5kZW50LmNvLnVnL2dhYm9uLXByZXNpZGVudC1ib25nby1kb2luZy13ZWxsLWluLW1vcm9jY28tYWZ0ZXItaWxsbmVzcy1wbS_SAQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:30:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.ug/gabon-president-bongo-doing-well-in-morocco-after-illness-pm/" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon president Bongo 'doing well' in Morocco after illness: PM&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libreville, Gabon | AFP | Gabon's President Ali Bongo is recovering well after being hospitalised in Morocco, his prime minister said after the two met in the ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWljOU1HbGpZQU1FYi1NckJRa0hDME5LQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.ug">Independent</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/Z7D1m2fGwV35b1Uzx4rjeAIk_U_eqBNrI4MxB00pibKjeg58H_mfHDzl0TH8li_2M3VhaR6BTH360VLUI3_TIIJZoy1M7kIrcM0vdRsm9lvL4wigT5Mo018p0A=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Morocco King Meets Gabon President In Hospital - New Vision</title><link>https://www.newvision.co.ug/new_vision/news/1490673/morocco-king-meets-gabon-president-hospital</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5ld3Zpc2lvbi5jby51Zy9uZXdfdmlzaW9uL25ld3MvMTQ5MDY3My9tb3JvY2NvLWtpbmctbWVldHMtZ2Fib24tcHJlc2lkZW50LWhvc3BpdGFs0gEA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 03:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newvision.co.ug/new_vision/news/1490673/morocco-king-meets-gabon-president-hospital" target="_blank"&gt;Morocco King Meets Gabon President In Hospital&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Vision&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PIC: King Mohamed VI of Morocco (left) visiting Gabon's President Ali Bongo at the military hospital in the capital Rabat. (Credit: Moroccan Royal Palace/AFP)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newvision.co.ug">New Vision</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/U93VOusPJX2wCcVsQXXTXMAcYIIrMpPnbHSl-uN2vABPG6LQkruMVbIDj6gMJQ0Lygt57Vbi0glmtk9C3kuQkSDbvWNmSKpBc-nMZfiUG0JL7gYzkj7nZ11hqgNKubp_WUSxH6MMsp9xN1B2oS_F9JFu=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Au Warns Gabon As Bongo Remains Incapacitated - New Vision</title><link>https://www.newvision.co.ug/new_vision/news/1489735/au-warns-gabon-bongo-remains-incapacitated</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5ld3Zpc2lvbi5jby51Zy9uZXdfdmlzaW9uL25ld3MvMTQ4OTczNS9hdS13YXJucy1nYWJvbi1ib25nby1yZW1haW5zLWluY2FwYWNpdGF0ZWTSAQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 07:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newvision.co.ug/new_vision/news/1489735/au-warns-gabon-bongo-remains-incapacitated" target="_blank"&gt;Au Warns Gabon As Bongo Remains Incapacitated&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Vision&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PHOTO: President Ali Bongo. The African Union on Saturday warned Gabon to respect constitutional order after a high court intervened in a crisis surrounding ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newvision.co.ug">New Vision</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/GPKb9HqYH4UigSM9PA__VRd4LES9jgEvoihGMyacAyZha7CT7ybAcZYp3EBeyoVk27oM1DiOLnAiZ763nmplME_U12z_V6NuLxpVOu624DJVlsZFQbdC1zaIIYyIzGUAAsigOOZlYxlHEljcNjBuwPTd8Q=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Gabon Presidency Admits Leader Ali Bongo Is Seriously Ill - New Vision</title><link>https://www.newvision.co.ug/new_vision/news/1489292/gabon-presidency-admits-leader-ali-bongo-seriously-ill</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiamh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5ld3Zpc2lvbi5jby51Zy9uZXdfdmlzaW9uL25ld3MvMTQ4OTI5Mi9nYWJvbi1wcmVzaWRlbmN5LWFkbWl0cy1sZWFkZXItYWxpLWJvbmdvLXNlcmlvdXNseS1pbGzSAQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newvision.co.ug/new_vision/news/1489292/gabon-presidency-admits-leader-ali-bongo-seriously-ill" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon Presidency Admits Leader Ali Bongo Is Seriously Ill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Vision&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gabon's presidency admitted for the first time on Sunday that President Omar Bongo, hospitalised for nearly three weeks in Saudi Arabia, is in a serious ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newvision.co.ug">New Vision</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/X4SdKjCkUppfDWyFlHd6knVWQSQ0eG0Af1BNAjGMCYg6Wa0svxmBtydtdXhEeuV043MhFuULnrRsmS4heJlueaOz6b8BOZJ-gMQzQAMwdfKKP2c8QkNmXUzS3BILOz-0ByYe_-sZUkEoJaG_xUBYwlZo4A=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Gabon Opposition Party Raises Temperature On Bongo's Health - New Vision</title><link>https://www.newvision.co.ug/new_vision/news/1489412/gabon-opposition-party-raises-temperature-bongos-health</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMia2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5ld3Zpc2lvbi5jby51Zy9uZXdfdmlzaW9uL25ld3MvMTQ4OTQxMi9nYWJvbi1vcHBvc2l0aW9uLXBhcnR5LXJhaXNlcy10ZW1wZXJhdHVyZS1ib25nb3MtaGVhbHRo0gEA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newvision.co.ug/new_vision/news/1489412/gabon-opposition-party-raises-temperature-bongos-health" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon Opposition Party Raises Temperature On Bongo's Health&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Vision&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Gabonese opposition party on Tuesday accused the government of peddling a "lie" over the health of President Ali Bongo after he was hospitalised in Saudi ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newvision.co.ug">New Vision</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/ULJfvQynvnB88wkYsb3QddU5tRPai-oeN4EbEdtiWTp7554iGtUR7PctPR_4dRamolz1yYbAlFcbQ4cqygtApSkK5NttTGLTk9sbbkeq-lYPYvzY3cucOIl-wWrq8GGE6BPnKASKGcNh-TlIsQM9Q5HkaQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Staying alive: world leaders who have had to prove they haven't died - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/staying-alive-world-leaders-who-have-had-to-prove-they-havent-died</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJELYaO27Vcf9TaHw7n05kwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 03:59:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/staying-alive-world-leaders-who-have-had-to-prove-they-havent-died" target="_blank"&gt;Staying alive: world leaders who have had to prove they haven't died&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is one of the stranger occupational hazards for world leaders: that at some point in their career they may have to deny reports of their own death. Just one day after the Nigerian president Muhammadu Buhari denied claims he had died and been replaced by a Sudanese impostor “clone”, another world leader has been forced to address rumours of his demise. Ali Bongo, the president of Gabon, made his first appearance on Monday since falling ill nearly six weeks ago. Rumours of Bongo’s death have been widespread since he collapsed at a conference in Saudi Arabia on 24 October, with sources tell...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Gabon's Bongo headed to Morocco to continue recovery: wife - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gabon-president/gabons-bongo-headed-to-morocco-to-continue-recovery-wife-idUSKCN1NW24Z</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECcYL8K8-a4zwH6KofR6LlUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 18:49:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gabon-president/gabons-bongo-headed-to-morocco-to-continue-recovery-wife-idUSKCN1NW24Z" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon's Bongo headed to Morocco to continue recovery: wife&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gabon's President Ali Bongo will leave Saudi Arabia, where he was hospitalized last month after suffering a stroke, to continue treatment in Morocco, his wife said on Tuesday. Bongo has not been seen in public since being admitted to hospital during a conference on Oct. 24. Gabon's top court ruled earlier this month that the vice president would chair the cabinet in Bongo's absence. In a post on her Facebook page, Sylvia Bongo wrote that her husband's health had improved significantly and that he would travel to Rabat on Wednesday. "To pursue his convalescence, the president, in concertatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Gabon opposition rejects president's call for talks to ease tensions - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-gabon-politics-idUSKBN16I0FH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGdhAP1kirIF30vD2_RNm3QqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 12:06:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-gabon-politics-idUSKBN16I0FH" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon opposition rejects president's call for talks to ease tensions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIBREVILLE (Reuters) - Gabonese President Ali Bongo has offered to hold talks with opposition parties in an apparent bid to ease tensions over his contested re-election last year, but his main political rival swiftly rejected the call for dialogue. Responding to a presidency statement issued late on Friday, opposition leader Jean Ping branded the proposal for talks starting on March 28 as a "masquerade" and said he would not participate. Ping, a former African Union chairman, accuses Bongo of cheating in order to win re-election in the August 2016 election and of using security forces to vi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>As Africa Cup of Nations Enters Elimination Phase, Many Fans Stay Home - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/as-africa-cup-of-nations-enters-elimination-phase-many-fans-stay-home/3695509.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHTUWSd_MYh-NZ-uBlOEYkkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwmp0i</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:05:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/as-africa-cup-of-nations-enters-elimination-phase-many-fans-stay-home/3695509.html" target="_blank"&gt;As Africa Cup of Nations Enters Elimination Phase, Many Fans Stay Home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Africa Cup of Nations enters the elimination phase Saturday in Gabon as eight of the 16 football (soccer) teams that started the tournament compete for the four places in the semi-finals. But many seats in the stadiums remain empty after the political opposition called on its supporters to boycott the event. Hundreds of secondary school students lined up at the government high school in the center of Libreville to receive entry tickets for AFCON matches. Youmbi Betrand, 16, says their head teacher gives them tickets - the value of which ranges between $5 - $10 to go to watch matches. A ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Equatorial Guinea leader's son on trial in France in absentia - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-africa-trial-idUSKBN19A2KR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDuF7qwBTTcg3X-MpFdOhc8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 17:56:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-africa-trial-idUSKBN19A2KR" target="_blank"&gt;Equatorial Guinea leader's son on trial in France in absentia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARIS (Reuters) - The son of Equatorial Guinea's president went on trial on Monday in his absence in Paris on charges of using money plundered from his country to buy Parisian luxury properties and exotic cars. Teodorin Obiang, eldest son of President Teodoro Obiang and a vice-president himself, denies charges of laundering embezzled public funds, for which he risks a sentence of 10 years in jail and huge fines if convicted. The case is the first of several to reach court in a broader judicial investigation into allegations of illicit acquisitions in France by long-time leaders and family r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Gabon's Stade Omar Bongo casts a shadow as the Africa Cup of Nations gets into full swing - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/international/gabons-stade-omar-bongo-casts-shadow-africa-cup-of-nations-full-swing-a7526826.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEyMR2GSO8OLFCWmxJWma1QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 18:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/international/gabons-stade-omar-bongo-casts-shadow-africa-cup-of-nations-full-swing-a7526826.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon's Stade Omar Bongo casts a shadow as the Africa Cup of Nations gets into full swing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the weeds, a goat bleats. In the ditch, a naked man washes himself. In a wired-off compound, diggers sit idle. And at the centre of it all is the Stade Omar Bongo, concrete supports reaching into the humid grey sky. There is a grass pitch and there are not merely goals in place but practice nets have been set up; teams will train here. This should have been the centrepiece of Gabon’s second Cup of Nations in five years, the president Ali Bongo’s tribute to his father, whom he succeeded after his death in 2009. But the stadium will not host any games at the 31st African Cup of Nations. It...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Political unrest in Gabon casts shadow over 2017 Africa Cup of Nations draw - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2016/oct/18/africa-cup-of-nations-2017-gabon-draw-football</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEtWjz7wmSEdP4uCOBi2pPMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2016/oct/18/africa-cup-of-nations-2017-gabon-draw-football" target="_blank"&gt;Political unrest in Gabon casts shadow over 2017 Africa Cup of Nations draw&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;No news, they say, is good news. Either that or it’s the result of a government blackout. The draw for the Africa Cup of Nations will be held in Libreville, Gabon, on Wednesday but yet again the buildup to a tournament has been dominated by doubts over where it will be staged as the aftershocks of Gabonese presidential elections continue to be reverberate. At the moment it seems the tournament will go ahead in Gabon, beginning on 14 January, but no one is confident. Even by the standards of the Cup of Nations, the 2017 edition has seemed ill-starred. In 2006, hosting rights were given to So...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Health of Gabon's hospitalized leader has greatly improved: presidency - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gabon-president/health-of-gabons-hospitalized-leader-has-greatly-improved-presidency-idUSKCN1NG0MB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELMOl3qlJGy_MwgkQrtydfsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 18:59:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gabon-president/health-of-gabons-hospitalized-leader-has-greatly-improved-presidency-idUSKCN1NG0MB" target="_blank"&gt;Health of Gabon's hospitalized leader has greatly improved: presidency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health of Gabon's President Ali Ben Bongo has greatly improved and he is recovering his physical abilities, his office said on Sunday, after sources said last month he suffered a stroke. Bongo was admitted to hospital on Oct. 24 in Saudi Arabia after the stroke, the sources said, though Gabonese authorities said he was merely suffering from fatigue. One TV station in Gabon has been banned for reporting he had died. The Bongo family has ruled for nearly half a century in Gabon, a country in central Africa that produces oil and was a French colony before independence. Bongo has been presi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Gabon VP takes over cabinet amid President Bongo's illness - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gabon-president/gabon-vp-takes-over-cabinet-amid-president-bongos-illness-idUSKCN1NK1K7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMWoCSOx7yXrEEHFQJc09wIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 11:47:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-gabon-president/gabon-vp-takes-over-cabinet-amid-president-bongos-illness-idUSKCN1NK1K7" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon VP takes over cabinet amid President Bongo's illness&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gabon's top court has ruled that the vice president will chair the cabinet in the absence of President Ali Bongo, who remains in hospital in Saudi Arabia after suffering a stroke last month. The decision, announced by the constitutional court on Wednesday, is the first move to fill the vacuum left after Bongo was admitted to hospital during a conference on Oct. 24. Bongo has not been seen in public since and his state of health is unknown. The government said he suffered a bout of fatigue and is recovering, but sources told Reuters that he had a stroke. "Only the president has the power to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Hospitalised Gabon leader Ali Bongo greatly improved: presidency - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/hospitalised-gabon-leader-ali-bongo-greatly-improved-presidency-181111132558573.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFl5G-bqFczPa2cPKxxBSukqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 17:38:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/hospitalised-gabon-leader-ali-bongo-greatly-improved-presidency-181111132558573.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hospitalised Gabon leader Ali Bongo greatly improved: presidency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health of Gabon's President Ali Bongo has "greatly improved" after the 59-year-old was hospitalised as a result of discomfort and "persistent vertigo", according to the presidency. The leader, who was admitted in a hospital in Saudi Arabia late last month, is "in a phase of recovering all his functions", spokesperson Ike Ngouni said in an official statement on Sunday. Bongo was in the kingdom's capital, Riyadh, to attend an investment summit and speak alongside other leaders but was not seen during the discussion. Ngouni said the president was transferred to King Faisal hospital after ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Gabon: Government Says President Recovering in Saudi Arabia - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/gabon-government-says-president-recovering-in-saudi-arabia/4653782.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO5Y4UfNg0TfKbFsTrr57xAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 16:56:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/gabon-government-says-president-recovering-in-saudi-arabia/4653782.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon: Government Says President Recovering in Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government of Gabon says President Ali Bongo Ondimba is recovering from an undisclosed illness in Saudi Arabia. The Central African nation's presidency said in a statement on Sunday that the latest word about the president's health was “extremely reassuring” and Bongo “continues to perform his duties.” The statement was released amid a swirl of rumors about the 59-year-old president's health. Officials said Bongo got dizzy at his hotel in Riyad on Oct. 24 and was taken to King Faisal Hospital. Bongo is the son of Gabon's late President Omar Bongo, who ruled the oil-rich country nation f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Gabon President Ali Bongo hospitalised in Saudi Arabia - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/gabon-president-ali-bongo-hospitalised-saudi-arabia-181029152942267.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0YPpzgQnK14xbZG9yHF6IqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 17:02:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/gabon-president-ali-bongo-hospitalised-saudi-arabia-181029152942267.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon President Ali Bongo hospitalised in Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gabon's President Ali Bongo has been hospitalised in Saudi Arabia with fatigue, his office said. Bongo was admitted to hospital last week because of "severe fatigue", government spokesperson Ike Ngouoni said in a statement on Sunday, while sources told Reuters news agency that he had suffered a stroke. The Gabonese president was still under observation on Monday at the King Faisal hospital in Riyadh, where he was taken on October 24. A medical and a diplomatic source both told Reuters that the president suffered a stroke. Ngouoni, however, denied this and said that Bongo instead had "severe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Gabon Leader Has Stroke, Sources Say, Govt Says it's Fatigue - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/gabon-leader-has-stroke-sources-say-govt-says-it-s-fatigue/4633569.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPaeP10sOLPumc9jck_3PwkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 15:20:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/gabon-leader-has-stroke-sources-say-govt-says-it-s-fatigue/4633569.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon Leader Has Stroke, Sources Say, Govt Says it's Fatigue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gabon's President Ali Bongo was hospitalized last week in Saudi Arabia after suffering a stroke, two sources told Reuters, while Gabonese authorities said he was admitted only because of fatigue. Bongo on Monday was still under observation at the King Faisal hospital in Riyadh where he was taken on Oct. 24. A medical and a diplomatic source both told Reuters that the president suffered a stroke. Government spokesman Ike Ngouoni denied this and said that Bongo instead had "severe fatigue" after months of strenuous work. The president was in Saudi Arabia to attend the Future Investment Initia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Botswana’s President Masisi joins the Giants Club - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/campaigns/elephant-campaign/botswana-s-president-masisi-joins-the-giants-club-a8591101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZzAwGYV63RKtDn9PL7N8kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 21:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/campaigns/elephant-campaign/botswana-s-president-masisi-joins-the-giants-club-a8591101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Botswana’s President Masisi joins the Giants Club&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Botswana’s new president Mokgweetsi Masisi became the fourth African Head of State to join the Giants Club when he signed the forum’s declaration at a ceremony attended by fellow African leaders. The Giants Club is an initiative of the international conservation organisation Space for Giants that unites the leaders of African elephant-range states with international financiers, conservationists and celebrities. Together, these individuals combine their exceptional political muscle, extensive financial resources, pioneering scientific expertise, and global reach and influence to fulfil the C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Gabon heads to the polls to elect members of parliament - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/gabon-heads-polls-elect-members-parliament-181006112901206.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMiQLDD5Gn7NAWVg2uxDpmkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 12:13:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/gabon-heads-polls-elect-members-parliament-181006112901206.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon heads to the polls to elect members of parliament&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;People in Gabon are voting in a long-delayed legislative and municipal polls, the first to be held since a presidential election two years ago marred by deadly violence and fraud allegations. Most polling stations in the capital Libreville opened at 8:00 am local time (0700 GMT) under grey skies and light rain on Saturday. Posters around Libreville were seen asking the country's 680,000 voters to turn up to elect 143 new MPs as well as other local officials. A divided opposition is unlikely to mount a successful challenge to President Ali Bongo's ruling Gabonese Democratic Party (PDG), opin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Gabon ruling party claims election win - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/gabon-ruling-party-claims-election-win-181007164535784.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL8e0Ga_-PDjGh6ZIpum5WoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 19:37:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/gabon-ruling-party-claims-election-win-181007164535784.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon ruling party claims election win&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Ali Bongo's ruling Gabonese Democratic Party (PDG) has won a legislative election by a landslide in the first round, the presidency said. "We have observed what looks like a landslide in favour of the [ruling] majority," presidential spokesman Ike Ngouoni said on Sunday, citing results posted publicly at voting stations. He said the PDG had won 80 of the 143 seats in the national parliament. Ngouoni said turnout was "relatively weak". The presidential spokesman said the electoral authority would announce definitive results later Sunday or on Monday. Some opposition candidates and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Gabon accuses Veolia of causing severe pollution - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a97a1e3a-2056-11e8-9efc-0cd3483b8b80</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI_6pr-kJJQLNdTJoT_SdDkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 12:14:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a97a1e3a-2056-11e8-9efc-0cd3483b8b80" target="_blank"&gt;Gabon accuses Veolia of causing severe pollution&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government of Gabon has stepped up its feud with Veolia, accusing the French water, waste management and energy group of causing widespread “severe pollution” at several operating sites in the central African nation. Last month, the Gabon government seized 35 sites operated by Veolia through its Gabonese subsidiary. Antoine Frérot, Veolia chief executive, responded angrily, saying his company would sue for breach of contract and arguing that the “expropriation” would damage the cause of long-term foreign investment in Gabon and the rest of Africa. But Emmanuel Issoze-Ngondet, prime mini...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>New TV show tells of capture of Gabon ivory smuggling gang - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/campaigns/GiantsClub/new-tv-show-tells-of-capture-of-gabon-ivory-smuggling-gang-a8175481.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMA_YIug_WiDFan5z_CqPjwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/campaigns/GiantsClub/new-tv-show-tells-of-capture-of-gabon-ivory-smuggling-gang-a8175481.html" target="_blank"&gt;New TV show tells of capture of Gabon ivory smuggling gang&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The extraordinary story of how the Gabonese wildlife service managed to capture the biggest ivory smuggling ring in the country’s history has been revealed by a new document. The programme, which was shown on the central African nations’s 24-hour TV news channel, detailed how it took two years for the criminals to be captured in an investigation that had been codenamed Operation Nzok, which means elephant in the local Fang language. The ivory smuggling network was busted in November last year and it was found that in 2017 alone more than 600 tusks, weighing a total of more than six tons, ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>2 Danish Journalists Violently Attacked in Gabon - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/two-danish-journalists-violently-attacked-in-gabon/4167232.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFFKFmZyPCIQW-_Ih4_S38kqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 12:31:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/two-danish-journalists-violently-attacked-in-gabon/4167232.html" target="_blank"&gt;2 Danish Journalists Violently Attacked in Gabon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man stabbed two Danish journalists in Gabon's capital, declaring it was in retaliation for U.S. attacks against Muslims and leaving one reporter in serious condition, Gabon's defense minister said. The attack Saturday occurred while the journalists were shopping at an artisanal market, a site popular with tourists. It is the first of its kind in this West African country where Muslims and Christians coexist peacefully. The stabbing was carried out in Libreville by a 53-year-old Niger national who screamed "Allah Akbar," said Gabonese Minister of Defense Etienne Massard Makaga. The attacke...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>