<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Google Allo - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZqYmpsNE9YRm1haElDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:36:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Google Allo to be officially discontinued by March 2019 - Dignited</title><link>https://www.dignited.com/38022/google-allo-is-officially-being-discontinued-by-march-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780126952784</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dignited.com/38022/google-allo-is-officially-being-discontinued-by-march-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;Google Allo to be officially discontinued by March 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Dignited&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.alphr.com/google/1010314/google-kills-off-hangouts-and-allo-in-a-cull-to-its-messaging-apps" target="_blank"&gt;Google kills off Hangouts and Allo in a cull to its messaging apps&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Alphr&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/12/07/losing-out-to-facebook-and-snapchat-google-tries-to-clean-up-messaging/" target="_blank"&gt;Losing out to Facebook and Snapchat, Google tries to clean up messaging - Tech News&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://bgr.com/2018/12/06/google-messaging-new-strategy-allo/" target="_blank"&gt;Google is finally fixing its incomprehensible messaging apps strategy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;BGR&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://phandroid.com/2018/12/06/googles-allo-will-officially-shut-down-next-spring/" target="_blank"&gt;Google’s Allo will officially shut down next Spring&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Phandroid - News for Android&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqeQgKInNDQklTVURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NrTUtFUWpRdXQtbGpZQU1FUXZFOFpDZEV6UkFFaTVIYjI5bmJHVWdhWE1nYzJoMWRIUnBibWNnWkc5M2JpQnBkSE1nYldWemMyRm5hVzVuSUdGd2NDQkJiR3h2S0FBUAE?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.dignited.com">Dignited</source></item><item><title>Inside Google’s Quest To Reinvent Chat With Machine Learning - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcodesign.com/90138040/inside-googles-quest-to-reinvent-chat-with-machine-learning</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHT9re1sc2q6dde8fpc2yzIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMIGcAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 07:00:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcodesign.com/90138040/inside-googles-quest-to-reinvent-chat-with-machine-learning" target="_blank"&gt;Inside Google’s Quest To Reinvent Chat With Machine Learning&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Allo is an honoree in the 2017 Innovation By Design Awards, Fast Company‘s annual celebration of the best ideas in design. See the rest of the winners, finalists, and honorable mentions here. Mobile chat is where it’s okay to be dumb. Your LinkedIn page may be a work of art wrought in HR-friendly prose; your tweets, so sharp you could shave with them. But texting? Let the autocorrect errors fly! Why punctuate? Isn’t that what old people do? In fact, why use words at all when any number of pictographic pokes, nods, and grunts available at the press of a button will get the job done faster? B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcodesign.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Google adds audio-only calls to Duo, file sharing to Allo - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-google-brazil-idUSKBN16T352</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGaTTghCZzqvW-2cy-YC_kgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 22:09:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-google-brazil-idUSKBN16T352" target="_blank"&gt;Google adds audio-only calls to Duo, file sharing to Allo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAO PAULO (Reuters) - Google said on Wednesday it would offer an audio-only option on its Duo video calls service to help users communicate using poor-quality connections, and was adding a feature to permit file sharing in group chats on its Allo messaging App. The company launched Google Duo in August, providing video calls for users on Android and iOS, pitting it against Apple Inc's FaceTime, Microsoft Corp's video-calling app Skype and Facebook Inc's Messenger. Google, owned by Alphabet Inc, said audio-only calls on Duo would be available from Wednesday in Brazil, and would be rolled out...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Google Maps solves the nagging 'What's your ETA?' problem - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2017/03/22/technology/google-maps-eta/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIRgABEKAw2uYZlTwSRmrP0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 23:59:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2017/03/22/technology/google-maps-eta/" target="_blank"&gt;Google Maps solves the nagging 'What's your ETA?' problem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Where are you?" "What's your ETA?" "When will you be here?" Google wants to help people answer those age-old (and tiresome) questions -- without using any words at all. On Wednesday, Google announced a Maps update that adds a new location-sharing feature. The update gives people the option to share their real-time whereabouts, and their travel routes, with select contacts for a chosen time period, according to a blog post from Google Maps engineering manager Daniel Resnick. To share your location information, Google Maps planted a "Share Location" button in the side tab on the Maps browser...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Big Questions Google Needs To Answer At I/O This Week - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcodesign.com/90124863/the-big-questions-google-needs-to-answer-this-week-at-google-io-2017</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOukyALGEmlUX9hVznaeKbkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMIGcAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 07:00:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcodesign.com/90124863/the-big-questions-google-needs-to-answer-this-week-at-google-io-2017" target="_blank"&gt;The Big Questions Google Needs To Answer At I/O This Week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This Wednesday, Google will open the doors to Google I/O, its biggest conference of the year. While aimed at developers, I/O is where Google announces stuff that any designer or consumer cares about–like the future of Android and Search. Last year, I/O was a product blitz: It brought us the Google Assistant, the Google Home speaker, Google’s first phone, the Pixel, and a AI-driven messenger called Allo. That’s all on top of its big push into VR for the everyman, known as Daydream. It was Google’s most important year ever in hardware, and it made the search and advertising company look prime...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcodesign.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>The Rise Of Auto-Complete Culture–And Why We Should Resist - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcodesign.com/90126569/the-rise-of-autocomplete-culture</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMs-mNwqvhbr7FZKkuCZmxgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMIGcAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 07:00:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcodesign.com/90126569/the-rise-of-autocomplete-culture" target="_blank"&gt;The Rise Of Auto-Complete Culture–And Why We Should Resist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A friend and fellow writer I hadn’t heard from for a while sent me an email the other day. She wanted some advice, and I readily offered it. Then she wrote me a nice response–the sort of casually witty, stupidly impressive little thing that no one I know could have written but her. And at the bottom of her thoughtful email, Google offered me three quick responses in the iOS Gmail app: Thanks! You’re welcome! Sounds good to me! With a tap, I could auto-fill my response to her. Just like on Google’s Allo Messenger or Apple’s iMessage, I could let the software respond to an email or text not w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcodesign.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Google’s New AI Tool Turns Your Selfies Into Emoji - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcodesign.com/90124964/exclusive-new-google-tool-uses-ai-to-create-custom-emoji-of-you-from-a-selfie</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECsnZd597xBqvwym4d6ozHAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMIGcAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 07:00:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcodesign.com/90124964/exclusive-new-google-tool-uses-ai-to-create-custom-emoji-of-you-from-a-selfie" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Google’s New AI Tool Turns Your Selfies Into Emoji&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Machine learning and artificial intelligence have, for a couple years, been hailed as the death knell to almost everything you can imagine: The information we consume, the way we vote, the jobs we have, and even our very existence as a species. (Food for thought: The stuff about ML taking over Homo sapiens totally makes sense, even if you haven’t just taken a huge bong rip.) So maybe it’s welcome news that the newest application of ML from Google, worldwide leaders in machine learning, isn’t to build a new Mars rover or a chatbot that can replace your doctor. Rather, its a tool that anyone ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcodesign.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Google unveils physical photo albums, Android O features and augmented reality app - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/05/17/google-unveils-physical-photo-albums-android-o-features-augmented/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJaIUptYB-t7aSuSp_jh2z0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 19:38:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/05/17/google-unveils-physical-photo-albums-android-o-features-augmented/" target="_blank"&gt;Google unveils physical photo albums, Android O features and augmented reality app&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google has unveiled its latest raft of updates alongside an all-new product: a physical photo album. The technology giant launched a host of new features for its apps, products and software at its annual developer's conference alongside the retro physical photo album. It also said it has reached 2 billion active users on Android devices. Key announcements of the event included an augmented reality tool called Google Lens, features of the upcoming Android O software, and a standalone virtual reality headset. Google will use its image recognition and AI software to make the albumsCredit: Gett...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Google can randomly share your search history with friends through its new messaging app - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/google-allo-search-history-revealed-messaging-app-a7630001.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC7L0tci6skPHK0LeN6io6oqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 18:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/google-allo-search-history-revealed-messaging-app-a7630001.html" target="_blank"&gt;Google can randomly share your search history with friends through its new messaging app&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Worrying issues have been discovered in Google’s messaging app, Allo. It has been found to be capable of sharing users’ past Google searches with contacts, without being prompted to. The discovery was made by Re/code’s Tess Townsend, who was using Allo to chat to a friend. Google marks International Women's Day with 13 amazing women - 13 show all Google marks International Women's Day with 13 amazing women - 1/13 Ida Wells An African-American journalist and activist born in Mississippi in 1862, she wrote prolifically on the fight for women’s suffrage as well as the struggle for civil rights...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>It's Time To Treat Siri, Alexa, and Google Assistant Like The Toddlers They Are - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcodesign.com/3069012/its-time-to-treat-siri-alexa-and-google-assistant-like-the-toddlers-they-are</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA0J8lc2hdmi7fUjY380RjwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMIGcAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcodesign.com/3069012/its-time-to-treat-siri-alexa-and-google-assistant-like-the-toddlers-they-are" target="_blank"&gt;It's Time To Treat Siri, Alexa, and Google Assistant Like The Toddlers They Are&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI doesn't understand human social norms. It's the Valley's fault, but until we talk to AI differently, it will continue to be our problem. A funny thing happened to Recode writer Tess Townsend when she was using Google's Allo messaging app with a friend. The friend asked the Allo AI assistant if it was a bot. And Allo, in a moment of confusion, responded with something unexpected—a link to a Harry Potter fan site. Why? Townsend's friend had searched for Harry Potter a few days ago. And when he put Allo on the spot with a question about its existence, it spit out a random link it had uttere...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcodesign.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Google I/O 2017: 8 Reasons To Pay Attention As Google Courts Developers - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40421126/google-io-2017-8-reasons-to-pay-attention-as-google-courts-developers</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBFRcSFaaZ_ANaMgkr0acDoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 21:19:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/40421126/google-io-2017-8-reasons-to-pay-attention-as-google-courts-developers" target="_blank"&gt;Google I/O 2017: 8 Reasons To Pay Attention As Google Courts Developers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This Wednesday and Thursday, Google is holding its annual developer shindig, I/O. The conference will turn the Shoreline Ampitheatre near the company’s headquarters in Mountain View, Calif. into an amusement park for nerds. With any luck, CEO Sundar Pichai won’t lead off on a dark note, as Mark Zuckerberg did by acknowledging a murder shared on Facebook at Facebook F8 and Satya Nadella did by referencing the possibility of technology leading us into an Orwellian future at Microsoft’s Build. Pichai will likely have much sunnier things to say about his company’s work in artificial intelligenc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>How Stickers Are Helping Humanize Chat Apps - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcodesign.com/3065406/how-stickers-are-helping-humanize-chat-apps</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENlnzMCGkfwQAj2mhuKbvOcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMIGcAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcodesign.com/3065406/how-stickers-are-helping-humanize-chat-apps" target="_blank"&gt;How Stickers Are Helping Humanize Chat Apps&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all its ubiquity, speaking over messenger is still not as fluid as chatting IRL. Can cute digital stickers change that? Emoji may have gone high-brow now that they're part of MoMA's permanent collection, but back on the front lines—on people's devices and in text conversations—a new form of pictorial communication has taken hold. They're called digital stickers, and when it comes to compensating for the lack of facial and visual cues in digital communication, they've got emoji beat. While the Snapchat-backed Bitmoji popularized stickers in the West (they've been in Asian markets for a f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcodesign.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Google’s message app Allo overshares data with friends - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/380746-googles-message-app-allo-overshares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO1GHdRXI2WYoWeIdu71SgwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 21:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/380746-googles-message-app-allo-overshares/" target="_blank"&gt;Google’s message app Allo overshares data with friends&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Privacy advocates are raising alarm about Google’s messenger app Allo, pointing out that its Google Assistant overshares search data when not prompted, and the app itself lacks encryption and is potentially open to government spying. “In the middle of our conversation, my friend directed Assistant to identify itself,” wrote Tess Townsend in her review of Allo in Re/code on Tuesday. “Instead of offering a name or a pithy retort, it responded with a link from Harry Potter fan website Pottermore.” Google’s Allo app can reveal what you’ve searched to your friendshttps://t.co/tmzCVODEVo pic.twit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Google Assistant is Getting Ready to Compete with Amazon Alexa and Microsoft Cortana - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/janakirammsv/2016/11/12/google-assistant-is-getting-ready-to-compete-with-amazon-alexa-and-microsoft-cortana/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEII0m6OWZao44FnncdvgmFQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/janakirammsv/2016/11/12/google-assistant-is-getting-ready-to-compete-with-amazon-alexa-and-microsoft-cortana/" target="_blank"&gt;Google Assistant is Getting Ready to Compete with Amazon Alexa and Microsoft Cortana&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market for personal assistants with conversational user experience is heating up. While Amazon has already launched the next generation Echo in the form of Echo Dot and Echo Tap, Google is busy turning its Assistant more intelligent and smarter than the competition. Starting December, developers will be able to create custom actions for Google Assistant. This will offer a similar experience of developing Alexa Skills for Echo. Google’s strategy of enabling developers to target its Assistant platform will instantly open up multiple channels to developers. They will be able to reach milli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Google admits chatbots were a bad idea - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90243776/google-admits-chatbots-were-a-bad-idea</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDIy1SmoZSPQ2dJWH11Q_7kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 13:00:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90243776/google-admits-chatbots-were-a-bad-idea" target="_blank"&gt;Google admits chatbots were a bad idea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google Assistant is getting an overhaul on smartphones, and it’s discarding one of 2016’s biggest tech fads in the process. When Google Assistant arrived a couple of years ago, chatbots were all the rage in products like Facebook Messenger and Microsoft’s Skype. Simulating a back-and-forth conversation was supposed to be more efficient than poking around in traditional apps, and chatbot proponents hyped this model as the future of software design. Google Assistant itself debuted as a feature within Google’s Allo messaging app, so you could exchange text messages with the search giant just l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Sundar Pichai Q&amp;A - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90227530/sundar-pichai-qa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENMJC1I0JN3714dxLWFq8kQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 07:00:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90227530/sundar-pichai-qa" target="_blank"&gt;Sundar Pichai Q&amp;A&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We all remember the face-plant that was Google Glass. Or the time when, in an infamous fit of over-engineering, Google tested 41 shades of the color blue on ad links to find the most profitable hue. Since then, however, the company has been steadily refining its design strategy to get out of the way and put users first. Last year, Google’s Allo messaging app was an honoree in Fast Company’s Innovation by Design Awards. This year, the company has presented a slate of sophisticated new products—including a range of smart speakers, a globe-trotting virtual experience, and a new interface for c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Is Your Small Business Leveraging Its Google My Business Page? - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesagencycouncil/2018/08/03/is-your-small-business-leveraging-its-google-my-business-page/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKZlg8fwtFb5pifzRFjYhjMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesagencycouncil/2018/08/03/is-your-small-business-leveraging-its-google-my-business-page/" target="_blank"&gt;Is Your Small Business Leveraging Its Google My Business Page?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pexels Developing a social media strategy can be difficult as there are so many different platforms to choose from. Not every business needs to have an account on every platform. And it doesn’t make sense to have a social media account without a goal or purpose. That’s why, at BusySeed, we sit down with every client individually to weigh the pros and cons of each platform directly related to their social media marketing goals. However, there are some platforms that every business should have. Google My Business absolutely falls in this category. Google My Business is an extension of its f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Google’s blob emojis are back, a year after they were redesigned - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90203712/googles-blob-emojis-are-back-a-year-after-they-were-redesigned</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHP8Us6leNy_lqMC_KUPqB8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 15:43:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90203712/googles-blob-emojis-are-back-a-year-after-they-were-redesigned" target="_blank"&gt;Google’s blob emojis are back, a year after they were redesigned&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Mutant egg yolks. Clippy’s deformed, inbred cousins. Lumpy, misshapen visages.” Those are the words of Fast Company‘s very own Mark Wilson talking about Google’s longtime emoji set, also known as “the blobs,” last year. Google spent 18 months carefully redesigning the emoji, unveiling the revamped version here on Co.Design just over a year ago. Despite the protests of Android users who loved the old emoji, the blobs were history. Or so we thought. Google is now bringing back the beloved if amorphous emoji as a sticker pack. [Image: Google] There were specific reasons Google redesigned its ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Google to launch iMessage and WhatsApp rival - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/04/20/google-launch-imessage-whatsapp-rival/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELlnTTz-9ys-FF7UNiR23LwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 11:16:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/04/20/google-launch-imessage-whatsapp-rival/" target="_blank"&gt;Google to launch iMessage and WhatsApp rival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google is launching a free messaging service that will link up with text messages to rival WhatsApp and Apple's iMessage. The messenger will be available on Android, the Google-owned operating system that runs almost every non-Apple smartphone on the market. The new service, named Chat, works similarly to traditional SMS text messages but will notify senders when the recipient has read their message and show if they are typing, like many messaging apps. It can support high resolution pictures and group conversations, like WhatsApp, as well as features like Gifs. It will be available on Andr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Google’s Risky Plan To Beat Apple And Facebook In The Chat Wars - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcodesign.com/90168922/googles-risky-plan-to-beat-apple-and-facebook-in-the-chat-wars</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM96uxFBHt0EjlQLcQAogEgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMIGcAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 15:20:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcodesign.com/90168922/googles-risky-plan-to-beat-apple-and-facebook-in-the-chat-wars" target="_blank"&gt;Google’s Risky Plan To Beat Apple And Facebook In The Chat Wars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google’s Android messaging app strategy has been a mess for years. Apple Messages, Facebook, and WhatsApp offer vastly better experiences and enjoy a much wider user base. The Mountain View company seems to have realized that to defeat its competition, it needs to do something drastic. A Verge exclusive reveals the simple and risky plan: First, stop the development of Google’s own proprietary messaging app, Allo, and reposition Hangouts as a competitor to the professional workgroup chat application Slack. Third, the company will put all of its messaging eggs in a basket called Rich Communi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcodesign.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Tired of texting? Google tests robot to chat with friends for you - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/feb/14/google-tests-robot-chat-reply-friends</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECSDKbdH6K83Mf3Xe-cw38oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 10:38:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/feb/14/google-tests-robot-chat-reply-friends" target="_blank"&gt;Tired of texting? Google tests robot to chat with friends for you&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you tired of the constant need to tap on a glass keyboard just to keep up with your friends? Do you wish a robot could free you of your constant communication obligations via WhatsApp, Facebook or text messages? Google is working on an AI-based auto-reply system to do just that. Google’s experimental product lab called Area 120 is currently testing a new system simply called Reply that will work with Google’s Hangouts and Allo, WhatsApp, Facebook Messenger, Android Messages, Skype, Twitter direct messages and Slack. Reply aims to take the smart AI-based suggested replies that are availa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Offensive chat app responses highlight AI fails - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2017/10/25/technology/business/google-allo-facebook-m-offensive-responses/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGlLvkfiTyo7sUvSKuOnJM0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 18:24:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2017/10/25/technology/business/google-allo-facebook-m-offensive-responses/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Offensive chat app responses highlight AI fails&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Messaging assistants and smart replies are meant to make lives easier by anticipating responses when chatting with friends. But tools from Google and Facebook sometimes struggle to appropriately insert themselves into conversations. For example, the smart reply feature in Google's Allo messaging app last week suggested I send the "person wearing turban" emoji in response to a message that included a gun emoji. My CNN Tech colleague was able to replicate the exchange in a separate chat. Google has fixed the response and issued an apology. "We're deeply sorry that this suggestion appeared in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item></channel></rss>