<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Samsung Group - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRGRuZGpjeUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:25:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Massive Galaxy S10 Upgrade Suddenly 'Confirmed' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/samsung-galaxy-s10-upgrade-release-date-cost-ultrasonic-fingerprint-reader-5g/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMyiu30uk6R3WMra7ewUJnIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/samsung-galaxy-s10-upgrade-release-date-cost-ultrasonic-fingerprint-reader-5g/" target="_blank"&gt;Massive Galaxy S10 Upgrade Suddenly 'Confirmed'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10 inadvertently became official following high-profile announcements by major US carriers. The news locked in a 5G upgrade for at least one of the four models Samsung will release. But now Samsung has confirmed what I consider to be an even bigger upgrade… Samsung has taken to the stage with chipset partner Qualcomm for the formal announcement of a ‘3D Sonic Sensor’, the world’s first commercial ultrasonic in-display fingerprint reader. And it is going to give the Galaxy S10 a massive advantage over rivals. Samsung Galaxy S10 concept What we h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECs8OiMwxPuwcZzcG4cRAdMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes no notch in the Galaxy S10, the 5G S10 confirmed for America, the OnePlus 5G heading to the UK, three new Nokia handsets, a review of the Pocophone F1, Huawei’s ongoing security issues, and an innovation award for the Pixel 3 and 3XL. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). No Notch, But There Will Be A Hole, In The New Galaxy S10 Samsung appe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Japan government to halt buying Huawei, ZTE equipment: sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-china-huawei/japan-government-to-halt-buying-huawei-zte-equipment-sources-idUSKBN1O600X</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDg2o64e5N4PEWa1sdvSWsqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:35:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-china-huawei/japan-government-to-halt-buying-huawei-zte-equipment-sources-idUSKBN1O600X" target="_blank"&gt;Japan government to halt buying Huawei, ZTE equipment: sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan plans to ban government purchases of equipment from China's Huawei Technologies Co Ltd and ZTE Corp to beef up its defenses against intelligence leaks and cyber attacks, sources told Reuters. Chinese tech companies are under intense scrutiny from Washington and some prominent allies over ties to the Chinese government, driven by concerns they could be used by Beijing for spying. A government ban in Japan will come after Huawei has already been locked out of the U.S. market and after Australia and New Zealand have blocked it from building 5G networks. Huawei has repeatedly insisted Bei...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy S10 Details Confirm Powerful Features - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-5g-qualcomm-snapdragon-855-confirmed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBfJb5891KEyjYbQeeJek7wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-5g-qualcomm-snapdragon-855-confirmed/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy S10 Details Confirm Powerful Features&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has confirmed its continuing partnership with Qualcomm will see the South Korean company use the new SnapDragon 855 system on chip inside 2019′s Galaxy smartphones, starting with its first 5G device for US market. Both Verizon and AT&amp;T have confirmed a 5G Galaxy smartphone will arrive in the first half of next year. While the connection was not explicitly made, Samsung’s VP of Product Marketing and Strategy, Justin Denison, confirmed that the upcoming US 5G smartphone from the South Korean company would be powered by Qualcomm’s SnapDragon 855 system on chip. The only handset we’re a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Oppo R17 Pro Review: The World's Fastest Charging Phone - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/12/05/oppo-r17-pro-review-the-worlds-fastest-charging-phone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJoY6kkbTRtA6Cs0CJ-gDosqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/12/05/oppo-r17-pro-review-the-worlds-fastest-charging-phone/" target="_blank"&gt;Oppo R17 Pro Review: The World's Fastest Charging Phone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Oppo R17 Pro with its gorgeous gradient-colored back. Most Chinese smartphone brands nowadays pump out four, five, or six devices a year, to a market that’s already beyond saturate. Many of these manufacturers barely differentiate each of these handsets, so much so that they tend to get lost in the noise and are forgotten quickly. However Oppo, for the most part, has done a solid job of making sure each release is worth covering, with at least one head-turning feature. The Find X, for example, was an absolute stunner in design and craftsmanship and will likely end up in one of the top t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm unveils new chip to power 5G smartphones - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-samsung-elec/qualcomm-unveils-new-chip-to-power-5g-smartphones-idUSKBN1O32P1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMecw1wB_A6sq8OQSIV_45wqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:51:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-samsung-elec/qualcomm-unveils-new-chip-to-power-5g-smartphones-idUSKBN1O32P1" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm unveils new chip to power 5G smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chip supplier Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) on Tuesday unveiled a new generation of mobile phone processor chips that will power 5G smartphones in the United States as soon as next year. The key feature of the Snapdragon 855 chip, launched at an event in Hawaii, is a so-called modem for phones to connect to 5G wireless data networks with mobile data speeds of up to 50 or 100 times faster than current 4G networks. Mobile carriers are investing in 5G networks and are eager to sell 5G phones and data plans to recoup investment costs. Qualcomm, the largest supplier...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Samsung Suddenly 'Confirms' Radical 5G Galaxy S10 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-5g-release-date-price-cost-verizon-att-upgrade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzHJ9vIrddPWJnbbQDtf0oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-5g-release-date-price-cost-verizon-att-upgrade/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Suddenly 'Confirms' Radical 5G Galaxy S10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We already know Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10 is the biggest shake-up of the Galaxy range in years. There will be four models (including a new, more affordable version), up to six cameras, massive displays and ‘gradient’ colour schemes. And now Samsung isn’t even trying to hide its biggest upgrade of all… In a pair of official announcements which are about as subtle as a brick, both Verizon and AT&amp;T have announced a partnership with Samsung to deliver a ‘5G Galaxy smartphone’ in the first half of 2019. And yes, we know exactly what this is. Galaxy S10 Plus Concept “5G is going to b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Plans Radical Update On Foldable Galaxy F - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/12/05/samsung-plans-radical-update-on-foldable-galaxy-f/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGlmI4by5kNOZuBLztkYrgsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/12/05/samsung-plans-radical-update-on-foldable-galaxy-f/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Plans Radical Update On Foldable Galaxy F&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung debuts its foldable phone technology at its developer conference. Photographer: David Paul Morris/Bloomberg Samsung could be planning to update its upcoming foldable phone lineup with a new concept, according to a recently filed patent. The proposed device, spotted by Patently Mobile, has a display that rolls up like a piece of paper into a cylindrical housing unit. With the screen being withdrawn and retracted when necessary. The patent details how a rollable OLED display will have to be sandwiched by several substrates to protect the durability of the panel, as is the case with an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENR6R3fi9qwUs_y2cSw6FUgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:42:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2" target="_blank"&gt;Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verizon Communications Inc and Samsung Electronics Co Ltd on Monday confirmed long-held industry expectations they would seek to steal a march on Apple Inc by launching U.S. 5G smartphones in the first half of 2019. The two companies said in a statement they would unveil a prototype, using Qualcomm Inc's modem chips, at the chipmaker's annual Snapdragon Technology Summit in Maui, Hawaii this week. While Verizon is leading the charge to trial 5G in some cities next year, industry analysts say the higher-speed networks are unlikely to be widely available until the middle of the next decade. A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>5G smartphones are coming in 2019. What does that mean? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/samsung-verizon-5g/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBg7H2jCZlAeINu5jVJYwXUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:58:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/samsung-verizon-5g/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;5G smartphones are coming in 2019. What does that mean?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;5G is already here, but you can't do much to access those super-fast speeds unless you live in a specific place with a particular piece of technology. That's about to change. Samsung and Verizon (VZ) jointly announced Monday the companies would sell a 5G smartphone in the first half of 2019. Although they didn't say which phone would support 5G, Samsung usually announces its latest Galaxy S smartphone in the spring. The mystery phone may not be the first 5G smartphone to hit the market. Unsure of other companies' plans, Verizon and Samsung hedged by saying it would be "one of the first." Bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy Leak Reveals Samsung's Spectacular S10 Plus - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/03/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-specifications-camera-design-notch-release-date/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFfT-5cLrw0yi53UeU63QAoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/03/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-specifications-camera-design-notch-release-date/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy Leak Reveals Samsung's Spectacular S10 Plus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More details are coming out around Samsung’s family of Galaxy S10 devices. With the attention is now on the S10 Plus the latest information give us the clearest idea yet of the upcoming South Korean flagship. The S10 Plus is the third of four handsets, lying just behind the powerful Galaxy S10 Ultra (which is expected to be the ‘specs monster’ with multiple cameras and potentially 5G connectivity), just ahead of the standard Galaxy S10, and well ahead of the entry-level S10 model. The Plus likely denotes a larger screen size (much as it does with the S9 and S9 Plus). The latest leaked detai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung's folding screen tech has been stolen and sold to China - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/tech/samsung-china-tech-theft/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL_L6ZknDZL5z2MTefhAGK4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:11:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/tech/samsung-china-tech-theft/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung's folding screen tech has been stolen and sold to China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung's latest bendable screen technology has been stolen and sold to two Chinese companies, according to prosecutors in South Korea. The Suwon District Prosecutor's Office charged 11 people on Thursday with stealing tech secrets from Samsung (SSNLF), the office said in a statement. The prosecutors allege that a Samsung supplier leaked blueprints of Samsung's "flexible OLED edge panel 3D lamination" to a company that it had set up. That company then sold the tech secrets to the Chinese firms for nearly $14 million, according to the prosecutors. Theydid not name the people or companies inv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>South Korea indicts group for leaking Samsung display tech to Chinese firm - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-samsung-elec/south-korea-indicts-group-for-leaking-samsung-display-tech-to-chinese-firm-idUSKCN1NY17K</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDzeIm4-V5qzXSiAFa1FdoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 10:34:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-samsung-elec/south-korea-indicts-group-for-leaking-samsung-display-tech-to-chinese-firm-idUSKCN1NY17K" target="_blank"&gt;South Korea indicts group for leaking Samsung display tech to Chinese firm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Korean prosecutors on Thursday said they have indicted nine people on suspicion of leaking Samsung Electronics Co Ltd flexible display technology to a Chinese company. The Suwon District Prosecutors' Office has charged the chief executive and eight employees of supplier Toptec Co Ltd for selling information earlier this year about Samsung's organic light-emitting diode (OLED) panels. The group are accused of forming a separate shell company that received information on the use of equipment and drawings of panels obtained from Samsung subsidiary Samsung Display, and which sold some of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Samsung Leak Suddenly Exposes Radical Galaxy S10 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/02/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-design-release-date-cost-price-upgrade-galaxy-s9-note9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENwpZru7pfpwX2Q2_ZX42pEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/02/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-design-release-date-cost-price-upgrade-galaxy-s9-note9/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Leak Suddenly Exposes Radical Galaxy S10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For its 10th-anniversary, Samsung is shaking up the Galaxy range. There will be no less than four Galaxy S10 models, and they will come with up to six cameras, 5G carrier support and the biggest phone displays Samsung has ever made. But there are also some controversial compromises (1,2) and arguably the most controversial of them all has just been confirmed… Having already successfully leaked the Galaxy S9 and Note 9 this year, the ever-prolific, ever mysterious Ice Universe has confirmed every model of Galaxy S10 will cut a hole into their displays: “The Galaxy S10 Lite, S10, and S10+ ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>SAMSUNG CSC - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/284625735/samsung-csc-by-berfu-hena-azazi</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMyC-9Qr-guxy0hJQzdwpi8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 22:03:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/284625735/samsung-csc-by-berfu-hena-azazi" target="_blank"&gt;SAMSUNG CSC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAMSUNG CSC&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>South Korea charges 9 people with selling Samsung secrets to China - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/29/south-korea-charges-9-people-selling-samsung-secrets-china/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED4ait6Ynt0JTi82dikPusMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 18:59:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/29/south-korea-charges-9-people-selling-samsung-secrets-china/" target="_blank"&gt;South Korea charges 9 people with selling Samsung secrets to China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Korea has indicted nine people and two companies on suspicion of leaking Samsung smartphone technology to China. The Suwon District Prosecutors’ Office said on Thursday that it had charged the chief executive and eight employees of Toptec, an equipment manufacturer engaged in the production of smartphone displays, with selling on confidential Samsung technology. The nine people are accused of receiving 15.5bn won (£10.8m) in exchange for providing information about Samsung’s flexible screen technology. The hardware that is alleged to have been stolen is used to create the curved scree...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Scouted: High-End TVs Compared: OLED vs QLED - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/high-end-tvs-compared-oled-vs-qled</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOjbqoaaJyXMdnej0DqVbQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/high-end-tvs-compared-oled-vs-qled" target="_blank"&gt;Scouted: High-End TVs Compared: OLED vs QLED&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When most people shop for a TV, they care about two things: screen size and price. But if you actually want the best picture quality TVs have to offer, you’ll be looking at high-end tech like OLED and QLED models. But despite the similar-looking acronyms, these two technologies are quite different. OLED TVs are available from a few different manufacturers, including LG and Sony in the US, and Philips and other manufacturers abroad. QLED is a Samsung-specific marketing term for TVs that use quantum dot technology, though other manufacturers are starting to come out with their own quantum-bas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Samsung Elec says it will cancel $4.4 billion worth of shares - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-samsung-elec-stocks/samsung-elec-says-it-will-cancel-44-billion-worth-of-shares-idUSKCN1NZ02O</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOu-hK9sXMHm9cXEtwBvIowqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:33:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-samsung-elec-stocks/samsung-elec-says-it-will-cancel-44-billion-worth-of-shares-idUSKCN1NZ02O" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Elec says it will cancel $4.4 billion worth of shares&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung Electronics Co Ltd (005930.KS: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) said on Friday it would cancel 4.9 trillion won ($4.4 billion) worth of its shares. Expected to be complete on Dec. 4, the cancellation was the second stage of its previously announced plan to cancel all of its treasury shares in two stages to enhance shareholder value. The first stage was canceled in May last year, it said. The South Korean tech giant last year rejected pressure from U.S. activist hedge fund Elliott for a major overhaul of its complicated structure, but accepted part of the fund's proposals by rev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S10 Leak Exposes Controversial New Cancellation - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/29/samsung-galaxy-s10-design-camera-display-notch-release-date-price-cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAUa90LdOMwpsR0rqXOd7r8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/29/samsung-galaxy-s10-design-camera-display-notch-release-date-price-cost/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S10 Leak Exposes Controversial New Cancellation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10 will be its most exciting upgrade in years. Not only does it promise a radical new design, but a flagship model with six cameras which openly taunts the iPhone X. That said, these changes come with some controversial compromises and another one has just been exposed… Following new leaks from historically accurate Korean site The Bell about the Galaxy S10’s camera systems, research from BGR has shown it is almost certain Samsung has been forced to scrap facial recognition on all four models. And this is a blow as Samsung was understood to be on the ver...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung workers say apology is ‘too little, too late’ - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/219ae36e-f20b-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKshHMKXTZk04dT4r15GdEcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/219ae36e-f20b-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung workers say apology is ‘too little, too late’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Little more than a year ago, Han Hye-kyung was surrounded by anti-union thugs, abused and left sobbing as she complained outside a court that her six years on the factory floor at Samsung had left her with a brain tumour and in a wheelchair. Ms Han, 40, and hundreds of other workers who also say they became seriously ill while working at the South Korean electronics group, spent more than a decade being stonewalled, doubted and ignored. Samsung insisted there was no connection between the conditions of its factories and the spike in cancer cases and other rare illnesses. But last Friday, th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Why Is Apple's ROE More Than Double Samsung's? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/28/why-is-apples-roe-more-than-double-samsungs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMNXvO7lAbtmeqLaQgqFs3sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 18:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/28/why-is-apples-roe-more-than-double-samsungs/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Is Apple's ROE More Than Double Samsung's?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman uses a smartphone while walking past an Apple Inc. store in Shanghai, China, on Tuesday, Nov. 27, 2018. Photographer: Qilai Shen/Bloomberg Return on equity is one of the most closely watched financial ratios for investors, as it indicates how efficiently a company has been deploying shareholder capital. Companies with a higher ROE compound their capital more efficiently and also often see more attractive valuations. Moreover, having a higher ROE means that companies are less likely to raise additional capital to fund their businesses, avoiding shareholder dilution. Smartphone behemo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>HP Inc revenue tops estimates on personal systems business - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/businessNews/idUSKCN1NY2QT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL3PfdG2eIYRMcAbXsa_UCYqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:49:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/businessNews/idUSKCN1NY2QT" target="_blank"&gt;HP Inc revenue tops estimates on personal systems business&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HP Inc's (HPQ.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) quarterly revenue beat analysts' estimates on Thursday, driven by growth in its personal systems business that sells notebooks and desktops and the acquisition of Samsung's printer business. Shares of HP Inc, which houses the hardware business of former Hewlett-Packard Co, were marginally up in extended trading. The personal systems business, which accounts for more than 60 percent of HP Inc's total revenue, rose 11 percent to $10.06 billion, beating analysts' average estimate of $9.78 billion, according to IBES data from Refinitiv. "On...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S10 Leak Exposes Potential Cancellation - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/27/samsung-galaxy-s10-cancellation-release-date-price-upgrade-galaxy-s9-active/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFBfAsVAKiVLNYmHil3jGbEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/27/samsung-galaxy-s10-cancellation-release-date-price-upgrade-galaxy-s9-active/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S10 Leak Exposes Potential Cancellation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Galaxy S10 may be getting more controversial with each passing day, but it remains Samsung’s biggest upgrade in years. Leaks tell us the flagship 10th-anniversary device will be the largest phone the company has ever made, sport an all-new design and six cameras. But, worryingly, new information suggests it might be vapourware… Picked up by the eagle-eyed bloggers at TechieRide, Samsung has quietly confirmed its new Galaxy S10 range by submitting it for certification in Russia. But the flagship is missing. Samsung Galaxy S10 and S10 Plus concept What Samsung certified was the ‘SM-G973...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung 860 QVO Solid State Drives Push Prices Down And Capacities Up - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/marcochiappetta/2018/11/27/samsung-860-qvo-solid-state-drives-push-prices-down-and-capacities-up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBEyswWoyD6WcrdHQwmVVjMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 22:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/marcochiappetta/2018/11/27/samsung-860-qvo-solid-state-drives-push-prices-down-and-capacities-up/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung 860 QVO Solid State Drives Push Prices Down And Capacities Up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Samsung 860 SSD QVO. Solid state drives remain one of the most effective upgrades for systems still hobbled by spinning, magnetic media, aka hard drives. Solid state drives not only offer much higher typical transfer rates than hard drives, but exponentially lower latency as well, which results in a perceptible improvement in responsiveness; systems boot faster, launch applications quicker, and just “feel” faster all around. The only real drawbacks to solid state drives currently are cost and capacity. Their price per gigabyte is higher than most hard drives and consumer solid state dri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Electronics apologises over factory worker cancer cases - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/samsung-electronics-apologises-factory-worker-cancer-cases-181123024347676.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENRQUynG5OTc-oAnnOwrIXwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 04:41:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/samsung-electronics-apologises-factory-worker-cancer-cases-181123024347676.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Electronics apologises over factory worker cancer cases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung Electronics on Friday apologised to workers who developed cancer after working at its semiconductor factories, bringing to an end a decade-long dispute at the world's top chipmaker. Campaign groups say 320 people developed work-related illnesses after being employed by Samsung Electronics, with 118 of them dying. "We sincerely apologise to the workers who suffered from illness and their families," said the company's co-President Kim Ki-nam. "We have failed to properly manage health risks at our semiconductor and LCD factories." Samsung Electronics is the world's biggest mobile phon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Cyber Monday 2018 Deals On Samsung TVs - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/26/cyber-monday-2018-deals-on-samsung-tvs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZiup2L37K3aChAEZCHZiMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/26/cyber-monday-2018-deals-on-samsung-tvs/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyber Monday 2018 Deals On Samsung TVs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the many other retail items with huge price cuts today, Samsung TVs are on sale at Walmart for Cyber Monday. We found the best discounts (all are at least 42 percent off) on these TVs, which promise a 4K, HD experience. Some are even bundled with additional toys, like this Xbox One X. Pick up your new TV today just in time for the holiday season, or give the best gift of the year (or both). Samsung 75-inch 4K Ultra HD Smart TV with Microsoft Xbox One X (QN75Q9FNA) Samsung QN75Q9FNA 75″ Q9FN QLED - List Price:$10,596.97 - Sale Price: $5,457.98 - Savings: $5,138.99 (48%) SAMSUNG 55-inch...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why Samsung thinks its huge 8K TV is the future of watching television - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-8k-tv-explained-review-latest-best-television-display-screen-a8643901.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED9p_SZH_EOlY6WPCy43aX0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-8k-tv-explained-review-latest-best-television-display-screen-a8643901.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why Samsung thinks its huge 8K TV is the future of watching television&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might not even be used to 4K, which – along with other new technologies like HDR – feels like it only just arrived and it is still expensive to buy the sets and difficult to find content to watch on them. But 4K is already old news, after Samsung revealed its first 8K TV meant for consumers – doubling the name, quadrupling the number of pixels on offer and heralding the future of screens. Samsung's newest television crams a full 33 million pixels into a vast display that it hopes becomes the ultimate way of watching the TV. Despite how it might sound, 8K is actually four times as many p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Samsung Electronics apologises to workers struck down by disease - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2b57424e-eedc-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBpHxkbi3PolleCSZyZHQdgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 06:48:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2b57424e-eedc-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Electronics apologises to workers struck down by disease&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung Electronics has made a formal apology to its workers suffering from serious occupational diseases and accepted a mediator’s compensation plan, drawing a final line under a decade-long dispute over its work environment. The South Korean technology giant on Friday admitted for the first time that it failed to properly address health risks posed to workers at its semiconductor and flat panel display plants and pledged to improve safety. “Our beloved colleagues and their families have suffered for a long time but Samsung Electronics failed to take care of this earlier,” said Kim Ki-nam,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Samsung's Galaxy S10 Will Get Unusual New Display - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/27/samsungs-galaxy-s10-will-get-unusual-new-display/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdWlRu3JHtMCXje5I2gJm4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 15:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/27/samsungs-galaxy-s10-will-get-unusual-new-display/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung's Galaxy S10 Will Get Unusual New Display&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung’s Galaxy S10 could have virtual no bezels thanks to the new Infinity-O display. Photographer: SeongJoon Cho/Bloomberg Samsung’s upcoming Galaxy 10 will finally sport a display notch, but it won’t be like anything we’ve seen before. At this year’s developer conference (at 1 hour 22 minutes in), Samsung confirmed that it’s working on new display styles that further shrink the bezel of its smartphones. But a new leak from Korean outlet ETnews suggests that Samsung might bring that technology to the Galaxy S10. In essence, the new “Infinity-O” display removes the top and bottom bezels –...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung apologises to workers who developed cancer after exposure to toxic chemicals - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/23/samsung-apologises-workers-developed-cancer-exposure-toxic-chemicals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBN4gh0QGtZyTQbf16cfn2EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:12:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/23/samsung-apologises-workers-developed-cancer-exposure-toxic-chemicals/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung apologises to workers who developed cancer after exposure to toxic chemicals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has apologised to employees who developed cancer at one of its computer chip manufacturing facilities following a ten-year legal battle. The announcement comes after the company and a group representing ailing Samsung workers agreed to accept compensation terms and end a highly-publicised standoff. The company's apology was part of the settlement. Kim Ki-nam, the head of Samsung’s semiconductor business, said: "We sincerely apologise to the workers who suffered from illness and their families. We have failed to properly manage health risks at our semiconductor and LCD factories.” Ca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy Leak Reveals Samsung's Stunning S10 Plus - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/28/samsung-galaxy-s10-ultra-memory-storage-specifications/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJLlnvR2O0TmqNII8H9Fq3MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 23:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/28/samsung-galaxy-s10-ultra-memory-storage-specifications/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy Leak Reveals Samsung's Stunning S10 Plus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung is planning a number of handsets in the Galaxy S10 family, from an entry-level device, through the workhorse standard models, to a high-end flagship model that will pack in the hardware. It now looks like this top model will feature some killer specifications when it is released. DJ Koh, president of mobile communications business at Samsung, holds up the new Samsung Galaxy Note (Photo by Drew Angerer/Getty Images) Reported by GF Securities in China (via ITHome), one model of the Galaxy S10 will feature an eye-watering 12 GB of RAM and 1 TB of storage. Given what we know of the S10 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>QLED vs OLED: How Cyber Monday 2018 Deals Stack Up For Each - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/26/qled-vs-oled-how-cyber-monday-2018-deal-stack-up-for-each/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGs9O3CvhtBSwCISavc4i7kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 21:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/26/qled-vs-oled-how-cyber-monday-2018-deal-stack-up-for-each/" target="_blank"&gt;QLED vs OLED: How Cyber Monday 2018 Deals Stack Up For Each&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAMSUNG 65″ class 4K (2160P) Ultra HD Smart QLED HDR TV QN65Q7FN (2018 Model) Both QLED and OLED TVs are on sale this Cyber Monday. Although both are different in their technologies and visual experience, they’re often compared as alternatives to the other. Regardless of which model you prefer, both OLED and QLED TVs are taking a huge discount during Cyber Week. Grab up your new TV before the sale ends tonight. 70-inch &amp; Larger QLED: Samsung 75-inch 4K Ultra HD Smart TV with Microsoft Xbox One X (QN75Q9FNA) - List Price: $10,596.97 - Sale Price: $5,457.98 - Savings: $5,138.99 (48%) OLED: S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Latest Galaxy S10 Leak Uncovers New Case Design - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/21/samsung-galaxy-s10-ceramic-case-new-leak-rumor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKWASIMcLbAa6yGVFykOgp0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/21/samsung-galaxy-s10-ceramic-case-new-leak-rumor/" target="_blank"&gt;Latest Galaxy S10 Leak Uncovers New Case Design&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung continues to prepare the ground for the release of the Galaxy S10 family, and new details are leaking out to excite and engage the fans. The latest is the inclusion of a ceramic back to the handsets. DJ Koh, president and CEO of Samsung Electronics, introduces the new Samsung Galaxy Note 9 smartphone at the Barclays Center, in Brooklyn (Photo by Drew Angerer/Getty Images) Samsung is expected to announce four different Galaxy S10 models in early 2019. The top-end model could be a monster of a camera phone with a total of six lenses (four at the back, and two at the front). There’s al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best Black Friday Laptop Deals On Apple Macbook Air, Lenovo IdeaPad, Samsung Chromebooks &amp; Others - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/23/best-black-friday-laptop-deals-on-apple-macbook-air-lenovo-ideapad-samsung-chromebooks-others/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBpcFX6t3MHIYRsp2XiQekYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/23/best-black-friday-laptop-deals-on-apple-macbook-air-lenovo-ideapad-samsung-chromebooks-others/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Black Friday Laptop Deals On Apple Macbook Air, Lenovo IdeaPad, Samsung Chromebooks &amp; Others&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there’s anything you can glean from the technology industry, it’s that PC vendors are desperately trying to get your attention. Often times, they’re willing to offer outstanding deals on their devices to boost market share in a highly commoditized environment. Asus ROG Strix Gaming Laptop This year, Black Friday is shaping up to be the best time of the year to buy new laptops. Companies that range as far as Dell, HP, Samsung, and others are all offering outstanding deals on laptops and all-in-one computers both big and small. Retailers, hoping to clear some stock, are ready to give you s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>OnePlus 6T Review: Competitors Have Caught Up In Value, But OnePlus Software Still King - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/22/oneplus-6t-review-competition-have-caught-up-in-value-but-oneplus-software-still-king/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECVMFsGN2osEfA5lkyveg1cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 08:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/22/oneplus-6t-review-competition-have-caught-up-in-value-but-oneplus-software-still-king/" target="_blank"&gt;OnePlus 6T Review: Competitors Have Caught Up In Value, But OnePlus Software Still King&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The OnePlus 6T has a 6.4-inch OLED display. The OnePlus 6T is the fifth phone from the upstart brand I’ve tested in a professional capacity, and this is the toughest one to judge. It’s not because the 6T isn’t good, or a step backwards. No, it’s the best OnePlus phone yet. But it’s trickier this time around because circumstances around the phone have changed. For years, OnePlus phones were undoubtedly the best value on the market. Other phones that ran on the same Snapdragon chipset almost always cost several hundred dollars more, and other phones in the mid-tier market were significantly l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Galaxy S10 Leak Suddenly Exposes Samsung's Radical Smartphone - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/20/samsung-galaxy-s10-leak-display-notch-camera-battery-life-release-date-cost-price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8WOcakR1kdyjYKb2zu2vkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/20/samsung-galaxy-s10-leak-display-notch-camera-battery-life-release-date-cost-price/" target="_blank"&gt;Galaxy S10 Leak Suddenly Exposes Samsung's Radical Smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Galaxy S10 is a smartphone worth getting excited about. We already know Samsung’s 10th-anniversary flagship will sport triple rear cameras, the world’s first ’ultrasonic’ in-display reader, new gradient color schemes and a dramatic redesign. But now a major new report reveals Samsung will go a lot further than this… In its exclusive, The Wall Street Journal reveals Samsung is planning to launch an even more radical flagship Galaxy S10 which will push boundaries beyond anything with have seen from the smartphone maker. Suitably, it’s codenamed the ‘Beyond X’. Galaxy S10 concept render Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S10 will have six cameras and 5G support, latest rumours hint - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s10-cameras-5g-latest-features-rumours-a8644691.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFYRUhvi19p0FJpH75h6nh8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s10-cameras-5g-latest-features-rumours-a8644691.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S10 will have six cameras and 5G support, latest rumours hint&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next flagship Samsung, presumably called the Galaxy S10, will feature twice as many cameras as Apple's latest iPhone, according to reports. Set to launch on the 10th anniversary of its first flagship smartphone, the Galaxy S10 will pack four cameras on the rear of the device and two on the front, according to The Wall Street Journal. The Galaxy S10 will also reportedly feature a 6.7-inch screen and will come with 5G support, though this may only be available in South Korea and the US. Its expected release date is February 2019. The latest rumours come just a month after Samsung unveiled...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Samsung doubles down on virtual assistant in growth push - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b23334e2-ec90-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHNyaNdnxtGCreiStF9lmUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 09:37:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b23334e2-ec90-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung doubles down on virtual assistant in growth push&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung Electronics is doubling down on Bixby, its voice assistant, with a plan to install the artificial intelligence platform on all of its electronics products by 2020 as it makes connected technologies a central part of its growth strategy. The digital voice assistant, which was launched last year, has featured only on Samsung’s premium smartphones so far, but will be extended to other mobile devices and home appliances such as televisions, refrigerators and air conditioners. According to the South Korean technology group it sells 500m units of electronics products a year, meaning Bixby...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S10 will have a hole not a notch, patent suggests - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s10-leaks-rumours-release-date-price-patent-notch-a8637101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIqAAX7uVPkWWbc79qHHkpoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 15:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s10-leaks-rumours-release-date-price-patent-notch-a8637101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S10 will have a hole not a notch, patent suggests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung may have figured out a way to make its forthcoming flagship smartphone, presumably called the Galaxy S10, a completely full-screen device that doesn't feature a notch design. A new patent submission shows a phone design that uses a small circle in the top left of the screen in order to incorporate a front-facing camera. The patent, first spotted by Dutch website LetsGoDigital, shows what the South Korean electronics giant may have in mind for its 2019 flagship phone. Slightly different design iterations both featured a small hole in the corner of the screen (LetsGoDigital) When Appl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Markets dragged lower by Apple and chipmakers - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/dcaa5d42-ec0c-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2I-AJoAQTBtK611WmD4akqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 08:33:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/dcaa5d42-ec0c-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57" target="_blank"&gt;Markets dragged lower by Apple and chipmakers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple and semiconductor makers led a broad sell-off in US equities on Monday, as doubts about industry growth and fears of a trade war weighed heavily on a sector that has been a driver of the long bull market. The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite closed down more than 3 per cent while the market benchmark S&amp;P 500 fell 1.6 per cent, in a day of almost relentless selling that carried over into Asia trading on Tuesday, where chipmakers and Apple suppliers were hit hardest. Investors pointed the finger at tensions between the US and China at a fractious Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation summit over...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Amazon's Best Black Friday 2018 TV Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnarcher/2018/11/19/amazons-best-black-friday-2018-tv-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK3CAMQPe7J9umzIhYbs_ugqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 18:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnarcher/2018/11/19/amazons-best-black-friday-2018-tv-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon's Best Black Friday 2018 TV Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. This is your final warning, AV bargain fans: We are now into the actual week of Black Friday. So if you want to make sure you bag the ultimate Thanksgiving bargain, you really need to be getting your purchasing plans together. To help you do just that, I’ve already put together guides to the headline TV deals from a whole range of key Black Friday retailers: Best Buy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Chipmakers face threat of long-term slump - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/13d1e010-e8c0-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_gLqGz8WcDyiLwy3tL2B8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 12:39:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/13d1e010-e8c0-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3" target="_blank"&gt;Chipmakers face threat of long-term slump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Apple, the world’s most valuable company, revealed this month that it would no longer disclose how many iPhones or Macs it sells, talk of “peak iPhone” swirled around the market. Although a seemingly minor reporting adjustment, the change reflects a broader concern that demand for smartphones is falling, sending shockwaves through the global semiconductor sector and other parts of the iPhone supply chain. That, combined with other problems from falling cryptocurrency values to global trade wars, has prompted questions over whether the once high-flying semiconductor industry is facing a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Leak, Samsung Folding Phone Images, Xiaomi Mi8 Pro Fights OnePlus 6T - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/16/android-news-headlines-samsung-galaxy-s10-galaxy-x-oneplus-6t-siaomi-mi8-pro-nokia71-revlew/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOz_ZZJEm5clsJ511wu8sFUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 00:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/16/android-news-headlines-samsung-galaxy-s10-galaxy-x-oneplus-6t-siaomi-mi8-pro-nokia71-revlew/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Leak, Samsung Folding Phone Images, Xiaomi Mi8 Pro Fights OnePlus 6T&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes new leaked details on the Galaxy S10, release date and rendered images of the folding Galaxy smartphone, hints of a new OnePlus 5G handset, the OnePlus 6T vs the Xiaomi Mi 8 Pro, a review of the Nokia 7.1, and what is happening to Google Maps. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). Visitors get a look at Samsung Galaxy Note9 smartphone at the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nubia X Review: Two Screens, Two Fingerprint Scanners, Too Weird? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/19/nubia-x-review-two-screens-two-fingerprint-scanners-too-weird/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMRKplmUcXBUJVI9HMccqAkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/19/nubia-x-review-two-screens-two-fingerprint-scanners-too-weird/" target="_blank"&gt;Nubia X Review: Two Screens, Two Fingerprint Scanners, Too Weird?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nubia X has a screen on the front and back of the phone. To what end will Chinese brands go to avoid needing a notch? Vivo designed a phone with a tiny pop-up camera module half a year ago. Then came Oppo with a phone whose entire forehead elevated up and down. And last month, Honor and Xiaomi each introduced slider phones just days apart. In between, there are smaller Shenzhen brands like Bluboo who experimented with a flip-over camera system. Nubia, however, may have come up with the most extreme idea yet. Its latest phone — a surprise release from a brand that was hit with a near dea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best Black Friday 2018 Samsung TV Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnarcher/2018/11/12/best-black-friday-2018-samsung-tv-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGlIWiI56K3UzFFpkFSQFsoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnarcher/2018/11/12/best-black-friday-2018-samsung-tv-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Black Friday 2018 Samsung TV Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. Samsung sells more TVs around the world than any other brand, so it seems reasonable to expect that Samsung TVs will be in particularly high demand during the upcoming Black Friday sales. Especially as the South Korean brand has delivered a much stronger range in 2018 than it did in 2017, thanks to big improvements in its latest high-end ‘QLED’ TVs, and a uniquely co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Amazon Pre-Black Friday 2018: Best Deals On TVs and Computers - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/14/amazon-pre-black-friday-2018-best-deals-on-tvs-and-computers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKiPG9pKPodz55s8vWcWRO4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/14/amazon-pre-black-friday-2018-best-deals-on-tvs-and-computers/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Pre-Black Friday 2018: Best Deals On TVs and Computers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black Friday is the busiest shopping day of the year. With each year, it just gets bigger. 2017 saw an increase of 29 percent of retail sales, resulting in a record-breaking $7.9 billion in sales. Retailers are well aware of this huge sales bump. They’ll do anything in their power to secure the hearts, minds, and wallets of the holiday shopping crowd. In an effort to capture shoppers’ loyalty early and often, some of the world’s biggest retailers are rolling out holiday sales earlier than ever before. Amazon is a great source for consumer electronics for a number of reasons. The online revi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy Images Reveal Samsung's Radical Folding Design - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/14/samsung-galaxy-f-folding-smartphone-render-images-design/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBWTqiHV5Fu-kldDGFjKkYgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/14/samsung-galaxy-f-folding-smartphone-render-images-design/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy Images Reveal Samsung's Radical Folding Design&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with a glance at a bright screen in a dark room, Samsung’s folding smartphone – the presumptively named Galaxy F – has caught the attention of the smartphone ecosystem. As well as the tantalising shots from the stage, enough details and descriptions of the technology are around to put together the look of the tablet/smartphone hybrid. Samsung Galaxy F 3rd Party Render (Lets Go Digital) With all this information, the team at Lets Go Digital has put together a digital render of what they believe the Galaxy F will look like: Samsung has already revealed that the foldable smartphone will h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Galaxy S10 Leak 'Confirms' Samsung's Nasty Surprise - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/11/samsung-galaxy-s10-leak-design-display-notch-camera-release-date-price-cost-5g/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHpfm7ACKou6ivBc1eYOstEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 01:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/11/samsung-galaxy-s10-leak-design-display-notch-camera-release-date-price-cost-5g/" target="_blank"&gt;Galaxy S10 Leak 'Confirms' Samsung's Nasty Surprise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excited about Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10? You should be. Leaks have revealed it has triple rear cameras, an ’ultrasonic’ in-display reader, gradient color schemes and a 5G option. That said, there’s a very good chance many will not like the new design… ‘Great Secret Features’ and ‘Nasty Surprises’ are my regular columns investigating the best features / biggest problems hidden behind the headlines. Samsung Galaxy S10 concept Following Samsung’s admission that it will embrace display notches in new Galaxy smartphones, the assumption was this would not be the case for the Galaxy S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Takes Its 1.5 to 2.5B Unit Opportunity To Developers At SDC 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickmoorhead/2018/11/11/samsung-takes-its-1-5-to-2-5b-unit-opportunity-to-developers-at-sdc-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIkMyVVRydQrYGWkC3jLu-wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 18:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickmoorhead/2018/11/11/samsung-takes-its-1-5-to-2-5b-unit-opportunity-to-developers-at-sdc-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Takes Its 1.5 to 2.5B Unit Opportunity To Developers At SDC 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung’s DJ Koh kicks off SDC 2018. Last week, I attended SDC 2018, Samsung’s sixth annual Developer Conference, in San Francisco, along with 5,000 other attendees. The event was a great chance to catch a glimpse of the technology that will power the coming generations of Samsung devices and services, and the company did not disappoint. SDC is a must-attend for anyone who closely follows the electronics giant and for developers who want access to future home IoT, mobile, and automotive markets. While Samsung wasn’t the first mover with IoT or mobile software developers,Samsung commands dev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Meet The Man Behind Oppo's (And OnePlus') Super Fast Charging Speeds - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/16/meet-the-man-behind-oppos-and-oneplus-super-fast-charging-speeds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAUcoiADdnVc6mms2Fi6I2MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/16/meet-the-man-behind-oppos-and-oneplus-super-fast-charging-speeds/" target="_blank"&gt;Meet The Man Behind Oppo's (And OnePlus') Super Fast Charging Speeds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oppo’s most premium phone, the Find X Lamborghini Edition, introduced the fastest charging tech seen in the industry. The biggest gripe I have with the new iPhone has nothing to do with its performance during active use, but rather when I’m not even touching the phone. The new iPhone XS can support fast charging up to 30 watt, but the charging brick Apple includes with the $1,200 phone is a putrid 5w plug that takes over three hours to fully charge. The larger Max needs another half hour on top of that. In the Android space, a fast-charging brick included in the packaging is just about stan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best Buy Pre-Black Friday 2018: Best Deals on TVs - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/14/best-buy-pre-black-friday-2018-best-deals-on-tvs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA_t3KbRMO01wch7ABXq-cwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/14/best-buy-pre-black-friday-2018-best-deals-on-tvs/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy Pre-Black Friday 2018: Best Deals on TVs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The massive Black Friday sales at Best Buy may begin at 5 p.m. on Thanksgiving Day, but that doesn’t mean you need to wait to get doorbuster deals on the best tech. Especially when it comes to big ticket items like TVs, the retailer is offering incredible deals leading up to November 22. These include discounts up to $300 on TVs from Samsung (which is quite comparable to what we expect to see onBlack Friday). As long as you’re spending $35 or more (which you will be if you purchase a TV), Best Buy offers free shipping. So not only can you skip the busy stores and lines on Black Friday, but...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung should try imagining a world where big firms respect workers - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/nov/08/samsung-should-try-imagining-a-world-where-big-firms-respect-workers</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN5LmR9-c8qTcArc2r6GhHoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 07:00:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/nov/08/samsung-should-try-imagining-a-world-where-big-firms-respect-workers" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung should try imagining a world where big firms respect workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think of your favourite gadgets and appliances, and it’s likely some of them started life in a rundown, mosquito-infested dormitory complex an hour’s drive from Malaysia’s capital, Kuala Lumpur. In each block there is a makeshift kitchen, a small, grubby toilet and three rooms crowded with bunk beds. There is no air conditioning to break the oppressively humid air. Outside, burning rubbish sends acrid fumes through the labour camp, which is strewn with broken furniture and an abandoned vehicle. To call it a slum would be generous. I’ve seen some truly appalling workers’ camps in Malaysia an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Possible delisting of BioLogics threatens Samsung’s growth strategy - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0e144fde-e7dd-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECb-6depSwa5k0mNPx9myl4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 11:11:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0e144fde-e7dd-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3" target="_blank"&gt;Possible delisting of BioLogics threatens Samsung’s growth strategy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The long-term growth strategy of Samsung was thrown into doubt on Wednesday after regulators in South Korea suspended trading of a key biopharmaceutical affiliate that the conglomerate hoped would power profits over the coming decades. Trading of Samsung BioLogics shares was halted after authorities found the group had violated accounting rules by intentionally inflating the value of an affiliate in 2015 ahead of a crucial public listing. The ruling will be a setback for Samsung — by far South Korea’s largest and richest conglomerate — which is attempting to expand into biopharmaceuticals ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Samsung foldable phone: Price and release date revealed in leak - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-foldable-phone-price-release-date-new-galaxy-f-2018-leak-a8629886.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVd7F0GkyfFFreP6hsth0kqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 13:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-foldable-phone-price-release-date-new-galaxy-f-2018-leak-a8629886.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung foldable phone: Price and release date revealed in leak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The name, price and release date of Samsung's mysterious foldable smartphone have finally been revealed, according to a South Korean news agency. Samsung teased the device at its annual developer conference last week, saying it will serve as the "foundation of the smartphone of tomorrow" – though few details about the phone were actually revealed. The so-called Galaxy F will be released in March 2019 and is expected to cost 2 million won (£1,370), the Seoul-based Yonhap News Agency reported. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/40 Designed by ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Samsung sees strong growth at auto electronics unit - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-portugal-websummit-samsung-idUSKCN1NB2BI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJqTgKQbZQaYl83Mb3eagi8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 17:16:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-portugal-websummit-samsung-idUSKCN1NB2BI" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung sees strong growth at auto electronics unit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung Electronics expects strong growth at its audio and auto electronics unit Harman, which has put the company "firmly in the picture of the automotive industry" as it eyes the autonomous car market, its chief strategy officer said. Samsung, the world's largest semiconductor manufacturer, bought Harman last year for $8 billion. "Now it's almost 20 months, still not two years (since the purchase), but I would say the honeymoon is over. Now we are in a business," Young Sohn, Samsung's Silicon Valley-based president and chief strategy officer, told Reuters on Tuesday during the Web Summit ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Apple Watch Series 4, iPad, Sony And Huawei Win Big At Pocket-lint Gadget Awards - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/14/apple-watch-series-4-ipad-sony-and-huawei-win-big-at-pocket-lint-gadget-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAxrvX-Z4F_lcl4kZ7H4GcoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/14/apple-watch-series-4-ipad-sony-and-huawei-win-big-at-pocket-lint-gadget-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Watch Series 4, iPad, Sony And Huawei Win Big At Pocket-lint Gadget Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last night, the internationally respected Pocket-lint Awards took place in central London. Pocket-lint is a global website based in the UK. But the reason the site’s awards are so well thought-of is that the calibre of the judges is remarkable. The Pocket-lint Awards taking place in London last night. Where other awards rely on the staff of the company who present them, here, the judges – and there are 45 of them – are drawn from multiple publications, cities and countries. There are many Forbes contributors among the judges, too, including Senior Contributor Gordon Kelly, TV expert John Ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung shows off new smartphone with foldable screen - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/samsung-shows-off-new-smartphone-with-foldable-screen-2018-11-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIcq9vKaAs_kGU7cQZeYbvEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/samsung-shows-off-new-smartphone-with-foldable-screen-2018-11-07" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung shows off new smartphone with foldable screen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WALL STREET JOURNAL By Timothy W. Martin Device with 7.3-inch screen should be ready for mass production in the coming months Samsung executive Justin Denison holds the new foldable Infinity Flex smartphone Wednesday in San Francisco. Bloomberg News SAN FRANCISCO — Samsung Electronics Co., suffering a handset sales slide, revealed a foldable-screen smartphone that folds like a book and opens up to tablet size. At a developer showcase event on Wednesday, Samsung (KR:005930) said the phone, which is 7.3 inches when opened, would be ready for mass production in the coming months. It boas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Best Buy 'Black Friday' 2018: Early Apple, Samsung, HDTV Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/13/best-buy-black-friday-2018-early-apple-iphone-samsung-hdtv-tv-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP_DzU10VcpEMPcqJFSTOVgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/13/best-buy-black-friday-2018-early-apple-iphone-samsung-hdtv-tv-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy 'Black Friday' 2018: Early Apple, Samsung, HDTV Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. Almost a week has passed since the release of Best Buy’s official 52-page Black Friday 2018 ad, and now (just like Walmart) the sales are starting. Best Buy has begun a Black Friday warm up sale and you will find a range of strong deals on HDTVs, smartphones, laptops, headphones and more. Working with my holiday sales partner BestBlackFrida...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi: Chinese phone maker arrives in the UK, looking to take on Apple and Samsung - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/xiaomi-china-uk-apple-samsung-buy-best-phone-deals-latest-a8626901.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHMX2OsWYmn_mVWD-hNtwu0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/xiaomi-china-uk-apple-samsung-buy-best-phone-deals-latest-a8626901.html" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi: Chinese phone maker arrives in the UK, looking to take on Apple and Samsung&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese phone company Xiaomi has finally launched its phones in the UK, ready to take on companies like Apple and Samsung. As well as its Mi 8 Pro flagship phone – which is now on sale, the first time the phone is available outside of China – the company is selling a wristband and a scooter as it attempts to spread across the world. The company is already the fourth biggest phone company in the world, after Samsung, Huawei and Apple. But it has mostly sold its products in China, and is now seeking to spread into more countries. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 43 show all Gadgets and tec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>eBay Pre-Black Friday 2018: 5 Best Deals On Smartphones - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/12/ebay-pre-black-friday-2018-5-best-deals-on-smartphones/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH-684CMwyqo2eaMa58MTMAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/12/ebay-pre-black-friday-2018-5-best-deals-on-smartphones/" target="_blank"&gt;eBay Pre-Black Friday 2018: 5 Best Deals On Smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re in the market for some outstanding deals on smartphones, turning to eBay might be the best move you can make. Thanks to a community of sellers all vying for your attention, eBay has become a popular destination for people seeking deals on devices. A quick search on the company’s website reveals a slew of offers on just about any product you want. And although you do need to be careful finding the right seller, eBay offers a handy set of tools to ensure you’re buying from a reputable source. In an effort to find you the best deals on smartphones, we’ve cut through listings across t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung's Foldable Galaxy X Has Two Big Hurdles - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/08/samsungs-foldable-galaxy-x-has-two-big-hurdles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO42xraSnM5IXbtJLEToJj8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/08/samsungs-foldable-galaxy-x-has-two-big-hurdles/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung's Foldable Galaxy X Has Two Big Hurdles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung’s Foldable phone. Samsung finally, officially, confirmed what has been speculated for some time - it’s releasing a foldable phone imminently. If you’ve been following the development of the Korean company’s first foldable smartphone – dubbed the Galaxy X – then you’ll be aware of the yearly launch delays. The competition from LG, Lenovo, Apple and smaller Chinese companies that have actually launched devices likely forced Samsung’s hand into yesterday’s preview. There are, however, at least two areas that make me sceptical about how popular this device will be. Firstly, software. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung unveils much-hyped foldable phone - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/08/samsung-unveils-much-hyped-foldable-phon?videoId=481040953</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDhipb1QemI6OlyAMcDJ3XYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 16:25:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/08/samsung-unveils-much-hyped-foldable-phon?videoId=481040953" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung unveils much-hyped foldable phone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung unveiled its heavily anticipated foldable phone to developers in San Francisco on Wednesday, urging Android programmers to start writing apps for the product it expects to deliver in the new year. Jane Lanhee Lee reports.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Smartphone maker Xiaomi launches in Britain with flagship device - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-xiaomi-britain-idUSKBN1ND296</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHfG1yZ03laFdRS-8dp03xYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 16:30:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-xiaomi-britain-idUSKBN1ND296" target="_blank"&gt;Smartphone maker Xiaomi launches in Britain with flagship device&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi, the world's fourth ranked smartphone maker, entered Britain on Thursday with the international debut of its flagship Mi 8 Pro, which it hopes will win fans in a market dominated by Samsung and Apple. Senior vice president Xiang Wang said Britain had a "cool" factor that aligned with the company's appeal to its customers. "The UK is one of the important global centers for technology," he said in an interview ahead of the company's London launch. "It is a young energetic place, so pretty much fits to our culture - we want to be the coolest company in our fans' minds." Xiaomi, which li...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Samsung 'Galaxy X' foldable phone tablet is finally ready to be unveiled - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-x-foldable-phone-release-date-new-smartphone-technology-a8619796.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFbvR-f1o8BvOIPfrNZrWeMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 11:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-x-foldable-phone-release-date-new-smartphone-technology-a8619796.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung 'Galaxy X' foldable phone tablet is finally ready to be unveiled&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung will reveal details of its much-anticipated foldable smartphone at its developer conference this week, an official at the South Korean electronics giant has revealed. The disruptive device, potentially named the Galaxy X or Galaxy F, was first teased in 2014 but details of the project have remained secret in the years since. In a break with its usual policy of keeping new products under wraps until they're ready to launch, Samsung plans to share some of the phone's features at the Samsung Developer Conference 2018, taking place in San Francisco from 7-8 November. Samsung shared an i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Samsung unveils foldable phone as it tries to regain edge on Apple - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/08/samsung-unveils-foldable-phone-as-it-tries-to-regain-edge-on-apple</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDRdSQdEbnXt89-gQCRxYlUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 04:23:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/08/samsung-unveils-foldable-phone-as-it-tries-to-regain-edge-on-apple" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung unveils foldable phone as it tries to regain edge on Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has unveiled its much-anticipated foldable phone and urged Android developers to start writing apps for the new device. The South Korean tech company needs to perfect the foldable phone to reverse steep declines in profit for its mobile division and restore some of the cachet its brand has lost to Apple. Foldable phones promise the screen of a small tablet in a pocket-sized device. Related: Apple and Samsung fined for deliberately slowing down phones At the unveiling in San francisco, Justin Denison, a senior vice president of mobile product marketing, showed a prototype with a scre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>With new One UI, Samsung shows some empathy for smartphone users - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90264362/with-new-one-ui-samsung-shows-some-empathy-for-smartphone-users</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFuV0ZYXcKfosTD_FGGWEx4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 18:13:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90264362/with-new-one-ui-samsung-shows-some-empathy-for-smartphone-users" target="_blank"&gt;With new One UI, Samsung shows some empathy for smartphone users&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research says we’re spending more than 3.5 hours a day looking at our smartphones. So the presentation of stuff on that little square of glass matters. Samsung has been a little slow getting hip to that. Its user interfaces over the years have betrayed a focus on what Samsung wants to present there, rather than what the user wants and/or needs to see. That’s been changing, however, and Samsung made perhaps its biggest leap yet into human-centric design today with the announcement of a new UX called One UI. Where Samsung once famously cluttered the UX with clunky icons, too much data, an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Smartphone makers bet on foldable screens as next big thing - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/e3cb8474411c43aa83efa562febc89b3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPUczssJNFGXnoulROz8EYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 22:46:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/e3cb8474411c43aa83efa562febc89b3" target="_blank"&gt;Smartphone makers bet on foldable screens as next big thing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — For the past few years, the smartphone industry has been searching for a breakthrough to revive a market mired in an innovation lull and a sales slump. A potential catalyst is on the horizon in the form of flexible screens that can be folded in half without breaking. Samsung and several rivals are preparing to roll out such screens to make devices more versatile for work and pleasure. The foldable screens could increase display space to the size of a mini-tablet, but fold like a wallet so they revert to the size of regular phones. But there are questions about price and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Samsung foldable phone 'Galaxy X' leak reveals screen details ahead of launch event - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-foldable-phone-galaxy-x-leak-screen-launch-event-release-date-a8615056.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMIvsaPmukmy7w1rMwhfpb4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-foldable-phone-galaxy-x-leak-screen-launch-event-release-date-a8615056.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung foldable phone 'Galaxy X' leak reveals screen details ahead of launch event&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has been teasing the release of a foldable phone since 2014 but the groundbreaking device may now be just a week away, as rumours abound that it will be unveiled at a conference hosted by the South Korean electronics giant. Potentially named the Galaxy X or Galaxy F, it is believed the bendy gadget will be demonstrated at the electronics giant's developer conference beginning on 7 November, with a potential release date set for some time in 2019. Samsung has been working with YouTube and Netflix to figure out ways to deliver content on the folding screen, The Wall Street Journal rep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Galaxy S10 Leak Reveals Samsung's Nasty Surprise - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-design-in-display-fingerprint-scanner-release-date-cost-upgrade-s9-note9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMy08aWRU4Wv3ON9a9YYfBUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 23:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-design-in-display-fingerprint-scanner-release-date-cost-upgrade-s9-note9/" target="_blank"&gt;Galaxy S10 Leak Reveals Samsung's Nasty Surprise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are many reasons why everyone is excited about Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10. Most notably the leaked triple rear cameras, ’ultrasonic’ in-display reader, new gradient color schemes and 5G option. Even Samsung is bragging about the Galaxy S10. But now there is news which will come as a nasty surprise to many… ‘Great Secret Features’ and ‘Nasty Surprises’ are my regular columns investigating the best features / biggest problems hidden behind the headlines. Samsung Galaxy S10 concept Leaked by Ice Universe, arguably the industry’s top Samsung insider right now, we learn the Gal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>