<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>SpaceX - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRE5tYTNsM0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:55:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Technical glitch sees Elon Musk's SpaceX Falcon rocket crash land in sea - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/technical-glitch-sees-elon-musks-spacex-falcon-rocket-crash/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ0qMY2klE1W9CArLCXz_1kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:05:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/technical-glitch-sees-elon-musks-spacex-falcon-rocket-crash/" target="_blank"&gt;Technical glitch sees Elon Musk's SpaceX Falcon rocket crash land in sea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Christmas turkey rocketed toward the International Space Station on Wednesday, along with cranberry sauce, candied yams and the obligatory fruitcake. The SpaceX booster missed its landing zone on the ground after liftoff, however, and ended up in the sea just a couple of miles offshore. Groans filled SpaceX Mission Control in Hawthorne, California, as live video showed the first-stage rocket booster spinning out of control, still high above Cape Canaveral. It was the company's first missed ground landing, although it has overshot floating barges plenty of times in the past, a tougher feat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>SpaceX rocket spectacularly smashes down to Earth in video - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/spacex-rocket-earth-crash-falcon-9-rocket-dragon-iss-international-space-station-a8671351.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBFCsHxnt_uRhR2JEmNjMA0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/spacex-rocket-earth-crash-falcon-9-rocket-dragon-iss-international-space-station-a8671351.html" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX rocket spectacularly smashes down to Earth in video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spectacular video shows a SpaceX rocket plunging to Earth and smashing into the sea. The mission was a success for the most part: the capsule carried by the rocket made it all the way to the International Space Station and dropped off important cargo to the floating lab. But the first stage that flew it there dropped back down with the intention of landing safely on Earth, something it has done successfully more than 30 times. This time around the booster ran into problems as it fell back down to Earth. The feed was cut as SpaceX seemed to realise the attempted landing was going to fail. Bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>SpaceX Launches Its 20th Rocket Of The Year, But Doesn't Quite Make The Landing - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanocallaghan/2018/12/05/spacex-launches-its-20th-rocket-of-the-year-but-doesnt-quite-make-the-landing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHMTxAlwHXbh56Yvw4rd48kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanocallaghan/2018/12/05/spacex-launches-its-20th-rocket-of-the-year-but-doesnt-quite-make-the-landing/" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX Launches Its 20th Rocket Of The Year, But Doesn't Quite Make The Landing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The launch was fine, but the landing didn’t quite go to plan SpaceX has successfully launched its 20th rocket of the year, a mission taking supplies to the International Space Station (ISS), but the landing wasn’t quite as successful. Their Falcon 9 rocket lifted off from Cape Canaveral’s Space Launch Complex 40 in Florida at 1.16pm Eastern time (6.16pm UTC) today, carrying the CRS-16 Dragon spacecraft into orbit. This is a mission under contract with NASA, as part of their Commercial Resupply Services (CRS) program. SpaceX also attempted to land the first stage booster of the rocket – the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Christmas turkey, fruitcake rocketing toward space station - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/bf2c68dfde1b48a69a93a354a3754ed7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDC2rX3qwm5S0QEXNctvekUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:10:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/bf2c68dfde1b48a69a93a354a3754ed7" target="_blank"&gt;Christmas turkey, fruitcake rocketing toward space station&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — Christmas turkey rocketed toward the International Space Station on Wednesday, along with cranberry sauce, candied yams and the obligatory fruitcake. The SpaceX booster missed its landing zone on the ground after liftoff, however, and ended up in the sea just a couple of miles offshore. Groans filled SpaceX Mission Control in Hawthorne, California, as live video showed the first-stage rocket booster spinning out of control, still high above Cape Canaveral. It was the company's first missed ground landing, although it has overshot floating barges plenty of times i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>SpaceX's Falcon rocket ditches in water after sending cargo to ISS (VIDEO) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445688-spacex-rocket-landing-failed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFzJftx9whYjzxqU-LyoJoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445688-spacex-rocket-landing-failed/" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX's Falcon rocket ditches in water after sending cargo to ISS (VIDEO)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SpaceX’s Falcon 9 rocket failed to stick the landing after successfully launching a supply pod to the International Space Station. CEO Elon Musk says the livestream should not have cut away from the failure. The CRS-16 mission launched supplies to the ISS on Wednesday, but the booster headed for the landing pad missed and landed in the water instead, ending SpaceX’s perfect record of 12 previous successful landings. Tracking shot of Falcon water landing pic.twitter.com/6Hv2aZhLjM — Elon Musk (@elonmusk) December 5, 2018 Musk also tweeted a video from on board the booster, showing the rocket...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Musk's Falcon X rocket crashes in sea - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ewxM7_RqBaQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENH8UoLnGwizp50ChzRrCE0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTD8vxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:29:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ewxM7_RqBaQ" target="_blank"&gt;Musk's Falcon X rocket crashes in sea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk posts videos on Twitter of one of his SpaceX Falcon rockets crash landing in the sea Get the latest headlines: http://www.telegraph.co.uk/ Subscribe: http://www.youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=telegraphtv Like us on Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/telegraph.co.uk Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/telegraph Telegraph.co.uk and YouTube.com/TelegraphTV are websites of The Telegraph, the UK's best-selling quality daily newspaper providing news and analysis on UK and world events, business, sport, lifestyle and culture.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Watch: SpaceX launches 64 satellites - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/03/spacex-launches-satellites-orig.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOhZXCISNvQx0IkxKBySGp0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:22:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/03/spacex-launches-satellites-orig.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;Watch: SpaceX launches 64 satellites&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SpaceX delivered 64 satellites into orbit in one fell swoop for a record-setting mission. This marks the 19th launch for SpaceX in 2018. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Here’s how to watch SpaceX’s Dragon take off for the space station - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90276893/spacex-dragon-launch-today-how-to-watch-the-falcon-9-rocket-blast-off-for-the-iss</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBOXDrakYzkZcqCG5-KOUkEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:01:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90276893/spacex-dragon-launch-today-how-to-watch-the-falcon-9-rocket-blast-off-for-the-iss" target="_blank"&gt;Here’s how to watch SpaceX’s Dragon take off for the space station&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SpaceX is having a very big week. On Monday, it launched a Falcon 9 rocket from California’s Vandenberg Air Force Base, which was headed to space—and the record books. As USA Today notes, the rocket’s booster was the first Falcon 9 to launch three missions, an important part of the company’s plan to reduce costs by reusing rockets. The booster was also the first to launch from all three of SpaceX’s pads (Kennedy Space Center, Cape Canaveral Air Force Station, and Vandenberg). If that wasn’t impressive enough, the launch was also SpaceX’s 19th launch of the year—the previous record was 18—an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>SpaceX launches biggest U.S. 'rideshare' mission with 64 satellites - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-spacex/spacex-launches-biggest-u-s-rideshare-mission-with-64-satellites-idUSKBN1O22JQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILNkrBjTI332rIJsH96M1gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:35:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-spacex/spacex-launches-biggest-u-s-rideshare-mission-with-64-satellites-idUSKBN1O22JQ" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX launches biggest U.S. 'rideshare' mission with 64 satellites&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk's SpaceX launched a Falcon 9 rocket from California on Monday carrying 64 small satellites into low orbit around the Earth, which the company called the largest-ever "rideshare" mission by a U.S.-based rocket. The mission, dubbed SSO-A, also marked the third voyage to space for the same Falcon 9 rocket - another milestone for SpaceX's cost-cutting reusable rocket technology. The Falcon 9 blasted off from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California at 10:34 a.m. local time (18:34 GMT) carrying satellites from 34 different companies, government agencies and universities. SpaceX said the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>SpaceX Rocket Sends Cremated Remains of 100 People Into Orbit - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/spacex-rocket-sends-cremated-remains-of-100-people-into-orbit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPA2irDFvxjeCCGFGjb2iU0qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:46:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/spacex-rocket-sends-cremated-remains-of-100-people-into-orbit" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX Rocket Sends Cremated Remains of 100 People Into Orbit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joe Skipper/Reuters, A SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket reportedly blasted off towards the cosmos Monday carrying a memorial satellite with the cremated remains of about 100 people. The San Francisco-based company Elysium Space said it sent the SpaceX rocket out into orbit with the ashes of military veterans, aerospace fans and others aboard, CNN reports. Relatives paid $2,500 to send a sample of ashes into the Milky Way via a 4-inch square satellite called a cubesat. According to Thomas Civeit, Elysium Space Founder and CEO, families will be able to track the Falcon for about four years as the space...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Reused rocket takes off carrying 64 satellites - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/b5adaacf957f49efba481aef2ef55914</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOXkO6cFTZRQc3R0fcVJCukqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgw3utQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:52:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/b5adaacf957f49efba481aef2ef55914" target="_blank"&gt;Reused rocket takes off carrying 64 satellites&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VANDENBERG AIR FORCE BASE, Calif. (AP) — A SpaceX rocket carrying 64 small satellites lifted off from California on Monday, marking the first time the same Falcon 9 rocket has been used in three space missions. The rocket blasted off from Vandenberg Air Force Base, arcing over the Pacific Ocean west of Los Angeles as it headed toward space. Minutes later, the rocket's first stage performed a so-called boost back maneuver and landed on an unmanned ship in the Pacific. The landing marked the first time SpaceX had flown a first stage three times. The first stage was previously launched and rec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>SpaceX Just Broke All Sorts Of Records With Its Latest Rocket Launch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanocallaghan/2018/12/03/spacex-just-launched-and-landed-the-same-rocket-for-a-third-time-on-a-record-breaking-mission/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDUgZXYNgLteUhev7qOoVgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 18:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanocallaghan/2018/12/03/spacex-just-launched-and-landed-the-same-rocket-for-a-third-time-on-a-record-breaking-mission/" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX Just Broke All Sorts Of Records With Its Latest Rocket Launch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company has now launched 19 rockets this year, its most ever SpaceX has successfully launched an ambitious mission to deploy 64 satellites into Earth orbit – while also setting new records for launches and landings alike. The Falcon 9 rocket lifted off from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California at 10.32am Pacific time (6.32pm UTC) today, December 3, taking its multiple payloads into low-Earth orbit. About eight minutes after launching, the first stage of the rocket successfully landed on the drone ship Just Read The Instructions, something that’s well beyond being routine by now. But ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>SpaceX launched 64 satellites in record-breaking mission - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/spacex-record-sso-a-mission/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEp3hVzUGKXL06egEV-s_EcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:50:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/spacex-record-sso-a-mission/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX launched 64 satellites in record-breaking mission&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SpaceX delivered 64 satellites into orbit in one fell swoop for a record-setting mission. Elon Musk's company launched a rocket from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California on Monday after a series of delays triggered by bad weather and last-minute inspections for the rocket. It marked one of the largest satellite ride-sharing missions ever launched and the most crowded single mission in US history, according to Spaceflight, SpaceX's customer for the launch. The mission illustrated the growing demand to launch small satellites, modern devices that some companies hope will empower an array o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Five planned missions to Mars - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/02/five-planned-missions-to-mars-nasa-esa-china-russia-uae-spacex-elon-musk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOk6R6nvr6JRNDrLT5GGX00qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 07:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/02/five-planned-missions-to-mars-nasa-esa-china-russia-uae-spacex-elon-musk" target="_blank"&gt;Five planned missions to Mars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nasa’s InSight Lander Last week, Nasa successfully landed its InSight probe on Mars, as part of a two-year mission to study the planet’s deep interior. Nasa is also planning a rover mission for 2020, to investigate signs of life and collect data for future expeditions. An artist’s impression of the ExoMars 2020 rover. Photograph: M Thiebaut/ESA ExoMars 2020 The European Space Agency and its Russian counterpart, Roscosmos, have joined forces on this mission, planned for summer 2020. Using a European rover and a Russian surface platform, the project aims to study the planet’s atmospheric gase...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The Latest: SpaceX lands rocket's first stage on ship - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/888cc6224c424f75a49eaa8732682c62</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK3EDVh9aLMXoESXwaR4QggqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgw3utQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:15:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/888cc6224c424f75a49eaa8732682c62" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: SpaceX lands rocket's first stage on ship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VANDENBERG AIR FORCE BASE, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on a SpaceX rocket launch from California (all times local): 11:10 a.m. For the third time, SpaceX has successfully launched and landed the same first stage of a Falcon 9 rocket. The spacecraft carrying dozens of small satellites lifted off Monday from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California. Minutes later, the first stage landed on an unmanned ship in the Pacific. The same first stage was previously launched and recovered on missions in May and August. Reusability is a major goal of SpaceX founder Elon Musk's rocket program. ___ 10:45 a.m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk drops plans for west LA tunnel, instead focuses on Dodger fans - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/elon-musk-drops-out-of-la-tunnel-to-build-another/10570208</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJh_PnCBm-NmGkyJmtRKSQUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:40:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/elon-musk-drops-out-of-la-tunnel-to-build-another/10570208" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk drops plans for west LA tunnel, instead focuses on Dodger fans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk has scrapped plans for a high-speed passenger tunnel under the West side of Los Angeles but is moving ahead with a similar proposal across town designed to whisk baseball fans to and from Dodger Stadium in Chicago. Mr Musk's underground transit venture, the Boring Company, gave up on its development of a 4.4-kilometre tunnel in West LA to settle litigation brought by community groups opposed to the project, the two sides said in a joint statement. The move came six months after Mr Musk, the high-tech baron better known as founder of electric car company Te...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>SpaceX launch: Rocket containing ashes of 100 people sent into space - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/spacex-launch-ashes-remains-rocket-falcon-9-shooting-star-memorial-elon-musk-a8665106.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAdyAgZ_bAunwwyFvsxVw0wqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/spacex-launch-ashes-remains-rocket-falcon-9-shooting-star-memorial-elon-musk-a8665106.html" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX launch: Rocket containing ashes of 100 people sent into space&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a unique application of commercial space flight, people are launching the cremated remains of their loved ones into a satellite that will orbit the earth. Companies including Elysium Space and Celestis offer their customers the poetic opportunity to send the ashes of dead people (and at least one dog) to travel among the stars. In 2012, the Falcon 9, a rocket from Elon Musk’s company SpaceX, carried a secondary payload of 308 sets of ashes while delivering supplies to a space station. Families had each sent a gram of ashes to the company Celestis and reserved a space in a capsule in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The ultimate high-fliers: The ultra-wealthy planning to be the first tourists in space - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9353a676-e80b-11e8-8827-ff56e7163c11</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEApVWOMMMqggWcDjs5q1w38qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwott6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 05:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9353a676-e80b-11e8-8827-ff56e7163c11" target="_blank"&gt;The ultimate high-fliers: The ultra-wealthy planning to be the first tourists in space&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Per Wimmer, a Danish financier in his fifties, will shortly be buckling his seatbelt for takeoff. Unlike the other expensive flights he has taken in his career, the champagne is likely to be served straight out of the bottle. The cost of the flight is also on the steep side, at $250,000 per ticket. But this flight comes with a difference: once the seatbelt sign has been switched off, Wimmer will be able to float over to the window. For this is a trip into space. The entire trip will take only two hours but will, literally, be out of this world. The experience will revolve around the view of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>This SpaceX Launch Will Send Over 60 Satellites Into Orbit - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2018/12/03/this-spacex-launch-will-send-over-60-satellites-into-orbit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBNQzSZR3qCu_tqCFu0XUOQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 17:44:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2018/12/03/this-spacex-launch-will-send-over-60-satellites-into-orbit/" target="_blank"&gt;This SpaceX Launch Will Send Over 60 Satellites Into Orbit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=1] At approximately 1:32pm ET Monday, a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket will be heading to orbit. That in itself isn’t unusual – this will be SpaceX’s 18th flight of a Falcon 9 this year, with another to follow tomorrow. What is unusual is what it’s sending to orbit – a stack of 64 different small satellites from 34 different organizations. This satellite launch was arranged by Seattle-based Spaceflight, which helps companies and organizations get satellites to orbit. “We’re not unlike any other kind of freight forwarder,” said Curt Blake, President of Spaceflight. “We just freight forward to or...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nasa chief criticses Elon Musk's weed-smoking podcast appearance - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/30/nasa-chief-criticses-elon-musks-weed-smoking-podcast-appearance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKc6mUdZtEHReJE6_Z43IpcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:29:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/30/nasa-chief-criticses-elon-musks-weed-smoking-podcast-appearance/" target="_blank"&gt;Nasa chief criticses Elon Musk's weed-smoking podcast appearance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk has been warned by Nasa’s most senior figure not to repeat his weed-smoking, whisky-drinking antics on a recent podcast if he wants to continue working with the space agency. Jim Bridenstein, the Nasa administrator, suggested that Mr Musk, an entrepreneur who is financing commercial space exploration, had acted inappropriately given his role with the company. Mr Musk’s SpaceX is one of two firms contracted to build a shuttle that will fly US astronauts to the International Space Station from American territory – something that was ended in 2011. Recent behavior by Mr Musk, who co-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>NASA chief says Elon Musk’s pot smoking ‘did not inspire confidence’ - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nasa-chief-says-elon-musks-pot-smoking-did-not-inspire-confidence-2018-11-29</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE-xuoS5QpzxnYLAqOwS1LYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nasa-chief-says-elon-musks-pot-smoking-did-not-inspire-confidence-2018-11-29" target="_blank"&gt;NASA chief says Elon Musk’s pot smoking ‘did not inspire confidence’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KEY WORDS By Mike Murphy SpaceX founder reportedly says he’ll behave better Elon Musk lit up on Joe Rogan’s podcast earlier this year. YouTube NASA’s administrator said Thursday that it was inappropriate for SpaceX founder Elon Musk to smoke marijuana on a podcast earlier this year, and that the incident “did not inspire confidence.” The pot-smoking incident in September reportedly irked NASA officials, and earlier this month the space agency ordered a safety review of SpaceX and Boeing Co. (BA) to evaluate the companies’ workplace cultures, “including the adherence to a drug-free environ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Richard Branson says Virgin Galactic will take people to space before Christmas - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/tech/richard-branson-virgin-galactic-first-flight-to-space/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM9xZRulhJEEyc2XeK6RxqkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:33:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/tech/richard-branson-virgin-galactic-first-flight-to-space/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Richard Branson says Virgin Galactic will take people to space before Christmas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inside Access, only on CNN Business, goes behind the scenes of the world's most innovative companies. The multimedia series went inside Richard Branson's Virgin empire and premiered live from Mojave, California, on November 30, 2018. Richard Branson says Virgin Galactic is on the verge of a major achievement: It will send astronauts into space by Christmas. The billionaire entrepreneur told CNN Business' Rachel Crane this week he is "pretty confident" his space tourism venture can achieve its milestone by the end of the year. "We have a brilliant group of astronauts who literally believe 10...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk: Workers should put in 100 hours a week to change the world - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/27/elon-musk-workers-should-put-80-hours-week-change-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENE5OFl2JBa2l69s1MgyZg8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:54:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/27/elon-musk-workers-should-put-80-hours-week-change-world/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk: Workers should put in 100 hours a week to change the world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla and SpaceX workers should put in 80 to 100 hours a week to "change the world", Elon Musk has said. The technology entrepreneur admitted that there were "way easier places to work" than his companies, adding: "Nobody ever changed the world on 40 hours a week." Asked how many hours a week were necessary, Mr Musk said: "Varies per person, but about 80 sustained, peaking above 100 at times. Pain level increases exponentially above 80." Mr Musk's comments attracted criticism from commentators who suggested that overwork could lead to decreased productivity. He is the founder and chief exec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk says he is probably going to go and live on Mars - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-mars-spacex-tesla-live-red-planet-earth-rocket-a8652101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEETeCs-sw3hIjOesOPLvv-oqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 11:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-mars-spacex-tesla-live-red-planet-earth-rocket-a8652101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk says he is probably going to go and live on Mars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk is probably going to live on Mars. That is, if he doesn't die first: something that is highly likely, given how risky the journey will be. And if he doesn't die on his way to the red planet, he could easily die once he get there. If he and his fellow travellers do manage to get to Mars and survive, life will be a difficult prospect, he has said. It is going to be lots of work and very little leisure time, he said, with the high chance that you might die from Mars's harsh environment before you get to enjoy it. Nasa's most stunning pictures of space - + show all Nasa's most stunnin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pint-Sized Space Race: Miniature Rockets Are Starting To Crowd Launch Pads - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2018/11/21/pint-sized-space-race-miniature-rockets-are-starting-to-crowd-launch-pads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGcOzZnZHKwE1DKCP4-NM78qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 15:38:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2018/11/21/pint-sized-space-race-miniature-rockets-are-starting-to-crowd-launch-pads/" target="_blank"&gt;Pint-Sized Space Race: Miniature Rockets Are Starting To Crowd Launch Pads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=0] Payam Banazadeh’s voice got excited as he described the satellites that his company, Capella Space, is building. Each satellite in his company’s planned constellation will come equipped with a large, powered, eight square-meter antenna. An antenna that folds neatly into the body of its satellite before launch. A satellite that’s less than two feet long and weighs less than 36 kg. Government satellites built a decade ago to do the same job are the size of a school bus. That trend of miniaturizing satellites is driving a new space race: one to build small rockets to launch the new bree...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk is talking about moving to Mars. But how close are we to that, really? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/elon-musk-says-he-could-make-it-to-mars-in-five-years/10553914</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJC9V-mVUInvJ1NTYNMXucqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 18:45:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/elon-musk-says-he-could-make-it-to-mars-in-five-years/10553914" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk is talking about moving to Mars. But how close are we to that, really?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk is so confident he'll get to Mars within his lifetime, he's already talking about moving there. "I know exactly what to do … we've recently made a number of breakthroughs that I am just really fired up about," he told Axios on HBO in an interview yesterday. But at the age of 47, time is ticking. He told Axios there was a 70 per cent chance he would personally ride to Mars on one of his SpaceX rockets. But with some scientists predicting it could take another 30 years for humans to get to the Red Planet, how feasible is his timeline? Let's — like NASA's InSight lander — delve a lit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>NASA to review workplace safety culture at SpaceX, Boeing - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-nasa/nasa-to-review-workplace-safety-culture-at-spacex-boeing-idUSKCN1NP2LI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHMWaHX_9VS_IwPNeyUeVQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMPT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:45:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-nasa/nasa-to-review-workplace-safety-culture-at-spacex-boeing-idUSKCN1NP2LI" target="_blank"&gt;NASA to review workplace safety culture at SpaceX, Boeing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. space agency NASA said on Tuesday it would review the workplace safety culture at SpaceX and Boeing Co, as the two companies gear up to fly astronauts to the International Space Station. The National Aeronautics and Space Administration said it would conduct a "cultural assessment study" of the companies, "including the adherence to a drug-free environment," prior to crew test flights scheduled to take place in the coming months. "We fully expect our commercial partners to meet all workplace safety requirements in the execution of our missions," said NASA in a statement. NASA did not g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>FCC approves request for SpaceX to send over 7,000 satellites into space - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fcc-approves-request-for-spacex-to-send-over-7000-satellites-into-space-2018-11-15</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG53W4doYRwrugmsuUvthnkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fcc-approves-request-for-spacex-to-send-over-7000-satellites-into-space-2018-11-15" target="_blank"&gt;FCC approves request for SpaceX to send over 7,000 satellites into space&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Elisabeth Buchwald A mock up of the Crew Dragon spacecraft is displayed during a media tour of SpaceX headquarters and rocket factory on August 13, 2018 in Hawthorne, California. Getty Images In an effort to expand global connectivity, on Thursday the Federal Communications Commission approved the requests of Elon Musk’s SpaceX to deploy over 7,000 orbiting satellites into space. With more orbiting satellites in space, it is expected that more Americans, especially those living in rural areas as well as people in developing countries, will be able to access high-speed inte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>SpaceX, TeleSat Canada bids get U.S. nod to expand satellite internet - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-fcc-satellite/spacex-telesat-canada-bids-get-u-s-nod-to-expand-satellite-internet-idUSKCN1NK2ET</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPLG-6e6YViap8yFy6_78WQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 21:40:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-fcc-satellite/spacex-telesat-canada-bids-get-u-s-nod-to-expand-satellite-internet-idUSKCN1NK2ET" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX, TeleSat Canada bids get U.S. nod to expand satellite internet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By David Shepardson WASHINGTON (Reuters - The U.S. Federal Communications Commission voted unanimously on Thursday to allow Tesla Inc (TSLA.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Chief Executive Elon Musk's Space X, Telesat Canada [PSPENC.UL] and two other companies to roll out new satellite-based broadband services. The FCC voted to grant "market access" requests to Telesat, Kepler Communications Inc and LeoSat MA, Inc to offer high-speed internet service and connectivity for sensors and other intelligence devices. The FCC, which had approved SpaceX's initial plans in March, further appr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Musk renames Mars rocket 'Starship' and says 'later versions' will travel to new star systems - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/20/musk-renames-mars-rocket-starship-says-later-versions-will-travel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHmYSh6HJDlgDF5fLvNt2oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 11:12:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/20/musk-renames-mars-rocket-starship-says-later-versions-will-travel/" target="_blank"&gt;Musk renames Mars rocket 'Starship' and says 'later versions' will travel to new star systems&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk has renamed his Mars rocket for the third time, calling it Starship, and revealed that it will travel to other star systems. The SpaceX founder said on Monday night that his space tourism company plans to rebrand its largest ship, that has not been built yet, as later versions plan to reach locations outside the orbit of the Sun. Mr Musk had previously named his Mars spaceship the Mars Colonial Transporter (MCT), then the Interplanetary Transport System (ITS), then the Big Falcon Rocket (BFR), and is now calling it simply Starship. The rocket is expected t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Nasa and SpaceX to test rocket that will carry people to space - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/nasa-spacex-launch-dragon-test-falcon-crew-astronauts-space-station-iss-a8645401.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOlGvVzVtx6KXfJ-bEwbTjUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/nasa-spacex-launch-dragon-test-falcon-crew-astronauts-space-station-iss-a8645401.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nasa and SpaceX to test rocket that will carry people to space&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nasa and SpaceX are about to launch a rocket that could mark the future of American spaceflight. The two organisations will team up to blast the Crew Dragon spacecraft, on the top of a Falcon 9 rocket, as part of a major test. Together, the two crafts could represent the future of missions carrying American astronauts. Nasa's most stunning pictures of space - + show all Nasa's most stunning pictures of space - 1/30 Earth from the ISS From the International Space Station, Expedition 42 Flight Engineer Terry W. Virts took this photograph of the Gulf of Mexico and U.S. Gulf Coast at sunset Nas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>SpaceX's crew rocket set for January test flight - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-nasa/spacexs-crew-rocket-set-for-january-test-flight-idUSKCN1NQ2F7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPs5vAX8Zn65Ec61exN6AZwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMPT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 19:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-nasa/spacexs-crew-rocket-set-for-january-test-flight-idUSKCN1NQ2F7" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX's crew rocket set for January test flight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first flight of a SpaceX rocket tailored to fly astronauts to the International Space Station is set for liftoff from Kennedy Space Center in Florida on Jan. 7, NASA said on Wednesday. The launch test is a crucial milestone in the space agency's Commercial Crew Program, which aims to launch humans to space from U.S. soil for the first time in nearly a decade. The U.S. National Aeronautics and Space Administration said SpaceX's Crew Dragon spacecraft - which will shuttle three astronauts to space from the same launch pad that sent Apollo 11's three-man crew to the moon in 1969 - will mak...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>SpaceX Launch Equals Its Record For Most Launches In A Year - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanocallaghan/2018/11/15/spacex-launches-and-lands-rocket-on-a-mission-for-qatar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN3y63EGuoClGy7GissVu9sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 21:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanocallaghan/2018/11/15/spacex-launches-and-lands-rocket-on-a-mission-for-qatar/" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX Launch Equals Its Record For Most Launches In A Year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first stage booster landed successfully on the drone ship SpaceX has successfully launched and landed a Falcon 9 rocket from the Kennedy Space Center in Florida, taking Qatar’s Es’hail-2 communications satellite into orbit, its 18th launch this year − equaling its previous record set in 2017. The two-stage rocket, which included a first stage booster flying for its second time, lifted off at 3.46pm Eastern time, sending the satellite towards a Geostationary Transfer Orbit (GTO) 35,000 kilometers above Earth. About nine minutes after lift-off, the first stage of the rocket then touched d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>NASA Safety Probe Of SpaceX And Boeing Could Further Delay Crewed Rocket Program - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeremybogaisky/2018/11/20/nasa-safety-probe-of-spacex-and-boeing-could-further-delay-manned-rocket-program/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE61nHL6zNb-xGaspaRjMCIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:29:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeremybogaisky/2018/11/20/nasa-safety-probe-of-spacex-and-boeing-could-further-delay-manned-rocket-program/" target="_blank"&gt;NASA Safety Probe Of SpaceX And Boeing Could Further Delay Crewed Rocket Program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=0] NASA is launching a probe of workplace safety and drug use at Boeing and SpaceX, the agency said Tuesday. The announcement of the investigation comes two months after SpaceX and Tesla CEO Elon Musk raised eyebrows when he took a drag on a marijuana joint and drank whiskey during a livestreamed interview with the comedian Joe Rogan. NASA characterized the investigation as “a cultural assessment study” into the two companies the agency has contracted to fly NASA astronauts to the International Space Station “to ensure the companies are meeting NASA’s requirements for workplace safety, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Startup Rocket Lab puts 6 small satellites into orbit - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/11/business/rocket-lab-commercial-smallsat-launch/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDxpbrtEEkjwzfJyg_mFvdwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 01:34:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/11/business/rocket-lab-commercial-smallsat-launch/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Startup Rocket Lab puts 6 small satellites into orbit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A scrappy American rocket startup just set the bar in the red-hot market for companies that launch small satellites. Rocket Lab's Electron rocket launched six small satellites -- or smallsats -- into a low-Earth orbit Sunday from New Zealand. It's the second time company's rocket, which is less than 60 feet tall, has done that. Rocket Lab's rivals have not yet pulled off an orbital launch, which means it is at the front of an increasingly crowded pack of rocket startups that want to launch smallsats for businesses and researchers. Other prominent companies in the dedicated smallsat launch i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>SpaceX seeks $750 million leveraged loan - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spacex-loan/spacex-seeks-750-million-leveraged-loan-idUSKCN1NB2G4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEitU-8uzbzLcwuvjeA7dYwqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 18:51:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spacex-loan/spacex-seeks-750-million-leveraged-loan-idUSKCN1NB2G4" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX seeks $750 million leveraged loan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jonathan Schwarzberg and Kristen Haunss NEW YORK (LPC) - Elon Musk's Space Exploration Technologies Corp, known as SpaceX, is looking to line up a $750 million leveraged loan, sources said. Bank of America Merrill Lynch is leading the transaction. A lenders presentation will be held by the SpaceX management team on November 7. SpaceX makes rockets and spacecraft. The company was founded by Elon Musk in 2002 as a way to help humans live on other planets. The Hawthorne, Calif.-based company now employs more than 6,000 people, according to its website. Elon Musk is also the chief executive ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tesla's Starman cruises beyond Mars to 'the restaurant at the end of the universe' - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-06/elon-musks-tesla-cruises-past-mars-orbit/10468508</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6rAizbpRHbc2MQGLmq4z4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 22:36:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-06/elon-musks-tesla-cruises-past-mars-orbit/10468508" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla's Starman cruises beyond Mars to 'the restaurant at the end of the universe'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly nine months after it blasted off from the Kennedy Space Centre, Elon Musk's Tesla Roadster has cruised beyond Mars, SpaceX has confirmed. External Link: SpaceX's tweet: Starman’s current location. Next stop, the restaurant at the end of the universe. Mr Musk's red electric vehicle, "driven" by the spacesuit-clad mannequin Starman, became the fastest car ever when it blasted off in February, and the original plan was to come close to the red planet but hopefully not nick it. Although the final firing of the rocket's upper stage back when it launched put the car on a more distant traje...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Stratolaunch Proves It Is Still On Track With 'Major' Rocket Engine Test - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanocallaghan/2018/11/08/stratolaunch-proves-it-is-still-on-track-with-major-rocket-engine-test/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVedha1QoSgjdeIrEU-zAMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 14:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanocallaghan/2018/11/08/stratolaunch-proves-it-is-still-on-track-with-major-rocket-engine-test/" target="_blank"&gt;Stratolaunch Proves It Is Still On Track With 'Major' Rocket Engine Test&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The aircraft has the biggest wingspan of any in the world Stratolaunch, a Seattle-based company that is building the world’s biggest plane to launch rockets into space, hasn’t had an easy time of late. They missed their own target to fly their plane for the first time this summer, and last month the company’s founder – Paul Gardner Allen – sadly passed away. So proving the company was still on track to become a player in the launch market was essential. And they’ve done that – on November 2, the company announced the successful firing of a key part of a rocket engine it is developing, calle...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Musk shakes up SpaceX in race to make satellite launch window: sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spacex-starlink-insight/musk-shakes-up-spacex-in-race-to-make-satellite-launch-window-sources-idUSKCN1N50FC</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG2OVopiyB4yqlPbDLT6sdAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 17:05:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spacex-starlink-insight/musk-shakes-up-spacex-in-race-to-make-satellite-launch-window-sources-idUSKCN1N50FC" target="_blank"&gt;Musk shakes up SpaceX in race to make satellite launch window: sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SpaceX Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk flew to the Seattle area in June for meetings with engineers leading a satellite launch project crucial to his space company's growth. Within hours of landing, Musk had fired at least seven people on the program's senior management team at the Redmond, Washington, office, the culmination of disagreements over the pace at which the team was developing and testing its Starlink satellites, according to two SpaceX employees with direct knowledge of the situation. Known for pushing aggressive deadlines, Musk quickly brought in new managers from SpaceX hea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Report: Elon Musk fired a bunch of SpaceX execs in Starlink shakeup - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90259755/report-elon-musk-fired-a-bunch-of-spacex-execs-in-starlink-shakeup</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIhT7Wrv34otSnk1t5m196kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:35:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90259755/report-elon-musk-fired-a-bunch-of-spacex-execs-in-starlink-shakeup" target="_blank"&gt;Report: Elon Musk fired a bunch of SpaceX execs in Starlink shakeup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between Tesla, SpaceX, the Boring Company, tweeting, and appearing on podcasts, Elon Musk apparently doesn’t have enough on his plate. In June, he reportedly flew to Redmond, Washington, and fired a whole bunch of engineers working on SpaceX’s Starlink program in order to get the satellites into space by the middle of next year, according to Reuters. If in the current news cycle you have forgotten where Starlink fits into Musk’s expansive dossier, it’s the satellite internet company meant to compete with companies like OneWeb and Canada’s Telesat. While companies like HughesNet have offered...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Mars &amp; Moon bases for military? Elon Musk ‘likes’ Trump’s Space Force plan - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/443052-elon-musk-space-force-bases/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENCXV9PUtIhuKorXqmfdtpkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/443052-elon-musk-space-force-bases/" target="_blank"&gt;Mars &amp; Moon bases for military? Elon Musk ‘likes’ Trump’s Space Force plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SpaceX founder Elon Musk said he likes US President Donald Trump’s idea for a military space force, suggesting it would be a good idea to set up “defense” bases on Mars and the Moon. The entrepreneur, who also founded Tesla, delved into his business plans for the coming year in an interview on the Recode Decode podcast. As conversation weaved between Tesla and SpaceX, Musk laid bare his admiration for Trump’s tentatively named Space Force. READ MORE: Use the Space Force! Internet sniggers over Trump’s idea for cosmic army “This may be a little controversial but I like the idea. I think it i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Is SpaceX’s Satellite Internet Project In Trouble? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2018/10/31/is-spacexs-satellite-internet-project-in-trouble/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMhP69M04ieQbTKcQYT2y-YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 21:49:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2018/10/31/is-spacexs-satellite-internet-project-in-trouble/" target="_blank"&gt;Is SpaceX’s Satellite Internet Project In Trouble?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=2] Reuters reported Wednesday that SpaceX CEO Elon Musk in June fired seven managers of the SpaceX team in its Redmond, Wash. office, which is focused on building out the company’s satellite internet project, dubbed “Starlink.” Those managers have since been replaced by other SpaceX employees, reportedly with an aim to launch the first set of satellites by the middle of 2019 and begin operations in 2020. The report suggests that the internet program is struggling to hire and maintain staff, and it may miss its ambitious timeline. SpaceX spokesperson Eva Behrend told Forbes in an email, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>China suffers a setback in the private space race - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/29/tech/landspace-china-space-news/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIbn-4FXaDeE3yVS0oe4YgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:45:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/29/tech/landspace-china-space-news/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;China suffers a setback in the private space race&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China's private space industry has suffered a setback after a leading startup failed in its first attempt to put a satellite in orbit. LandSpace, a three-year-old company based in Beijing, said "something abnormal occurred" in the third phase of the launch Saturday that was meant to send a satellite into orbit for CCTV, China's state-run television network. The company is one of several Chinese startups that are trying to follow in the footsteps of Elon Musk's SpaceX in making a viable business out of commercial space launches. LandSpace says it's the first private company in China to recei...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Chinese privately developed rocket fails to reach orbit - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-space-landspace/chinese-privately-developed-rocket-fails-to-reach-orbit-idUSKCN1N2078</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPlOfMLrbVSpXpEG_0yiCigqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMPT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 12:07:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-space-landspace/chinese-privately-developed-rocket-fails-to-reach-orbit-idUSKCN1N2078" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese privately developed rocket fails to reach orbit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A privately developed Chinese carrier rocket failed to reach orbit after lifting off from Jiuquan Satellite Launch Center on Saturday, in a blow to the country's nascent attempts by private companies to rival Elon Musk's SpaceX. The three-stage rocket, Zhuque-1, was developed by Beijing-based Landspace. The company said in a microblog post after nominal first and second stages that the spacecraft failed to reach orbit as a result of an issue with the third stage. "Before Zhuque carrier rocket was launched, its mission was already completed," the company said in the post on Saturday, without...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk claims Twitter locked his account after bizarre 'I love anime' post - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/elon-musk-twitter-locked-account-hacked-anime-wolverine-tweet-post-tesla-spacex-a8597081.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIXQlzYSJ2jGgskUu-OvGssqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 08:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/elon-musk-twitter-locked-account-hacked-anime-wolverine-tweet-post-tesla-spacex-a8597081.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk claims Twitter locked his account after bizarre 'I love anime' post&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk has claimed Twitter locked his account fearing it had been hacked following several bizarre posts about anime. The Tesla and Space X chief appeared to profess his love for the Japanese style of animation in a tweet sent on Monday. A second post, apparently written by Musk around 40 minutes later, stated he owned a wolverine, describing it as “chibi” – a Japanese slang term for short or small. And I own a chibi Wolverine — Elon Musk (@elonmusk) 22 October 2018 Hours later, Musk tweeted again, claiming Twitter had locked his account, seemingly in the belief the unusual messages mean...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s tunnel system that will put cars on 150mph ‘skates’ to open in December - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/22/elon-musks-la-tunnel-will-transport-people-150mph-skates-open/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJBThpc5cn9r93l2uSP6Pg4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 09:33:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/22/elon-musks-la-tunnel-will-transport-people-150mph-skates-open/" target="_blank"&gt;Elon Musk’s tunnel system that will put cars on 150mph ‘skates’ to open in December&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk has come a step closer to creating a "loop" transit system beneath Los Angeles to bring an end to "soul-destroying traffic" in the city. Taking to Twitter, the billionaire SpaceX founder said his underground tunnel for the project "is almost done" and will be ready on December 10. In a follow-up tweet, a fan asked whether the December 10 opening was "in real time or Elon time?" and Musk replied "I think real." The tunnel, which is being built by Musk's Boring Company, will contain autonomous electric skates capable of transporting cars and people at speeds of up to 125-150mph. "T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Space junk plunges out of orbit and crashes on California farm (PHOTOS) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/441828-space-junk-satellite-debris/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBGxf6F81zFOFCYuAEyXdWYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 13:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/441828-space-junk-satellite-debris/" target="_blank"&gt;Space junk plunges out of orbit and crashes on California farm (PHOTOS)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Debris believed to have come from a space communications program has crashed down at a walnut farm in California, with investigators working on the idea that it came from a recently decayed satellite launched in the 1990s. When charred metal fragments were found by an orchard owner in Hanford, investigators from Kings County Police Department dispatched to the scene were puzzled. Then they turned their attentions to a nearby airbase. Mysterious space object that landed on California ranch identified https://t.co/CqBRlMYhz6 pic.twitter.com/vNQfeKApVG — Rich Tehrani @LicensingLive, Nov 12-13 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>We once marvelled at Neil Armstrong. Now space is a playground for the rich - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/17/race-for-space-greed-nasa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOBbnM-Q1-H7DRQII6IkITUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 05:00:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/17/race-for-space-greed-nasa" target="_blank"&gt;We once marvelled at Neil Armstrong. Now space is a playground for the rich&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The promised journey is from Earth to the edge of space, rather than London Euston to Crewe, but the story of Richard Branson’s company Virgin Galactic still has echoes of a bad passenger experience on his trains. For the best part of a decade, his potential customers have been waiting for an experience that was meant to arrive in 2011, with only one certainty to hang on to: the tickets are eye-wateringly expensive. The price for Virgin rocket travel now apparently hovers at around £250,000, and reports suggest that among those patiently waiting to climb aboard are Katy Perry, Justin Bieber...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Move over, lovers—Virginia is for rockets, too! - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90252741/move-over-lovers-virginia-is-for-rockets-too</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAMowjTw6X2NUkGDD4cFWAAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 12:59:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90252741/move-over-lovers-virginia-is-for-rockets-too" target="_blank"&gt;Move over, lovers—Virginia is for rockets, too!&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back in July, New Zealand space startup Rocket Labs announced it was looking for a U.S. location for its new launch site. (You gotta keep Blue Origin and SpaceX on their toes, after all.) The company has now made its selection—Virginia, home of Smithfield Ham. Specifically, Rocket Labs will let its Electron rockets fly from NASA’s Wallops Flight Facility on Wallops Island, Virginia. The site will serve as Rocket Lab’s second dedicated launch complex. By design, Launch Complex 2 is well-located to serve U.S. government and commercial missions. As soon as the second site is up and running, Ro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>'Strangest thing I've ever seen in the sky': SpaceX launch confuses and amazes observers - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-09/spacex-launch-confuses-and-amazes-observers/10354900</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELhzDRy9If1qMX24IyBdY7oqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 01:41:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-09/spacex-launch-confuses-and-amazes-observers/10354900" target="_blank"&gt;'Strangest thing I've ever seen in the sky': SpaceX launch confuses and amazes observers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When SpaceX launched a rocket carrying an Argentine Earth-observation satellite from California's central coast, both the night sky and social media lit up. People as far away as San Francisco, Sacramento, Phoenix and Nevada, posted photos of the Falcon 9 rocket's launch and return on Sunday night (local time). It was the first time SpaceX landed a first-stage booster back at its launch site at Vandenberg Air Force Base, about 210 kilometres north-west of Los Angeles. The Air Force warned residents they might see multiple engine burns by the first stage and hear one or more sonic booms as i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>SpaceX lands Falcon 9 rocket in California for first time - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/spacex-falcon-9-elon-musk-launch-site-california-rocket-landing-tesla-a8574701.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGYbyF94_ZuLau68Lnzn9dIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 16:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/spacex-falcon-9-elon-musk-launch-site-california-rocket-landing-tesla-a8574701.html" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX lands Falcon 9 rocket in California for first time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SpaceX has landed its Falcon 9 rocket for the first time in California, another landmark achievement for Elon Musk. It was the first time the company has landed its reusable booster on the west coast, but it had previously done so at least 30 times according to the company – all in Florida and on barges in the Pacific Ocean. The Falcon 9 has now taken the Argentine satellite SAOCOM 1A into orbit, launching from Vandenberg Air Force Base northwest of Los Angeles. - Read more SpaceX to fly mystery person around the Moon It took off at approximately 7pm local time on Sunday and the booster cam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Jeff Bezos' rocket company wants to send 'millions' to live in space - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/15/jeff-bezos-rocket-company-wants-send-millions-live-space/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFe8HQEozpyuNy6vHh06lGEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 17:35:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/15/jeff-bezos-rocket-company-wants-send-millions-live-space/" target="_blank"&gt;Jeff Bezos' rocket company wants to send 'millions' to live in space&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jeff Bezos’ aerospace firm Blue Origin has revealed ambitions to send millions of people into outer space. The Amazon tycoon's company says it “believes in a future where millions of people are living and working in space”. In a new video posted on its website the company says “Now is the time to open the promise of space to all, and lay the way for generations to come. “When our descendants look to the stars, perhaps from a rocky moon or colonies floating in space, they’ll remember this time. “When they reflect on where it started, they’ll remember this place.” The Amazon chief executive f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>‘Aliens are real’: SpaceX West Coast launch freaks Californians out (PHOTOS, VIDEOS) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/440642-aliens-spacex-launch-california/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0KxJyYbguFdREkWGLC8QkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 09:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/440642-aliens-spacex-launch-california/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Aliens are real’: SpaceX West Coast launch freaks Californians out (PHOTOS, VIDEOS)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Residents across California were dumbfounded and awe-struck Sunday night as a strange object ignited the night sky. While many people’s first instinct was to think aliens were en route, it was, in fact, a SpaceX rocket launch. Despite repeated warnings during the week in the build-up to the launch, it appears many residents in California didn’t get the memo. Out here in Bakersfield when I look up in the sky and see this wtf.. pic.twitter.com/chTquV5eLW — 🛫 (@Juanism69) October 8, 2018 ALIENS ARE REAL pic.twitter.com/yh88VOh4w6 — Nate Garner (@natekgarner) October 8, 2018 Welp, I’m halfway ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Tequila, flamethrowers and baseball caps: Elon Musk’s strange brand tie-ins - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/441171-musk-teslaquila-weird-products/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFi9XIWU9YkuSnCZF3VzhWgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 14:18:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/441171-musk-teslaquila-weird-products/" target="_blank"&gt;Tequila, flamethrowers and baseball caps: Elon Musk’s strange brand tie-ins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla founder Elon Musk has trademarked a new tequila named after his famed electric cars. Teslaquila is the latest product-linked idea dreamt up by the Space X mastermind that’s a bit off-brand. Teslaquila Reports emerged Friday that Tesla registered a new trademark with the Patent and Trademark Office for ‘Teslaquila’. Musk appeared to confirm the reports, tweeting, “Teslaquila coming soon…” and sharing a “visual approximation“ of what the new drink’s label could look like. Visual approximation pic.twitter.com/sMn3Pv476Y — Elon Musk (@elonmusk) October 12, 2018 The electric car creator fi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Japanese Tycoon Going on SpaceX Rocket Says He Trusts Musk - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/japanese-tycoon-going-on-spacex-rocket-says-he-trusts-musk/4605816.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJPGnumbiJAxZbyUg12lhCQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 14:19:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/japanese-tycoon-going-on-spacex-rocket-says-he-trusts-musk/4605816.html" target="_blank"&gt;Japanese Tycoon Going on SpaceX Rocket Says He Trusts Musk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese online retail tycoon who plans to travel to the moon on the SpaceX rocket says he respects and trusts Elon Musk as a fellow entrepreneur, despite his recent troubles. "Twitter can get you into trouble," Yusaku Maezawa, chief executive of Zozo Inc., said Tuesday at the Foreign Correspondents' Club in Tokyo. "And that can be said of Elon Musk, too." Musk's tweet in August that declared he had secured financing for a Tesla buyout got him in trouble with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. Under a settlement, Tesla and Musk each must pay a $20 million penalty. Musk also st...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>SpaceX launch, a "big and bold" family affair - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/10/08/spacex-launch-a-big-and-bold-family-affa?videoId=471462281</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOolwwa1suRORkhmtQg51cQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 14:07:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/10/08/spacex-launch-a-big-and-bold-family-affa?videoId=471462281" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX launch, a "big and bold" family affair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With their young daughter Caroline, Austin and Frankie Podrat joined other spectators on the beach in Ventura to watch Sunday night's spectacular launch of a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket from Vandenberg Air Force Base. Rough cut (no reporter narration).&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>SpaceX rocket launch captivates Californians as it lights up the evening sky - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/08/us/spacex-california-rocket-elon-musk/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEC1cxNLyCAAnD5Uk_KpJW4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 19:33:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/08/us/spacex-california-rocket-elon-musk/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX rocket launch captivates Californians as it lights up the evening sky&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rocket launches are always guaranteed to make people look up to the sky in awe, but the latest SpaceX liftoff might have just raised the bar for a long time. Elon Musk's company on Sunday successfully launched a Falcon 9 rocket into the evening California sky, prompting locals to post pictures and videos of the spectacular light show on social media. The rocket delivered the Argentine satellite SAOCOM 1A into orbit about 12 minutes after liftoff from Vandenberg Air Force Base, 160 miles northwest of Los Angeles. In a first for SpaceX in the West Coast, Falcon 9's first stage returned to the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>SpaceX rocket launch lights up evening sky - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/10/08/spacex-rocket-launch-lon-orig.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHVRL0AgIhhgqgRCA328O_cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 09:10:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/10/08/spacex-rocket-launch-lon-orig.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;SpaceX rocket launch lights up evening sky&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk's company successfully launched a Falcon 9 rocket into the evening California sky, prompting locals to post pictures and videos of the spectacular light show on social media. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Space race: Richard Branson trolls Elon Musk, says he must sleep more - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/440878-branson-trolls-musk-space/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFTgWlT737kHYxvIR7vudNMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 14:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/440878-branson-trolls-musk-space/" target="_blank"&gt;Space race: Richard Branson trolls Elon Musk, says he must sleep more&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a new space race heating up, two business titans could be set for a war of words of galactic proportions as Sir Richard Branson has offered some unsolicited advice to his rival Elon Musk. “I think that learning the art of delegation better would be his one flaw,” the billionaire founder of Virgin Galactic said of his SpaceX counterpart. “He’s got to find time for himself. He’s got to find time for his health and for his family. And you know he’s a wonderfully creative person. He shouldn’t be getting very little sleep,” Branson told CNBC when asked what advice he would give his fellow b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>First SpaceX mission with NASA astronauts set for June 2019 - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/05/first-spacex-mission-nasa-astronauts-set-june-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOGNLcJAKlKMOgjMYh-_oscqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 22:39:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/05/first-spacex-mission-nasa-astronauts-set-june-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;First SpaceX mission with NASA astronauts set for June 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NASA has announced the first crewed flight by a SpaceX rocket to the International Space Station (ISS) is expected to take place in June 2019. It will be the first manned US launch to the orbiting research laboratory since the space shuttle program was retired in 2011, forcing US astronauts to hitch costly rides aboard Russian Soyuz spacecraft. A flight on Boeing spacecraft is set to follow in August 2019. The timetable for both launches has already been postponed several times, but NASA said Thursday it would now be providing monthly updates on deadlines. "This new process for reporting ou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Rocket carrying Argentinian satellite takes off successfully - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f5742855f79541e79da5b3b741b02c87</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBvcZvLKJhKPfaKYL2x30cUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvKadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 03:46:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f5742855f79541e79da5b3b741b02c87" target="_blank"&gt;Rocket carrying Argentinian satellite takes off successfully&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VANDENBERG AIR FORCE BASE, Calif. (AP) — A SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket carried an Argentinian Earth-observation satellite into space Sunday and for the first time landed a first-stage booster back at its California launch site. The primary purpose of the mission was to place the SAOCOM 1A satellite into orbit, but SpaceX also wanted to expand its recovery of first stages to its launch site at Vandenberg Air Force Base, about 130 miles (209 kilometers) northwest of Los Angeles. SpaceX had previously flown first-stage rockets back to land after Florida launches but had not done so on the West Coas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Bezos’ Blue Origin, Others Get $2.3 Billion in US Rocket Contracts - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/bezos-blue-origin-others-get-2-3-billion-in-us-rocket-contracts/4608755.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJmVzKbS9XWLcDfrq7iJsocqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 01:51:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/bezos-blue-origin-others-get-2-3-billion-in-us-rocket-contracts/4608755.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bezos’ Blue Origin, Others Get $2.3 Billion in US Rocket Contracts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Air Force on Wednesday said that it had awarded a total of $2.3 billion in contracts to develop rocket launch systems for national security missions. The awards go to Amazon.com billionaire Jeff Bezos' Blue Origin; United Launch Services, part of the United Launch Alliance (ULA) joint venture between Boeing Co and Lockheed Martin Corp; and Northrop Grumman Innovation Systems. The three contracts are part of a Department of Defense initiative to assure constant military access to space and curb reliance on foreign-made rocket engines, like ULA's flagship Atlas V rocket that uses Rus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Jeff Bezos' space company is designing a lunar lander for trips to the moon - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-space-x-moon-travel-rocket-lunar-lander-a8567401.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHsXjvOreV5TeBE-rxRw9nYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 19:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-space-x-moon-travel-rocket-lunar-lander-a8567401.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jeff Bezos' space company is designing a lunar lander for trips to the moon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jeff Bezos‘ private space transport company is designing a large lunar lander that it claims will provide reusable access to the moon’s surface. Blue Origin‘s lander is part of the firm’s mission to help create a future where millions of people live and work in space, the company said in a statement. Researchers are currently in the conceptual design phase of the project. “The next logical step in this path is a return to the Moon,” a spokesperson for Blue Origin said on Wednesday. “To do this we need reusable access to the lunar surface and its resources.” Read more - Bernie Sanders introd...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Bezos' space company designing large lunar lander - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-blueorigin/bezos-space-company-designing-large-lunar-lander-idUSKCN1MD27Z</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEuIYhKBx2fbIy_RZ-ckOakqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMPT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 17:13:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-blueorigin/bezos-space-company-designing-large-lunar-lander-idUSKCN1MD27Z" target="_blank"&gt;Bezos' space company designing large lunar lander&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jeff Bezos' space company is in the conceptual design phase of a large lunar lander that it says will provide reusable access to the moon's surface and its resources, Blue Origin said on Wednesday. The lander is part of Blue Origin's broader mission of enabling a future in which millions of people live and work in space, the company said. "The next logical step in this path is a return to the Moon," Blue Origin said in a statement. "To do this we need reusable access to the lunar surface and its resources." The company, founded by Amazon.com Inc Chief Executive Officer Bezos, has said it ai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Review Of Michael H. Gorn's 'Spacecraft' Book - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/francistapon/2018/10/06/review-of-michael-h-gorns-spacecraft-book/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMWTwxHup8TTlhMdA9LLAt4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 16:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/francistapon/2018/10/06/review-of-michael-h-gorns-spacecraft-book/" target="_blank"&gt;Review Of Michael H. Gorn's 'Spacecraft' Book&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why has adventure travel exploded in the last few years? Two reasons: - Cheap flights. - Fewer visa complications (the European Union’s expansion opened Eastern Europe and Africa is simplifying its visa procedures too). As a result, people have quickly checked off their classic international bucket list destinations such as Egypt,Venice, Zanzibar andCzechia. Now travelers want something more exotic and adventurous: Gambia, Guinea-Bissau and outer space. A reporter takes a smartphone photo of a mock-up of the Crew Dragon spacecraft during a media tour of SpaceX headquarters and rocket factor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Meet the first civilian who will orbit the moon - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/10/03/yusaku-maezawa-spacex-moon-sje-lon-orig.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED7yUI_dnF4vDYTJRu_QCAMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 18:48:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/10/03/yusaku-maezawa-spacex-moon-sje-lon-orig.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;Meet the first civilian who will orbit the moon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese billionaire Yusaku Maezawa will be the first passenger in a SpaceX trip around the moon. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Thanks, SEC--Musk's Twitter Feed Has Already Gone Silent - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/lianeyvkoff/2018/09/30/thanks-sec-musks-twitter-feed-has-already-gone-silent/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKFTFBF7z2NpwkPNFdk-L84qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 20:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/lianeyvkoff/2018/09/30/thanks-sec-musks-twitter-feed-has-already-gone-silent/" target="_blank"&gt;Thanks, SEC--Musk's Twitter Feed Has Already Gone Silent&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk, chief executive officer for Space Exploration Technologies Corp. (SpaceX), speaks during an event at the SpaceX headquarters in Hawthorne, California, U.S., on Monday, Sept. 17, 2018. Photographer: Patrick T. Fallon/Bloomberg Elon Musk has been fined $20 million for trying to impress his girlfriend with errant tweets, but let’s face it–we are all paying the price. In addition to forcing Musk to step down from his chairman role of Tesla, the SEC is mandating the company add two independent board members and establish new communications protocols that oversee his communications. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Jeff Bezos' Blue Origin inks rocket deal with Boeing, Lockheed Martin - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/09/27/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-inks-rocket-deal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOByeQA3nk0FS8vY_uKrxYgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 18:36:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/09/27/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-inks-rocket-deal/" target="_blank"&gt;Jeff Bezos' Blue Origin inks rocket deal with Boeing, Lockheed Martin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blue Origin, the space exploration company run by Jeff Bezos, has won a contract to supply engines for rockets launching US military and spy satellites into orbit. The bespoke BE-4 engine will power the Vulcan rocket when it takes its maiden voyage in 2020. The sum of the deal between Blue Origins and Vulcan maker United Launch Alliance, a joint venture between Boeing and Lockheed Martin is thought to be worth billions, according to the Wall Street Journal. United Launch Alliance currently relies on Russian-made engines and had been on the market for an American-made product following geopo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item></channel></rss>