<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>iPhone - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNREkzYkc1NmN4SUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:31:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Apple Loop: Poor iPhone Sales Frighten Apple, Frustrating iPhone 5G Delay, Huge iPhone XR Price Cut - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/apple-news-headlines-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-iphone-xr-discount-5g-airpods/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJnlWej_IG0szwozRXTPvhQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/apple-news-headlines-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-iphone-xr-discount-5g-airpods/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Loop: Poor iPhone Sales Frighten Apple, Frustrating iPhone 5G Delay, Huge iPhone XR Price Cut&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at another week of news from Cupertino, this week’s Apple Loop includes Apple’s response to falling iPhone sales, no 5G for next year’s iPhone, the return of TouchID, no new AirPods for Christmas, the first official iPhone XR cover, and the legend of the Apple Store. Apple Loop is here to remind you of a few of the very many discussions that have happened around Apple over the last seven days (and you can read my weekly digest of Android news here on Forbes). iPhone XR’s $300 Discount Apple continues to react to the low sales of the iPhone with decisions that feel more pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Snip, snip: Morgan Stanley latest to cut Apple target on China woes - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cc64bbcc-fa2f-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHvfyuM0NnrZQOunEFYOEcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:20:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cc64bbcc-fa2f-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Snip, snip: Morgan Stanley latest to cut Apple target on China woes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Apple price cut club welcomed a new member on Friday after Morgan Stanley blamed the Chinese smartphone market for weakening the outlook for iPhone sales. Flattening iPhone sales have stoked concerns on Wall Street that consumer demand has peaked for Apple’s most important device. In September, the tech giant offered a weaker than expected forecast for the holiday quarter and said it would no longer offer a quarterly breakdown of sales for each of its devices. Meanwhile, key iPhone suppliers have lowered financial guidance, and the Wall Street Journal reported last month that Apple redu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>This was the hottest app trend of the year - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-was-the-hottest-app-trend-of-the-year-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKH29I3-FLi2Bb9RtKaV4dUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwuJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-was-the-hottest-app-trend-of-the-year-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;This was the hottest app trend of the year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MONEYISH By Nicole Lyn Pesce Self-care apps topped Apple’s 2018 trends list, as consumers spent $32 million on mindfulness apps like Calm, Headspace and 10% Happier Self-care apps teaching meditation and mindfulness are the year’s top trend. Stígur Már Karlsson /Heimsmyndir/iStock Apps were all about inner peace in 2018. Apple named “self-care” its app trend of the year with its Best of 2018 list released earlier this week, which highlighted what apps, games, movies and music were on everyone’s list — and fingertips — over the past year. “We became mindful of some amazing wellness apps,” th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Google’s Pixel Slate: Great Chromebook, not-so-great iPad/Surface rival - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90272364/googles-pixel-slate-great-chromebook-not-so-great-ipad-surface-rival</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHEukDmmvBBRCMQzQw3xFwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 06:00:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90272364/googles-pixel-slate-great-chromebook-not-so-great-ipad-surface-rival" target="_blank"&gt;Google’s Pixel Slate: Great Chromebook, not-so-great iPad/Surface rival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since their 2011 launch, Chromebooks have been synonymous with low-cost, easily managed laptops that have strong appeal for education. But in 2013, when Google shipped the first Chromebook Pixel–a premium machine with a touchscreen–it became clear that the company was intent on exploring new frontiers for its browser-centric Chrome OS operating system. Google’s new Pixel Slate tablet, which starts at $599, represents the culmination of those efforts. With its minimalist operating system and minimalist form factor, it’s the best pure web tablet ever made. But the Pixel Slate also offers the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Apple's New iPhones Have An Expensive Secret - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/apple-iphone-xs-max-xr-price-cut-cost-discount-reduction-upgrade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFfFBgkdrV5Hzgcm_L69zJIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/apple-iphone-xs-max-xr-price-cut-cost-discount-reduction-upgrade/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple's New iPhones Have An Expensive Secret&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple may have quietly begun to cut iPhone prices, but it may just be the start. A new report reveals much bigger price cuts appear inevitable if the company hopes to boost interest in the iPhone XS (details), iPhone XS Max (details) and iPhone XR (details)… Picked up by Business Insider, news has broken today that iPhone camera lens maker Largan Precision has reported a jaw-dropping 29% fall in November revenue compared to the same period last year (the new iPhones went on sale in September). And the blowback on Apple may have expensive consequences. Apple’s iPhone XS, iPhone XS Max and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple iOS 12.1.1 Release: Should You Upgrade? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/apple-ios-12-1-1-release-should-you-upgrade-iphone-ipad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA2IbpHUN-xKiY3NEWnMlBcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/apple-ios-12-1-1-release-should-you-upgrade-iphone-ipad/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple iOS 12.1.1 Release: Should You Upgrade?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While iOS 12.1 left a gaping security hole in the lockscreen, it was otherwise a very solid update which eliminated some pretty fundamental (and also ridiculous) flaws from previous releases. Apple has now released iOS 12.1.1 and it’s an important upgrade, but is it bug-free? Here’s everything you need to know… Apple iOS 12 Who Is It For? iOS 12.1.1 is compatible with all iOS 11 compatible devices. This means the iPhone 5S or later, iPad mini 2 or later and 6th generation iPod touch or later. Compatible devices will be automatically prompted to upgrade but, if that doesn’t happen, you can ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Deals Linger: 2018 MacBook Pro, MacBook Air, iPad Pro, Dell XPS 13, HP Spectre, Price Laptop Tablet - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brookecrothers/2018/12/08/deals-linger-2018-macbook-pro-macbook-air-ipad-pro-dell-xps-13-hp-spectre-price-laptop-tablet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBqCGbEu-Eru1vHKQQsmH0sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brookecrothers/2018/12/08/deals-linger-2018-macbook-pro-macbook-air-ipad-pro-dell-xps-13-hp-spectre-price-laptop-tablet/" target="_blank"&gt;Deals Linger: 2018 MacBook Pro, MacBook Air, iPad Pro, Dell XPS 13, HP Spectre, Price Laptop Tablet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black Friday and Cyber Monday deals really never went away. The deals below have hung around — but don’t expect them to linger forever. iPad, early 2018. iPad Pro / iPad 2018: you may find better 2018 iPad deals now than a couple weeks ago at Best Buy (main Best Buy iPad Pro deal page / 3 days only). The following are all 2018 models unless otherwise indicated. - iPad Pro 10.5-inch, Wi-Fi, 64 GB: reduced to $499.99 at Best Buy was $649.99 – $150 off. - iPad Pro 10.5-inch, Wi-Fi, 256 GB: reduced to $624.99 at Best Buy was $799.00 – $175 off. - iPad 9.7-inch, Wi-Fi, 32 GB: reduced to $269.99 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why 40% iPhone Discount Is Bad For Apple - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/petercohan/2018/12/06/why-40-iphone-discount-is-bad-for-apple/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPGDTNFIdPidc20ik9tLfkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/petercohan/2018/12/06/why-40-iphone-discount-is-bad-for-apple/" target="_blank"&gt;Why 40% iPhone Discount Is Bad For Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KIEV, UKRAINE – 2018/10/06: Apple co-founder Steve Jobs portrait is seen with price list of Apple iPhone mobile phones in his hands, next to a mobile phone shop in down town. (Photo by Pavlo Gonchar/SOPA Images/LightRocket via Getty Images) Apple shares have fallen 26% from their October 2018 high and they’re poised to fall further. You can argue that Apple’s decline is due to factors beyond its control. For example, the White House threatened to endanger Apple by putting it in the cross-hairs of its China trade war. But a Bloomberg report that Apple is offering a 40% discount on the iPhone...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>NVIDIA BrandVoice: AI For Mobile: New Solutions To Speed Up Performance - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/nvidia/2018/12/07/ai-for-mobile-new-solutions-to-speed-up-performance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL9VBNQiWHvUfWkFseF7avoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:25:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/nvidia/2018/12/07/ai-for-mobile-new-solutions-to-speed-up-performance/" target="_blank"&gt;NVIDIA BrandVoice: AI For Mobile: New Solutions To Speed Up Performance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;[id=2] More than 5 billion people around the world have a mobile phone connection, according to a recent study by GSMA Intelligence. We can’t imagine our lives without mobile phones, which are gradually turning from convenient everyday tools into things like medical devices. It’s not surprising that many companies are developing AI tools for mobile devices. But there’s a serious shortage of professionals in the AI industry with multi-field expertise. An engineer may be a great mobile software developer but lacks knowledge in machine learning—or conversely, an ML engineer or data scientist m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How Rapidly Declining NAND And DRAM Prices Could Benefit Apple - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/12/06/how-rapidly-declining-nand-and-dram-prices-could-benefit-apple/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM53eTMLe5hyCxdj2LIU_bcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/12/06/how-rapidly-declining-nand-and-dram-prices-could-benefit-apple/" target="_blank"&gt;How Rapidly Declining NAND And DRAM Prices Could Benefit Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pedestrians walk past an Apple Inc. store in Shanghai, China, on Tuesday, Nov. 27, 2018. Photographer: Qilai Shen/Bloomberg Apple is poised to see its growth slow down over 2019, amid a mixed response to its latest iPhone XR and XS models and increasing saturation in the smartphone market. That said, Apple could see tailwinds from fast-declining prices for both DRAM and NAND memory, which form a significant cost component for the company. In this note, we take a look at the potential impact of the declining memory prices on Apple’s margins using the iPhone XS Max (256 GB), likely one of App...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Dr. Sanjay Gupta tests the Apple Watch's new ECG heart monitor - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/health/apple-watch-ecg-app-review/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJTbWVIx4IPkdeGn1nlhA5UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:12:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/health/apple-watch-ecg-app-review/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Sanjay Gupta tests the Apple Watch's new ECG heart monitor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the Apple Watch Series 4 was announced in September, one of its most anticipated functions has been the promise to perform a mobile electrocardiogram (ECG or EKG) whenever a consumer wants. The feature becomes available in the United States on Thursday via a software update. This new ECG app represents a big venture into health for Apple. The company's ambition is for Apple and health to become as closely linked as Apple and music. It even produced a commercial featuring people who say the Apple Watch has helped them lead healthier lives. Apple says its new ECG application and the abi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>CSI and the art of the smartphone - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0e6eb200-f94c-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJ0_jYmQ4fHAbflYAI2E14qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:55:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0e6eb200-f94c-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;CSI and the art of the smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FT subscribers can click here to receive #techFT every day by email. “These [smartphone] devices are almost under our skin now. There’s no absolute distinction between one’s inner world and the outside world, the individual and the societal. This isn’t the stuff of theoretical essays any more.” Not the words of a tech expert, but of Alex Farquharson, director of the Tate Britain gallery and chair of the judges of the prestigious Turner art prize, which has just been awarded to an artist who submitted an iPhone video. Charlotte Prodger's video art melds references to standing stones, 1970s l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>More Bad News From Apple As iPhone XR Price Slashed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/apple-iphone-xr-discount-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-price-sale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEABRDM_nzBTtK33HlXkv86sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/apple-iphone-xr-discount-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-price-sale/" target="_blank"&gt;More Bad News From Apple As iPhone XR Price Slashed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding to the signs that the newest iPhones are not meeting Apple’s internal sales targets, let alone the lofty ambitions of significantly increasing the annual sales of the iOS-powered smartphones, details of the actions taken by Tim Cook’s team to boost sales have come to light. Tim Cook, CEO of Apple speaks while unveiling new products during a launch event at the Brooklyn Academy of Music on October 30, 2018 (Photo by Stephanie Keith/Getty Images) Writing for Bloomberg, Mark Gurman notes on an increase in carrier subsidies, an increase in bundled extras, and now an almost unheard of $30...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>OnePlus to make first 5G phone in Europe with EE, company claims - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/oneplus-5g-phone-ee-bt-qualcomm-faster-internet-connection-network-a8669226.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPiYCwu5P2Fo3VR-FvNzilMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/oneplus-5g-phone-ee-bt-qualcomm-faster-internet-connection-network-a8669226.html" target="_blank"&gt;OnePlus to make first 5G phone in Europe with EE, company claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OnePlus is going to make the first 5G phone available in Europe, the company has said. The decision could entirely change the way that phones work and will introduce a transformative technology to the UK, Andy Lau, OnePlus’s chief executive and founder, told The Independent. The phone maker has teamed up with EE to make the handset available, aiming to have it ready for users in 2019. The two companies have signed a research and development partnership that will help deliver much faster and more reliable internet connections across the UK, they said. 5G technology has become one of the most...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Russian tech group Yandex launches own smartphone - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/025d31d6-f860-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdaaZqTZ9aRmxHEdfgimm8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:16:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/025d31d6-f860-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Russian tech group Yandex launches own smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian technology group Yandex has launched its first ever smartphone, as the company seeks to leverage its dominant position in apps and services into hardware sales. Yandex, which runs the most popular search engine in Russia, hopes its Yandex.Phone will bind users closer to its suite of products, from food delivery and taxi hailing apps to marketplace and music streaming platforms, as competition rises for online services. The Android-based smartphone’s launch comes amid a fierce race for market share in Russia’s fledgling e-commerce industry, where Yandex and Russian lender Sberbank ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Apple Releases iOS 12.1.1: Details About The New Features You Should Know About - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/12/05/apple-releases-ios-12-1-1-details-about-the-new-features-you-should-know-about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2uY1syWRfkIyQGWJz-susqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/12/05/apple-releases-ios-12-1-1-details-about-the-new-features-you-should-know-about/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Releases iOS 12.1.1: Details About The New Features You Should Know About&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;iOS 12 screenshot Today Apple released the iOS 12.1.1 update for the iPhone and iPad with several new features and bug fixes. Apple had rolled out three betas for developers before releasing it to the public today. What Is Included In The iOS 12.1.1 Update? As iOS 12.1.1 is a minor point update, it contains several new subtle features and bug fixes. Here is a breakdown of what is included in the update: For the iPhone XR, notification preview using Haptic Touch is now supported. Apple integrated Haptic Touch on the iPhone XR instead of 3D Touch. The iPhone XS and XS Max both have 3D Touch s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple's Own iPhone XR Case Revealed At Last: Here's All You Need To Know - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/05/apples-own-iphone-xr-case-revealed-at-last-heres-all-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG3mDSkm5XBmXVuXwd2agPYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/05/apples-own-iphone-xr-case-revealed-at-last-heres-all-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple's Own iPhone XR Case Revealed At Last: Here's All You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Apple iPhone XR is one of the most beautiful phones you can buy. You can read my review of it here. The new clear iPhone XR cases on all six of the colors. It’s also one of the most colorful. So, how can you clad it in a case without disguising its beauty, whether you’ve chosen the especially gorgeous yellow, the deeply attractive coral, the calming blue, the feisty PRODUCT(RED), the snowy-simple white or the enigmatic space gray? You can read my round-up of the best cases here but you’ll see that Apple hasn’t made a single one of them. Well, today Apple finally revealed its own Apple-m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple patents interchangeable AirPods with health tracking features - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/05/apple-patents-interchangeable-airpods-health-tracking-features/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9eSCEj2JA9ZwnbKrRBPbIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:11:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/05/apple-patents-interchangeable-airpods-health-tracking-features/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple patents interchangeable AirPods with health tracking features&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple is working on interchangeable AirPod headphones that come with health tracking features to measure heart rate and stress levels. That's according to a new patent filed by the firm which reveals how a new version of its wireless in-ear headphones would be able to fit in either ear. The filing shows the device slipping into the ear canal and being held in place with a bendable band. Apple's current wireless AirPods were first launched in 2016, although some users have complained they can easily fall out or become uncomfortable. Apple removed the headphone jack from its iPhone models fro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Apple assembler Foxconn considering iPhone factory in Vietnam -state media - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-foxconn-iphone-vietnam/apple-assembler-foxconn-considering-iphone-factory-in-vietnam-state-media-idUSKBN1O3128</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENh53oo0PL73JJldku-Twj4qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 03:26:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-foxconn-iphone-vietnam/apple-assembler-foxconn-considering-iphone-factory-in-vietnam-state-media-idUSKBN1O3128" target="_blank"&gt;Apple assembler Foxconn considering iPhone factory in Vietnam -state media&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foxconn, the world's biggest electronics contract manufacturer and a key Apple Inc supplier, is considering setting up a factory in Vietnam to mitigate any impact of an ongoing trade war between the United States and China, Vietnamese state media reported. The move would be one of the first significant steps by a major company with large manufacturing facilities in China to secure an additional production base outside the country because of trade tensions between the world's top two economies. The report also comes as several executives of other corporations interviewed by Reuters singled o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENR6R3fi9qwUs_y2cSw6FUgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:42:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2" target="_blank"&gt;Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verizon Communications Inc and Samsung Electronics Co Ltd on Monday confirmed long-held industry expectations they would seek to steal a march on Apple Inc by launching U.S. 5G smartphones in the first half of 2019. The two companies said in a statement they would unveil a prototype, using Qualcomm Inc's modem chips, at the chipmaker's annual Snapdragon Technology Summit in Maui, Hawaii this week. While Verizon is leading the charge to trial 5G in some cities next year, industry analysts say the higher-speed networks are unlikely to be widely available until the middle of the next decade. A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>This is how much Steve Jobs’ autograph is now worth - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-how-much-steve-jobs-autograph-is-now-worth-2018-12-05</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENAAqMmvwCgECv5Infm_Fn8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwuJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-how-much-steve-jobs-autograph-is-now-worth-2018-12-05" target="_blank"&gt;This is how much Steve Jobs’ autograph is now worth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jacob Passy Since 2000, this particular John Hancock has increased in value nearly 28% every year Apple’s iconoclastic founder penned one of the most expensive autographs in the world. Getty Images Steve Jobs did a lot of things in his lifetime: He co-founded Apple (AAPL) he helped create one of the first mass-market personal computers and introduced the world to the iPhone and iPad, among his many accomplishments. One thing he rarely did: Sign autographs. As a result, Steve Jobs’ autograph is one of the most expensive in the world, worth 40,000 pounds (nearly $51,000 or 40 iPhone Xs-es)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm unveils new chip to power 5G smartphones - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-samsung-elec/qualcomm-unveils-new-chip-to-power-5g-smartphones-idUSKBN1O32P1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMecw1wB_A6sq8OQSIV_45wqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:51:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-samsung-elec/qualcomm-unveils-new-chip-to-power-5g-smartphones-idUSKBN1O32P1" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm unveils new chip to power 5G smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chip supplier Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) on Tuesday unveiled a new generation of mobile phone processor chips that will power 5G smartphones in the United States as soon as next year. The key feature of the Snapdragon 855 chip, launched at an event in Hawaii, is a so-called modem for phones to connect to 5G wireless data networks with mobile data speeds of up to 50 or 100 times faster than current 4G networks. Mobile carriers are investing in 5G networks and are eager to sell 5G phones and data plans to recoup investment costs. Qualcomm, the largest supplier...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump wants iPhones made in the US. That could be bad news for Americans - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/tech/trump-tariffs-apple-iphones/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOQ6OoVJQ30_PnHSBh1Pre8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:50:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/tech/trump-tariffs-apple-iphones/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump wants iPhones made in the US. That could be bad news for Americans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump is considering new tariffs on China that could make iPhones way more expensive for Americans. Trump said this week that he won't rule out an additional round of tariffs on Chinese exports thatwould hit Apple's signature product as well as laptops. Such a move would hurt US consumers and American companies because the taxes would be levied on the goods when they enter the country. Apple would have to decide whether to raise its prices to compensate. "The direct impact would be in the United States," said Bryan Ma, analyst with research firm IDC. "If push comes to shove...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New iPhone Leak Exposes Apple's Nasty Surprise - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-xs-max-xr-upgrade-problem-5g-price-cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKXV3t_Srlgj2YNZgtxojBAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-xs-max-xr-upgrade-problem-5g-price-cost/" target="_blank"&gt;New iPhone Leak Exposes Apple's Nasty Surprise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mounting evidence suggests Apple’s iPhone XS (details), iPhone XS Max (details) and iPhone XR (details) are not selling well even despite price cuts. We already know the crowd-pleasing innovation Apple has planned to win users back, but it might not be enough after a major source confirmed the most serious problem with the company’s new iPhones… Bloomberg reports Apple has fallen substantially behind its rivals and will not be able to equip iPhones with 5G until late 2020 at the earliest. And 5G is about to become a game-changer. Apple’s iPhone XS, iPhone XS Max and iPhone XR Bloomberg’s ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How Bad ApplePay UX Could Cost Apple The Payments Race - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/duenablomstrom1/2018/12/05/how-bad-applepay-ux-could-cost-apple-the-payments-race/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdOI_pqSWWlaOem9THIufcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/duenablomstrom1/2018/12/05/how-bad-applepay-ux-could-cost-apple-the-payments-race/" target="_blank"&gt;How Bad ApplePay UX Could Cost Apple The Payments Race&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contactless – Fast, Easy, Convenient With the new models of the phone, Apple had to take another step towards “paying with one’s mind” and decide on the most secure and effective user experience to adapt ApplePay to screens without a thumbprint. What they came up with is a process that seems minutely different to the untrained eye but is in fact vastly more complicated than the one they had before and as such is the biggest fail l have seen then perform in usability. How it works You can find a tutorial here but in short, to pay with the new devices one has to perform however many clicks th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple's stock sours, Microsoft's soars. Say what?! - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/86b8b9e7ebc2452aa496cd75fc5c6d61</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHey5Xri0lhTSPUE8TMhg7AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:27:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/86b8b9e7ebc2452aa496cd75fc5c6d61" target="_blank"&gt;Apple's stock sours, Microsoft's soars. Say what?!&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wall Street investors are enamored with a newly emergent tech company. It has nothing to do with posting selfies or finding a soul mate. The company is instead making billions of dollars selling cloud-computing and other technical services to offices around the world. Say hello to Microsoft, the 1990s home-computing powerhouse that is having a renaissance moment - eclipsing Facebook, Google, Amazon and the other tech darlings of the late decade. And now it is close to surpassing Apple as the world's most valuable publicly traded company. Yes, that Microsoft. As other tech giants stumble, it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>You probably already own the No. 1 item on teenagers’ holiday wish list - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/for-the-first-time-teens-want-fortnite-v-bucks-and-cryptocurrency-instead-of-cash-2018-11-14</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOjLDARJb8Vc-CjxSjE1JLYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/for-the-first-time-teens-want-fortnite-v-bucks-and-cryptocurrency-instead-of-cash-2018-11-14" target="_blank"&gt;You probably already own the No. 1 item on teenagers’ holiday wish list&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Quentin Fottrell Fortnite ‘V-Bucks’ and Bitcoin are also making an appearance on their holiday wish lists Some American teenagers want cryptocurrency and Fortnite “V-Bucks” virtual currency instead of cash. Getty Images/iStockphoto You might want the same thing as your child this holiday season. Some U.S. holiday wish lists crisscross all generations and some, well, don’t. Analyst firm Piper Jaffray said the No. 1 item on U.S. teenagers’ wish list this holiday season is Apple’s (AAPL) iPhone. In fact, their top four consumer brands — Apple Watch, MacBooks and Airpods — all come in those...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Apple Unveils 2018's Most Popular Apps: Fortnite, YouTube, Minecraft And More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/12/04/apple-unveils-2018s-most-popular-apps-youtube-fortnite-minecraft-and-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAO7MdGnBE_q5uTbuq7rcrUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/12/04/apple-unveils-2018s-most-popular-apps-youtube-fortnite-minecraft-and-more/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Unveils 2018's Most Popular Apps: Fortnite, YouTube, Minecraft And More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite and YouTube were the absolute most popular apps of 2018, for both iPhones and iPads. Selfie-editor FaceTune ($3.99) was the most popular paid app on the iPhone while drawing app Procreate ($9.99) won the top spot on the iPad. (Photo by Hannah Smith / ESPAT Media / Getty Images) Today, Apple unveiled the list of the most popular apps and games (free and paid) for iPhone and iPad in 2018 and you’ll find below the top 10 charts for each category. This year, Battle Royale-style games like Fortnite and PUBG Mobile dominated global gaming culture with exciting, last-player-standing actio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>iPhone app helped trap pharmacist who killed his wife at home so he could move on new love interest - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/04/iphone-app-helped-trap-pharmacist-killed-wife-home-could-move/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDt_7RePcS4oIh2AboNnX_MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:36:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/04/iphone-app-helped-trap-pharmacist-killed-wife-home-could-move/" target="_blank"&gt;iPhone app helped trap pharmacist who killed his wife at home so he could move on new love interest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A pharmacist was found guilty of murdering his wife after an iPhone app allowed the police to track his movements whilst she lay motionless in their home. Mitesh Patel, 37, injected his wife Jessica with insulin and strangled her with a Tesco bag at their Middlesbrough home, then staged a break-in to make it look like an intruder had attacked her and bound her with tape. The couple ran a successful pharmacy together, but their marriage was unhappy, with the husband repeatedly seeking sex with men he met on the Grindr dating app. And he was secretly in a relationship with Dr Amit Patel, his ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>It’s Apple vs. the cloud in race to be the world’s most valuable tech company - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/its-apple-vs-the-cloud-in-race-to-be-the-worlds-most-valuable-tech-company-2018-12-04</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1WfaIBA9HcsxNzxEojShQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/its-apple-vs-the-cloud-in-race-to-be-the-worlds-most-valuable-tech-company-2018-12-04" target="_blank"&gt;It’s Apple vs. the cloud in race to be the world’s most valuable tech company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERESE POLETTI'S TECH TALES By Therese Poletti Microsoft and Amazon are challenging Apple for top spot, and Google isn’t far behind In Tuesday trading, Microsoft and Apple were trading the market-cap lead back and forth as Amazon remained close and Google brought up the rear. MarketWatch photo illustration/Getty Images, iStockphoto, Bloomberg After nearly a decade of Apple Inc. dominance, there is an evolving four-way race among the top tech giants that is pitting the cash cow against a trio of cloud-computing colossuses. On Friday, Microsoft Corp. (MSFT) (MSFT) (MSFT) ended the week as th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>iPhone: New Apple handset with faster 5G internet will not arrive until 2020, report claims - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/iphone-5g-release-date-apple-new-faster-internet-update-a8667116.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG33uTE2kblKqnMBP8jnl84qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/iphone-5g-release-date-apple-new-faster-internet-update-a8667116.html" target="_blank"&gt;iPhone: New Apple handset with faster 5G internet will not arrive until 2020, report claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple might not make a 5G iPhone until 2020, leaving its customers without the latest, fastest internet technology. The new report from Bloomberg comes despite the fact that networks – and most other major manufacturers – are preparing to update for the technology over the next year. It will mean that Apple will be far from the first to the market with the fast new internet technology. Rivals like Samsung are expected to launch their own 5G phones soon, which will theoretically benefit from vastly improved connectivity. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Apple iPhone Sales Off To A Slow Start This Holiday Season - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyswan/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-sales-off-to-a-slow-start-this-holiday-season/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECX_QcHVflT5gTr9TGOgd2MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyswan/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-sales-off-to-a-slow-start-this-holiday-season/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple iPhone Sales Off To A Slow Start This Holiday Season&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The iPhone XS, left, and XS Max are displayed side to side during an event to announce new products at Apple headquarters Wednesday, Sept. 12, 2018, in Cupertino, Calif. (AP Photo/Marcio Jose Sanchez) photo credit: ASSOCIATED PRESS The day after the keynote address, Consumer Purchase Intent Data was already telling us that Apple was going to have a very rough road ahead of it. Since then, the stock has fallen big. More importantly, the holiday shopping season has begun. This gives us fresh consumer insights to tap into from the first week of the season. 2018 Holiday Slowdown? Black Friday...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sharp contractors axe 3,000 staff as iPhone sensor output shifts: union - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sharp-job-cuts/sharp-contractors-axe-3000-staff-as-iphone-sensor-output-shifts-union-idUSKBN1O22RL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL_btwAOHBxwHC8Xdry10MUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 08:37:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sharp-job-cuts/sharp-contractors-axe-3000-staff-as-iphone-sensor-output-shifts-union-idUSKBN1O22RL" target="_blank"&gt;Sharp contractors axe 3,000 staff as iPhone sensor output shifts: union&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly 3,000 foreign workers subcontracted to Sharp Corp have been laid off in central Japan, a labor union said, as the firm moves production of some sensors for Apple iPhones to a Chinese plant owned by its parent Foxconn. The labor union said some of the laid off workers were its members. The union is in Mie Prefecture in central Japan, where Sharp's plant is located. The news of the relocation, first reported by the Nikkei business daily, and the layoffs sent Sharp shares down 5.7 percent on the Tokyo Stock Exchange. This compares to the broader Tokyo market's 2.4 percent decline. The d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Fortnite, Drake and driving test practise app come top of Apple's App Store for 2018 - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-drake-driving-test-best-app-apple-app-store-iphone-2018-a8666621.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLxm7iGgoQk5WhbRFwVOckqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 10:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-drake-driving-test-best-app-apple-app-store-iphone-2018-a8666621.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite, Drake and driving test practise app come top of Apple's App Store for 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple has revealed the most popular of all its apps as 2018 comes to a close. Fortnite is, predictably, the most downloaded free game of the year by people eager to play on their iPhones. The game recently said it had been played by more than 200 million people and is entirely free to download on iOS, as it is on every platform. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/42 5G wireless internet is expected to launch in 2019, with the potential to reach speeds of 50mb/s Getty - 2/42 Uber has halted testing of driverless vehicles after a woman was kil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Study finds half of most popular VPN apps linked to China - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e5567d8a-ee65-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMR5ZOFzwW94Rfzq7_vBAtEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 03:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e5567d8a-ee65-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Study finds half of most popular VPN apps linked to China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than half of the world’s 30 most popular smartphone apps for browsing the internet privately are owned by Chinese companies, according to a new study that raises significant privacy concerns. Seventeen of the apps, which offer to connect users to the internet through a secure tunnel known as a “virtual private network” (VPN), were owned either by Chinese companies or companies appearing to have links to China. Collectively, the apps, which include TurboVPN, VPN Proxy Master, VPN 360 and Snap VPN, have been downloaded more than 100m times on Android devices and iPhones. But the companie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Apple Reveals The Best Apps And Games Of 2018 For iPhone, iPad, Mac - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/04/apple-reveals-the-best-apps-and-games-of-2018-for-iphone-ipad-mac/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8t_F3fSjwVbhz7rM5PNQ8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/04/apple-reveals-the-best-apps-and-games-of-2018-for-iphone-ipad-mac/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Reveals The Best Apps And Games Of 2018 For iPhone, iPad, Mac&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple reveals, each December, which apps have been the year’s top sellers, biggest grossers and most popular for the year. Apple’s choicest apps for 2018 The highlights aren’t just made up of what sits at the top of the charts the longest or sells the most copies. More interesting are what the editorial teams at Apple have chosen as their favorites, across iPhone, iPad, Apple TV and Mac. It also includes podcasts and sales of ebooks. There are different lists for various countries, but here I’m going to take a look at the apps and other items on the US and UK lists, and throw in a choice or...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Suddenly 'Confirms' Radical 5G Galaxy S10 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-5g-release-date-price-cost-verizon-att-upgrade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzHJ9vIrddPWJnbbQDtf0oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-5g-release-date-price-cost-verizon-att-upgrade/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Suddenly 'Confirms' Radical 5G Galaxy S10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We already know Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10 is the biggest shake-up of the Galaxy range in years. There will be four models (including a new, more affordable version), up to six cameras, massive displays and ‘gradient’ colour schemes. And now Samsung isn’t even trying to hide its biggest upgrade of all… In a pair of official announcements which are about as subtle as a brick, both Verizon and AT&amp;T have announced a partnership with Samsung to deliver a ‘5G Galaxy smartphone’ in the first half of 2019. And yes, we know exactly what this is. Galaxy S10 Plus Concept “5G is going to b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Poor iPhone Sales Wipe Out Landmark Achievement As Microsoft Beats Apple - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/03/apple-iphone-xs-iphone-xr-sales-valuation-defeat-microsoft-victory/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdhq3sdcGC6cH2NGileSZQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 23:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/03/apple-iphone-xs-iphone-xr-sales-valuation-defeat-microsoft-victory/" target="_blank"&gt;Poor iPhone Sales Wipe Out Landmark Achievement As Microsoft Beats Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was all going so well for Apple. It was the world’s first trillion-dollar company; it was expanding into a service based revenue model; and three new iPhone handsets were on their way to lead the charge into the future with facial recognition, a new visual identity, and the latest custom-designed chips. Then it moved out of the fast lane and its long-standing competitor took the lead. CEO of Apple Tim Cook unveils new products during a launch event at the Brooklyn Academy of Music (Photo by VCG/VCG via Getty Images) There’s no doubt that the A12 chips inside the latest iPhone devices are...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Music’s arrival on Amazon’s Echo is both surprising and logical - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90275969/apple-musics-arrival-on-amazons-echo-is-both-surprising-and-logical</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA9l-BpPlmHoWNqzL3vJSXEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 17:40:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90275969/apple-musics-arrival-on-amazons-echo-is-both-surprising-and-logical" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Music’s arrival on Amazon’s Echo is both surprising and logical&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last Christmas, we had a platform dilemma at my mom’s house. The only thing she loves more than her iPhone 8 is the Amazon Echo in her living room. She likes to call out old jazz tunes from the couch at night. Even so, she let her Amazon music service subscription expire. She refuses to pay for two music services, and she doesn’t like having two digital assistants in her life. Things will be simpler this Christmas. Apple made the surprising move last week of bringing Apple Music to Amazon’s Alexa-powered devices. Now my mom can standardize on Apple Music—which has some pretty great curated ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Apple will wait until at least 2020 to release a 5G iPhone - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/03/apple-will-wait-least-2020-release-5g-iphone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA4VQPPcjFON2AfYdkPBXgEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:47:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/03/apple-will-wait-least-2020-release-5g-iphone/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple will wait until at least 2020 to release a 5G iPhone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple is said to be holding off releasing an iPhone which can connect to 5G until at least 2020, giving its rivals the chance to steal a lead on the tech giant for speedier service. According to Bloomberg, the next iPhone being released by Apple will not connect to 5G networks, and the company is expected to wait at least a year after the initial deployment of 5G technology. Rivals Huawei and Samsung are readying to launch their own 5G phones next year, offering customers data speeds up to 100 times faster than those available through current 4G networks. Earlier today, Samsung announced i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Apple’s stock bounces back after analyst says investors should buy the dip - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/apples-stock-bounces-back-after-analyst-says-investors-should-buy-the-dip-2018-11-15</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9I8DCiZHisF4t6mciFi08qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/apples-stock-bounces-back-after-analyst-says-investors-should-buy-the-dip-2018-11-15" target="_blank"&gt;Apple’s stock bounces back after analyst says investors should buy the dip&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RATINGS GAME By Tomi Kilgore Shares set to snap 5-day losing streak as market cap climbs back above $900 billion. Getty Images Shares of Apple Inc. rebounded Thursday, as they attempted to snap a five-day skid lower, after Morgan Stanley analyst Katy Huberty said she believes the recent weakness has been an overreaction to sales warnings from smartphone suppliers, which has created a buying opportunity. The iPhone maker’s stock (AAPL) surged 2.5%, after plunging 11% over the previous five sessions. The selloff knocked Apple’s market capitalization below $900 billion for the first time i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Apple's iPhone XR is company's best-selling model, executive says - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-iphone/apples-iphone-xr-is-companys-best-selling-model-executive-says-idUSKCN1NX2QS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM7NyOXJSPaIXMqVbCtDxkcqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 21:29:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-iphone/apples-iphone-xr-is-companys-best-selling-model-executive-says-idUSKCN1NX2QS" target="_blank"&gt;Apple's iPhone XR is company's best-selling model, executive says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple Inc's iPhone XR has been the company's best-selling iPhone model every day since it went on sale in mid-October, a company executive told Reuters on Wednesday. The iPhone XR, which costs $749, was announced alongside two other models, the iPhone XS and XS Max, which start at $999. The XR brings many key features of those phones to a lower price point, and analysts widely viewed it as Apple's effort to bring facial recognition unlocking and its newest processing chip to a wider set of buyers. But a string of negative forecasts from smartphone suppliers in recent weeks has sparked conce...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Project Fi Is Now Available For Almost All Android and iPhones - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/28/project-fi-is-now-available-for-almost-all-android-and-iphones/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKx7xhWN0dbUhx1f6OERbKQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 18:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/28/project-fi-is-now-available-for-almost-all-android-and-iphones/" target="_blank"&gt;Project Fi Is Now Available For Almost All Android and iPhones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Project Fi is now Google Fi. Google’s Project Fi was an attractive alternative to the major mobile service providers like Verizon, AT&amp;T and T-Mobile. Too bad it no longer exists. Project Fi has been rebranded as Google Fi and it’s even better now than it was before. Fi is inexpensive, contract-free and provides international data coverage at no extra cost. The major drawback with Fi was that it was only available on a limited number of phones. That changed today. Google Fi now works with iPhones and most Android phones. Not all Android phones will work with Fi but most of the currently popu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>4 Strategies For Embracing The Digital Detox - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bryancollinseurope/2018/11/29/4-strategies-for-embracing-the-digital-detox/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPZJwDe9et2MSKtJFeMItj4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 19:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bryancollinseurope/2018/11/29/4-strategies-for-embracing-the-digital-detox/" target="_blank"&gt;4 Strategies For Embracing The Digital Detox&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wireless wifi or sign for remote internet access icon vector on white background, Flat style for graphic and web design Credit: Getty Royalty Free I recently read that 11% of internet users tried a digital detox in the past week. When I heard the word “detox,” I immediately thought of a hermit living in a cave, miles from the nearest Ethernet port or phone charger. It struck me as a nice place for deep thinking but also as a completely impractical way of living or working. Then I reconsidered what a digital detox can look like. Use A Dumb Phone “What is Hugh Jackman’s net worth?” That’s jus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>U.S. top court leans towards allowing Apple App Store antitrust suit - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-apple/u-s-top-court-leans-towards-allowing-apple-app-store-antitrust-suit-idUSKCN1NV175</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFuwlzl9T1nxU263C1O1B0UqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 18:10:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-apple/u-s-top-court-leans-towards-allowing-apple-app-store-antitrust-suit-idUSKCN1NV175" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. top court leans towards allowing Apple App Store antitrust suit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. Supreme Court justices on Monday appeared open to letting a lawsuit proceed against Apple Inc (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) that accused it of breaking federal antitrust laws by monopolizing the market for iPhone software applications and causing consumers to overpay. The nine justices heard an hour of arguments in an appeal by the Cupertino, California-based technology company of a lower court's decision to revive the proposed class-action lawsuit filed in federal court in California in 2011 by a group of iPhone users seeking monetary damages. The lawsuit said Apple v...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Walmart Black Friday 2018: Apple iPad Gets A Big Price Cut - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/21/walmart-black-friday-2018-apple-ipad-gets-a-big-price-cut/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHNWqid52-3X-nKuEZe1r9EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/21/walmart-black-friday-2018-apple-ipad-gets-a-big-price-cut/" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart Black Friday 2018: Apple iPad Gets A Big Price Cut&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple products are the Cadillacs of the electronics world. They have a reputation for elegant design, strong performance, and cutting-edge capability that holds up over time. You don’t need to replace an Apple product every year. They don’t go on sale all that often, because of their reputation. Apple iPad This deal from Walmart is that much more striking because of that fact. Starting tonight, the latest model of Apple iPad will be on sale for $80 off! That means you can get a tablet with an impressive 9.7″ screen, powered by an A10 Fusion chip with 64-bit architecture and Embedded M10 cop...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Open Banking: A Wave Bigger Than The Internet And Mobile - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesfinancecouncil/2018/11/19/open-banking-a-wave-bigger-than-the-internet-and-mobile/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMF99fHAogg1GhO2cZgtJcwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesfinancecouncil/2018/11/19/open-banking-a-wave-bigger-than-the-internet-and-mobile/" target="_blank"&gt;Open Banking: A Wave Bigger Than The Internet And Mobile&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty A lot has been written about open banking. In Europe and elsewhere, it’s discussed in the context of regulation, privacy and other considerations. In other circles, like in Latin America, it’s seen as a distant wave. Search people’s expressions in related conversation and they seem to say “Keep an eye on it, but it’s not a pressing concern. It’s a choice we could make some time down the road.” But what if it’s not? What if it’s inevitable? What if it’s the next technical and transformational change in financial services, bigger than the internet and mobile combined? It is precisely th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court could allow suit over Apple iPhone apps' sales - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/d423fc0a45b04b11bab6b1b98a6c4676</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPkTPcB_jAdkKbghmpPbU-AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvqGdAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 21:22:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/d423fc0a45b04b11bab6b1b98a6c4676" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court could allow suit over Apple iPhone apps' sales&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court seemed ready Monday to allow an antitrust lawsuit to go forward that claims Apple has unfairly monopolized the market for the sale of iPhone apps. Apple faced skeptical questions from justices who seemed concerned about the control the Cupertino, California-based company exerts over iPhone users who must purchase software for their smartphones exclusively through its App Store. The arguments dealt with the fruits of technology that, over the past 10 years, have made more than 2 million apps available to iPhone users, but in the courtroom there were also r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Opinion: This Apple true believer just sold all of his firm’s shares - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-apple-true-believer-just-sold-all-of-his-firms-shares-2018-11-20</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFDv-2HN5NeffCszjQQY0y4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-apple-true-believer-just-sold-all-of-his-firms-shares-2018-11-20" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: This Apple true believer just sold all of his firm’s shares&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VITALIY KATSENELSON'S CONTRARIAN EDGE By Vitaliy Katsenelson Slower growth, mature products, and faster competition pressure the stock Getty Images Our firm bought Apple shares for clients’ portfolios in 2013, and we are used to being a contrarian voice when it comes to the stock — we loved it when it was hated. Now we are contrarian again — this time going against the company’s faithful. Here are key reasons why we sold our entire Apple stake just last week: The iPhone, though indispensable, is a mature product. Since introduction of the iPhone X, (AAPL) as been raising prices on iPhones....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>5 Best Walmart Black Friday Phone Deals: Apple, LG &amp; Samsung - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/22/5-best-walmart-black-friday-phone-deals-apple-lg-samsung/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMN72LROnFpC-PTeyHMPnTMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/22/5-best-walmart-black-friday-phone-deals-apple-lg-samsung/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Best Walmart Black Friday Phone Deals: Apple, LG &amp; Samsung&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walmart’s iPhone XS Black Friday deals 2018. If you’re looking to upgrade your phone this Black Friday, then there are some genuinely decent deals floating around. Discounts directly from Samsung and Google are the best right now, but don’t ignore the big retailers. Here are the five best phone deals at Walmart right now. The best deal that Walmart is offering right now is a $400 gift card with the purchase of an iPhone 8, 8+ or iPhone X. But that also comes with a 24-month Verizon, Sprint or AT&amp;T contract, which is something you should avoid if possible. For the latest Samsung and Apple p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How much for that app? U.S. top court hears Apple antitrust dispute - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-apple/how-much-for-that-app-us-top-court-hears-apple-antitrust-dispute-idUSKCN1NU0JV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKW5gfE15ktcpxhhfhKRz8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 16:46:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-apple/how-much-for-that-app-us-top-court-hears-apple-antitrust-dispute-idUSKCN1NU0JV" target="_blank"&gt;How much for that app? U.S. top court hears Apple antitrust dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When iPhone users want to edit blemishes out of their selfies, identify stars and constellations or simply join the latest video game craze, they turn to Apple Inc's App Store, where any software application they buy also includes a 30 percent cut for Apple. That commission is a key issue in a closely watched antitrust case that will reach the U.S. Supreme Court on Monday. The nine justices will hear arguments in Apple's bid to escape damages in a lawsuit accusing it of breaking federal antitrust laws by monopolizing the market for iPhone apps and causing consumers to pay more than they sho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Apple Music to launch on Amazon Echo speakers - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/388c1964-f498-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPstgMP5aVKZ-KfhsKGSi9MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:17:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/388c1964-f498-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Music to launch on Amazon Echo speakers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Hey Siri, make friends with Alexa.” Apple and Amazon appear to be embracing the festive spirit of peace to set aside their years-long rivalry in smart speakers and music streaming. Just in time for Christmas, Apple Music is set to launch on Amazon’s Echo speakers on December 17, the two companies announced on Friday. Echo owners will be able to ask Amazon’s Alexa assistant to play tracks, albums and playlists. The tie-up marks the first time that the Apple streaming service, which the FT reported earlier on Friday now has 56m subscribers around the world, can be controlled by another compa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Apple's Superficial Jihad For Data Privacy Is A Cynical Joke - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonmarkman/2018/11/24/apples-superficial-jihad-for-data-privacy-is-a-cynical-joke/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDtIlMAoB_ujSfoTcZDUItcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonmarkman/2018/11/24/apples-superficial-jihad-for-data-privacy-is-a-cynical-joke/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple's Superficial Jihad For Data Privacy Is A Cynical Joke&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tim Cook understands rebranding. He transformed Steve Jobs’ scrappy, innovative company into a sleepy, iterative cash cow. Now he’s trying to change the rules for big tech. The Apple chief executive was in Brussels on Wednesday. He wants worldwide regulators to dramatically curtail the amount of personal data that technology companies can collect. Data protection with businessman on a black background In the current climate, the message hits the right notes. Cook is casting Apple as a privacy warrior, a wiry David fighting the good fight against the data industrial complex set up for the be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Target Vs Best Buy Sales: Biggest Black Friday 2018 Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/19/target-black-friday-2018-best-buy-sales-iphone-galaxy-xbox-deals-shipping-times-redcard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEPJefItXNcGAw-Wj-gBEzQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/19/target-black-friday-2018-best-buy-sales-iphone-galaxy-xbox-deals-shipping-times-redcard/" target="_blank"&gt;Target Vs Best Buy Sales: Biggest Black Friday 2018 Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. What are the best Black Friday deals? With just four days to go, Best Buy’s impressive 52-page ad and Target’s bold 47-page ad confirm these retailers have many of them. But who comes out on top? There are some big differences and some easy mistakes to make. So let’s make sure you know where you shop. This is the fifth in my Black Friday Vs Series. Working alongside ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Loop: Poor iPhone Sales Panic Apple, Sudden iPhone XS Price Cut, iPad Pro's Big Mistake - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/30/apple-news-headlines-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-price-cut-sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHwqJ09sU9ixS02ssuHUalEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 23:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/30/apple-news-headlines-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-price-cut-sales/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Loop: Poor iPhone Sales Panic Apple, Sudden iPhone XS Price Cut, iPad Pro's Big Mistake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at another week of news from Cupertino, this week’s Apple Loop includes low iPhone sales, Apple pushing a positive iPhone XR message, more iPhone price cuts, the good news around no iPhone sales information, why the iPad Pro smart connector has failed, the latest Apple patents, the App Store heading to the Supreme Court, and Project Fi coming to iPhone. Apple Loop is here to remind you of a few of the very many discussions that have happened around Apple over the last seven days (and you can read my weekly digest of Android news here on Forbes). More iPhone Discounts To F...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple removes over 700 apps from Chinese App Store - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/29/apple-removes-700-apps-chinese-app-store/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDzdfsc6X-AywGOerI7oo9gqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 21:10:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/29/apple-removes-700-apps-chinese-app-store/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple removes over 700 apps from Chinese App Store&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple has removed hundreds of iPhone apps from its App Store in China, in the company’s latest crackdown in one of its biggest markets. More than 700 apps have been removed from the Chinese App Store in recent days, according to local reports. They include apps developed by Sogou, a Chinese alternative to Google, and Pinduodo, an online retail app. The apps have been banned for flouting App Store rules that prohibit companies from installing software updates on their apps without Apple’s permission, it is understood. Apple requires that app updates, such as new features or security improvem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Facebook admits telling employees not to use iPhones, while noting Mark Zuckerberg's disagreement with Apple CEO - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/facebook-iphones-employees-mark-zuckerberg-android-apple-tim-cook-a8634791.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELP7vRyKHKSw4Il8dZtvt9EqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/facebook-iphones-employees-mark-zuckerberg-android-apple-tim-cook-a8634791.html" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook admits telling employees not to use iPhones, while noting Mark Zuckerberg's disagreement with Apple CEO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has admitted that employees are encouraged to use Android smartphones instead of iPhones, but denies claims that this is because Apple CEO Tim Cook "infuriated" Mark Zuckerberg. The Facebook founder ordered executives to not use iPhones after Mr Cook criticised firms who monetise their customers' data, according to The New York Times. In a blog post responding to the report, the social network acknowledged that there had been disagreements between Mr Zuckerberg and Mr Cook in the past, though did not say explicitly that this contributed to the firm's phone policy. "Tim Cook has con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>US Top Court Open to Antitrust Suit Against Apple App Store - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-top-court-open-to-antitrust-suit-against-apple-app-store-/4674271.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEICvQFvxN1tozQ3OjHJ7YRUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwip0i</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 17:03:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-top-court-open-to-antitrust-suit-against-apple-app-store-/4674271.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Top Court Open to Antitrust Suit Against Apple App Store&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. Supreme Court justices on Monday appeared open to letting a lawsuit proceed against Apple Inc that accused it of breaking federal antitrust laws by monopolizing the market for iPhone software applications and causing consumers to overpay. The nine justices heard an hour of arguments in an appeal by the Cupertino, California-based technology company of a lower court's decision to revive the proposed class-action lawsuit filed in federal court in California in 2011 by a group of iPhone users seeking monetary damages. The lawsuit said Apple violated federal antitrust laws by requiring app...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Magic Leap: face time - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d405f5d6-ec0f-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZ-_fteFPYSLYvOZPT5GAEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 17:26:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d405f5d6-ec0f-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57" target="_blank"&gt;Magic Leap: face time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secretive US start-up Magic Leap is known for three things: making “mixed reality” headsets that combine virtual images with the real world, raising money from top-tier investors such as Google, Alibaba and Saudi Arabia’s wealth fund, and working 3,000 miles away from Silicon Valley in Florida. The distance keeps prying eyes away, but has proved no barrier to funding. So far the company has raised $2.3bn. CB Insights values it at slightly less than $5bn. Believers say Magic Leap hardware may replace smartphones. Who needs a screen when the internet is all around you? The company has already...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Walmart's Worst Black Friday 2018 Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/16/walmart-black-friday-2018-sales-iphone-apple-samsung-galaxy-xbox-ps4-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFLJpICSufl0Gve-glUHR4MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 01:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/16/walmart-black-friday-2018-sales-iphone-apple-samsung-galaxy-xbox-ps4-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart's Worst Black Friday 2018 Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. Walmart released its coveted 32-page Black Friday ad last week with sales on TVs, Apple iPhones, Samsung Galaxy smartphones and tablets, and the Xbox One, PS4 and Nintendo Switch. The ad contains some great deals, but there are also some very high profile ones you need to know should be avoided… Note: While I call these Walmart’s “worst” deals that doesn’t mean they ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Explaining The Recent Apple Selloff, And Why The Stock Looks Undervalued - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/23/explaining-the-recent-apple-selloff-and-why-the-stock-looks-undervalued/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHI7c4odEVfxaGAEmeLKNkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 13:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/23/explaining-the-recent-apple-selloff-and-why-the-stock-looks-undervalued/" target="_blank"&gt;Explaining The Recent Apple Selloff, And Why The Stock Looks Undervalued&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signage is displayed after an Apple Inc. event in the Brooklyn borough of New York, U.S., on Tuesday, Oct. 30, 2018. Photographer: Jeenah Moon/Bloomberg Apple’s stock has seen a sharp sell-off in recent weeks, falling by close to 25% from all-time highs seen in October. The declines have largely been driven by reports that the company is cutting back production orders for the iPhone XS, XS Max, and XR, casting doubt on the uptake of the company’s newest devices. While the concerns are legitimate, considering that the iPhone accounts for about two-thirds of Apple’s revenues, we believe that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>5 Phones That Will Actually Last An Entire Day At A Music Festival - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/isisbriones/2018/11/30/5-phones-that-will-actually-last-an-entire-day-at-a-music-festival/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMdUl21z1eWyXd9-S0HhLkgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 01:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/isisbriones/2018/11/30/5-phones-that-will-actually-last-an-entire-day-at-a-music-festival/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Phones That Will Actually Last An Entire Day At A Music Festival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Group of friends taking a selfie at a music festival. Carrying around a ton of gear at a music festival is the worst. Not only will it take longer for you to go through security lines, but having to keep up with everything can really slow you down. The essentials really include your phone, wristband, ID and if you want to save money, a water bottle. Apart from those basic needs, many people tend to lug around unnecessary things like portable phone chargers and battery packs. Let’s leave those days behind by investing in phones that are capable of actually lasting you an entire day of festiv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Cyber Monday 2018: Best Walmart Deals You Can Still Buy - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/27/cyber-monday-2018-best-walmart-iphone-microsoft-xbox-one-x-nintendo-hd-tv-deals-you-can-still-buy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEplRdA1NCBVVzte-Zn8IRMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 02:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/27/cyber-monday-2018-best-walmart-iphone-microsoft-xbox-one-x-nintendo-hd-tv-deals-you-can-still-buy/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyber Monday 2018: Best Walmart Deals You Can Still Buy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. Thought you missed out on the Black Friday and Cyber Monday sales? Think again. Walmart has joined Amazon’s extended sale by announcing the extension of its best Cyber Monday deals. These are the bargains you can still buy… Walmart’s Cyber Monday 2018 sales continue Walmart continues to offer its Cyber Monday free two-day shipping for milli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Black Friday 2018 UK Event Revealed: Big-Value Gift Cards With iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple Watch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/22/apple-black-friday-2018-uk-event-revealed-big-value-gift-cards-with-iphone-ipad-mac-apple-watch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMBHAHmWHwIE-FdzLlHr5u8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/22/apple-black-friday-2018-uk-event-revealed-big-value-gift-cards-with-iphone-ipad-mac-apple-watch/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Black Friday 2018 UK Event Revealed: Big-Value Gift Cards With iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Apple Shopping Event is this year a four-day affair, that’s three days more than usual. And while it’s often on Thanksgiving itself, this time it’ll run from Black Friday through Cyber Monday. It offers gift cards with some purchases, all at least the same value as last year’s event, sometimes more. Apple Watch Nike+ and its strap colours So, what’s available and should you buy? After all, my colleague Gordon Kelly has pointed out that Apple often limits its offers and looking elsewhere often yields better prices. Check out his rundown of it and alternative offers. So, here are all the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Taiwan's Tech Giants Chase Apple Orders To Survive World Smartphone Slowdown - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphjennings/2018/11/30/taiwans-tech-giants-chase-apple-orders-to-survive-world-smartphone-slowdown/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDLows4YJ-6XLT9Pslsk2WwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphjennings/2018/11/30/taiwans-tech-giants-chase-apple-orders-to-survive-world-smartphone-slowdown/" target="_blank"&gt;Taiwan's Tech Giants Chase Apple Orders To Survive World Smartphone Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An employee, right, demonstrates the camera function on the iPhone XS Max, right, and the iPhone XS at an Apple store during its launch in Hong Kong on Sept. 21, 2018. Orders from Apple may help Taiwanese tech firms ride out this year’s slump in global smartphone sales. (Photo: Anthony Kwan/Bloomberg) Forecasters are all pointing the same direction: Smartphone sales will drop globally this year for the first time and probably won’t grow again until around 2020 when 5G telecom networks start spreading in a big way. Smartphone shipments will likely fall 1.3% this year compared to 2017, partly...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Americans spent over $3 billion last year fixing their smartphone screens - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/americans-spent-over-3-billion-last-year-fixing-their-smartphone-screens-2018-11-20</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDpOVXjGHc-VFHa8ydmFOwsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/americans-spent-over-3-billion-last-year-fixing-their-smartphone-screens-2018-11-20" target="_blank"&gt;Americans spent over $3 billion last year fixing their smartphone screens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jacob Passy Some states have considered ‘right-to-repair’ legislation allowing consumers to repair their own phones without violating their warranties Replacing a cracked smartphone screen could set you back as much as $329, depending on the model. Getty Images/iStockphoto That cracked smartphone screen? It will likely cost you more than you’d think. Two in three smartphone owners reported damage to their phones in the past year, according to a study released Tuesday by Allstate subsidiary SquareTrade (ALL) Cracked screens were the most common form of damage, accounting for 29% of damage...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>The Nomad Charging Wallet Doubles As a Phone Battery - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-nomad-charging-wallet-doubles-as-a-phone-battery</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPkd9btnOu-JXwyb91FALfQqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:19:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-nomad-charging-wallet-doubles-as-a-phone-battery" target="_blank"&gt;The Nomad Charging Wallet Doubles As a Phone Battery&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smartphones are more powerful than ever, but battery technology hasn’t improved much in the past decade or so. You’d be pretty lucky to get more than a day or two out of your phone, and if you’re using it heavily—like when you’re traveling—you might not even make it through dinner. As a result, portable battery packs have become quite popular, but they aren’t exactly stylish...or easy to carry around. That’s why Nomad, in addition to their phone cases and other accessories, developed a series of charging wallets for the iPhone. Constructed with Horween leather, these wallets should develop ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Nubia X Review: Two Screens, Two Fingerprint Scanners, Too Weird? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/19/nubia-x-review-two-screens-two-fingerprint-scanners-too-weird/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMRKplmUcXBUJVI9HMccqAkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/19/nubia-x-review-two-screens-two-fingerprint-scanners-too-weird/" target="_blank"&gt;Nubia X Review: Two Screens, Two Fingerprint Scanners, Too Weird?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nubia X has a screen on the front and back of the phone. To what end will Chinese brands go to avoid needing a notch? Vivo designed a phone with a tiny pop-up camera module half a year ago. Then came Oppo with a phone whose entire forehead elevated up and down. And last month, Honor and Xiaomi each introduced slider phones just days apart. In between, there are smaller Shenzhen brands like Bluboo who experimented with a flip-over camera system. Nubia, however, may have come up with the most extreme idea yet. Its latest phone — a surprise release from a brand that was hit with a near dea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Learning Data Science and Machine Learning A On Mobile Phone With CoCalc And Juno - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gregoryferenstein/2018/11/30/learning-data-science-and-machine-learning-a-on-mobile-phone-with-cocalc-and-juno/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGKtWHm6-pRRZREG9JSVIQ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gregoryferenstein/2018/11/30/learning-data-science-and-machine-learning-a-on-mobile-phone-with-cocalc-and-juno/" target="_blank"&gt;Learning Data Science and Machine Learning A On Mobile Phone With CoCalc And Juno&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CoCalc in Juno for a Udacity assignment One of the most difficult things about learning a new skill is finding time to study. Being able to complete assignments in between meetings or while traveling can make all the difference in the ability to make regular progress. Unfortunately, none of the online courses in programming, data science and machine learning I’ve taken over this past year have great mobile solutions. The best I’ve seen is Udacity.com, which built an online coding environment for some of its quizzes, but not for the more realistic editing environments involving complex tasks...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The most downloaded iOS apps of 2018 - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/tech/ios-most-popular-apps/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK6-ogLQyl2nixNIA8UWcA0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:02:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/tech/ios-most-popular-apps/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The most downloaded iOS apps of 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social media dominated the top apps of the year. On Tuesday, Apple unveiled its list of the most downloaded iPhone apps of 2018. Topping the list is YouTube, followed by Instagram, Snapchat, Messenger and Facebook, respectively. Bitmoji — a Snapchat-owned app that lets users create an emoji that looks like them — dropped to sixth place on the list. It was the most downloaded app last year. It's been a challenging year for some social media companies, such as Facebook, which has faced criticism over privacy issues, data misuse, misinformation and election meddling on its platform. Neverthele...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item></channel></rss>