<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Counter-Strike: Global Offensive - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR2d6Y0hZeWVoSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:44:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Facebook Loves E-Sports - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/jonmarkman/2016/11/15/facebook-loves-e-sports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKe45vxoOKAZrspd396IXTkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/jonmarkman/2016/11/15/facebook-loves-e-sports/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook Loves E-Sports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Billionaires and technology behemoths see something in e-Sports. Now Facebook is taking a harder look, too. Recently The Information reported the social media giant firm has been in talks about streaming rights for Vainglory, a popular mobile e-sport title. You can’t blame them. Consulting firm Deloitte forecasts e-sports will generate $500 million in sales in 2016 with more than 150 million viewers. That’s up from $400 million in 2015. And Facebook already hooked up with Activision Blizzard (ATVI) subsidiary Major League Gaming back in May to stream e-sports tournaments. Clearly, Facebook ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Twitter to stream eSports events - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2017/03/02/technology/twitter-esports-stream/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF93x9J2MAP96dyKzet3kTQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 17:20:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2017/03/02/technology/twitter-esports-stream/" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter to stream eSports events&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This Saturday the highly anticipated Intel Extreme Masters tournaments will be held in Katowice, Poland. And now eSports fans have a new way to watch the action -- on Twitter. It's the first of 15 eSports events that Twitter will air as part of its just-announced partnership with ESL, the world's largest eSports company, and DreamHack, which is touted as the world's largest computer festival. Related: eSports business is booming Twitter will live stream more than 1,500 hours of programming from ESL One, Intel Extreme Masters and DreamHack tournaments. The deal is the latest in a series of p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Fnatic Esports Brand Receives Over $7 Million In Financing - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2017/04/10/fnatic-esports-brand-receives-over-7-million-in-financing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDhHRaCb7YMPLPOvPMX70FEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2017/04/10/fnatic-esports-brand-receives-over-7-million-in-financing/" target="_blank"&gt;Fnatic Esports Brand Receives Over $7 Million In Financing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of data points in the realm of esports that are difficult to verify, including how much revenue is being received by the industry on an annual basis, as well as what accounts for said revenues. One area where there is no dispute in quantifying esports’ success is in the space of raising funds, which many esports teams have been able to accomplish with speed and skill. The latest leading esports brand to raise significant capital is Fnatic, which announces a financing round of more than $7 million. Investors include Raptor Group, owners of AS Roma and the Boston Celtics; Hers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>What Is Going To Happen In The Esports Industry In 2017? - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/paularmstrongtech/2017/01/17/what-is-going-to-happen-in-the-esports-industry-in-2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELTuesysUNxNyK4BPha0uzMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/paularmstrongtech/2017/01/17/what-is-going-to-happen-in-the-esports-industry-in-2017/" target="_blank"&gt;What Is Going To Happen In The Esports Industry In 2017?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOURCE: Red Bull As Theresa May outlined her plans for the UK to hard-exit Europe, the Mobile Games Forum kicked off in London today with a solid international lineup from the likes of Rovio, Bandai Namco, Twitch, King and a huge delegation from Korea, to name a few. Revenue, monetization and retention were unsurprisingly key themes of the day but surprisingly esports received more interest than VR. I spoke with several of the executives at the show about what – in their opinion – 2017 and beyond holds for the world of esports: Companies Need To Focus On First-Time Churners Motti Colman, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>YouTube makes its biggest e-sports bet with FACEIT streaming deal - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-alphabet-youtube-faceit-idUSKBN16N257</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN1ObnM2Nu1JSuyS569NkTEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 15:05:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-alphabet-youtube-faceit-idUSKBN16N257" target="_blank"&gt;YouTube makes its biggest e-sports bet with FACEIT streaming deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Anya George Tharakan (Reuters) - Alphabet Inc's YouTube is doubling down on the lucrative business of competitive gaming, where players square off on virtual games for big prize money in tournaments. The video site on Thursday made its biggest investment in the business to date, signing a multi-year deal with e-sports platform FACEIT to stream its competitive gaming league, the Esports Championship Series (ECS). E-sports has been touted as one of the next big things in live events, drawing millions of spectators online. Traditional media companies and big videogame publishers are all cla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>World's best gamers do battle as 'eSports' takes off Down Under - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-05-07/worlds-best-gamers-do-battle-in-sydney/8504550</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDvLo_wFEWxt6HmIH1ckRFUqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 08:17:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-05-07/worlds-best-gamers-do-battle-in-sydney/8504550" target="_blank"&gt;World's best gamers do battle as 'eSports' takes off Down Under&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world's best were at Sydney's Olympic Park once again this weekend, but the battles were in cyberspace rather than on a sporting field. Forty top professional gamers took part in the Intel Extreme Masters — a mecca for video game enthusiasts. About 10,000 keen gamers packed the precinct at the weekend to watch the stars play Counter-Strike — a multiplayer first-person shooter that pits teams against each other in simulated battle — while hundreds of thousands more tuned in from overseas. Nick Vanzetti, the managing director of ESL Australia, the local arm of the world's largest "eSports...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Activision, EA, Ubisoft And Others Should Be Going To Bat For Their Demonetized YouTubers - Forbes Now</title><link>//www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/08/23/activision-ea-ubisoft-and-others-should-be-going-to-bat-for-their-demonetized-youtubers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIrqPmVLchjZj5mcX8J8zMUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 15:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="//www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/08/23/activision-ea-ubisoft-and-others-should-be-going-to-bat-for-their-demonetized-youtubers/" target="_blank"&gt;Activision, EA, Ubisoft And Others Should Be Going To Bat For Their Demonetized YouTubers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Destiny/Call of Duty Yesterday, I published an article about the current plight of YouTubers attempting to cover any sort of video game involving guns, ie. the vast majority of the most popular games in the industry. Over the past few months and weeks, things have regressed to a point where practically any video that features third or first-person shooter content is being flagged as “not suitable for advertisers” and demonetized instantly. That includes videos with guns in the title or thumbnail, but also even just footage featuring those games. I talked to some of the YouTubers affected by...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Beyond The Void's E-Sports Game Launching World's First MOBA Gaming ICO - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/rogeraitken/2016/10/24/beyond-the-voids-e-sports-game-launching-worlds-first-moba-gaming-ico/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANL6Qx060Qs9nehpvcMKpQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 18:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/rogeraitken/2016/10/24/beyond-the-voids-e-sports-game-launching-worlds-first-moba-gaming-ico/" target="_blank"&gt;Beyond The Void's E-Sports Game Launching World's First MOBA Gaming ICO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond The Void, a new ‘free-to-play’ RTS-MOBA game could be poised to storm the gaming industry backed by an initial coin offering (ICO) and Ethereum blockchain tokens, which are being presented in a gaming partnership at this week’s ‘Money2020’ and CoinAgenda industry events in Las Vegas, the world’s gambling capital. But it may also have an uphill struggle to beat the market leaders in the space. Specifically, Beyond The Void is launching an ICO in partnership with decentralized conglomerate OpenLedger and crowdfunding group, who are on a mission to take the best and brightest blockchain...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'Rainbow Six Siege' Hitting 20M Players Is Astonishing In The Current Shooter Market - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/08/05/rainbow-six-siege-hitting-20m-players-is-astonishing-in-the-current-shooter-market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJo87EjrW26oOl7Yw3DUeiYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 16:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/08/05/rainbow-six-siege-hitting-20m-players-is-astonishing-in-the-current-shooter-market/" target="_blank"&gt;'Rainbow Six Siege' Hitting 20M Players Is Astonishing In The Current Shooter Market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rainbow Six Siege Ubisoft has found great success with the Tom Clancy brand as of late with The Division setting sales records for a new IP and Ghost Recon Wildlands overperforming expectations. But there’s no better example of a game exceeding its potential than what we’ve seen with Rainbow Six Siege. The strategic shooter now has 20M registered players. “Our community is growing and so is our ambition to make Siege a shooter that is here to stay,” says Product Director Nicolas Lefebvre. For a game that seems to fly under the radar in most gaming circles, there are an incredible number of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>State 'Jock Taxes' May Start Applying To Esports Players - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2017/02/03/state-jock-taxes-may-start-applying-to-esports-players/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEASedDC85mWNLQhOuSQSf3kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2017/02/03/state-jock-taxes-may-start-applying-to-esports-players/" target="_blank"&gt;State 'Jock Taxes' May Start Applying To Esports Players&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo: Carlton Beener/ESL) Professional competitive esports players consider themselves professional athletes. Their games require mental and physical capabilities that are extraordinary as compared with the average gamer. They are signed to professional teams. They practice, compete and experience sports-related injuries just like LeBron James, Aaron Rodgers and Serena Williams. They get paid to play, just like Curry and Messi (well, maybe not just like, but you get the point). They are paid salaries and can win prize money. There are endorsement dollars for some, too. Just about ev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>AlphaDraft Closes, Marking End For Fantasy Esports? - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2016/10/20/alphadraft-closes-marking-end-to-fantasy-esports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELuebWHoPb7Irm8sQqd3zFUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 17:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2016/10/20/alphadraft-closes-marking-end-to-fantasy-esports/" target="_blank"&gt;AlphaDraft Closes, Marking End For Fantasy Esports?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The esports industry, which is expected to produce $493 million in revenues in 2016, does not guarantee success for all entrants. One example of a company making an early exit is AlphaDraft, a fantasy esports site that at one time was a darling for investments and even achieved being acquired within a couple years of its founding. AlphaDraft will end its operations on October 21, according to an email distributed to its user base. Fantasy esports has not caught on with the general public, despite the successes of the esports industry. (Photo by Yuya Shino/Getty Images for TOKYO GAME SHOW) “...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>When football met eSports: PSG's tale of two sports at one club - CNN</title><link>http://edition.cnn.com/2016/12/14/sport/esports-football-paris-saint-germain-psg-bora-yellowstar-kim/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC5Q0tfusKso-1LuQPEwCzQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 10:08:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://edition.cnn.com/2016/12/14/sport/esports-football-paris-saint-germain-psg-bora-yellowstar-kim/" target="_blank"&gt;When football met eSports: PSG's tale of two sports at one club&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Paris Saint-Germain's training ground, players are hard at work training for their big European competition in 2017. But this isn't in the French capital, it's in Berlin. And the players won't be facing Barcelona in the Champions League, but will play the likes of Schalke 04 and Team LDLC in the European "League of Legends" Challenger Series where teams face off in the online battle arena video game. After all, this isn't a football side -- it's an eSports team. PSG eSports is the electronic counterpart to France's most successful soccer side of recent years. It was established in Octobe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Immortals CEO Noah Whinston On The Unstable 'Dota 2' Scene - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2017/04/26/immortals-ceo-noah-whinston-on-the-unstable-dota-2-scene/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFf5ABQc3nnWtXYm-IQDji0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2017/04/26/immortals-ceo-noah-whinston-on-the-unstable-dota-2-scene/" target="_blank"&gt;Immortals CEO Noah Whinston On The Unstable 'Dota 2' Scene&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immortals CEO Noah Whinston Immortals has grown from a new organisation with a lot of financial backing into one of the biggest eSports teams in the world in just a couple of years. While few teams have had the financial backing that they have received it is still an impressive feat, and one that few have managed to replicate. After launching with a North American League of Legends team Immortals has quickly expanded into Counter-Strike: Global Offensive, Overwatch, Smash Bros and Vainglory. The player roster covers most of the major eSports, with the majority of the teams and players compe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>How Five Brazilian Esports Champions Won $1.8 Million Playing 'Counter-Strike: GO' Last Year - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2017/01/27/how-five-brazilian-esports-champions-won-2-million-playing-counter-strike-global-offensive-last-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENu1ZTVHmTPCMUXdOI-omZIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2017/01/27/how-five-brazilian-esports-champions-won-2-million-playing-counter-strike-global-offensive-last-year/" target="_blank"&gt;How Five Brazilian Esports Champions Won $1.8 Million Playing 'Counter-Strike: GO' Last Year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: MLG/Graphics: Nick DeSantis, Forbes Staff Long an esport dominated by European clubs like Fnatic and Virtus.pro, Counter-Strike: Global Offensive saw the rise and reign of an all-Brazilian squad in 2016. The five-man team carried two organizations into the top three of our prize money list and collectively earned $1.8 million. Here’s the story of their year. Photo: Sebastian Ekman, DreamHack/Graphics: Nick DeSantis, Forbes Staff Six days after replacing two of its players and its coach, Luminosity make a Cinderella run at the FACEIT Stage 3 Finals. Falling to Swedish legends, Fnati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Sony And ESL Partnering To Deliver New NBA 2K eSports Event - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2016/10/22/sony-and-esl-partnering-to-deliver-new-nba-2k-esports-event/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHCuXb3RiftB3D4VVgkR7X4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 20:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2016/10/22/sony-and-esl-partnering-to-deliver-new-nba-2k-esports-event/" target="_blank"&gt;Sony And ESL Partnering To Deliver New NBA 2K eSports Event&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Saturday, Sony Entertainment’s Vice President of Brand Marketing John Koller announced a new partnership with the Electronic Sports League (ESL) to deliver a new eSports tournament feature for the PlayStation 4. image from 2K Sports The first event will be an NBA 2K17 tournament that runs from October 27 thru November 26. This event is open to anyone with a PS4, a copy of NBA 2K17 and an ESL account. Major cup rounds will take place every Saturday. The Top 3 winners will receive a Sony branded prize pack, such as a DualShock 4 and other PlayStation gear. The signup process for the tourna...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>NBA 2K's ELeague Could Change The Competitive Gaming Scene - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2017/02/09/nba-2ks-eleague-could-change-the-competitive-gaming-scene/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGXHRZ55Pdp2h59ui9nxuKUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 06:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2017/02/09/nba-2ks-eleague-could-change-the-competitive-gaming-scene/" target="_blank"&gt;NBA 2K's ELeague Could Change The Competitive Gaming Scene&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Basketball Association and 2K Sports have teamed up for an official eSports league and the competitive gaming world may never be the same. image: Take-Two On Thursday, the NBA and Take-Two Interactive Software announced their plans to launch the NBA 2K eLeague, per a news release provided to Forbes. It will be a professional gaming league backed by the NBA. This is the first time in history a competitive gaming league will be operated by an American professional sports league. The new venture is scheduled to start in 2018. The teams will be run by real NBA organizations. Those ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Marielle "Layla" Louise Becomes The First Female 'Dota 2' Player To Compete In A Major Qualifier - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2017/03/08/marielle-layla-louise-becomes-the-first-female-dota-2-player-to-compete-in-a-major-qualifier/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPpyZyEpr6djvDX6AA7TbdEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 21:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2017/03/08/marielle-layla-louise-becomes-the-first-female-dota-2-player-to-compete-in-a-major-qualifier/" target="_blank"&gt;Marielle "Layla" Louise Becomes The First Female 'Dota 2' Player To Compete In A Major Qualifier&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Credit: Valve After placing in the top two in the first North American open qualifier, female Dota 2 player Marielle “Layla” Louise and her team Wheel Whreck While Whistling secured a spot in the closed qualifier for the Kiev Major. This makes her the first woman to compete in a closed qualifier for a major Dota 2 event. Despite being the first female to make it this far in a Valve hosted competition, Layla is actually a somewhat unknown player. She has played for some lower tier teams in North America, but Wheel Whreck While Whistling is the first one of any real note. Wheel Whreck While W...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>The rise of eSports: are addiction and corruption the price of its success? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2017/jun/16/top-addiction-young-people-gaming-esports</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEcQPRSCAdckRoCG3vvFRDYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 11:24:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2017/jun/16/top-addiction-young-people-gaming-esports" target="_blank"&gt;The rise of eSports: are addiction and corruption the price of its success?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you had been away from the planet for the past quarter of a century, one of the few things you might find comfortingly familiar on your return is the world of sport. While the digital revolution has transformed the way we shop, chat, date, do politics and consume culture, sport looks largely unchanged. From football to cricket to golf, it’s still the same old staples, hitting a ball into a hole or goal or over a boundary. There hasn’t been a major new sport invented for more than a century. Or has there? In the East End of London, Sam Mathews is holding court at Fnatic’s HQ, otherwise kn...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The Gfinity Elite Draft - What happens when esports embrace traditional sports methodology - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/gfinity-elite-draft-happens-esports-embrace-traditional-sports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOknCTbJ9Uu1qxvXjqMF1nkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 19:14:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/gfinity-elite-draft-happens-esports-embrace-traditional-sports/" target="_blank"&gt;The Gfinity Elite Draft - What happens when esports embrace traditional sports methodology&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gfinityis the UK’s leading esports event organiser. Over the past three years it has hosted major events in almost every competitive video game out there, from Call of Duty to Splatoon. Its permanent arena in London houses scores of events each year, some of which are entirely Gfinity run while others are in partnership with the likes of Activision, OMEN by HP or Microsoft. But after years of mixing between partner events and one off Gfinity showcases they finally have a new plan to establish themselves as a global player in esports. The Gfinity Elite Series is a ten week competition that i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fnatic, Echo Fox, NRG, Rogue And Immortals Sign Up For Mobile Esports - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2017/02/09/major-esports-teams-sign-on-for-mobile-competition/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJOmyMbf4oq28XhQaHWKXYsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2017/02/09/major-esports-teams-sign-on-for-mobile-competition/" target="_blank"&gt;Fnatic, Echo Fox, NRG, Rogue And Immortals Sign Up For Mobile Esports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teams like Fnatic, Echo Fox, NRG, Rogue and Immortals are quickly becoming household names in the rapidly growing world of esports. As such, it is a big coup for Super Evil Megacorp to welcome the aforesaid teams into its leading mobile esport environment Vainglory. Former NBA player Rick Fox is adding his esports team Echo Fox into Super Evil Megacorp’s Vainglory competition. (Photo by John Lamparski/Getty Images for Advertising Week New York) “In some ways this is not a piece of news that in itself, overnight, means billions of dollars; however, it’s a very important sign of the times and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Bud Light Brings Back Esports All-Stars Program - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2017/05/25/bud-light-brings-back-esports-all-stars-program/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLj7z39Ajo8xeZZKh0eNoEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 11:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2017/05/25/bud-light-brings-back-esports-all-stars-program/" target="_blank"&gt;Bud Light Brings Back Esports All-Stars Program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A screen shot of Ninja streaming on Bud Light’s esports channel. More than 3.6 million minutes of esports competition on Twitch were watched with Bud Light branding attached during the 2016 Bud Light All-Stars program, and there have been over 433,000 YouTube views of the documentaries made about the Bud Light All-Stars. With a passion to penetrate the market of esports enthusiasts, Bud Light decided to bring its All-Stars program back for a second year with the official announcement coming later today. “We recognized the importance, scope and opportunity in esports, and we recognized the p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>XLIVE -- Festivals, eSports and Live Events Get Their Own Conference - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/bradauerbach/2016/12/30/xlive-festivals-esports-and-live-events-get-their-own-conference/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECMMnD2nQMFNtLDXENBGm8kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 02:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/bradauerbach/2016/12/30/xlive-festivals-esports-and-live-events-get-their-own-conference/" target="_blank"&gt;XLIVE -- Festivals, eSports and Live Events Get Their Own Conference&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ubiquity of music festivals, the growth of eSports and the realization that consumers increasingly value experiential activities were the underlying themes (and raisons d’etre) at XLIVE 2016. The recent conference in Las Vegas covered all aspects of a rapidly expanding business sector. The most out-of-this-world exhibitor was Sky Canvas. Founded by a Japanese physicist, the company will be launching a satellite in the next year or so. Customers, for an undisclosed amount, can schedule a meteor shower during a 30 minute window almost anywhere in the world. With a tag line ‘shooting stars...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Here Are 20 Great First-Person Shooters You Can Get Dirt Cheap During The Steam Summer Sale - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/06/28/here-are-20-great-first-person-shooters-you-can-get-dirt-cheap-during-the-steam-summer-sale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENNVUfQwOjYWYTtz5gnwjpQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/06/28/here-are-20-great-first-person-shooters-you-can-get-dirt-cheap-during-the-steam-summer-sale/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are 20 Great First-Person Shooters You Can Get Dirt Cheap During The Steam Summer Sale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DOOM is 50% off during this year’s Steam Summer Sale. The Steam Summer Sale keeps chugging along, and I keep scouring it for good deals on games I enjoy. In this installment of our Steam Summer Sale deal finder, I give you first-person shooters. I’m a big FPS player and there’s a ton of these on Steam. I was going to do 10, but then it blew up to 15 and then…well, you get the picture. There’s actually a few extras in here, so the total is even higher. As long as you enjoy shooting stuff with a mouse and keyboard, there will be something here for you. Great deals abound to help drain your wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>ELEAGUE Nabs Snickers As Latest Esports Sponsor - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/alexkay/2016/10/31/eleague-nabs-snickers-as-latest-esports-sponsor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC5FSNHGhMOz_Jd_bra3h1cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/alexkay/2016/10/31/eleague-nabs-snickers-as-latest-esports-sponsor/" target="_blank"&gt;ELEAGUE Nabs Snickers As Latest Esports Sponsor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second season of ELEAGUE recently began play and now has a new partner involved with its televised Counter-Strike: Global Offensive action. It was announced that Snickers has signed on as an official marketing partner with Turner and WME IMG’s joint esports venture. According to the Esports Inquirer, Snickers will be the “official chocolate bar” of the league and will sponsor a number of segments and air spots during telecasts. Seth Ladetsky, VP of Turner Ad Sales, believes that this partnership is a win-win for both parties: We are excited to welcome SNICKERS into ELEAGUE and to be wor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>‘Overwatch’ heading for the big esports league - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/34a640aa-a2aa-11e6-82c3-4351ce86813f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIlkUQGJsP7YhrMZg65O_4AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 18:30:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/34a640aa-a2aa-11e6-82c3-4351ce86813f" target="_blank"&gt;‘Overwatch’ heading for the big esports league&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activision Blizzard is launching its first esports league around its popular Overwatch game, as it looks to recreate the multibillion-dollar franchises and highly paid players of traditional US sports such as NFL football and NBA basketball. The move is an attempt to professionalise the fast-growing industry of competitive videogaming, which has gone from niche hobby to mass-market entertainment in the last few years. Activision’s approach is designed to introduce regular salaries for top players, increase prize money and attract new sponsors. Overwatch, a team-based shooting game for PCs a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>eSports business is booming - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/sports/2017/03/02/esports-business-boom-esl-starcraft-2-counterstrike-csgo-league-of-legends-pkg.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENrRBdukQBs0_2amIPApk8cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 16:53:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/sports/2017/03/02/esports-business-boom-esl-starcraft-2-counterstrike-csgo-league-of-legends-pkg.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;eSports business is booming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;eSports business is booming. With the rapid growth of the industry towards the $1 billion mark in 2019, get ready to see it all over your screens. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Top 10 'Counter-Strike: Global Offensive' Esports Teams Won A Total Of $7.7 Million In 2016 - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2017/01/27/the-top-10-counter-strike-global-offensive-esports-teams-won-a-total-of-7-million-in-2016/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMNuoCFROI8EAaHzPpv7cvUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2017/01/27/the-top-10-counter-strike-global-offensive-esports-teams-won-a-total-of-7-million-in-2016/" target="_blank"&gt;The Top 10 'Counter-Strike: Global Offensive' Esports Teams Won A Total Of $7.7 Million In 2016&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: Adela Sznajder, DreamHack/Graphics: Holly Warfield, Forbes Staff Already a popular esport, Counter-Strike: Global Offensive grew immensely in 2016 with $1 million prize pools and new events like ELEAGUE. Keep in mind, prize money is just a portion of these 10 teams’ income, which includes league revenue shares, sponsorship deals and more. READ: How SK Gaming Won $1.8 Million In 2016 Photo: Helena Kristiansson, ESL/Graphics: Holly Warfield, Forbes Staff Luminosity entered the year ready to prove themselves to CS:GO’s titans and did so in only half a year. The all-Brazilian squad won...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Illegal Gambling Case Concerning CS:GO Is Kicked Out Of Court - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2017/04/04/illegal-gambling-case-concerning-csgo-is-kicked-out-of-court/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAQEaspuf2nD0HIC2jlGgRwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 21:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2017/04/04/illegal-gambling-case-concerning-csgo-is-kicked-out-of-court/" target="_blank"&gt;Illegal Gambling Case Concerning CS:GO Is Kicked Out Of Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is very little case law that specifically focuses on the business practices and legal issues surrounding the vastly expanding realm of esports. One case, which centered around a claim that a company was aiding and abetting illegal gambling, could have provided promising precedent for the industry, but that is no longer a possibility. A lawsuit filed by multiple teenagers against Valve Corporation, the creator of Counter Strike: Global Offensive (CS:GO), has been punted by the U.S. District Court for the Western District of Washington and will now be adjudicated in arbitration. As such...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Battlegrounds' Meteoric Rise Has Accompanied 'Dota 2' and 'CS:GO' Declines - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/09/09/battlegrounds-meteoric-rise-has-accompanied-dota-2-and-csgo-declines/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhWOsqb0ymmQrcLIxrXK00qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/09/09/battlegrounds-meteoric-rise-has-accompanied-dota-2-and-csgo-declines/" target="_blank"&gt;Battlegrounds' Meteoric Rise Has Accompanied 'Dota 2' and 'CS:GO' Declines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds Two weeks ago it was news that PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds had surpassed Dota 2 in concurrent players for the first time. Today? Battlegrounds is flat-out blowing Dota out of the water, boasting 200-250,000 more players at any given time, topping 1 million concurrent for the first time this week, according to SteamCharts. It’s unknown (no pun intended) just how much Battlegrounds can continue to rise. Dota 2 topped out at nearly 1.3 million players in February 2016, and I’m not sure what other games have gotten close to that mark. Even major titles like GTA 5...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>FACEIT And YouTube Speak Out On The New Lucrative Broadcast Deal For The ECS 'CS:GO' League - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2017/03/16/faceit-and-youtube-speak-out-on-the-new-lucrative-broadcast-deal-for-the-ecs-csgo-league/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEzlJ5zE7QVmqi7aFfOINC0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2017/03/16/faceit-and-youtube-speak-out-on-the-new-lucrative-broadcast-deal-for-the-ecs-csgo-league/" target="_blank"&gt;FACEIT And YouTube Speak Out On The New Lucrative Broadcast Deal For The ECS 'CS:GO' League&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main stage at the ECS Season 2 finals. Tournament organiser FACEIT and YouTube have just announced a new deal that will see the ECS Counter-Strike: Global Offensive league be broadcast exclusively on YouTube. The deal means all of the competition will be broadcast live exclusively on YouTube, along with all video on demand content. Previously the league’s live broadcasts were exclusive to Twitch, who were heavily involved with the competition. However the switch to YouTube will give viewers extra benefits such as 1080p live streams and live rewind features that have not been possible on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Multi-Million Dollar Big Data Deal Paves The Way For Esports Betting - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2016/11/17/multi-million-dollar-big-data-deal-paves-the-way-for-esports-betting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSY6NZkHfcUlqNe-r8Lfg0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2016/11/17/multi-million-dollar-big-data-deal-paves-the-way-for-esports-betting/" target="_blank"&gt;Multi-Million Dollar Big Data Deal Paves The Way For Esports Betting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By 2020, wagering on esports competitions is expected to reach $29.8 billion, with 15.4 million individuals placing wagers on the outcomes of video game competitions. As such, bookmakers must prepare for extreme growth in this area, equipping themselves with requisite data and analysis to cater to bettors while protecting against accumulation of losses in the cases of wise competitors. Sportradar, through its brand Betradar, noticed an early opportunity and has entered into a partnership with esports big data startup DOJO Madness in order to become first-to-market in offering bookmakers a s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Super League Gaming Raises $5 Million Series C - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2016/10/26/super-league-gaming-raises-5-million-series-c/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELZhxbUSOFiD0ZpaB93XQY4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 14:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2016/10/26/super-league-gaming-raises-5-million-series-c/" target="_blank"&gt;Super League Gaming Raises $5 Million Series C&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super League Gaming, an interactive video game league to be played in movie theaters, has raised $5 million in a Series C round of funding. The company, based in Santa Monica, California has now raised a total of $20 million since its creation in 2014. The Series C round was led by Toba Capital and aXiomatic. In September, it was announced that aXiomatic, an esports investment group founded by Golden State Warriors co-owner Peter Guber and Washington Wizards majority owner Ted Leonsis, made its first esports investment through the purchase of the esports franchise Team Liquid. This is the s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Why The Intersection Of Music And Esports Is Bigger Business Than Ever - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/cheriehu/2018/10/25/why-the-intersection-of-music-and-esports-is-bigger-business-than-ever/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENzpVl1TIiXP1By-HDFKsFkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/cheriehu/2018/10/25/why-the-intersection-of-music-and-esports-is-bigger-business-than-ever/" target="_blank"&gt;Why The Intersection Of Music And Esports Is Bigger Business Than Ever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HONG KONG, HONG KONG – August 26, 2018: Audience members watch as Team MIBR is announced as the Champion of the ZOTAC Cup Masters CS:GO 2018 at the ICBC (Asia) E-Sports &amp; Music Festival Hong Kong on August 26, 2018 in Hong Kong, Hong Kong. (Photo by Anthony Kwan/Getty Images for Hong Kong Tourism Board) On Tuesday, Drake and Scooter Braun continued their reign as influential trendsetters in the music business when they announced an investment in 100 Thieves, one of Forbes’ most valuable esports companies. But when it comes to the intersection of music and esports, Drake and Braun are far fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What Olympic Recognition Could Mean For Esports, And Vice Versa - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dbloom/2018/10/18/esports-olympics-recognition-ioc-esl-advertising-sponsors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMf5T1VbllY6GvQ2bqboAOgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 19:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dbloom/2018/10/18/esports-olympics-recognition-ioc-esl-advertising-sponsors/" target="_blank"&gt;What Olympic Recognition Could Mean For Esports, And Vice Versa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(AP Photo/Terrin Waack) Esports could be an Olympics demonstration sport as soon as 2024 in Paris. The challenge, however, is figuring out how to incorporate a hot, fast-moving and highly fractured new sector into the careful, slow-moving processes of a massive, well-established traditional sports institution and its infrastructure, in a way that benefits both sides and opens new opportunities for brands that want to do business with both. “This is the last remaining mountain to conquer (for esports) to be acknowledged not just by the young but the entire world,” said Michal Blicharz, VP of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Loot boxes 'blur lines' between gambling and gaming, regulators warn - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/09/17/loot-boxes-blur-lines-gambling-gaming-regulators-warn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIP_5runb2J1ZqIzj2plfFcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 16:21:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/09/17/loot-boxes-blur-lines-gambling-gaming-regulators-warn/" target="_blank"&gt;Loot boxes 'blur lines' between gambling and gaming, regulators warn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK Gambling Commission is set to investigate the increasingly ‘blurred line’ between video games and gambling, amid growing concerns that children are being exposed to betting by third-party websites and in-game ‘loot boxes’. Loot boxes are containers in games filled with mystery virtual items, such as weapons or currency. Players can get the items either by paying or through game play. In a joint declaration with 13 other European gambling commissions and the Washington State Gambling Commission, regulators said that they will ‘thoroughly analyse’ the way video games are designed, incl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>‘Fortnite’ frenzy may have peaked as Twitch viewership falls sharply - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fortnite-frenzy-may-have-peaked-as-twitch-viewership-falls-sharply-2018-09-18</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMTfDCb8Wv2yATF4Vv10zHEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 11:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fortnite-frenzy-may-have-peaked-as-twitch-viewership-falls-sharply-2018-09-18" target="_blank"&gt;‘Fortnite’ frenzy may have peaked as Twitch viewership falls sharply&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RATINGS GAME By Tomi Kilgore Twitch viewership falls 13% for ‘Fortnite’ in August, but jump 48% for Activision games Twitch streamer and professional gamer Tyler "Ninja" Blevins Getty Images Interest in “Fortnite,” which has taken the videogame world by storm since its release last year, may have peaked, as data compiled by Piper Jaffray showed that viewership on streaming video platform Twitch suffered the steepest-ever monthly decline for the game. Amazon.com Inc.’s (AMZN) Twitch is a leading social-gaming platform. “Overall, we believe tracking Twitch viewership can provide insight i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>EA faces prosecution in Belgium over FIFA 19 'loot boxes' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/ea-faces-prosecution-belgium-fifa-19-loot-boxes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIkzZncNcvTqGhwmJS_MY4MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 12:17:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/ea-faces-prosecution-belgium-fifa-19-loot-boxes/" target="_blank"&gt;EA faces prosecution in Belgium over FIFA 19 'loot boxes'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Video game publisher Electronic Arts is reportedly under threat of prosecution in Belgium after refusing to remove ‘loot boxes’ from its FIFA football series. Loot boxes are virtual containers filled with mystery in-game items, such as weapons or currency. Players can get items in loot boxes either by paying or through game play. In April of this year, the Belgian Gambling Commission (BGC) ruled that ‘loot boxes’ were gambling under existing Belgian law and therefore illegal. However, the ruling has not yet been tested in court. Companies that fail to comply with the ruling could face fin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Meet The Analysts That Will Break Down The FACEIT London 'CS:GO' Major - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2018/08/31/meet-the-analysts-that-will-break-down-the-faceit-london-csgo-major/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhZylw5sHnayRY06_UpWrkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 17:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2018/08/31/meet-the-analysts-that-will-break-down-the-faceit-london-csgo-major/" target="_blank"&gt;Meet The Analysts That Will Break Down The FACEIT London 'CS:GO' Major&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spunj will be at the Major The CS:GO Major is the most prestigious event on the Counter-Strike calendar, and for such an event only the best broadcast talent are selected to walk viewers through the action. For the upcoming FACEIT London Major the team has decided to bring on a load of current and former pro players as analysts, to break down the in game goings on in extreme detail. This has meant that some big names have been left off the list, but there is no doubt that the group of analysts, which includes Björn “THREAT” Pers, Sean “seang@res” Gares, Damian “daps” Steele, Jacob “Pimp” Wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Esports Platform GRID Aims To Improve Data Use - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2018/09/05/new-esports-platform-grid-aims-to-improve-data-use/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO-OXltkP4ItDjQ7n7TyTWQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 20:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2018/09/05/new-esports-platform-grid-aims-to-improve-data-use/" target="_blank"&gt;New Esports Platform GRID Aims To Improve Data Use&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Major is coming to the UK. Data in esports has always been a weird area, as it is much easier to get lots of in game data than say in the world of sports, but few people have actually found a use for it. However, a new company called GRID aims to change all that by making in-game data accessible, engaging and commercially viable. GRID is founded by Moritz Maurer, who previously worked for Genius Sports and helped develop the first in play betting system for esports. After leaving Genius Sports he has built GRID, and is now launching the platform alongside the FACEIT London CS:GO Major. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Valve Announces Limited Free To Play Version Of 'CS:GO' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2018/08/30/valve-announces-limited-free-to-play-version-of-csgo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMuVJ9Y3nhx9cuSrysRHok0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 22:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2018/08/30/valve-announces-limited-free-to-play-version-of-csgo/" target="_blank"&gt;Valve Announces Limited Free To Play Version Of 'CS:GO'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CS:GO is going free to play Despite Valve having multiple successful free to play games, Counter-Strike: Global Offensive (CS:GO) is the one that has always remained a paid title. That is until now, as Valve is releasing a free version of the shooter that will allow anyone to play offline against bots and watch professional matches. If you head over to the Steam store and install CS:GO – Free, you will have access to a limited version of CS:GO. You will not be able to play any online matches, or connect to any public servers, which is obviously the only real way of playing CS:GO. However, y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>James Bardolph On Using Community Casters At The 'CS:GO' Major: 'That Was Not In Consideration' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2018/08/30/james-bardolph-on-using-community-casters-at-the-csgo-major-that-was-not-in-consideration/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPhnC2Z4b1nreE0N7seBFssqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 00:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2018/08/30/james-bardolph-on-using-community-casters-at-the-csgo-major-that-was-not-in-consideration/" target="_blank"&gt;James Bardolph On Using Community Casters At The 'CS:GO' Major: 'That Was Not In Consideration'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Major is coming to the UK. The CS:GO Major is the biggest event in the world of Counter-Strike, and fans expect the very best the scene has to offer both in and out of the game. But earlier this year it was rumoured that FACEIT would be using a pair of community casters for certain stages of the Major, which many fans were concerned about. However, James Bardolph has revealed that was never in his plans for the event. FACEIT previously ran a competition to find a pair of new casters, and the chosen duo would be able to cast matches at the ECS Season 5 LAN finals. The eventual winners were...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Opening Matches For The FACEIT London 'CS:GO' Major Revealed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2018/08/31/opening-matches-for-the-faceit-london-csgo-major-revealed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEODJZ4qucQdbSrbRqyUuieIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 11:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2018/08/31/opening-matches-for-the-faceit-london-csgo-major-revealed/" target="_blank"&gt;Opening Matches For The FACEIT London 'CS:GO' Major Revealed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Astralis headline the opening round of the Major. The next CS:GO Major is right around the corner, and we have finally found out which teams will be facing off in the first round of competition. FACEIT has revealed the opening matches for the London Major, which will be played in a Swiss formatt, the teams that win their opening match will then play against other teams that also won, while the losers will play the teams that lost. Opening up the first ever CS:GO Major on UK soil will be Space Soldiers vs. Rogue, which is set to take place at 10am BST on September 5. After that the matches w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fashion Meets Gaming With Nick Cavello of D Market - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccasuhrawardi/2018/08/12/fashion-meets-gaming-with-nick-cavello-of-d-market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB_Z8IncMEd6tA2B9hD-ju0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 00:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccasuhrawardi/2018/08/12/fashion-meets-gaming-with-nick-cavello-of-d-market/" target="_blank"&gt;Fashion Meets Gaming With Nick Cavello of D Market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A look from Tomm Hilfiger XPLORE, a smart chip enabled, reward-based collection of gaming-inspired clothes. Just over a week ago, Tommy Hilfiger launched Tommy Jeans XPLORE, a collection of denim and accessories embedded with what they call smart chip technology. Inspired by the gaming industry and the challenge/reward-based loyalty that gaming breeds in users, Hilfiger’s smart chips allow wearers to earn points for wearing the clothes and for playing a Bluetooth-enabled game, points which can be exchanged for rewards like gift cards and exclusive merchandise, even tickets to the brand’s ru...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'It’s incredibly widespread': why eSports has a match-fixing problem - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/jul/31/its-incredibly-widespread-why-esports-has-a-match-fixing-problem</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBxpuKHLL9XpAiG6HvN7CjsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 07:00:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/jul/31/its-incredibly-widespread-why-esports-has-a-match-fixing-problem" target="_blank"&gt;'It’s incredibly widespread': why eSports has a match-fixing problem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2017, the global eSports economy was estimated to stand at around $696m, attracting an audience of over 385 million people, according to Newzoo. But the industry’s formidable growth has attracted more than just hordes of professional gamers, avid viewers and brands offering lucrative sponsorship deals. Organised criminals and low-level chancers have seen an opportunity to influence match outcomes and profit from them in betting markets. As the industry has grown, a string of match-fixing scandals have unfolded, embroiling some of the most prestigious competitive gaming tournaments. Popul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>In a league of their own: Sydney gets first dedicated esports arena - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-31/first-dedicated-esports-arena-opens-in-sydney/9820418</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHqGIB75GFA0qdoTRY-lPfIqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDc2g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 05:33:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-31/first-dedicated-esports-arena-opens-in-sydney/9820418" target="_blank"&gt;In a league of their own: Sydney gets first dedicated esports arena&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deep in the bowels of a movie theatre complex in Sydney's inner suburbs, construction workers and production teams have been working feverishly to get ready for opening night. The theatre's screen, however, has been removed and in its place sits a large elevated stage on which two huge LED screens stand. They are displaying not trailers for upcoming features, but rather an easily recognisable character from the classic console game Street Fighter. This weekend the venue will host the first event of Elite Series, Australia's first ever city-based club esports league. Photo: Gfinity esports g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Active Shooter video game condemned by parents of Parkland victims - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/may/29/active-shooter-video-game-parkland-school-massacre-florida</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP4qbxKE5hOgRw-LeO7e7JUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 12:09:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/may/29/active-shooter-video-game-parkland-school-massacre-florida" target="_blank"&gt;Active Shooter video game condemned by parents of Parkland victims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A video game that simulates a school shooting incident has been labelled “disgusting” and “despicable” by parents of children who died during the mass shooting at a school in Parkland, Florida, in February. Billed by its Russian publisher, Acid, as a swat team simulator, Active Shooter invites players to take on the role of an armed officer responding to a school shooting. However, the game also allows users to play as the shooter or as a civilian attempting to escape the scene. Using a first-person perspective, similar to shooters such as Call of Duty, Doom and Counter-Strike, the game loo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Easy trap to fall into': why video-game loot boxes need regulation - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/may/29/gamers-politicians-regulation-video-game-loot-boxes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAZVppzsop7dcvRrbkkBHsEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 05:50:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/may/29/gamers-politicians-regulation-video-game-loot-boxes" target="_blank"&gt;'Easy trap to fall into': why video-game loot boxes need regulation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Loot boxes are like scratch-off cards: you open one out of curiosity, get a little prize, think ‘darn, maybe next time,’ and then it just turns into a habit,” says Brian. “I got a big prize with my first $20 and thought, ‘Hey, maybe I’ll get something good again,’ and spent another $5 next week, and then $5 more. It’s a disturbingly easy trap to fall into.” Brian (not his real name), a 25-year-old American Reddit user who responded to a Guardian call-out, is one of millions of players who buy “loot boxes”, lucky-dip boxes that cost real money and yield random virtual rewards. Loot boxes ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>From Unikrn To Skin Betting: How The Supreme Court's Sports Gambling Ruling Impacts Esports - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2018/05/15/from-unikrn-to-skin-betting-how-the-supreme-courts-sports-gambling-ruling-impacts-esports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH7s3z1i3XtK5A8iL1g6TPkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2018/05/15/from-unikrn-to-skin-betting-how-the-supreme-courts-sports-gambling-ruling-impacts-esports/" target="_blank"&gt;From Unikrn To Skin Betting: How The Supreme Court's Sports Gambling Ruling Impacts Esports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The crowd at the Spring Split Finals of the North American League of Legends Championship Series. Founded in 2014, Unikrn is a Seattle-based web platform where users can bet on the outcome of esports matches, from League of Legends to Counter-Strike: Global Offensive. Backed by, among others, Mark Cuban and Ashton Kutcher, Unikrn has pulled in $10 million in equity financing, plus around $80 million from last year’s sale of its Ethereum-based cryptocurrency. And with the Supreme Court’s decision Monday to effectively open the door for state-regulated betting on sports, Unikrn stands to win ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Extreme eSports: the very male, billion-dollar gaming industry at a stadium near you - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/may/08/extreme-esports-the-very-male-billion-dollar-gaming-industry-at-a-stadium-near-you</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAAFKukovUejsfNVReJjulQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/may/08/extreme-esports-the-very-male-billion-dollar-gaming-industry-at-a-stadium-near-you" target="_blank"&gt;Extreme eSports: the very male, billion-dollar gaming industry at a stadium near you&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whenever an artist scheduled to play Qudos Bank Arena at Sydney Olympic Park doesn’t sell enough tickets, the venue tactfully drapes black cloth over the empty seats in the theatre’s uppermost section. Filling more than 18,000 seats is quite an ask, which is why only top-flight acts like Pink, Katy Perry, Shania Twain and Kendrick Lamar are attempting it in coming months. The black cloth is not needed today. Sydney gaming enthusiasts have filled the venue almost to capacity for the Intel Extreme Masters (IEM), a three-day professional video game tournament that rivals anything Qudos has hos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Belgium is right to class video game loot boxes as child gambling - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/apr/26/belgium-is-right-to-legislate-against-video-game-loot-boxes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELWzx_rbH6j23w-zjp4ULPkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 12:16:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/apr/26/belgium-is-right-to-legislate-against-video-game-loot-boxes" target="_blank"&gt;Belgium is right to class video game loot boxes as child gambling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, the Belgian minister of justice, Koen Greens, announced the result of an investigation that the country’s Gaming Commission conducted into video game “loot boxes”, a mechanic that lets players pay real money for a chance at winning virtual items. It found that three popular games – Overwatch, Counter-Strike: Global Offensive and Fifa 18 – were in violation of gambling legislation. This is a significant finding, because controversy over loot boxes has been raging for at least six months: are they actually a form of gambling? Worse, are they a form of gambling that is particularly ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Rainbow Six: Siege' Just Had Its Best Day Ever, Nearly 3 Years After Launch - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/03/08/rainbow-six-siege-just-had-its-best-day-ever-three-years-after-launch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMdZ_OirAmqq_PZlfJ908qQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/03/08/rainbow-six-siege-just-had-its-best-day-ever-three-years-after-launch/" target="_blank"&gt;'Rainbow Six: Siege' Just Had Its Best Day Ever, Nearly 3 Years After Launch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rainbow Six Siege just broke a major record on Steam. Rainbow Six: Siege was one of those games that I once thought might not make it. Ubisoft’s hardcore team-based competitive shooter struggled out the gates, with lukewarm reviews and a low player base. Well all that’s changed. Today, the game peaked at 176,856 concurrent players on Steam Tuesday. That’s the most it’s ever had, and places it at #4 on Steam’s top played games. Here are the top five (at peak Tuesday) so you can get a sense of just what this means: - PUBG: 2,611,750 concurrent players - Counter-Strike: GO: 609,949 concurrent ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Indefinitely Suspended Esports Streamer Takes On Amazon-Owned Twitch In Court - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2018/02/20/indefinitely-suspended-esports-streamer-takes-on-amazon-owned-twitch-in-court/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG4JuKlXPwfHoaPW29t31M0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2018/02/20/indefinitely-suspended-esports-streamer-takes-on-amazon-owned-twitch-in-court/" target="_blank"&gt;Indefinitely Suspended Esports Streamer Takes On Amazon-Owned Twitch In Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spotlight will be on Amazon-owned Twitch as it is being sued by one of its most popular former streamers. (Photo by Chesnot/Getty Images) James “PhantomL0rd” Varga has become a sort of esports superhero. He has over 229,000 Twitter followers, more than 508,000 YouTube subscribers and another 428,000 people who like his Facebook page. Varga initially amassed his following due to his skill as a competitive video game player, focusing on the popular League of Legends and Counter-Strike: Global Offensive games. On the popular streaming service Twitch, Varga earned roughly 16,000 paid subscr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Everyone Is Betting On Growth Of Esports Wagering In 2018 - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2018/02/12/everyone-is-betting-on-growth-of-esports-wagering-in-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPRomuLy7fQfqx7QgyZXvz4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 13:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2018/02/12/everyone-is-betting-on-growth-of-esports-wagering-in-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Everyone Is Betting On Growth Of Esports Wagering In 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betting operators are excited about the potential for growth surrounding wagers on PlayUnknown’s Battlegrounds (PUBG) matches. (Photo by VCG/VCG via Getty Images) Optimism for the future of betting on esports is very high. In a survey filled out by thirty-one respondents representing small endemic sites (esports-first or esports-only) to the largest non-endemic global operators (mainstream betting operators that also offer esports), 100% of the respondents indicated a belief that the esports handle will grow in 2018, and 82% hypothesize that the sophistication of esports wagering will catch...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Are eSports the future of Olympics? 5 things you wouldn’t expect from pro gaming - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/sport/418401-esports-olympics-future-gaming/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKlzHt0pacNZsei0bYwdugYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwlujfAw</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 09:21:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/sport/418401-esports-olympics-future-gaming/" target="_blank"&gt;Are eSports the future of Olympics? 5 things you wouldn’t expect from pro gaming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Competitive video gaming, or eSports, played warm-up to this year’s Winter Olympics. Now recognized as “real” sports by Olympic officials, eSports are gunning for a spot of their own in the medal table. Intel Corp, an Olympic sponsor, brought professional gamers to PyongChang, where the Olympics are now in full swing, earlier this week. They played Starcraft II, a popular real-time strategy game that involves tactical thinking, concentration and quick reflexes – and rekindled the debate on whether the rigorous requirements are enough for eSports to become part of the Olympics. The Internati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>The First Esports Convention Is Heading To Seattle - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2018/02/02/the-first-esports-convention-is-heading-to-seattle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN3tqGqGaKOYzDlhuSl6kUEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 23:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alexknapp/2018/02/02/the-first-esports-convention-is-heading-to-seattle/" target="_blank"&gt;The First Esports Convention Is Heading To Seattle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo by Jens Schlueter/Getty Images) Champions, fans and those interested in careers in the growing competitive gaming industry will come together Memorial Day Weekend at the GG Expo in Seattle for the first convention dedicated to esports. Although there are a number of video game conferences out there to connect fans, there hasn’t yet been any major conventions that are primarily focused on esports as opposed to video games more generally. That’s a major void that the organizers of the Expo are interested in filling. “There are a lot of shows that cover video games very broadly,” said J...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Meet Australian sport's next big thing - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-01-28/the-esports-phenomenon-moves-into-australia/9357496</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH7Vh5lPpvtFDnIYnCEWDukqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDc2g4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 22:13:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-01-28/the-esports-phenomenon-moves-into-australia/9357496" target="_blank"&gt;Meet Australian sport's next big thing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marcus Gomes is 20 years old, packs a slight frame and — with not one A-League goal to his name — has become one of the hottest signings in Australian soccer. Meet the new world of competitive online gaming — or esports — a sophisticated and professional cyber sporting code which is starting to attract the attention of some of Australia's biggest traditional clubs. The world of esports can be split into categories of games such as fighting, first-person shooter, sporting, multiplayer online battle arenas and real-time strategy. Every esports game is different, with different games played on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>'Insurgency: Sandstorm' Looks Like The Shooter To Beat In 2018 - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/01/31/insurgency-sandstorm-looks-like-the-shooter-to-beat-in-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOyYzhrQXpywCo8glbrWN0wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/01/31/insurgency-sandstorm-looks-like-the-shooter-to-beat-in-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'Insurgency: Sandstorm' Looks Like The Shooter To Beat In 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insurgency: Sandstorm looks incredible. Insurgency: Sandstorm is one of my most highly-anticipated first-person shooters of 2018. Recently stripped of its single-player campaign, the game is now 100% multiplayer focused. That was probably the right decision for New World Entertainment to make—doubling down on what’s made their previous games so top-notch rather than squandering resources on an expensive campaign. (Note: I’d still love to play a solo campaign made by this team, but I absolutely understand why this has been cut.) In any case, check out this new trailer for the game and tell m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'PUBG' Hits 3 Million Players On Xbox One As It Averages 3 Million Concurrents On Steam - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/01/12/pubg-hits-3-million-players-on-xbox-one-as-it-averages-3-million-concurrents-on-steam/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOP2I9VJ_YUqo3X0m1EmjmkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 15:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/01/12/pubg-hits-3-million-players-on-xbox-one-as-it-averages-3-million-concurrents-on-steam/" target="_blank"&gt;'PUBG' Hits 3 Million Players On Xbox One As It Averages 3 Million Concurrents On Steam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUBG on Xbox One PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds is showing no signs of slowing down in 2018, continuing to grow not only on PC, but also its first platform expansion, Xbox One. On Steam, PUBG is still blowing every other game in the history of the platform out of the water, now averaging 3-3.1 million concurrent players at any given time. For comparison’s sake, DOTA 2 peaked at 1.29 million and CS:GO peaked at about 850K. Just a few months ago in September I was writing how impressive it was that PUBG had broken DOTA’s record with 1.3 million concurrents, and it’s literally over 3 million as...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>‘They see the potential’: why J-Lo and Gillette want a piece of the eSports action - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2017/dec/25/esports-jennifer-lopez-gillette-audi-mercedes-benz-a-piece-of-the-action</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI4wcBIULwCBIa4fRqNisjsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 12:35:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2017/dec/25/esports-jennifer-lopez-gillette-audi-mercedes-benz-a-piece-of-the-action" target="_blank"&gt;‘They see the potential’: why J-Lo and Gillette want a piece of the eSports action&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there are any doubts that computer games can become a mainstream spectator sport, then Jennifer Lopez and Stan Kroenke are not listening. The superstar singer and Arsenal’s majority shareholder have both put money into eSports teams, as the gaming competitions with millions of followers worldwide aim for even greater public appeal. Lopez has bought into a team franchise for the new Overwatch League, in which teams from cities such as Seoul, San Francisco and London play Overwatch, a mass-participation shooting game. The global competition for the game, which launches in January, also inc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Here Are All The Winners Of The 2017 Game Awards - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/08/here-are-all-the-winners-of-the-2017-game-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGJSV1nrd9_jd1s_jO-NsF8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 16:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/08/here-are-all-the-winners-of-the-2017-game-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are All The Winners Of The 2017 Game Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the winner is… Well, the fourth annual Game Awards have come and gone. Without question, last night’s awards were the best so far (more thoughts on that in a separate post) and all the winners were well-deserving. It was a tough year, with tons of amazing games to choose from. Below are all the winners, as well as a look at how well I did in my predictions (not terrible, it so happens.) I didn’t predict in categories I don’t really follow such as eSports. We’ll start with GOTY, which went to Zelda, surprising no one…. Game of the Year Horizon Zero Dawn Persona 5 PlayerUnknown’s Battlegr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>FIFA 18 to join esports tournament Gfinity Elite Series for its third season, starting in 2018 - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fifa-18-join-esports-tournament-gfinity-elite-series-third-season/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOjzfKtH6UuwHfSG6Cv3H0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 10:12:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fifa-18-join-esports-tournament-gfinity-elite-series-third-season/" target="_blank"&gt;FIFA 18 to join esports tournament Gfinity Elite Series for its third season, starting in 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the UK's biggest esports tournaments is the Gfinity Elite Series, where competitors across a series of games compete in professional play, and its third season will, for the first time, include FIFA 18. It will be played in the competition alongside other esports titles, with top-performing teams earning points with each victory. The Gfinity Elite Series is unique in that each season of play sees teams drafting up players. On January 8, players will be able to compete in the Gfinity Challenger Series, proving their skills ahead of the team draft for the Gfinity Elite Series. The top ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Campaigners call for video game laws fit for the internet age - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/12/08/campaigners-call-video-game-laws-fit-internet-age/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHz1Tfi6QJnIF5auTUD87pgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/12/08/campaigners-call-video-game-laws-fit-internet-age/" target="_blank"&gt;Campaigners call for video game laws fit for the internet age&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain’s video games watchdog has failed to ban a single violent game as campaigners warn that laws are not keeping up with advances in technology. Children’s charities and relatives of those killed by murderers thought to be acting out violent scenes from games are calling for an urgent review of rules meant to prevent young people obtaining the most gratuitously brutal games over the internet. The Video Standards Council (VSC) was accused by peers earlier this week of “not doing its job” after it emerged that it had not banned any violent games since it became the industry watchdog in 20...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>From Belgium To Hawaii, Potential 'Battlefront 2' Loot Box Legislation Would Be Complicated - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/11/22/from-belgium-to-hawaii-potential-battlefront-2-loot-box-legislation-would-be-complicated/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKSAg4KNBgD3phMd6B75DJ0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/11/22/from-belgium-to-hawaii-potential-battlefront-2-loot-box-legislation-would-be-complicated/" target="_blank"&gt;From Belgium To Hawaii, Potential 'Battlefront 2' Loot Box Legislation Would Be Complicated&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Battlefront 2 I have lived through a lot of “yell a lot about video games” controversies in my time, but I have truly never seen anything like what’s currently happening in Star Wars Battlefront 2. I saw fans yell until the Mass Effect 3 ending was fixed through DLC. I saw fans yell until Diablo 3’s Auction House was killed. But I have never seen fans yell until not only were microtransactions stripped out of a game like Battlefront 2, but it called into question the predatory practices of the entire industry. That’s precisely what’s starting to happen now, as this has moved beyond “EA did ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>The best shooter video games - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/best-shooter-video-games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMaEe3tMVX1Touvv6AcXpToqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 10:36:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/best-shooter-video-games/" target="_blank"&gt;The best shooter video games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the last two and a half decades, the first-person shooter has been a mainstay in the video game world. Never shying away from a bit of controversy, they're typically games about killing hundreds of bad guys in sequence on a Rambo-like rampage through levels. But shooters aren't all bloody rampages without meaning, style, or substance. In case you're not too well-versed in the genre, or just need some good recommendations, we've put together a list of the best shooting games, from the bombastic gorefests to smaller indie affairs. Wolfenstein 2: The New Colossus What is it on? PS4, Xbox O...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Gfinity Elite Series esports week 6 highlights | In the penultimate week of the regular season, the race for playoff spots is even more intense - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/gfinity-elite-series-esports-week-6-highlights-penultimate-week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOl6Qb7T34jdWyMVD8zms9QqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 16:49:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/gfinity-elite-series-esports-week-6-highlights-penultimate-week/" target="_blank"&gt;Gfinity Elite Series esports week 6 highlights | In the penultimate week of the regular season, the race for playoff spots is even more intense&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the Gfinity Arena in London, the Gfinity Elite Series is under way, a series of esports tournaments across three popular titles, where teams and individual players battle it out for glory and cash prizes. We're currently on week six of the current Gfinity Elite Series season, with competitors playing in the fighting game Street Fighter 5, the football-cum-driving game Rocket League, and the first-person team shooter Counter-Strike: Global Offensive. Given it's six weeks in, teams are growing their reputations and making a stand for certain positions on the podium. There's only one more w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Power of Backstories: How TV Can Help Humanize eSports - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alanwolk/2017/10/12/the-power-of-backstories-how-tv-can-help-humanize-esports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAFSvPGp6pH1ZRRYh9UMgGgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alanwolk/2017/10/12/the-power-of-backstories-how-tv-can-help-humanize-esports/" target="_blank"&gt;The Power of Backstories: How TV Can Help Humanize eSports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(AP Photo/Jacques Brinon, File) 2017 has not been a very good year for sports on TV: NFL ratings are down and ESPN continues to shed viewers. The one bright sport has been eSports, or the potential of eSports, to be more exact. And while the notion that watching other people play video games is somehow a sport and that millions of people enjoy watching it may seem curious to old school sports fans, there’s more to eSports than meets the eye. Before we begin looking in to how eSports plays out on TV, it’s probably helpful to have some background: eSports began almost 20 years ago in Europe,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Ten Years Ago, Valve Launched 3 Brand New Games All At Once In The Orange Box - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/10/11/ten-years-ago-valve-launched-3-brand-new-games-all-at-once-in-the-orange-box/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDnGjcQ0SfipgaVVGwj6Q4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 15:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/10/11/ten-years-ago-valve-launched-3-brand-new-games-all-at-once-in-the-orange-box/" target="_blank"&gt;Ten Years Ago, Valve Launched 3 Brand New Games All At Once In The Orange Box&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Orange Box just turned ten. It’s been a decade since Valve released the Orange Box, one of video gaming’s most important box-sets filled with a treasure trove of now-classic games. The box, which actually released as a physical box rather than just a digital purchase (rare on PC these days) came out on October 10th, 2007 on PC and Xbox 360, with a PS3 version releasing later that same year. The Orange Box was met with universal critical acclaim, Team Fortress 2 remains one of the most popular games on Steam. The Orange Box included: - Half-Life 2 - Half-Life 2: Episode 1 - Half-Life 2: ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item></channel></rss>