<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Bethesda Softworks - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREV5TTJvMkVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:21:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>'The Outer Worlds' Is The 'Fallout' Game We've All Been Waiting For - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/the-outer-worlds-is-the-fallout-game-weve-all-been-waiting-for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGjPrtVHWOtdZJjl-xuPCsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/the-outer-worlds-is-the-fallout-game-weve-all-been-waiting-for/" target="_blank"&gt;'The Outer Worlds' Is The 'Fallout' Game We've All Been Waiting For&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Outer Worlds looks great. I imagine the developers at Obsidian have been watching the Fallout 76 with grim wonder and more than a little schadenfreude. After all, this is a studio who missed out on a bonus from publisher Bethesda because their game, Fallout: New Vegas, didn’t top 85 on Metacritic. Fallout 76 hasn’t even come close to that number. While New Vegas had its problems—Obsidian, like Bethesda, isn’t known for bug-free projects—it was an instant classic and a much-beloved entry into the franchise. Fallout 76 is a disaster. So it must have been rather serendipitous for Obsidian ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda Responds To The 'Fallout 76' Support Glitch That Exposed Customer Data - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/bethesda-responds-to-the-fallout-76-support-glitch-that-exposed-customer-data/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_lZzx3tbgSpyrhNYJ_2BoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/bethesda-responds-to-the-fallout-76-support-glitch-that-exposed-customer-data/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda Responds To The 'Fallout 76' Support Glitch That Exposed Customer Data&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bethesda explains what happened in the support ticket fiasco. I’ve already written at length about the crazy glitch that allowed Fallout 76 players to accidentally gain access to other players’ personal information and support tickets. It was quite an astonishing technical error, even for Bethesda. Now the publisher has responded with a lengthy email sent out to the press yesterday afternoon. Here’s the full statement: As previously reported, onDecember 5, 2018, we experienced an error with our Customer Support website that resulted in the exposure of a limited number of customer support ti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>A 'Fallout 76' Support Ticket Glitch Gave Players Access To Everyone's Personal Information - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/05/a-fallout-76-support-glitch-leaked-players-personal-information-for-all-the-world-to-see/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQTdTWvDuUMEgrxC4uQ1doqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/05/a-fallout-76-support-glitch-leaked-players-personal-information-for-all-the-world-to-see/" target="_blank"&gt;A 'Fallout 76' Support Ticket Glitch Gave Players Access To Everyone's Personal Information&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the most shocking twist yet, Fallout 76 players’ private information was just revealed to the whole world. In what may very well be the most bizarre and unsettling twist in the ongoing saga that is Fallout 76, players reported Wednesday that they inadvertently gained access to the support tickets of fellow Fallout 76 players. Not only did other gamers gain access to these tickets, they were able to see personal information such as addresses, phone numbers and credit card information. It gets weirder, of course—I’m not sure it could get any worse—because not only could players see this in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda Is Sending 'Fallout 76' Power Armor Edition Customers Canvas Bags, After All - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/04/bethesda-is-sending-fallout-76-power-armor-edition-customers-canvas-bags-after-all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-W8AGxQHvSVdfxTRLNozoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/04/bethesda-is-sending-fallout-76-power-armor-edition-customers-canvas-bags-after-all/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda Is Sending 'Fallout 76' Power Armor Edition Customers Canvas Bags, After All&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Power Armor Edition customers will get the bag at last. Bag-gate may soon draw to a close, as Fallout 76 publisher Bethesda is finally doing right by its customers. Following the launch of the game, super-fans who spent $200 on the special Power Armor Edition of the game discovered that instead of the nice canvas bag that was advertised when they pre-ordered, Bethesda had sent out cheap nylon bags instead. This revelation was made worse when Bethesda’s customer service responded in a less-than-helpful manner, sparking more outrage and frustration among players and some severe articles in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 5 Biggest Problems With 'Fallout 76' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/05/the-5-biggest-problems-with-fallout-76/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgaube4gkhPC4VU4mY_GPIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/05/the-5-biggest-problems-with-fallout-76/" target="_blank"&gt;The 5 Biggest Problems With 'Fallout 76'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 is riddled with problems. Here are five of them. Well, I hate to tell you “I told you so.” But I told you so. When I wrote an article about Fallout 76 and how dubious I was that it would be a good game ready for a release in 2018, I received tons of backlash from angry fans. Now the game is rocking a 49/100 Metacritic score (on Xbox One, it’s slightly higher on PC and PS4) with a 2.7 user score. That’s just about the worst-reviewed AAA game of the year, and one of the worst-reviewed AAA games in recent memory, and certainly of this console generation. Ouch. Forbes Games writer Pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Making Good Use Of Your Time In The Elder Scrolls Online's New Free Trial Event - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/12/05/making-good-use-of-your-time-in-the-elder-scrolls-onlines-new-free-trial-event/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_MBDEA86hfbVtdcP20RiwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/12/05/making-good-use-of-your-time-in-the-elder-scrolls-onlines-new-free-trial-event/" target="_blank"&gt;Making Good Use Of Your Time In The Elder Scrolls Online's New Free Trial Event&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ‘Elder Scrolls Online’ If you think you might enjoy the Elder Scrolls Online but haven’t been willing to buy the game, you can play for free for six days to find out if it’s your cup of tea. The free trial period begins on Thursday December 6 and runs through Tuesday the 11th on PC, Mac, Xbox One and PS4. Console players need an Xbox Live Gold or PlayStation Plus membership to take advantage of the free trial. The Xbox One X enhanced version looks noticeably better than the PS4 Pro if that option is available and you’re sitting the right distance from a 4K screen. The free trial gives y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda Gave 'Influencers' Nice 'Fallout 76' Canvas Bags Instead Of Fans Who Spent $200 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/03/bethesda-gave-influencers-nice-fallout-76-canvas-bags-just-not-customers-who-paid-200/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIEeO5uyyDof8dbkj316-IQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/03/bethesda-gave-influencers-nice-fallout-76-canvas-bags-just-not-customers-who-paid-200/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda Gave 'Influencers' Nice 'Fallout 76' Canvas Bags Instead Of Fans Who Spent $200&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76′s ‘bag-gate’ controversy deepens. In many ways, at least for those of us who comment on the video game industry’s many foibles, Fallout 76 is the gift that keeps on giving. Not so much, however, if you spent $200 on the game’s Power Armor Edition, thought you’d get a nice canvas bag, and were sent a cheap nylon bag instead. This on top of the game being a hot pile of steaming garbage, riddled with performance issues, bland combat and recycled assets. Of course, the story only gets better—or worse, depending on where you’re sitting. If you’re me, writing about just how low and scu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>It's Hard To Imagine How 'Fallout 76' Ever Goes Free-To-Play - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/04/its-hard-to-imagine-how-fallout-76-ever-goes-free-to-play/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBqDydoO9xJnVNvRsuwiQdUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/04/its-hard-to-imagine-how-fallout-76-ever-goes-free-to-play/" target="_blank"&gt;It's Hard To Imagine How 'Fallout 76' Ever Goes Free-To-Play&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Fans watched the price of Fallout 76 dip all the way down to around $35 just a week or two after launch around Black Friday sale time, and that combined with its myriad issues caused an old refrain to start up again. “Well, it’s only a matter of time until it goes free-to-play.” It’s the go-to for any struggling game when they realize it’s the best way to bulk up their playerbase, as they’ll hope to make money in other ways. But you do not usually hear this when talking about an enormous, just-released triple A product like Fallout 76, which should tell you what dire straits it’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda Offers Players $5 In Microtransactions For Issue With $200 'Fallout 76' Power Armor Edition - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/29/bethesda-offers-players-5-in-microtransactions-for-issue-with-200-fallout-76-power-armor-edition/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAh4K22PNLPCNAQqnEZ45l8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 12:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/29/bethesda-offers-players-5-in-microtransactions-for-issue-with-200-fallout-76-power-armor-edition/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda Offers Players $5 In Microtransactions For Issue With $200 'Fallout 76' Power Armor Edition&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After somehow managing to shoehorn Fallout 76 into my review of Red Dead Online yesterday, I swore I was going to take a break for a while. But Bethesda is just the gift that keeps on giving, this time thanks to their handling of a rather ridiculous issue with the $200 Fallout 76 Power Armor Edition. And now players are not especially happy with the $5 in microtransaction currency they’re being given for their troubles. While I’m sure plenty of people have buyer’s remorse for that just because of the state of the game itself, a further issue has been discovered as players have been shipped ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda's Silence Of The State Of 'Fallout 76' At Launch Is Deafening - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/27/bethesdas-silence-of-the-state-of-fallout-76-at-launch-is-deafening/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEnR7z_v_SR0d1dXnRLjvzIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 14:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/27/bethesdas-silence-of-the-state-of-fallout-76-at-launch-is-deafening/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda's Silence Of The State Of 'Fallout 76' At Launch Is Deafening&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Fallout 76 is a unique disaster in the gaming industry. A huge game based on a huge IP that took years to craft, and yet its arrival has been marked by some of the lowest critic and user scores in modern gaming history. While Bethesda has often been given free passes for buggy titles, Fallout 76 has taken things to a new level on that front, and its technical issues are compounded by the core design problems of a multiplayer, survivalist Fallout experience few people asked for, or if they did, this is definitely not what they had in mind. And yet we have heard practically nothing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76 review | A lonely post-apocalyptic world of little consequence - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/fallout-76-review-lonely-post-apocalyptic-world-little-consequence/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM1U089I7ZhT7y5k42QZnakqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 09:19:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/fallout-76-review-lonely-post-apocalyptic-world-little-consequence/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76 review | A lonely post-apocalyptic world of little consequence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the dawn of Reclamation Day I left Vault 76, weary eyed and slightly optimistic about the journey that laid ahead of me in West Virginia. Despite all the doom and gloom that had been directed towards Fallout 76, this divergent multiplayer instalment of Bethesda's post-apocalyptic series, moving from single-player immersion to an online playground. As a Fallout fan I had faith that Bethesda’s ambitious idea could pay-off. But the more hours I gave, the more that faith was drained and the worse the experience became. I did a piece about what Bethesda should change to the game after the bet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76 review – a pointless walk in the post-apocalypse - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/19/fallout-76-review-playstation-xbox-pc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIy3KURyac766-mZ_o2sO8UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 13:45:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/19/fallout-76-review-playstation-xbox-pc" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76 review – a pointless walk in the post-apocalypse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Fallout 76’s opening moments, you are urged to leave your underground vault and remake America after a nuclear apocalypse, adventuring through Appalachia collecting scrap to build with and weapons and armour to help survive the irradiated environment and the monsters, super mutants and robots that now call it home. You’re not alone in this endeavour: online, you can team up with, or attack, your fellow former vault-dwellers – or you can ignore them completely, treating the game as a solo experience (that nonetheless requires a constant internet connection). Rebuilding the world with stra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>After A Historically Bad Launch, Is 'Fallout 76' Worth Saving? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/23/after-a-historically-bad-launch-is-fallout-76-worth-saving/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPnbkn257L0IlVVcQihm4SYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 14:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/23/after-a-historically-bad-launch-is-fallout-76-worth-saving/" target="_blank"&gt;After A Historically Bad Launch, Is 'Fallout 76' Worth Saving?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 While I did not particularly enjoy my time with Fallout 76, I was not expecting the critical and public reaction to it to be quite this harsh. Fallout 76 may be the highest profile release with the lowest review scores I can remember seeing in at least a decade, or really since metascores became a thing. It’s Bethesda’s lowest rated game by a huge margin, it’s scoring worse than No Man’s Sky, Mass Effect Andromeda, vanilla Destiny and all those other big titles that were high profile critical disappointments at launch. It’s hovering around Duke Nukem Forever territory in terms of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Is Already $20 Off For Black Friday, But It Still Might Be Overpriced - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/23/fallout-76-is-already-20-off-for-black-friday-but-it-still-might-be-overpriced/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsAsZivq-zR5Uz-A2UvF_MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 14:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/23/fallout-76-is-already-20-off-for-black-friday-but-it-still-might-be-overpriced/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Is Already $20 Off For Black Friday, But It Still Might Be Overpriced&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 It’s rare to see big discounts on recently-released AAA games for Black Friday, at least those that came out in the past month or so. Red Dead Redemption 2 is still basically sitting at the MSRP of $60 at most retailers, despite some little collectible pack-ins to make it look a little more like a deal. Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 is seeing a couple of discounts, but the game was released just long enough to go for that to make a little more sense. And then we’ve got Fallout 76, a game that was released just one week ago and yet is already seeing some pretty steep discounts across ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Big E3 Press Conferences Are A Waste Of Time And Money - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/06/16/the-big-pre-e3-press-conferences-are-a-waste-of-time-and-money/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGdX7pqwdOG_xUKyEEOFr5EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 16:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/06/16/the-big-pre-e3-press-conferences-are-a-waste-of-time-and-money/" target="_blank"&gt;The Big E3 Press Conferences Are A Waste Of Time And Money&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The colorful arch before entering Bethesda’s pre-E3 themepark. This year was my first time at E3, and I spent much of it attending the big pre-E3 conferences. I went to EA’s Live Show on Saturday. On Sunday I attended both Microsoft’s presser in the afternoon, and Bethesda’s bizarre ‘Bethesda Land’ conference that evening. On Monday I missed the Ubisoft press conference, having gotten all my appointments at EA Play pushed back due to traffic issues (I stayed in Venice, EA Play was in Hollywood, most of the rest of E3 stuff took place in downtown LA….) Then, finally, I attended Sony’s showca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Elder Scrolls Online: Morrowind review: The Force Awakens of gaming - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/elder-scrolls-online-morrowind-review-2017-ps4-pc-xbox-one-release-mmo-expansion-a7792001.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIzRRLnuiEtCxqnGhjaZwuEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/elder-scrolls-online-morrowind-review-2017-ps4-pc-xbox-one-release-mmo-expansion-a7792001.html" target="_blank"&gt;Elder Scrolls Online: Morrowind review: The Force Awakens of gaming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Elder Scrolls Online: Morrowind, the first additional 'Chapter' to the MMO (read: expansion), Bethesda seems to have taken a sly tip from Hollywood. This is essentially The Force Awakens of the gaming world: a nostalgic draw that's broad enough in its appeal to satiate newcomers. We zoom back 700 years before the events of 2002's The Elder Scrolls III: Morrowind here, and those subtle differences and shifts in time are obvious in-game. Settlements are (conveniently) smaller; a few of the cities you may remember don't even exist yet, but are hinted at. You may find a page detailing Vive...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Baftas 2017: indie Inside wins big but Uncharted 4 takes best game - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/apr/07/baftas-2017-indie-title-inside-wins-big-but-uncharted-4-takes-best-game</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBsGNmPm0scORJniUPWxjv8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 07:10:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/apr/07/baftas-2017-indie-title-inside-wins-big-but-uncharted-4-takes-best-game" target="_blank"&gt;Baftas 2017: indie Inside wins big but Uncharted 4 takes best game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At last year’s Bafta Game Awards, the developer of Her Story, Sam Barlow, famously so struggled with his three awards that he carried them around in a champagne bucket. This year, indie developer Playdead went one better by winning four for their dystopian puzzle platformer Inside: artistic achievement, game design, narrative, and original property. After their previous game, Limbo, won none from four in 2011, the team at Playdead were delighted to take home so many this year: “We kind of expected to continue the clean slate, so we’re very happy.” Inside just missed out on the award for bes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Here Are Some Short-Term (Non-Bug) Fixes 'Fallout 76' Needs ASAP - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/24/here-are-some-short-term-non-bug-fixes-fallout-76-needs-asap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIwot1TduNlzdOumlIw7Fc8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 13:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/24/here-are-some-short-term-non-bug-fixes-fallout-76-needs-asap/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are Some Short-Term (Non-Bug) Fixes 'Fallout 76' Needs ASAP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Much ink has been spilled about what ails Fallout 76, whether it be its litany of bugs or problems with its core concept, but for this piece, I wanted to focus on things that were hopefully more realistic than total revamps of the entire concept of the game, and less obvious than things that need to be addressed like “get the server to stop kicking people” or “patch bugs that are causing players to become immortal god kings longing for death.” Rather, I wanted to focus on what I think would be a number of short-term fixes for Fallout 76 that could hopefully be rolled out soon-ish...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Building Prey: how artists shape video game worlds - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/jul/26/building-prey-game-developer-arkane-artists-shape-video-game-worlds</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVgg52bbLkL0UZv0yEKw4QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 11:00:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/jul/26/building-prey-game-developer-arkane-artists-shape-video-game-worlds" target="_blank"&gt;Building Prey: how artists shape video game worlds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think of the most impressive, memorable video games of the last 40 years and they tend to have one thing in common: unity of vision. From the sludgy corridors of Doom to the vast art deco chambers of Bioshock, great games take place in intricately realised worlds where every aspect – from armour to architecture – reflects a consistent visual theme. As in the movie industry, the creation of detailed virtual worlds often involves the production of concept art – reams of sketches and paintings, based on early script drafts and discussions, fashioned to provide a target look for designers, arti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>It Sure Is Interesting To Rewatch That 'Fallout 76' Todd Howard E3 Reveal Now - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/21/it-sure-is-interesting-to-rewatch-that-fallout-76-todd-howard-e3-reveal-now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECEyVrWuOgMxqIf3Ci_DWEEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/21/it-sure-is-interesting-to-rewatch-that-fallout-76-todd-howard-e3-reveal-now/" target="_blank"&gt;It Sure Is Interesting To Rewatch That 'Fallout 76' Todd Howard E3 Reveal Now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo by Christian Petersen/Getty Images Fallout 76 has arrived not just as a middling title in a storied franchise, but as possibly the worst-reviewed major release of the year. Of the last few years, in fact, with a current Metascore current hovering around Duke Nukem Forever low-50s levels, a smidge of irony for Bethesda, who once famously denied Obsidian bonuses because Fallout: New Vegas was one point below an 85. I posted my own review yesterday, which did little to bring its average up, and I thought it might be appropriate to go back to where this all starter, to 2018’s E3 reveal of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bafta games awards 2017: Inside and Uncharted 4 lead the way - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/mar/09/bafta-games-awards-2017-inside-and-uncharted-4-lead-the-way</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF__u9V8tPihRRA3ZftTTvUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 10:58:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/mar/09/bafta-games-awards-2017-inside-and-uncharted-4-lead-the-way" target="_blank"&gt;Bafta games awards 2017: Inside and Uncharted 4 lead the way&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bafta has announced the nominations for the 2017 British Academy Game Awards with indie title Inside and blockbuster Uncharted 4 leading the way. Fifty games received nominations across 15 categories, but many appear more than once. Inside has the most potential wins since it is nominated in seven separate categories – every category for which it qualifies. Big-budget blockbuster Uncharted 4, on the other hand, has eight nominations in total, but across fewer categories, so it could take home a maximum of six trophies. In the Performer category, Uncharted 4 represents half the total nominat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'The Elder Scrolls Online: Morrowind' Brings Vvardenfell, PVP Battlegrounds and The Warden Class - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/toddkenreck/2017/01/31/the-elder-scrolls-online-morrowind-brings-vvardenfell-pvp-battlegrounds-and-the-warden-class/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELRL92EKqXtQeMMvVXpvkNYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 19:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/toddkenreck/2017/01/31/the-elder-scrolls-online-morrowind-brings-vvardenfell-pvp-battlegrounds-and-the-warden-class/" target="_blank"&gt;'The Elder Scrolls Online: Morrowind' Brings Vvardenfell, PVP Battlegrounds and The Warden Class&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Elder Scrolls Online: Morrowind has just been announced as one of the biggest updates to the game yet. The game will open up the area of Vvardenfell with a whole new set of adventures, dungeons and characters. This will be the largest new zone added to ESO since the games launch. New updates include a new nature-based magic-using class known as The Warden. There are no details on The Warden’s new skill lines, but we do know that the three will focus on pets, nature abilities and ice. The War Bear will be an ultimate and it will remain as long as it lives, and can be buffed and healed. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Dishonored 2 review: One of the most inventive stealth games ever made - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/dishonored-2-review-corvo-emily-kaldwin-gameplay-bethesda-powers-a7421271.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM85rkCiIMg04aNNWW79zNIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 16:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/dishonored-2-review-corvo-emily-kaldwin-gameplay-bethesda-powers-a7421271.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dishonored 2 review: One of the most inventive stealth games ever made&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're slowly learning that history is a cyclical beast - even if the cost of such a lesson feels like too much to bear. Dunwall has seen 15 years pass since the murder of Empress Jessamine Kaldwin, a trigger for the events of 2012's stealth action-adventure game Dishonored; in which players stalk the shadows as master assassin Corvo Attano, the Empress' bodyguard framed for her murder and hellbent on clearing his name - while ridding his city of its oppressors and putting Jessamine's daughter, Emily, on her rightful place on the throne. On the very anniversary of Jessamine's death, corrupti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>E3 2017 - Bethesda announce Wolfenstein 2, The Evil Within 2 and Doom VR - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/e3-2017-bethesda-announce-wolfenstein-2-evil-within-2-doom/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELhkva6liVxR-l4l-jX-lKYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:03:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/e3-2017-bethesda-announce-wolfenstein-2-evil-within-2-doom/" target="_blank"&gt;E3 2017 - Bethesda announce Wolfenstein 2, The Evil Within 2 and Doom VR&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Wolfenstein 2: The New Colossus announced - Sequel to Shinji Mikami's The Evil Within coming 13 October - New content for Dishonored 2 in The Death of the Outsider - Doom and Fallout 4 displayed in VR Bethesda took to the Los Angeles night to show off its upcoming video games in a sharp E3 conference that followed the US publisher's remit for 'hardcore' titles. It even constructed its very own miniature fairground dubbed 'Bethesdaland', as a handful of new games were announced. The headline reveal was a new Wolfenstein, continuing the successful reboot of the classic Nazi-blasting shooter...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>There Isn't Really Much To Say About The 'Quake Champions' Beta - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/13/there-isnt-really-much-to-say-about-the-quake-champions-beta/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAftHuKsPXdXE4G1SLI-cEQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/13/there-isnt-really-much-to-say-about-the-quake-champions-beta/" target="_blank"&gt;There Isn't Really Much To Say About The 'Quake Champions' Beta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quake Champions This weekend, the Quake Champions beta has lifted its NDA, allowing the game to be streamed for the first time, and everyone can see how it plays and share their thoughts ahead of the game’s eventual 2017 release. After playing the game for a while, and planning to do some sort of “good, bad and in-between” post about it, I find that I’m having trouble formulating terribly complex thoughts about the game past one simple one: Well, it’s Quake. This is a compliment, I suppose. Turning Quake into an alleged “hero shooter” has in reality done very little to make the game stray f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Fallout 4's Ridiculously Huge, 58 GB HD Texture Pack Has Arrived - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/02/07/fallout-4s-ridiculously-huge-58-gb-hd-texture-pack-has-arrived/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMUoCmg5B5k68HbpaZRbNk0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 15:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/02/07/fallout-4s-ridiculously-huge-58-gb-hd-texture-pack-has-arrived/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 4's Ridiculously Huge, 58 GB HD Texture Pack Has Arrived&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: Bethesda/Treyman1115 While there may be no more official Fallout 4 DLC to come, Bethesda has gone and released an enormous update to the game all the same. Enormous in terms of file size, at the very least. The new addition to the game is a 58 GB texture pack, one which adds more detail to the various textures found all throughout the game. If you’re wondering why the game didn’t launch with the upgraded textures in the first place, that file size might give you some clue. It isn’t just that it takes up a lot of hard drive space, and players may have to figure out whether or not it’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Bethesda Should Make Russian-Hacker-Themed 'Fallout 4' DLC After CNN Gaffe - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/01/03/bethesda-should-make-russian-hacker-themed-fallout-4-dlc-after-cnn-gaffe/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHg-bb49jIGrFmbZdnx5FGIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 18:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/01/03/bethesda-should-make-russian-hacker-themed-fallout-4-dlc-after-cnn-gaffe/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda Should Make Russian-Hacker-Themed 'Fallout 4' DLC After CNN Gaffe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN used footage from the ‘Fallout 4′ hacking mini-game in a video about Russian hacks. (Screengrab: Erik Kain) The word “hacking” is rather nefarious sounding, but most people have no idea what it actually involves. When we think of hacking we conjure up images of The Matrix or Mr. Robot, or possibly even video games, which have dozens of examples of hacking mini-games to pull from. Games like Deus Ex: Mankind Divided and BioShock have players navigate little puzzles to access certain areas. And if you want to get into one of the many locked monochrome consoles in Fallout 4, you’ll have to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'Elder Scrolls 6' Is Likely Being Delayed To Protect 'The Elder Scrolls Online' And 'Skyrim' - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/06/14/elder-scrolls-6-is-likely-being-delayed-to-protect-the-elder-scrolls-online-and-skyrim/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJWSMdniONQpwOOe3bwlS6YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/06/14/elder-scrolls-6-is-likely-being-delayed-to-protect-the-elder-scrolls-online-and-skyrim/" target="_blank"&gt;'Elder Scrolls 6' Is Likely Being Delayed To Protect 'The Elder Scrolls Online' And 'Skyrim'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Elder Scrolls Online: Morrowind Bethesda’s showcase was short and sweet this year, focusing only on games in their imminent future like The Evil Within 2 and Wolfenstein 2: The New Colossus. What fans were hoping for was a tease, a tiny glimpse at the long-awaited Elder Scrolls 6. But not only was it not seen, when pressed about the topic, Bethesda’s Todd Howard admitted that Elder Scrolls 6 is relatively low on Bethesda’s to-do list and not even in development officially at this point. “[We] have at least two major titles that they are working on before we’re gonna get to Elder Scrolls...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76': 5 Things That Could Have Saved It From Total Disaster - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/23/fallout-76-5-things-that-could-have-saved-it-from-total-disaster/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHKllbnsz0ncebFc0rTudxQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/23/fallout-76-5-things-that-could-have-saved-it-from-total-disaster/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76': 5 Things That Could Have Saved It From Total Disaster&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The release of Fallout 76 hasn’t been a success. PARIS, FRANCE – OCTOBER 27: Visitors queue to play the video game ‘Fallout 76′ developed and published by Bethesda Softworks during the ‘Paris Games Week’ on October 27, 2018 in Paris, France. ‘Paris Games Week’ is an international trade fair for video games and runs from October 26 to 31, 2018. (Photo by Chesnot/Getty Images) The reviews have been brutal and the game currently has Metacritic scores of 49, 50 and 55 on Xbox One, PS4, and PC, respectively. Despite a recent patch that measured 47 GB in size, it doesn’t appear as though most of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>E3 2017 press conferences, games and rumours - Everything you need to know about gaming's biggest show - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/e3-2017-press-conferences-games-rumours-everything-need-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEESwnqdv7Rdo7aQUxMKjl4EqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 12:28:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/e3-2017-press-conferences-games-rumours-everything-need-know/" target="_blank"&gt;E3 2017 press conferences, games and rumours - Everything you need to know about gaming's biggest show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is that time of the year again when the games world starts turning its gaze to Los Angeles and the industry’s biggest trade show. E3 2017 is now just a month away, with all the hype, hardware and lovely new games that entails. It’s shaping up to be a big one. Microsoft has a shiny new console to show off in Project Scorpio, Sony will want to keep up the momentum for its best-selling PlayStation 4 while Nintendo will be aiming to build on the strong start Switch has had since its launch in March. While the third-party publishers such as EA, Bethesda and Ubisoft will be looking to make the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Here Are The Nominees For The 2017 Game Developer's Choice Awards - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2017/01/06/here-are-the-nominees-for-the-2017-game-developers-choice-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAfJcIX_qyNNKen2B53ONGEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 07:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2017/01/06/here-are-the-nominees-for-the-2017-game-developers-choice-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are The Nominees For The 2017 Game Developer's Choice Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Credit: Bethesda Softworks/YouTube End-of-the-year video game awards are given by players, journalists and reviewers, and industry professionals. The players’ choices carry weight because they are the people who actually play the games. The journalists and reviewers usually have experienced more games than players or pros. Industry professionals know more than anyone else about what it takes to actually make a video game. Each of these groups brings a different perspective to gaming and it’s always interesting to see how their nominees for outstanding achievement in video games differ. The...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Fallout 4 review: 'unmissable' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/fallout-4-review/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEALEEgCTDYSj6fTktoxoTDcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/fallout-4-review/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 4 review: 'unmissable'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like war, some things never change. In Fallout 4, like previous games in the series, you still spend much of your time poking through belongings, separating junk from treasure. Hours are dedicated to talking to people with horrifying faces, most of which you can also blow into mush with a well placed gunshot. It is still incredibly ambitious in scope. And like Fallout 3 and New Vegas, it is unmissable. But despite these similarities, Bethesda has taken some massive steps forward with Fallout 4. The first big change - and it was one that Bethesda shouted about in the marketing campaign - is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim Special Edition' Review (PS4): Conjure Familiar - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2016/10/31/the-elder-scrolls-skyrim-special-edition-review-ps4-conjure-familiar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6KNjxIeGDGw_RDKQ248QoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 14:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2016/10/31/the-elder-scrolls-skyrim-special-edition-review-ps4-conjure-familiar/" target="_blank"&gt;'The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim Special Edition' Review (PS4): Conjure Familiar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo: Bethesda) Skyrim. Just the word will conjure up dozens or hundreds of hours of memories for players who have lived in the world sometime in the past five years. It’s one of the greatest RPGs ever made, and is considered one of the gold standards of the genre to this day. It’s a game that has aged surprisingly well, so a fully-fledged remaster seemed like a no-brainer, and that’s what Bethesda has just given us in the form of this “Special Edition.” However, for those fans hoping that in the past five years, Bethesda has improved upon the original in any significant way, you may be d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Watch Bethesda's E3 2017 Press Conference Right Here - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/06/11/watch-bethesdas-e3-2017-press-conference-right-here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENfuucOLNTnRfA8R662xHZwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/06/11/watch-bethesdas-e3-2017-press-conference-right-here/" target="_blank"&gt;Watch Bethesda's E3 2017 Press Conference Right Here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bethesda’s E3 Showcase remains mostly a mystery. Bethesda’s E3 2017 press conference starts late this evening. The festivities won’t kick off until 9 p.m. Pacific Time, which is midnight on the East Coast. It’s also one of the more intriguing pressers of this year’s E3, since right now the only upcoming game from Bethesda is the new Quake. The game publisher doesn’t have any other upcoming games, so there’s lots of room for big, splashy announcements. One rumor that’s been swirling about is for a game called Starfield, which would apparently bridge the worlds of the Elder Scrolls and Fallou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Well, Here's Some Awkward 'Skyrim Special Edition' Day One Coverage - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/10/28/well-heres-some-awkward-skyrim-special-edition-day-one-coverage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHX9GQckjVTMEYQItHc7NgUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 13:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/10/28/well-heres-some-awkward-skyrim-special-edition-day-one-coverage/" target="_blank"&gt;Well, Here's Some Awkward 'Skyrim Special Edition' Day One Coverage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: Bethesda Here we are, kicking off the official era of Bethesda no longer caring about pre-release review coverage for their games, having pledged to only give members of the press copies of their titles the day before launch, somehow spinning that as good for everyone involved. Needless to say, the press hasn’t been too pleased, and I think most fans agree with them. Even if many gaming fans have been at odds with the press over different issues in the last few years, “no information about the functionality or quality of a game ahead of launch” isn’t exactly something anyone but a ga...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Bethesda's Decision To Withhold Review Copies Is Bad For Gamers And Sets A Dangerous Precedent - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/10/25/bethesdas-decision-to-withhold-review-copies-is-bad-for-gamers-and-sets-a-dangerous-precedent/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOOaIKcp22Z61WPATwdXNWUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 02:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/10/25/bethesdas-decision-to-withhold-review-copies-is-bad-for-gamers-and-sets-a-dangerous-precedent/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda's Decision To Withhold Review Copies Is Bad For Gamers And Sets A Dangerous Precedent&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skyrim: Special Edition comes out Friday; reviewers get code on Thursday. (Credit: Bethesda) Bethesda has changed their policy regarding review copies in a way that’s bad for consumers, critics, the relationship between Bethesda and its friends in the media, and the video game industry as a whole. It sets a bad precedent for video game publishers and ultimately will lead to less information in the hands of consumers. Today in a blog post, Bethesda wrote that “we value media reviews.” They then went on to prove how no, they do not in fact value reviews and would prefer to do away with them e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'Dishonored 2' Totally Fumbles Its Split-Hero Core Concept - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/11/11/dishonored-2-totally-fumbles-its-split-hero-core-concept/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDoPM-TmgODmg0WIJrHq-OEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 15:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/11/11/dishonored-2-totally-fumbles-its-split-hero-core-concept/" target="_blank"&gt;'Dishonored 2' Totally Fumbles Its Split-Hero Core Concept&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: Bethesda Dishonored 2 comes out today, and thanks to Bethesda’s new review copy policy, you probably won’t see many full reviews out for at least a little while. But copies did go out about a day and a half before launch, and as such, I’ve worked my way through most of the game after a couple marathon sessions. And there’s one aspect I feel like I need to comment on above all others. Dishonored 2 was sold on a pretty central concept, a sequel to the acclaimed original that lets you play either as Corvo, the hero of the first game, or (spoilers) Emily, his daughter and current empress...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>3 Reasons 'Elder Scrolls Online' Now Has 8.5 Million Players - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/toddkenreck/2017/02/27/3-reason-elder-scrolls-online-now-has-8-5-million-players/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEqGZ5LfWJilEHBNCcbtQhkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/toddkenreck/2017/02/27/3-reason-elder-scrolls-online-now-has-8-5-million-players/" target="_blank"&gt;3 Reasons 'Elder Scrolls Online' Now Has 8.5 Million Players&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;You would be hard-pressed to find an MMO that has so rapidly evolved as Elder Scrolls Online. What was once a game that was met with mixed reviews has course corrected into becoming one of the best games out there. In a recent interview with MMORG.com, game director Matt Firor said that ESO has 8.5 million players based on copies of the game that have been sold. There are lot of good reasons for why ESO is growing in players in such an otherwise tough genre. (Image: Bethesda) You can go anywhere at anytime: Elder Scrolls Online once had level-based zones which caused some quests to be nearl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Se anuncian los nominados para los Game Developers Choice Awards - Niubie</title><link>https://www.niubie.com/2017/01/se-anuncian-los-nominados-para-los-game-developers-choice-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF44rOsDetonzHGlWWc9ifUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsunyCjCC6NkCMKv-qgM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 20:02:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.niubie.com/2017/01/se-anuncian-los-nominados-para-los-game-developers-choice-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;Se anuncian los nominados para los Game Developers Choice Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Niubie&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Se han revelado los nominados a los Game Developers Choice Awards, donde los títulos que destacan con más menciones son Inside, Overwatch, Firewatch y Uncharted 4. Los premios a los ganadores se entregarán el 1 de marzo durante la Game Developers Conference 2017, en un evento conducido nuevamente por Tim Schafer, fundador de Double Fine Productions. Sin más, enseguida tienen la lista completa de nominados: JUEGO DEL AÑO - Uncharted 4: A Thief's End (Naughty Dog / Sony Interactive Entertainment) - Overwatch (Blizzard Entertainment) - Inside (Playdead) - Dishonored 2 (Arkane Studios / Bethesd...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.niubie.com">Niubie</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Review (Xbox One X): Look Upon My Works And Despair - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2018/11/20/fallout-76-review-xbox-one-x-look-upon-my-works-and-despair/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM9pxtsq2vJmeacljSDjtEkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 13:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2018/11/20/fallout-76-review-xbox-one-x-look-upon-my-works-and-despair/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Review (Xbox One X): Look Upon My Works And Despair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 When is the right time to review a deeply flawed, clearly unfinished game? Is it when more bugs are patched? When the servers stabilize? When the player population becomes more engaged? When the content is bolstered by enough new stuff to pump life into the world? Perhaps, so maybe a week and 35-40 hours with Fallout 76 isn’t giving it enough of a fair shake, and yet I think the line has to be drawn somewhere when it comes to the state of new games at launch. I’m drawing it here. Fallout 76 feels like a shell of a game. It looks, sounds and acts like a Fallout title, but undernea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Dishonored 2' Review: A Disappointing Sequel - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2016/11/18/dishonored-2-review-a-disappointing-sequel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHafxlQBppOBvFCzZrIo4hUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2016/11/18/dishonored-2-review-a-disappointing-sequel/" target="_blank"&gt;'Dishonored 2' Review: A Disappointing Sequel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minor spoils follow. Credit: Bethesda Dishonored was one of my favorite games of 2012, combining terrific first-person combat with magic powers and a strong, but optional, stealth component. You could play the game however you liked, sewing chaos and death, or sneaking your way through each mission. As an assassin out for justice and revenge, you could kill your objectives or take them out non-lethally (though not necessarily non-violently.) It was a breath of fresh air in the gaming space, with a beautiful art-style reminiscent of Half-Life 2 (Dishonored’s art director worked on both games...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Target May Have Just Leaked The Existence Of Bethesda's 'Game of Thrones' Video Game - Forbes Now</title><link>//www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/08/27/target-may-have-just-leaked-the-existence-of-bethesdas-game-of-thrones-video-game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOCK9wznuOBescTvL8Ug5wYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 15:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="//www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/08/27/target-may-have-just-leaked-the-existence-of-bethesdas-game-of-thrones-video-game/" target="_blank"&gt;Target May Have Just Leaked The Existence Of Bethesda's 'Game of Thrones' Video Game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Game of Thrones For years now, I’ve been asking why no one has bothered to make a proper Game of Thrones video game, given the enormous popularity of the series and the notion that Westeros existing as a fantasy open world RPG in a game seems like a no-brainer. We’ve gotten a few poor attempts at Thrones titles over the years, most recently Telltale’s narrative-driven game that had to awkwardly work within existing show plot points, but never a full-on, massive RPG. That may be about to change. A NeoGAF user spotted a new listing at Target that appears to be a mostly blank landing page exce...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>'Only Yu Can Save The World' In Latest 'Prey' Trailer - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/03/23/only-yu-can-save-the-world-in-latest-prey-trailer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO6RzDtRQ_neR3_MEeC51aIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 16:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/03/23/only-yu-can-save-the-world-in-latest-prey-trailer/" target="_blank"&gt;'Only Yu Can Save The World' In Latest 'Prey' Trailer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The above trailer is all about freedom of choice in Arkane Studios’ upcoming sci-fi first-person-shooter Prey, and about how your choices shape the main protagonist, Morgan Yu. It’s also an Asian pun, and you…or, er…’Yu’ won’t be able to get that pun out of your head the entire time you/Yu watch it. Whether you/Yu take this sort of punning as mildly racist or just an unnecessary distraction while trying to watch a video about a game you’re interested in is up to you/Yu. You/Yu might not even notice! You/Yu might not even care! For me, every time one of the developers says “you” in the video...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>This Is What Worries Me About Bethesda's New 'Prey' - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/04/27/this-is-what-worries-me-about-bethesdas-new-prey/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBW2x7ROyXNjzjgx2ZQa3w8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 19:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/04/27/this-is-what-worries-me-about-bethesdas-new-prey/" target="_blank"&gt;This Is What Worries Me About Bethesda's New 'Prey'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can play the first hour of Prey on PS4 or Xbox One right now, but not on PC. There’s a new demo out for Prey, the rebooted sci-fi shooter from Dishonored 2 developer Arkane Studios and publisher Bethesda. You can download the 13+ GB demo right now on PS4 and Xbox One—but not on PC. The demo is aptly titled Prey Demo: Opening Hour. In it you can play the opening hour of the game, obviously, and see if it’s something you might like to buy. That’s great, and I love this demo renaissance that’s blossomed across the industry. Mostly demos are multiplayer betas these days, so it’s especially ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Prey is the first-person shooter that lets you play as a coffee mug - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/prey-first-person-shooter-arkane-studios-gameplay-bethesda-coffee-mug-a7695861.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENSTKr9tCZ3wyLZt_VzU_UYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 14:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/prey-first-person-shooter-arkane-studios-gameplay-bethesda-coffee-mug-a7695861.html" target="_blank"&gt;Prey is the first-person shooter that lets you play as a coffee mug&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the vastly overcrowded world of the first-person shooter, it’s strange what makes a mark. The ability to transform into a coffee cup and roll around the floor, for one, as it’s with little shame I admit that’s what first peaked my interest in Arkane Studios’ latest, Prey. That, and the fact Arkane are behind the wildly entertaining Dishonored series, now once more teaming with Bethesda on a remake-in-name-only of 2006’s Prey. We’re flinging ourselves a world away from the towering Victoriana-steampunk of Dishonored here, however, with the preview I had the chance to play seeing you wake ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Gods, guns and gross-out: the best video games of autumn 2017 - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/sep/14/best-video-games-of-autumn-2017-star-wars-cuphead-super-mario-nintendo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECr9ICJejfb40tOnLkcsn6EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 06:00:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/sep/14/best-video-games-of-autumn-2017-star-wars-cuphead-super-mario-nintendo" target="_blank"&gt;Gods, guns and gross-out: the best video games of autumn 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dishonored: Death of the Outsider A spin-off from the acclaimed Dishonored stealth adventures, Death of the Outsider pits popular background character Billie Lurk against the God-like figure at the centre of the first two titles. After Horizon: Zero Dawn, Life is Strange: Before the Storm and Uncharted: The Lost Legacy, it’s another big title with an intriguing female protagonist, and the putrid grandeur of this steampunk universe is always worth wallowing in. - 15 September (Bethesda); PC, Playstation 4, Xbox One. Cuphead In development for several years, the much-anticipated platform adve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>When is the Bethesda E3 2017 press conference and can we expect Starfield and The Evil Within 2? - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/bethesda-e3-2017-press-conference-can-expect-starfield-evil/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIAr3n8SWsna-0vUfsDzRacqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 12:13:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/bethesda-e3-2017-press-conference-can-expect-starfield-evil/" target="_blank"&gt;When is the Bethesda E3 2017 press conference and can we expect Starfield and The Evil Within 2?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bethesda returns for its third E3 press conference. The boutique publisher has made a name for itself over the past three years for its fast-paced, gameplay-heavy string of announcements for meaty, ‘hardcore’ titles. Clearly the Maryland team has a taste for it and we expect more of the same this year, catching more details for Quake Champions and possibly seeing a sequel to The Evil Within. There should also be a new game from Bethesda’s own Game Studios (Fallout, Elder Scrolls) which could be one of the show’s most intriguing announcements. E3 2017 - The 33 most wanted gamesWhen is E3 201...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Prey' Day One Impressions: What Kind Of Game Is This, Exactly? - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/05/prey-day-one-impressions-what-kind-of-game-is-this-exactly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEJ_8pVf96qFaXxEaFhSOzAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 15:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/05/prey-day-one-impressions-what-kind-of-game-is-this-exactly/" target="_blank"&gt;'Prey' Day One Impressions: What Kind Of Game Is This, Exactly?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arkane’s Prey I’m not exactly sure how official, scored reviews from some outlets are online already for Prey, considering review copies just went out yesterday (broken street dates, but like most people, I’m just starting to get into the game, having put in 4-5 hours since I got my hands on it. This is a true first impressions piece, because not only did I not attend the Prey live preview event, I didn’t play the hour-long demo this week and uh, I have not played 2006’s Prey either. So this is literally my first time with this game and this series. I’m a bit confused. The marketing for Pre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Skyrim: Special Edition interview - Todd Howard on remastering the fantasy epic - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/skyrim-special-edition-interview---todd-howard-on-remastering-th/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0ZHV03uVKYwfPqUhoTpFcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 10:11:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/skyrim-special-edition-interview---todd-howard-on-remastering-th/" target="_blank"&gt;Skyrim: Special Edition interview - Todd Howard on remastering the fantasy epic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2011 the Game Director of Bethesda Game Studios, Todd Howard, finished up work on The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim. This Norse fantasy, sandbox role-playing game was one of the most anticipated releases of the last console generation, and the hype was palpable. It shot to unprecedented success, earning countless Game of the Year awards, smashing sales targets and capturing the hearts and minds of millions. As we approach the game’s fifth anniversary, Bethesda is about to commemorate its original release with a remaster. It’s no surprise –– the game still has an enormous fan base, reams of cos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ten Things I Wish I Knew When I Started 'Prey' - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/09/ten-things-i-wish-i-knew-when-i-started-prey/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjf1QxNZx84hZgqVD7QcLsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 15:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/09/ten-things-i-wish-i-knew-when-i-started-prey/" target="_blank"&gt;Ten Things I Wish I Knew When I Started 'Prey'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arkane’s Prey Prey came out last Friday, and I’ve been doing little else but play it since. The review situation was a little wonky so I didn’t get to beat the game before it was live, but that doesn’t mean my incessant play hasn’t taught me some valuable lessons. As I tend to always do, I wanted to impart some of my wisdom from my time spent with the game. In this case, this is a rare occasion where I have not fully beaten the game yet, but I believe I’m probably about 70-80% done, and there are so many things to talk about with Prey, I have plenty of material regardless. This will not get...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>You Get More "Skyrim: Special Edition" On Xbox One Than On Playstation 4 - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2016/10/26/you-get-more-skyrim-special-edition-on-xbox-one-than-on-playstation-4/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAsXytJVs1eDbU4rM3fX6e0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 07:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2016/10/26/you-get-more-skyrim-special-edition-on-xbox-one-than-on-playstation-4/" target="_blank"&gt;You Get More "Skyrim: Special Edition" On Xbox One Than On Playstation 4&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Credit: Bethesda Softworks/YouTube Comparisons of video games on the Xbox One (XB1) and Playstation 4 (PS4) often involve arcane differences in graphics performance that have little or no effect on gameplay if the game is doing its job of engaging the player. That’s not the case with Bethesda’s Skyrim: Special Edition that is scheduled for release this Friday. Both consoles have the game but the XB1 has more of it than the PS4. Skyrim has been a target for the modding community since it first appeared in 2011 thanks to Bethesda’s staunch support of mods for its games. A little less than a y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Dishonored 2: Live-action trailer shows off Emily's new powers - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/dishonored-2-live-action-trailer-ps4-xbox-pre-order-emily-kaldwin-shadow-walk-a7378206.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMlF3l2wVGpd8fCeGcz--7oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 12:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/dishonored-2-live-action-trailer-ps4-xbox-pre-order-emily-kaldwin-shadow-walk-a7378206.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dishonored 2: Live-action trailer shows off Emily's new powers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fans of steampunk aesthetics and shadowy assassin skills are in for a treat: Bethesda's making a grand return to the world of Dishonored. Dishonored 2 flashes forward 15 years from the original game; the young girl you once battled through Dunwall to help to her rightful place on the throne - at least, depending on how you played the game - is now a grown woman. Though Dunwall has prospered under Emily Kaldwin's rule, she is suddenly dethroned by Delilah, a deranged witch armed with powerful black magic. What's most exciting here is that Bethesda lets players explore its world and missions ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Dishonored: Death of the Outsider review – short, but strong on atmosphere - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/sep/18/dishonored-death-of-the-outsider-review-arkane</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAsXDkjPjvkfVt5hWnKRD7YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 10:05:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/sep/18/dishonored-death-of-the-outsider-review-arkane" target="_blank"&gt;Dishonored: Death of the Outsider review – short, but strong on atmosphere&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dishonored’s new standalone adventure has quite the setup: you have to murder a god. Throughout the five year history of this steampunk stealth adventure series, this eponymous deity, the Outsider, has been at the centre of everything – dealing in regicide, revenge and all the juicy stuff in between. He’s an omnipotent force who watches and intervenes from the void – a mysterious place between worlds – giving mortals like Billie Lurk, our new protagonist, spectral powers. In Dishonored 2, protagonists Corvo Attano and Emily Kaldwin each had their own unique abilities to reflect their person...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>If You Don't Know 'Prey' Is Coming Out Tomorrow, I Don't Blame You - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/04/if-you-dont-know-prey-is-coming-out-tomorrow-i-dont-blame-you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIlDyx8vDWZvlAZnuYhQTQQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 19:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/04/if-you-dont-know-prey-is-coming-out-tomorrow-i-dont-blame-you/" target="_blank"&gt;If You Don't Know 'Prey' Is Coming Out Tomorrow, I Don't Blame You&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prey, out tomorrow Tomorrow, Bethesda will release Prey, their long-gestating space-horror game, but if you didn’t have any idea that was the case, I don’t blame you. I blame Bethesda. We have once again arrived in a situation where Bethesda’s new policy forbidding early, embargoed review copies for their games may be doing active harm to that game, only this time I think Prey might be the prime example of the possible effects of that decision. Last year, Bethesda announced that it would no longer be giving out advance review copies of its games with preset embargoes. They were inspired to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'Prey' Is Starting To Grow On Me Like An Alien Space Virus - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/06/prey-is-starting-to-grow-on-me-like-an-alien-space-virus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIJRHcODClK_EVE-QzcCDBYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 15:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/06/prey-is-starting-to-grow-on-me-like-an-alien-space-virus/" target="_blank"&gt;'Prey' Is Starting To Grow On Me Like An Alien Space Virus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arkane’s Prey Yesterday, Bethesda released Prey, its new space horror(?) game that revamps the concept of the original from 2006 and is heavily influenced by System Shock, Deus Ex and Dishonored (it shares a developer with that last one). I wrote up my initial impressions based on my first few hours of play, and it seemed like a game that didn’t really understand its identity. The action was clunky, the stealth/horror aspect wasn’t really scary and the puzzles were pretty straightforward. But while I still think that it doesn’t really excel in any of those areas, the more I play (and I’ve t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>‘Fallout 76’ Brings Players Together for a Crushingly Lonely Experience - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fallout-76-brings-players-together-for-a-crushingly-lonely-experience</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIf7hBDDvsSzBtri1CdDAB8qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMKv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 09:55:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/fallout-76-brings-players-together-for-a-crushingly-lonely-experience" target="_blank"&gt;‘Fallout 76’ Brings Players Together for a Crushingly Lonely Experience&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bethesda “Nobody helps anybody anymore.” So says an audio recording pulled off a dead body sitting on the porch of a small shack that has seen better days. The body had been “Sophie,” and in her final days, she wasn’t too happy about her situation. She had survived the bomb dropping, the one that irradiated the Appalachian world in which Fallout 76 exists. But in the apocalypse, things went from bad to worse and she, I assume, sat on the porch and waited to die of blight or radiation poisoning or something equally horrific. These audio recordings have been around in games for a long time—no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>How I Finally Fell In Love With 'Skyrim' This Christmas - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/12/30/how-i-finally-fell-in-love-with-skyrim-this-christmas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPO64TYblNdwMmOh_UDHsaAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 01:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/12/30/how-i-finally-fell-in-love-with-skyrim-this-christmas/" target="_blank"&gt;How I Finally Fell In Love With 'Skyrim' This Christmas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skyrim Special Edition (Credit: Bethesda) I’ve always wanted to like The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim more than I ever have in practice—a problem I had with Oblivion as well, and one that I have with lots of RPGs (as well as MMOs like The Elder Scrolls Online.) Skyrim is riddled with problems, of course, from bugs and glitches to uneven acting and quest design. But it’s always been the lackluster combat that left me cold. And I hate that, because this is exactly the kind of game I dreamed about as a kid: Sprawling, epic, filled with secrets and quests and magical items, dark secrets and shadowy ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>E3 2016: Bethesda unveil Quake Champions, Skyrim remastered release date, new Fallout 4 content and Prey reboot - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/e3-2016-bethesda-unveil-quake-champions-skyrim-remastered-releas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF0k3X9NFk9VZEKoZbut4PEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 06:20:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/e3-2016-bethesda-unveil-quake-champions-skyrim-remastered-releas/" target="_blank"&gt;E3 2016: Bethesda unveil Quake Champions, Skyrim remastered release date, new Fallout 4 content and Prey reboot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bethesda Softworks,has looked to consolidate its position as one of the video game industry’s premier third-party publishers with a strong showcase at E3 2016. At its showcase at the LA Hangar, Bethesda revealed a quickfire selection of games, including brand new titles, reboots, remasters and content for existing games. Here are the highlights. The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim Special Edition Bethesda Games Studios Skyrim has been one of the most successful fantasy RPGs of recent years. The tale of the Dragonborn, travelling the northern realms of Tamriel, captured the imagination with its brea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>E3 2017 diversity report: female game characters mask lack of progress - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/jun/16/e3-2017-diversity-report-female-game-characters-mask-lack-of-progress-white-men-conferences</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKtrMMxPnLyLh2xEwUHE4Z4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 11:00:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/jun/16/e3-2017-diversity-report-female-game-characters-mask-lack-of-progress-white-men-conferences" target="_blank"&gt;E3 2017 diversity report: female game characters mask lack of progress&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most gamers, early June is a kind of video-game Christmas. Summer brings E3 and its associated press conferences with the biggest names in publishing and development telling us what games and consoles to expect in the coming year. For the most part, audiences are shown cinematic trailer after cinematic trailer of grizzled white men brandishing guns on missions they’ve “just gotta take alone” introduced by white dudes in a blazer/T-shirt/jeans/trainers combo. Some shows manage to do better than others in offering audiences diverse games, and diverse speakers. Last year, we looked at how ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76': The 5 Harshest Critical Quotes From Respected Reviewers - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/22/fallout-76-the-5-harshest-critical-quotes-from-respected-reviewers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAJmHWY8Q45G1IKTrUDmxysqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/22/fallout-76-the-5-harshest-critical-quotes-from-respected-reviewers/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76': The 5 Harshest Critical Quotes From Respected Reviewers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Game development is difficult. Studios are celebrated when they come up with innovative concepts that step outside the box when the results are fun and engaging experiences. Unfortunately, new-fangled ideas don’t always pan out, and that seems to be the problem with Bethesda’s Fallout 76. Fallout 76 Most of the major publications have weighed in on the latest edition from the successful series and let’s just say the review scores haven’t been favorable. Fallout 76 [PS4 - 50] https://t.co/p31OUPH9zx [PC - 55] https://t.co/cc16KEpLfP [XONE - 53] https://t.co/c7cdWeGIf1 IGN: “The rich wastelan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Oddly, 'Skyrim' Isn't Confirmed For The Nintendo Switch - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/10/21/oddly-skyrim-isnt-confirmed-for-the-nintendo-switch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRG_5ro1gWrboZ5dMbo7zsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/10/21/oddly-skyrim-isnt-confirmed-for-the-nintendo-switch/" target="_blank"&gt;Oddly, 'Skyrim' Isn't Confirmed For The Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skyrim may only appear on Nintendo’s Switch in this trailer. (Credit: Nintendo/Bethesda) There’s a new trailer for Bethesda’s upcoming Skyrim: Special Edition out. Once again, it looks really sharp, improving on the original in all sorts of ways, including the addition of volumetric god rays, improved textures, and more color. Here’s the new trailer: There’s something odd about the trailer, however. It notes a release on PC, PS4 and Xbox One. There’s nothing at all about Nintendo’s new console, the Switch. In yesterday’s Switch reveal, we clearly saw the game being played, but developer and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>My Own 'Review' Of 'Prey' Underscores Bethesda's Embargo Policy Problems - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/08/my-own-review-of-prey-underscores-bethesdas-embargo-policy-problems/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHNmY8VjwVr_aVmzS7wWin8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/05/08/my-own-review-of-prey-underscores-bethesdas-embargo-policy-problems/" target="_blank"&gt;My Own 'Review' Of 'Prey' Underscores Bethesda's Embargo Policy Problems&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arkane’s Prey I’m getting pretty deep into Prey now, Bethesda’s new space-horror-puzzle-explorer (sure we’ll go with that) which was released on Friday. Outside of my thoughts on the game, I’ve already talked about Bethesda’s unique review copy policy in which there’s no embargo and codes go out just a few hours before launch, and I really didn’t want to get into it again, but something’s just happened that illustrates the problems with this idea pretty clearly. My Twitter feed is full of other game journalists getting 10, 20, 40 hours into their Prey playthroughs, so I wanted to check the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'Dishonored 2' and 'Titanfall 2's Unique Level: Who Wore It Better? - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/11/14/dishonored-2-and-titanfall-2s-time-hop-level-who-wore-it-better/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMqDARXjznlb8OXBHedDm_MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 15:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/11/14/dishonored-2-and-titanfall-2s-time-hop-level-who-wore-it-better/" target="_blank"&gt;'Dishonored 2' and 'Titanfall 2's Unique Level: Who Wore It Better?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: EA/Bethesda Dishonored 2 and Titanfall 2 aren’t exactly games that have all that much in common besides the number after their name and the fact that they both came out within a couple weeks of each other this fall. But this who have played both will realize that they do share one important connection, a concept for a level that’s almost identical. Mild Spoilers Follow. In about the middle of each game, both Titanfall 2 and Dishonored 2 throw players for a loop by introducing a one-level-only mechanic that allows them to hop back and forth in time seamlessly in particular level. In T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>I'll Say It Again: 'Fallout 76' Needs An Offline Mode - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/18/ill-say-it-again-fallout-76-needs-an-offline-mode/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMgDhvAWa4Fyv0WhbmsXCxcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 14:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/18/ill-say-it-again-fallout-76-needs-an-offline-mode/" target="_blank"&gt;I'll Say It Again: 'Fallout 76' Needs An Offline Mode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 I don’t particularly enjoy essentially rewriting an article I’ve already written, as I said this exact thing before Fallout 76 was released. And yet spending a full 24 hours with the game (as an in-game challenge completion pop-up helpfully told me), I have evolving thoughts on this. Namely, I still very much believe that Fallout 76 needs an offline mode. I thought one of two things could happen when I got to play the full release of Fallout 76: 1) I would see the light and understand that yes, this game really is better on live servers with other people. or 2) The game is so bad...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76 beta: 6 things for Bethesda to address at release - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fallout-76-beta-review-6-things-bethesda-address-release-date/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRh4iXBfJCau_YqlH4-QsQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 13:36:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fallout-76-beta-review-6-things-bethesda-address-release-date/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76 beta: 6 things for Bethesda to address at release&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 will release on Wednesday 14 November, but we have already been given a good idea of how the game plays from a series of beta sessions, that have happened sporadically over the last couple of weeks. As this is the first time Bethesda has taken an post-apocalyptic world online the Fallout 76 Beta, for people who had pre-ordered and downloaded the game set in West Virginia, allowed the US-based video game publisher to stress test its servers. And see what changes it has to make to fix glitches before the game’s full release next week. With the Fallout 76 Beta over ahead of the full...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76: Server Launch Times, Day-One Patch And What You Need To Know - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/12/fallout-76-server-launch-times-day-one-patch-and-what-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwl5Y3Ck-2U0P8snWfr5YsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/12/fallout-76-server-launch-times-day-one-patch-and-what-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76: Server Launch Times, Day-One Patch And What You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 We’ve all been screwing around in the beta for a few days, but it’s time to finally dive into West Virginia with both feet. Bethesda’s ambitious, odd and controversial Fallout 76 launches tomorrow, marking arguably the most interesting AAA release of the fall season. It’s a Fallout game, make no mistake about that. It’s just a very strange Fallout game, one that both fits the mold of previous titles and totally turns the idea on its head. First things first, however: this is an online game, and so we’re not playing until servers go live and the developer lets us loose into the wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Release Date And 10 Things You Should Know Before You Buy The Game - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/12/fallout-76-release-date-and-10-things-you-should-know-before-you-buy-the-game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0-Kzxwor7kUecvnOnPbZ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 15:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/12/fallout-76-release-date-and-10-things-you-should-know-before-you-buy-the-game/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Release Date And 10 Things You Should Know Before You Buy The Game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next piece of Bethesda’s post-apocalyptic Fallout franchise will be available on November 14 for PC, Xbox One and PlayStation 4. It’s called Fallout 76, and by all accounts, it is a noticeably different experience than the previous versions of the series. Fallout 76 With a larger map, a new twist on the core plot and a different approach to gameplay, Fallout 76 figures to be one of the more memorable releases in the series’ history. Let’s take a look at the 10 things you should know about Fallout 76. It’s Thin On Pre-Order Bonuses The biggest pre-order bonus has already expired. Gamers ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>I Feel Like I Already Know Everything That's Going To Happen With The 'Fallout 76' Launch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/12/i-feel-like-i-already-know-everything-thats-going-to-happen-with-the-fallout-76-launch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBDi36lLpeiSYdih9dr4gQUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/12/i-feel-like-i-already-know-everything-thats-going-to-happen-with-the-fallout-76-launch/" target="_blank"&gt;I Feel Like I Already Know Everything That's Going To Happen With The 'Fallout 76' Launch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76765 I don’t like judging a game before its technically released, but sometimes, it’s hard not to. Fallout 76 is out tomorrow, and it’s going to be buggy. I feel I can say this with 99% confidence. For one thing, Bethesda games are always buggy. For another, the beta had some bugs in it, and it wasn’t all that long ago. For another, Bethesda basically told us that things were going to be a little rough in the early stages. If you’re playing this game at launch, that’s the first thing you should have on your mind. The thing about this release, however, is that I have this strange se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Is A Success In Spite Of All Its Pointless Online Nonsense - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/14/fallout-76-is-a-success-in-spite-of-all-its-pointless-online-nonsense/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHJcDdHv5YvrDOYvVDFiMcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 15:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/14/fallout-76-is-a-success-in-spite-of-all-its-pointless-online-nonsense/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Is A Success In Spite Of All Its Pointless Online Nonsense&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Today is officially launch day for Fallout 76, but in an endless parade of Bethesda’s ongoing bugs with the game, it launched in some regions and some platforms early yesterday. This also comes after a number of limited time betas, so many players, myself included, have gotten our hands on the game for a good while now. God help me, overall, I like it. While I have been almost relentlessly negative about many aspects of Fallout 76 since its inception, playing the game so far has been a…mostly enjoyable experience. But with one big caveat. The reason I’m enjoying Fallout 76 is bec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Golden Joystick Awards 2018 | How to watch and all the nominees - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/golden-joystick-awards-2018-watch-nominees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3KA0fVaF1wB9q8sax9LyAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 14:56:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/golden-joystick-awards-2018-watch-nominees/" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Joystick Awards 2018 | How to watch and all the nominees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 36th Golden Joystick Awards 2018 are imminent, with the world's longest-running and most prominent game award ceremonies taking place this Friday. The Golden Joysticks will be at the Bloomsbury Big Top on 16 November and will be hosted by comedian Danny Wallace, the awards will celebrate the last year of the gaming industry across multiple categories. The categories cover a wide range across the industry including storytelling and esports alongside the more traditional disciplines of audio and visual. There is also a new category this year recognising the best co-operative games. Sony's...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item></channel></rss>