<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Microsoft Corporation - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFJ6ZGpRU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:27:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Microsoft adopts ethical principles aiming to bar misuse of face recognition technology - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-microsoft-facial-recognition/microsoft-adopts-ethical-principles-aiming-to-bar-misuse-of-face-recognition-technology-idUSKBN1O52NS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG-LmMTy0RaJqyJK7P4Mt9sqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:42:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-microsoft-facial-recognition/microsoft-adopts-ethical-principles-aiming-to-bar-misuse-of-face-recognition-technology-idUSKBN1O52NS" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft adopts ethical principles aiming to bar misuse of face recognition technology&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Corp on Thursday announced ethical principles for the use of its facial recognition technology, saying it would bar such technology from being used to engage in unlawful discrimination and would encourage customers to be transparent when deploying such services. In a blog post on Thursday, Microsoft President Brad Smith pushed for urgency in regulating facial-recognition technology, while adding that tech companies should self regulate too. "We believe it's important for governments in 2019 to start adopting laws to regulate this technology. The facial recognition genie, so to spe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Google’s Pixel Slate: Great Chromebook, not-so-great iPad/Surface rival - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90272364/googles-pixel-slate-great-chromebook-not-so-great-ipad-surface-rival</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHEukDmmvBBRCMQzQw3xFwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 06:00:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90272364/googles-pixel-slate-great-chromebook-not-so-great-ipad-surface-rival" target="_blank"&gt;Google’s Pixel Slate: Great Chromebook, not-so-great iPad/Surface rival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since their 2011 launch, Chromebooks have been synonymous with low-cost, easily managed laptops that have strong appeal for education. But in 2013, when Google shipped the first Chromebook Pixel–a premium machine with a touchscreen–it became clear that the company was intent on exploring new frontiers for its browser-centric Chrome OS operating system. Google’s new Pixel Slate tablet, which starts at $599, represents the culmination of those efforts. With its minimalist operating system and minimalist form factor, it’s the best pure web tablet ever made. But the Pixel Slate also offers the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Microsoft president calls for new rules for facial recognition technology to prevent bias - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/07/microsoft-president-calls-new-rules-facial-recognition-technology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHQrArm1IeAkRsgr7-iiqAUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:43:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/07/microsoft-president-calls-new-rules-facial-recognition-technology/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft president calls for new rules for facial recognition technology to prevent bias&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft president Brad Smith has called for new regulation to govern the widespread roll-out of facial recognition technology to avoid bias and discrimination. Speaking at an event in Washington DC on Thursday, Mr Smith said that countries around the world are at risk of a "race to the bottom" as companies are forced to choose between being responsible to society or improving their market share. Mr Smith said: "We believe that the world needs to have confidence that this technology will be used well, that people's rights need to be protected. "We also believe that if the world has confide...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Microsoft president calls for regulation of AI facial recognition technology over discrimination fears - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/microsoft-google-ai-facial-recognition-technology-brad-smith-discrimination-civil-liberties-us-a8673181.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOkeLHEBRLp78het0d2R9b8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/microsoft-google-ai-facial-recognition-technology-brad-smith-discrimination-civil-liberties-us-a8673181.html" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft president calls for regulation of AI facial recognition technology over discrimination fears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president of Microsoft has called for greater government regulation of AI facial recognition technology, because of the risk of it discriminating against women and people of colour. In a rare incident of a tech giant calling for greater government scrutiny, Brad Smith said such regulation would help avoid “a commercial race to the bottom, with tech companies forced to choose between social responsibility and market success”. The comments of Mr Smith, 59, which were released at the same time as a report by a research group consisting of both Microsoft and Google employees also calling fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Taking aim at Intel, Qualcomm launches chip for business PCs - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-intel/taking-aim-at-intel-qualcomm-launches-chip-for-business-pcs-idUSKBN1O52EF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMQ8c2KjxC_rzSRxRnY1uL8qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:50:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-intel/taking-aim-at-intel-qualcomm-launches-chip-for-business-pcs-idUSKBN1O52EF" target="_blank"&gt;Taking aim at Intel, Qualcomm launches chip for business PCs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), the biggest supplier of chips for mobile phones, on Thursday pushed further into the PC market with a line of chips designed to power business machines. Qualcomm's "Snapdragon" processor chips historically have been at the heart of mobile phones like Alphabet Inc's (GOOGL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Google Pixel phone and many Samsung Electronics Co Ltd (005930.KS: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) devices. Over the past year, though, Qualcomm adapted its chips to operate PCs running Microsoft Corp's (MSFT.O: Quot...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Google Chrome Code Will Power The Next Microsoft Edge Browser - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/leemathews/2018/12/06/google-chrome-code-will-power-the-next-microsoft-edge-browser/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELDQnz0d4GEeXkWTU2zWcKsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/leemathews/2018/12/06/google-chrome-code-will-power-the-next-microsoft-edge-browser/" target="_blank"&gt;Google Chrome Code Will Power The Next Microsoft Edge Browser&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, Internet Explorer ruled the World Wide Web. As time went on, IE languished and was knocked off its perch by Firefox and Google Chrome. Then Microsoft fought back with a new browser called Edge. Image: Microsoft Edge was new inside and out, built to provide the best browsing experience on Windows 10. That was three years ago. Today, despite the fact that it’s an excellent browser, Edge is still struggling to draw much of a crowd. Clearly Microsoft decided that it was time for a dramatic shift in strategy. The company has announced that it’s going to completely overhaul Edge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Breaks Its Flagship PC With New Windows 10 Update - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2018/12/06/microsoft-breaks-its-flagship-pc-with-new-windows-10-update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF7ppgFTKqRudLJmXGze6b0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2018/12/06/microsoft-breaks-its-flagship-pc-with-new-windows-10-update/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Breaks Its Flagship PC With New Windows 10 Update&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some Surface Book 2 owners may be a bit grumpy this week after a routine Windows 10 cumulative update left their shiny convertible laptops displaying nothing more than a BSOD. It’s yet another black eye on what has been a ceaseless string of problematic Windows 10 updates over the last several months. From the infamous file-deleting bug and breaking Windows Media Player and iCloud, to buggy default apps and broken audio, Microsoft has been proving its critics right: the process and speed of rolling out new Windows updates and features needs a deep overhaul. Microsoft Surface Book 2 The culp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Puts The Hurt On Windows Tech Support Scammers - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/leemathews/2018/12/05/microsoft-puts-the-hurt-on-windows-tech-support-scammers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTx_b-5uTQiUQJCnjrWsYwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/leemathews/2018/12/05/microsoft-puts-the-hurt-on-windows-tech-support-scammers/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Puts The Hurt On Windows Tech Support Scammers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have you ever seen an alert telling you to call for Windows tech support? Or gotten a phone call out of the blue from someone claiming to work for Microsoft? They’ve been a persistent menace for years, but Microsoft is fighting back. Hard. Photo credit: Getty Last week, police in India staged coordinated raids on shady tech support call centers. 100 officers descended on 16 different facilities. The raids resulted in the arrest of 39 individuals who had pretended to be employees of Microsoft, HP, Dell, Google, and even Apple to defraud victims overseas. According to Ajay Pal Sharma, Senior ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft is worried facial recognition tech will erode civil liberties - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90278121/microsoft-is-worried-facial-recognition-tech-will-erode-civil-liberties</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKDYiVZW-STul2T9TDcEvQoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:10:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90278121/microsoft-is-worried-facial-recognition-tech-will-erode-civil-liberties" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft is worried facial recognition tech will erode civil liberties&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI Now, a New York University-affiliated public interest group that counts employees of Microsoft and Google as its members, has raised the alarm over the inevitable uses of facial recognition technologies by governments and law enforcement agencies that, they believe, will erode our civil liberties, reports the Verge. In a paper published on Thursday, AI Now warns of the U.S. becoming a China-like surveillance state thanks to facial recognition tech. In China, the technology is already being used to publicly shame people in debt, track minorities, and block people from entering certain hou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>It’s Apple vs. the cloud in race to be the world’s most valuable tech company - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/its-apple-vs-the-cloud-in-race-to-be-the-worlds-most-valuable-tech-company-2018-12-04</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1WfaIBA9HcsxNzxEojShQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/its-apple-vs-the-cloud-in-race-to-be-the-worlds-most-valuable-tech-company-2018-12-04" target="_blank"&gt;It’s Apple vs. the cloud in race to be the world’s most valuable tech company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERESE POLETTI'S TECH TALES By Therese Poletti Microsoft and Amazon are challenging Apple for top spot, and Google isn’t far behind In Tuesday trading, Microsoft and Apple were trading the market-cap lead back and forth as Amazon remained close and Google brought up the rear. MarketWatch photo illustration/Getty Images, iStockphoto, Bloomberg After nearly a decade of Apple Inc. dominance, there is an evolving four-way race among the top tech giants that is pitting the cash cow against a trio of cloud-computing colossuses. On Friday, Microsoft Corp. (MSFT) (MSFT) (MSFT) ended the week as th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>White House huddles with tech executives on future of jobs - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-technology/white-house-huddles-with-tech-executives-on-future-of-jobs-idUSKBN1O51XF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBfM-2dKWzB9ET7Ymlkqb3kqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:13:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-technology/white-house-huddles-with-tech-executives-on-future-of-jobs-idUSKBN1O51XF" target="_blank"&gt;White House huddles with tech executives on future of jobs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration, which has had strained relations with technology companies, met on Thursday with top tech executives to discuss ways to "ensure American dominance" of innovation and the future of high tech jobs. Chief executive officers who participated included Microsoft Corp's (MSFT.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Satya Nadella, Alphabet Inc's (GOOGL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Sundar Pichai, Qualcomm Inc's (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Steven Mollenkopf and Oracle Corp's (ORCL.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Safra Catz, the White ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Puts More Brain-Power Into Machine Learning For Azure Cloud - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adrianbridgwater/2018/12/05/microsoft-puts-more-brain-power-into-machine-learning-for-azure-cloud/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ68S_917nwpI4eZY1_RV_oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/adrianbridgwater/2018/12/05/microsoft-puts-more-brain-power-into-machine-learning-for-azure-cloud/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Puts More Brain-Power Into Machine Learning For Azure Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicolo Fusi works in the automated machine learning research team at Microsoft Research The discussion has been open for a while now. We know we want Machine Learning (ML) to be able to drive the Artificial Intelligence (AI) and smart automation that we demand in tomorrow’s software — but how do we build, train and further educate the ML brains we seek to now bring forward? Computer brains are built with models that are exposed to datasets, which are then trained, tested and enriched over time as they learn what’s right, what’s wrong and ultimately what is altogether culturally and ethicall...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Lenovo and Qualcomm Build An Always-Connected PC To Make A Road Warrior Happy - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/05/lenovo-and-qualcomm-build-an-always-connected-pc-to-make-a-road-warrior-happy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJx-M4LaEEySopeqs6XqQtMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/05/lenovo-and-qualcomm-build-an-always-connected-pc-to-make-a-road-warrior-happy/" target="_blank"&gt;Lenovo and Qualcomm Build An Always-Connected PC To Make A Road Warrior Happy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently had the chance to get the new Lenovo Yoga C630-13Q50 laptop with the Qualcomm Snapdragon 850 System-on-Chip (SOC) to review. It is the first of a second generation of always-connected PCs (ACPC) that Microsoft is promoting to help reinvent the PC to be more usable in an era where more people are using smartphones. The “always connected” feature has added a new twist to my requirements going forward, which I’ll address later. I have a number of preferences for my work laptop. It needs to have a good feeling keyboard and accurate trackpad. It needs to be relatively light. It needs ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Hitting a 'brick wall' was good for this Microsoft exec - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/success/microsoft-accessibility-jenny-lay-flurrie/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENHx5s4cBiI74g0NPYkPM2AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:03:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/success/microsoft-accessibility-jenny-lay-flurrie/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hitting a 'brick wall' was good for this Microsoft exec&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jenny Lay-Flurrie has spent years making Microsoft products more accessible for others. One day, she could work on a project that will improve her own life. Microsoft's chief accessibility officer happens to be deaf. She currently relies on human interpreters, lip reading, apps that translate speech into text and a trusty standby to do her job. "I have to have my notebook with me ... a pen and paper is a good thing," she told CNN. But advances in artificial intelligence could soon allow technologists to design a digital sign language interpreter. Lay-Flurrie thinks Microsoft could be the co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Microsoft may reboot its Windows web browser again - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90276339/microsoft-may-reboot-its-windows-web-browser-again</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHFm1ZDtsITXsJwqZMQM2UMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:10:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90276339/microsoft-may-reboot-its-windows-web-browser-again" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft may reboot its Windows web browser again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Microsoft launched Windows 10 in 2015, it came with a new web browser called Edge, which replaced the aging Internet Explorer as the default and offered interesting new features such as Cortana suggestions and page annotation. Now, sources tell Windows Central that Microsoft plans to throw out that browser and build a new one based on Chromium, an open-source engine that was originally used in Google Chrome. The new browser is reportedly codenamed “Anaheim,” and Microsoft could introduce it next year. While Edge has some interesting ideas, and it generally feels slicker and more respon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Learning, Empathy And Diversity Have Put Microsoft On A Path Of Unstoppable Growth - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/caterinabulgarella/2018/12/04/learning-empathy-and-diversity-have-put-microsoft-on-a-path-of-unstoppable-growth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFOWXATVFz1YBXNHpq75zO8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/caterinabulgarella/2018/12/04/learning-empathy-and-diversity-have-put-microsoft-on-a-path-of-unstoppable-growth/" target="_blank"&gt;Learning, Empathy And Diversity Have Put Microsoft On A Path Of Unstoppable Growth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BELLEVUE, WA – NOVEMBER 28: Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella at the Microsoft Annual Shareholders Meeting . (Photo by Stephen Brashear/Getty Images) The news that Microsoft is “worth as much as Apple” is further proof that its efforts to re-invent itself are paying off. For those who view the resurgence of the Redmond giant as being mostly driven by a winning strategy, a word of caution is in order. Could the Microsoft we know today successfully pursue the same objectives (e.g., cloud computing, opening up to other platforms, zeroing in on forward-thinking acquisitions such as the latest partner...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Enhances Azure For Running Container, IoT And Machine Learning Workloads - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/janakirammsv/2018/12/04/microsoft-enhances-azure-for-running-container-iot-and-machine-learning-workloads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJZg1q55UJGQ6fi1hd8Tax8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 02:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/janakirammsv/2018/12/04/microsoft-enhances-azure-for-running-container-iot-and-machine-learning-workloads/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Enhances Azure For Running Container, IoT And Machine Learning Workloads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft hosted a virtual event called Microsoft Connect(); to make strategic announcements related to developers tools, platforms, and cloud. With the latest enhancements, Azure gained new capabilities to run containerized applications, industrial IoT workloads and training machine learning models. Code Window Microsoft Connect(); is typically scheduled just before AWS re:Invent. The Azure team utilizes the event to counter some of the announcements made by its archrival. This year, Microsoft chose to host it a week later. But the significance of the announcements is no less than what’s a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Diffbot's Knowledge Graph Indicates Machine Learning Still Remains Early In Its Lifecycle - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidteich/2018/12/05/diffbots-knowledge-graph-indicates-machine-learning-still-remains-early-in-its-lifecycle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK5ooU-JCwrOz55bfT3ubAAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidteich/2018/12/05/diffbots-knowledge-graph-indicates-machine-learning-still-remains-early-in-its-lifecycle/" target="_blank"&gt;Diffbot's Knowledge Graph Indicates Machine Learning Still Remains Early In Its Lifecycle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence Diffbot is a startup focused on using artificial intelligence to better provide companies information found on the internet. The core product is a knowledge graph they claim has mapped “over 10 billion entities” with their associated information and relationships. As part of their marketing, they have released a short report about the state of the machine learning industry. The key slide I saw in the report is included here. Diffbot ML Report – Employers of ML talent The slide purports to show which organizations are hiring machine learning (ML) talent. The top compa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Amazon: AWSome - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4c6f6e22-f754-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVbGFyk_ce-0vluz47cc1sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:38:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4c6f6e22-f754-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon: AWSome&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services’ journey from side gig to profit mainstay is a decent rejoinder to those who sneer at flops such as the Fire Phone. Amazon’s experiment in cloud services has transformed into a business expected to generate more than $26bn in revenue this year. Cloud computing is a crowded market. AWS may be the industry leader by size but Google is regarded as offering the most innovative data analysis tools, while Microsoft’s hybrid service appeals to conservative organisations nervous about putting all of their information on to the cloud. AWS has designs on both businesses. New tools...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Amazon briefly overtakes Microsoft and Apple to become world’s most valuable company - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/03/amazon-briefly-overtakes-microsoft-apple-become-worlds-valuable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIg94xTW-GAz1R6xAl2ZLI8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 20:07:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/03/amazon-briefly-overtakes-microsoft-apple-become-worlds-valuable/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon briefly overtakes Microsoft and Apple to become world’s most valuable company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon briefly become the world’s most valuable publicly-listed company for the first time on Monday. The online shopping giant briefly overtook Microsoft, which itself overtook Apple last week, ending the iPhone maker's five-year run at the top. Shares in Amazon rose 4.7pc, giving the company a market capital of $865bn (£680bn). Its share price fell in later trading, leading Apple to regain its crown. The news follows a major downturn in trading across tech shares in recent weeks. Amazon's value surpassed $1 trillion earlier this year before the so-called FAANG stocks - Facebook, Amazon, A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Mastercard and Microsoft have a frightening plan to create universal “digital identities” - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90276216/mastercard-and-microsoft-announce-frightening-universal-id-partnership</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIhNDdgWrlkIAR16TA3WZdkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 12:10:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90276216/mastercard-and-microsoft-announce-frightening-universal-id-partnership" target="_blank"&gt;Mastercard and Microsoft have a frightening plan to create universal “digital identities”&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes a business inadvertently drops the pretense and just tells the world its real intentions. We saw this yesterday, when Amazon bragged about how it “allowed” an employee to lose 100 pounds by endlessly delivering boxes. Amazon saw this as a heartwarming tale about how great it is to work for the e-commerce juggernaut. It completely missed the subtext: Who needs a gym when someone can physically labor for their corporate overlord and lose weight? Now we have another, possibly darker example. Mastercard announced a new partnership with Microsoft that is tackling “digital identities.” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Monday: Windows 10 To Show Apps Using Mic, Skype Adds Subtitles, New Office Icons - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/12/03/microsoft-monday-windows-10-to-show-apps-using-mic-skype-adds-subtitles-new-office-icons/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFINzlbTG8q2Y-DAgIrJuEsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 02:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/12/03/microsoft-monday-windows-10-to-show-apps-using-mic-skype-adds-subtitles-new-office-icons/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Monday: Windows 10 To Show Apps Using Mic, Skype Adds Subtitles, New Office Icons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pedestrians walking in front of the Microsoft store in New York. Photographer: Mark Kauzlarich/Bloomberg “Microsoft Monday” is a weekly column that focuses on all things Microsoft. This week “Microsoft Monday” features news about a new SwiftKey feature for Android, redesigned Office icons, a $480 million HoloLens contract with the U.S. Army, redesigned Office icons, real-time captions and subtitles on Skype, Windows 10 adding a list of apps using the mic and much more! New SwiftKey Feature For Android SwiftKey for Android This past week, Microsoft announced a new feature on SwiftKey for And...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Technology: is it game over for consoles? - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0a46b2ac-f70a-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO9YaoUBjxgIIggsdvhkLtkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0a46b2ac-f70a-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Technology: is it game over for consoles?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Home entertainment has always been a ruthless business, but games consoles’ 50-year territorial war for the living room has been endlessly brutal. On screen, it is fought with chainsaws, battleaxes, plasma rifles or the Poltergust 3000 spectral vacuum cleaner. Behind the scenes, though, is an even bloodier conflict fought with long-term bets on technology, balance sheets, exclusivity agreements and games so intricate that they require 1,000-strong armies of staff to produce. The casualties are frequent. Who remembers the Casio PV-1000, the Timlex Mega Duck and the Bandai Playdia? Each may h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Amazon Cloud Moves Up The Storage Stack - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/moorinsights/2018/12/04/amazon-cloud-moves-up-the-storage-stack/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAPixM0y_560u3EEfwm2-G0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/moorinsights/2018/12/04/amazon-cloud-moves-up-the-storage-stack/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Cloud Moves Up The Storage Stack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week Amazon.com held its re:Invent conference. Amazon always delivers, and as such, it is always one of my favorite events. The company takes the concept of “give the customer what the customer wants” to an extreme when it comes to cloud services. There is nothing that is off-limits. This year was no exception—Amazon flooded the event with a barrage of announcements across its range offerings. Storage is my swim-lane, so let’s delve into the new and different ways the company is serving storage to its AWS customers. For most of its existence, Amazon AWS provided basic block and object ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft vows to hand over all its technologies to ‘ethical &amp; honorable’ US military - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445406-microsoft-technologies-us-military/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGiVwOsfbURG1DMcGnzpzRsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445406-microsoft-technologies-us-military/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft vows to hand over all its technologies to ‘ethical &amp; honorable’ US military&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As big tech in the US faces increased opposition from its own employees over Pentagon contracts, the head of Microsoft Corporation appears to have decided to throw his weight behind the US military and to offer them full support. Microsoft is “going to provide the US military with access to the best technology ... all the technology we create. Full stop,” Brad Smith, the president of the tech giant, said at the Reagan National Defense Forum, held at the Ronald Reagan Presidential Library in Simi Valley, California. Smith also sought to explain his decision, saying his company actually wants...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Surpasses Apple as Most Valuable Public Company - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/microsoft-surpasses-apple-as-most-valuable-public-company/4682375.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ-KC0orfGQHnpAR7NiXVyQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 01:48:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/microsoft-surpasses-apple-as-most-valuable-public-company/4682375.html" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Surpasses Apple as Most Valuable Public Company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft's big bet on cloud computing is paying off as the company has surpassed Apple as the world's most valuable publicly traded company. The software maker's prospects looked bleak just a few years ago, as licenses for the company's Windows system fell with a sharp drop in sales of personal computers. But under CEO Satya Nadella, Microsoft has found stability by focusing on software and services over the internet, or the cloud, with long-term business contracts. That 1990s personal-computing powerhouse is now having a renaissance moment, as it eclipses Facebook, Google, Amazon and the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Microsoft’s new Office icons are a familiar idea in simpler new form - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90273711/microsofts-new-office-icons-are-an-familiar-idea-in-simpler-new-form</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDpCaSFPdtpurGy8F7_z9LMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 12:00:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90273711/microsofts-new-office-icons-are-an-familiar-idea-in-simpler-new-form" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft’s new Office icons are a familiar idea in simpler new form&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For as long as I can remember–which would be since the days of 1991’s Word for Windows 2.0–Microsoft’s Office apps have sported icons that represent them with a letter and a bit of graphical suggestion of the work they help you do. Today, the company is unveiling a new set of icons for Word, Excel PowerPoint, OneNote, Teams, and various other components of the Office suite. The first major revision in five years, they continue with the classic elements but are a re-do rather than a refresh. (They’re debuting with Office’s mobile and web incarnations and will roll out over time.) [Photo: cou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Salesforce stock logs best day in 3½ years as analysts embrace confidence in growth - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/salesforces-stock-gains-lead-sp-500-higher-as-analysts-embrace-confidence-in-growth-2018-11-28</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEy3QwXDJztfq1kRjwWgGpEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/salesforces-stock-gains-lead-sp-500-higher-as-analysts-embrace-confidence-in-growth-2018-11-28" target="_blank"&gt;Salesforce stock logs best day in 3½ years as analysts embrace confidence in growth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RATINGS GAME By Wallace Witkowski Stock leads S&amp;P 500 gainers Wednesday, while Adobe comes in second Mural on the 61st floor of Salesforce Tower in San Francisco. Wallace Witkowski Salesforce.com Inc. shares rallied for their strongest gain in more than three-and-a-half years Wednesday as analysts took a strong earnings report and outlook as a sign the customer-relations management software company may be insulated from a feared tech downturn. Salesforce (CRM) shares surged 10.3% to close at $140.64 for their best one-day percentage gain since April 29, 2015, after third-quarter result...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>How Microsoft Regained Its Crown As The World's Biggest Company - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andrewcave/2018/11/30/how-microsoft-regained-its-crown-as-the-worlds-biggest-company/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOiJKON2NzonrTFG1FPf71gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 04:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andrewcave/2018/11/30/how-microsoft-regained-its-crown-as-the-worlds-biggest-company/" target="_blank"&gt;How Microsoft Regained Its Crown As The World's Biggest Company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading Revival: Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella (Photo credit: Stephen Brashear/Getty Images) What were the chances 16 years ago when Microsoft lost its crown as the world’s most valuable company that it would regain the position? Slim at most. History shows that the name at the top of the market capitalization charts changes only with epochs and that previous incumbents have little chance of revisiting their glories. Time moves on. Technology changes. And companies that lose their way don’t get a second chance. Not all the time however. It’s close-run thing but trading closed today with Micro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Salesforce earnings: Can a strong quarter overcome ‘bear goggles’? - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/salesforce-earnings-its-all-about-the-fourth-quarter-billing-outlook-2018-11-21</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKOAw8Xv-xbAgFaNCAOjKYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 18:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/salesforce-earnings-its-all-about-the-fourth-quarter-billing-outlook-2018-11-21" target="_blank"&gt;Salesforce earnings: Can a strong quarter overcome ‘bear goggles’?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EARNINGS OUTLOOK By Wallace Witkowski Dreamforce results may be overshadowed by fourth-quarter outlook amid tech-stock weakness Tech investors’ views may be clouded by “bear goggles,” one analyst says. Warner Bros. Salesforce.com Inc. is expected to show strong results from its Dreamforce quarter Tuesday, but after a storm of poor tech forecasts put “bear goggles” on investors, the cloud-software company’s outlook will be the most closely watched disclosure. Salesforce (CRM) is scheduled to report earnings after the market closes Tuesday. Analysts largely report healthy channel checks foll...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Microsoft's market value overtakes Apple's to close out week - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-microsoft-apple/microsofts-market-value-overtakes-apples-to-close-out-week-idUSKCN1NZ2RP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBqylKrZfwJe9kF9P9KJMDQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:49:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-microsoft-apple/microsofts-market-value-overtakes-apples-to-close-out-week-idUSKCN1NZ2RP" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft's market value overtakes Apple's to close out week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Corp's (MSFT.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) stock market value closed above Apple Inc's (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) for the first time in eight years on Friday as the Windows maker benefited from growth in cloud computing while Apple was hit by investor concern about iPhone demand. Shares of Microsoft rose 0.6 percent to end the week at $110.89, putting its market capitalization at $851.2 billion. Apple shares fell 0.5 percent to $178.58 on the day, adding up to a market value of $847.4 billion. The two stocks jostled for the top spot over the course o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Microsoft surpasses Apple as most valuable U.S. company - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/microsoft-surpasses-apple-as-most-valuable-us-company-2018-11-30</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK_WEYnGBd7s2vjLCNSN8vcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/microsoft-surpasses-apple-as-most-valuable-us-company-2018-11-30" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft surpasses Apple as most valuable U.S. company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Wallace Witkowski After briefly surpassing Apple earlier in week, Microsoft retakes top spot for first time in 15 years Back on top after 3,796 trading days. Getty Images It’s official: Microsoft Corp. on Friday took back its title as the most valuable U.S. company by market capitalization at the close of trading, unseating Apple Inc. after a more than two-year run in the top spot. Microsoft (MSFT) shares rose 0.6% to close at $110.89 Friday for a market cap of $851.22 billion, while Apple’s (AAPL) stock fell 0.5% to close at $178.58 for a market cap of $847.43 billion. Earlier in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Opinion: Forecasts see no dark clouds on horizon for Salesforce, Nutanix - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/forecasts-see-no-dark-clouds-on-horizon-for-salesforce-nutanix-2018-11-27</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENoOgvZ3LyA2rPCPFZMYLPYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 12:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/forecasts-see-no-dark-clouds-on-horizon-for-salesforce-nutanix-2018-11-27" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: Forecasts see no dark clouds on horizon for Salesforce, Nutanix&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARKETWATCH FIRST TAKE By Therese Poletti Cloud-related companies may be a haven in a potential tech storm Salesforce Co-CEO Marc Benioff said he sees “several years” of economic growth ahead. Bloomberg News Investors jittery about the murky forecasts from several tech companies this quarter were pleased Tuesday that any references to clouds referred only to products, and not the outlooks for software firms Salesforce.com Inc. and Nutanix Inc. Both companies reported results that beat analysts’ expectations, sending their shares soaring in after-hours trading. The stock of Salesforce (CRM) ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>3DMark Port Royal DirectX Ray Tracing Benchmark To Debut In January - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/marcochiappetta/2018/11/29/3dmark-port-royal-directx-ray-tracing-benchmark-to-debut-in-january/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECkaETPoa2Tt2W3EHN6UuhMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 22:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/marcochiappetta/2018/11/29/3dmark-port-royal-directx-ray-tracing-benchmark-to-debut-in-january/" target="_blank"&gt;3DMark Port Royal DirectX Ray Tracing Benchmark To Debut In January&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The launch of NVIDIA’s GeForce RTX-series of graphics cards have everyone interesting in gaming and graphics talking about ray tracing. NVIDIA’s Turing architecture is the first to feature dedicated compute units, specifically designed to accelerate ray tracing on the GPU in hardware. Ray tracing, however, is not a new concept in graphics — it’s NVIDIA’s specific approach that is new. A Screenshot From 3DMark Port Royal. Prior to NVIDIA’s RTX-series disclosures, Microsoft announced that it would be introducing DirectX Raytracing – or DXR – and that it would be bringing it to the DirectX 12 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Consolidation ahead for business software start-ups - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e7c0c4e8-f3e9-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO3GRlZNJwx_dHncdw4UiNkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 16:43:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e7c0c4e8-f3e9-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Consolidation ahead for business software start-ups&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine you ran an online service with 1bn users, each paying an annual subscription of $100. Dustin Moskovitz, one of the founders of Facebook, sketched out that rosy picture this week when asked about the potential for the company that consumes his time these days. Asana, the project management software concern he founded a decade ago, is a very long way from reaching this imagined nirvana. It doesn’t disclose revenues but, in an interview, Mr Moskovitz says it is just reaching the point where it could consider a stock market listing, which usually means revenues of $100m for a company li...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Microsoft passes Apple to become most valuable company - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/tech/microsoft-apple-most-valuable-company/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSkKAwmTpSGjVu8oqh65YMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:01:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/tech/microsoft-apple-most-valuable-company/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft passes Apple to become most valuable company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple has officially been dethroned as the world's most valuable company. After flirting with reclaiming the title all week, Microsoft (MSFT) passed Apple on Friday and ended the day as the most valuable company, with a market cap of $851 billion. Both companies remain well below the $1 trillion milestone that Apple and Amazon hit earlier this year. Apple (APPL) first passed Microsoft to become the world's most valuable company in 2010, as its consumer hardware business thrived while Microsoft's floundered. Now, Microsoft is thriving in large part by focusing not on consumers, but enterpris...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Opinion: Cisco turns concerns into positives with strong earnings - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/cisco-turns-investor-concerns-into-positives-with-strong-earnings-2018-11-14</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECRmPd6MNjx0rI8a3Tm6DRkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 15:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/cisco-turns-investor-concerns-into-positives-with-strong-earnings-2018-11-14" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: Cisco turns concerns into positives with strong earnings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARKETWATCH AND LEARN By Therese Poletti But more tariffs in January could be ‘bad for everybody’ Cisco headquarters in San Jose, Calif. Getty Images Bearish investors have had a list of concerns about Cisco Systems Inc., but on Wednesday, the networking giant seemed to tick off many items on those lists and knock them down, one by one. Earlier, Cisco (CSCO) reported better-than-expected results for its fiscal first quarter, buoyed by strong product sales across the board and all geographies. Its shares jumped 5% in after-hours trading Wednesday, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average (DJI...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Here Are All The New 'Xbox Games Pass' And Xbox One Backwards Compatibility Games - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/11/30/here-are-all-the-new-xbox-games-pass-and-xbox-one-backwards-compatibility-games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHOmJhBBU4r--BBFYFXkbbYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/11/30/here-are-all-the-new-xbox-games-pass-and-xbox-one-backwards-compatibility-games/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are All The New 'Xbox Games Pass' And Xbox One Backwards Compatibility Games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mutant Year Zero A bunch of new (and old) games are coming to Xbox One. Three new games are landing on Xbox Games Pass, Microsoft’s ‘Netflix of video games’, while another batch of older titles is now backwards compatible on the Xbox One. Let’s take a look at all these new additions, starting with the backwards compatibility games. New Xbox One Backwards Compatible Titles All three new titles announced for backwards compatibility are available as we speak. - Aliens vs Predator - Sonic Unleashed - Kingdoms of Amalur: Reckoning I’m happy to see Kingdoms of Amalur: Reckoning on this list. I ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft wins $479.2 million contract from U.S. Army - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mircosoft-contract/microsoft-wins-4792-million-contract-from-us-army-idUSKCN1NY054</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDsLMNfSaWyNaCGu7Km4pHEqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 01:25:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mircosoft-contract/microsoft-wins-4792-million-contract-from-us-army-idUSKCN1NY054" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft wins $479.2 million contract from U.S. Army&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Army said on Wednesday that it has awarded Microsoft Corp (MSFT.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) a $479.2 million contract to supply prototypes for the Army's augmented reality systems helping soldiers in training and combat missions. The Army posted the contract award on its website. "Augmented reality technology will provide troops with more and better information to make decisions," a Microsoft spokesperson said in an emailed statement. Bloomberg, which earlier reported the deal, said the contract went though a bidding process with key tech companies including Magic Leap...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>5 Lessons Apple Can Learn From Microsoft's Comeback - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mohanbirsawhney/2018/11/30/5-lessons-apple-can-learn-from-microsofts-comeback/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFraXQc7xfN9r2J47M1r5wYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mohanbirsawhney/2018/11/30/5-lessons-apple-can-learn-from-microsofts-comeback/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Lessons Apple Can Learn From Microsoft's Comeback&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft accomplished the seemingly unthinkable this week: pulling ahead of Apple in terms of stock market valuation for the first time since 2010. Microsoft, which used to look at the world solely through Windows, has made a comeback as a growth company by betting on the cloud and transforming its business model. For Apple, which is fixated on the iPhone, there are lessons to be learned from Microsoft’s surprising comeback. Microsoft has made significant changes under CEO Satya Nadella, which brings to mind one of my favorite sayings: “If you want to do change management, you have to chan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Dell posts revenue jump ahead of voting on VMware offer - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-dell-results-idUSKCN1NY2SB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO_z3kCHFRq7hJXjWcC1YAYqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:21:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-dell-results-idUSKCN1NY2SB" target="_blank"&gt;Dell posts revenue jump ahead of voting on VMware offer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dell Technologies Inc (DVMT.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) reported a 15 percent rise in quarterly revenue on Thursday, as businesses were forced to upgrade their systems running on older Windows technology and on strong performance by software maker VMware. The results come ahead of voting on the company's offer to buy back shares tied to its 81 percent economic stake in VMware Inc (VMW.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), which would allow Dell a return to public markets without going through the rigors of a traditional initial public offer process. Dell earlier this month ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Monday: Passing Apple In Value, Windows 10 Bug Breaks WMP, LinkedIn Student Voices - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/11/26/microsoft-monday-passing-apple-in-value-windows-10-bug-breaks-wmp-linkedin-student-voices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFt6r3fgIIvGGBI2kny1440qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/11/26/microsoft-monday-passing-apple-in-value-windows-10-bug-breaks-wmp-linkedin-student-voices/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Monday: Passing Apple In Value, Windows 10 Bug Breaks WMP, LinkedIn Student Voices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Microsoft logo displayed outside the Microsoft Technology Center near Times Square (Photo by Drew Angerer/Getty Images) “Microsoft Monday” is a weekly column that focuses on all things Microsoft. This week “Microsoft Monday” features news about the company passing Apple in value, the digital health feature for Launcher on Android, LinkedIn Student Voices, a bug in Windows 10 causing WMP to break and much more! Passing Apple In Value Today Microsoft briefly surpassed Apple as the world’s most valuable company based on market capitalization. The last time that Microsoft was ahead of Apple...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The market right now doesn’t care how fantastic your stocks are - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-market-right-now-doesnt-care-how-fantastic-your-stocks-are-2018-11-19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-Ra8Zi6Cqm6uJcvE72XeoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 23:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-market-right-now-doesnt-care-how-fantastic-your-stocks-are-2018-11-19" target="_blank"&gt;The market right now doesn’t care how fantastic your stocks are&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;VITALIY KATSENELSON'S CONTRARIAN EDGE By Vitaliy Katsenelson In the short run, good decisions don’t always produce lucrative results Getty Images The Roman philosopher Seneca wasn’t talking about the stock market when he wrote that “Time discovers truth,” but he could have been. In the long run a stock price will reflect a company’s (true) intrinsic value. In the short run the pricing is basically random. Here are two real-life examples. Let’s say you had the smarts to buy Microsoft (MSFT) in November 1992. It would have been a brilliant decision in the long run — the software giant’s stoc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>IBM's Big Bet On 'Hybrid' Cloud, Will It Work? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2018/12/01/ibms-big-bet-on-hybrid-cloud-will-it-work/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENr3r1GssOE9IbdW3F60mWoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 15:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2018/12/01/ibms-big-bet-on-hybrid-cloud-will-it-work/" target="_blank"&gt;IBM's Big Bet On 'Hybrid' Cloud, Will It Work?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Michael Nagle/Bloomberg IBM is betting big on the next emerging cloud market– the “hybrid” multicloud. That’s a computing environment that combines multiple cloud providers and clouds—public, private, software-as-a-service. And that’s why the technology giant is paying bucks to acquire Red Hat. The open source technology company will bring to IBM an innovative hybrid cloud platform, and a vast open source developer community. IBM’s strategy begins with the premise that most companies view the cloud opportunity as incorporating their on-premises facilities, private clouds, and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft's stock market value pulls ahead of Apple's - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-microsoft-apple/microsofts-stock-market-value-pulls-ahead-of-apples-idUSKCN1NX2G3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECh-C9Tq296_eKhtoZpSOcYqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:03:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-microsoft-apple/microsofts-stock-market-value-pulls-ahead-of-apples-idUSKCN1NX2G3" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft's stock market value pulls ahead of Apple's&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Corp's (MSFT.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) stock market value surpassed Apple Inc's (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), pulling ahead by as much as $3 billion on Wednesday as the Windows software maker benefited from optimism about demand for cloud computing services. Shares of Microsoft jumped 3 percent, pushing its market capitalization up to $848 billion. With the broad market rebounding from a recent slump, Apple also rose, but less than Microsoft. Its 2.17 percent increase put Apple's market capitalization at $845 billion, just four months after the iPh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Microsoft was briefly the world’s most valuable company again - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9c943de2-f240-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAlvGjIsmXRvd5KvXaj10e4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:18:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9c943de2-f240-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft was briefly the world’s most valuable company again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft briefly reclaimed its title as the world’s most valuable company from its longstanding rival Apple in afternoon trading on Tuesday, almost two decades after it last sat atop the stock market rankings. The moment capped a five-year rally for the software group that has seen its stock price increase nearly three-fold. Most of that rise has come under chief executive Satya Nadella, who has overseen stabilisation in Microsoft’s traditional Windows and Office software businesses, as well as surging growth from the cloud. Apple has been the world’s most valuable company for about seven ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Microsoft becomes world's most valuable company after passing Apple for first time since 2010 - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/28/microsoft-becomes-worlds-valuable-company-passing-apple-first/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELNz2BT2BvFuId0bFuSw0X8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 18:24:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/28/microsoft-becomes-worlds-valuable-company-passing-apple-first/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft becomes world's most valuable company after passing Apple for first time since 2010&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has overtaken Apple as the world’s most valuable publicly-listed company, 16 years after the software giant lost its crown in the wake of the dotcom crash. On Wednesday, Microsoft’s market value reached $850bn (£664bn), seeing it surpass its old rival for the first time since 2010 following a prolonged decline in Apple’s share price. The news caps an extraordinary turnaround for Microsoft under its chief executive Satya Nadella, who took charge of the company just under five years ago and has overseen a tripling of its share price. Meanwhile, Apple’s share price has fallen by almo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Cyber Monday Laptop Deals Continue: MacBook Pro, HP Spectre, Microsoft Surface Pro 6, Dell XPS 13 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brookecrothers/2018/11/26/cyber-monday-laptop-deals-continue-macbook-pro-hp-spectre-microsoft-surface-pro-6-dell-xps-13/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBCuZ1q6W7h_xpanzmppH7cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 09:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brookecrothers/2018/11/26/cyber-monday-laptop-deals-continue-macbook-pro-hp-spectre-microsoft-surface-pro-6-dell-xps-13/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyber Monday Laptop Deals Continue: MacBook Pro, HP Spectre, Microsoft Surface Pro 6, Dell XPS 13&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;2018 MacBook Pro 13 On Cyber Monday, Best Buy, B&amp;H Photo, HP, Dell, and Microsoft continue to offer steep discounts on laptops. As of Sunday, November 25, 2018, 11 PM PT. Pricing could change. This post may be updated. The 2018 13-inch MacBook Pro continues to see steep discounts at retailer B&amp;H Photo. All models below are the mid-2018 13.3-inch MacBook Pro: - 2.3 GHz, 16 GB RAM, 512 GB SSD reduced to $1,999 from $2,199. From B&amp;H - 2.7 GHz, 16 GB RAM, 512 GB SSD reduced to $2,299 from $2,499. From B&amp;H - 2.3 GHz, 8 GB RAM, 256 GB SSD reduced to $1,649 from $1,799. From B&amp;H MacBook (12-inch) ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft And LinkedIn Can Revolutionize Retail - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brittainladd/2018/11/26/microsoft-and-linkedin-can-revolutionize-retail/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBG5jN-6D2K_KkUR0Iy5qg0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brittainladd/2018/11/26/microsoft-and-linkedin-can-revolutionize-retail/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft And LinkedIn Can Revolutionize Retail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft and LinkedIn have the potential to create a new retail experience. Photo Credit: I recently had the pleasure of providing strategy recommendations to several executives from Microsoft’s Global Retail team including Shelley Bransten, Corporate Vice President, Global Retail &amp; Consumer Goods. I am not going to reveal the ideas that I provided to Bransten and others at Microsoft other than to state that Bransten referred to the ideas as “powerful.” Bransten joined Microsoft in September 2018 from Salesforce. Bransten will lead Microsoft’s global retail vision and strategy with the go...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>For the first time in 8 years, Apple is worth less than Microsoft - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90272352/for-the-first-time-in-8-years-apple-is-worth-less-than-microsoft</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL3KH8Sw_TsE8QDQbt7CZrwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:33:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90272352/for-the-first-time-in-8-years-apple-is-worth-less-than-microsoft" target="_blank"&gt;For the first time in 8 years, Apple is worth less than Microsoft&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has overtaken Apple as the world’s most valuable company. On a day when tech stocks are recovering from a bummer week last week, Microsoft reached a valuation of $814 billion Monday. As of 1 p.m. its market cap had settled back to $807 billion. Meanwhile, Apple’s market cap was slightly less at $805 billion. Both companies have seen higher valuations earlier in the year. Microsoft hit a valuation of $887 billion prior to “Red October,” in which many tech stocks suffered. In August Apple became the first company to hold a trillion-dollar valuation (hitting a peak of $1.12 trillion)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Wants To Show You Ads In The Windows 10 Mail App - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2018/11/16/microsoft-wants-to-show-you-ads-in-the-windows-10-mail-app/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI6NJjEGi3HGpOqIK8EDH7AqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2018/11/16/microsoft-wants-to-show-you-ads-in-the-windows-10-mail-app/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Wants To Show You Ads In The Windows 10 Mail App&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I may not be the world’s most passionate Windows 10 fan, but Microsoft’s built-in Mail app is actually quite decent. Unfortunately, Microsoft is planning to tarnish that reputation by introducing personalized ads into the operating system’s default email client, regardless of what email service you’ve plugged into it — including work accounts via Exchange Server and Exchange Online. Windows 10 Mail icon In a support page spotted by Thurrott.com, Microsoft justifies this with the following statement: “Consistent with consumer email apps and services like Outlook.com, Gmail, and Yahoo Mail, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Top 3 Rarest Limited Edition Xbox One Consoles - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mitchwallace/2018/11/29/the-top-3-rarest-limited-edition-xbox-one-consoles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDU7g93GtrqASV6f5p8_7FoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 13:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mitchwallace/2018/11/29/the-top-3-rarest-limited-edition-xbox-one-consoles/" target="_blank"&gt;The Top 3 Rarest Limited Edition Xbox One Consoles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which rare Xbox One console is your favorite? Limited edition consoles are kind of my thing. Not in that I own a ton of them, but more because I just like the idea of console manufacturers releasing something special and hard to get. It’s like toy chase figures, but for video game hardware. To celebrate the rarest of Microsoft’s consoles, I’ve compiled a short list of some of my favorites. Keep in mind that this is a personal list, and composed in no specific rarity order. Just something fun I’ve put together to show my appreciation for elusive hardware. Which console is your favorite? And ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Even in our digital world, the humble sticky note abides - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90268250/even-in-our-digital-world-the-humble-sticky-note-abides</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECl44Agfzf-4QZdsGxujWD4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 06:00:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90268250/even-in-our-digital-world-the-humble-sticky-note-abides" target="_blank"&gt;Even in our digital world, the humble sticky note abides&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;E-readers and tablets have us doing more of our reading on screens than ever before. The latter category, including devices such as the iPad Pro and Surface Pro, even offers pens for scribbling notes. Other lower-profile offerings, such as the Sony Digital Paper and the reMarkable tablet, use e-ink screens to closely mimic the experience of writing on paper, at least as much as technology allows today. But while these products may veer toward delivering the utility and portability of a pad of paper, there’s one paper-based stalwart that tech hasn’t been able to match: the humble sticky note...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Microsoft vs Apple: core values - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cb49926a-f243-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE14pbgufChVe56TKgBvp0YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:10:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cb49926a-f243-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft vs Apple: core values&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ascent of Microsoft is a victory for pragmatism. Forget the sleek designs and new product ambitions of Apple. Work stalwart Microsoft is on the brink of eclipsing the iPhone maker’s towering market capitalisation. Soon, the world’s most valuable stock could be a company that sells office software and data space to corporate clients. Seattle-based Microsoft is immune to the whims of gadgetry fashion. Consumer privacy scandals and trade wars have hardly touched it. As such, Microsoft has been free to keep driving its customers online, then persuading them to buy more services and storage ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Microsoft: Wall Street’s most resilient mega-cap? - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/bb5de854-f196-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH7_VLgcYTQ1BM5cVMBhASAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 19:38:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/bb5de854-f196-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft: Wall Street’s most resilient mega-cap?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Wall Street life closes a door on your record run of share price resilience, sometimes it opens a window …or Windows, as is the case with Microsoft. The maker of the famed Office products and Xbox gaming console is making its case to be the hardiest of the S&amp;P 500’s biggest stocks as well as reclaim the title of the world’s most valuable company as the market capitalisation of Apple tumbles. Microsoft could soon take over Apple as the most biggest listed company in the world. On Monday, the former’s shares were up as much as 2.8 per cent, with a market cap of about $813bn, and close to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Report: Microsoft Working On A Radical New Xbox For 2019 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/17/report-microsoft-working-on-a-radical-new-xbox-for-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELRj-qnO9WXb0VsGrj8W-2UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/17/report-microsoft-working-on-a-radical-new-xbox-for-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;Report: Microsoft Working On A Radical New Xbox For 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Halo The next generation of Xbox consoles might still be more than a year off, but Microsoft is reportedly still looking to switch of up its hardware game in 2019. A new report from Thurrott suggests that the company has plans for a discless, entry-level Xbox One for release next year. This will be part of the Xbox One family and not the upcoming set of next-gen machines codenamed Scarlett. The intent would appear to be budget-oriented, and according to Thurott Microsoft is looking to price the new machine at $200 or less. It is also apparently working on another version of the Xbox One S f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why Microsoft is a better bet than Apple - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/investing/microsoft-apple-market-cap-big-tech-analysis/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEOuX1Y_g0eAxDngCW5vEgsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:41:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/investing/microsoft-apple-market-cap-big-tech-analysis/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why Microsoft is a better bet than Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the last couple days,Microsoft and Apple have been taking turns as the world's most valuable publicly traded company. Don't be surprised if Microsoft eventually puts Apple in its rear view mirror for good. Microsoft is generating strong sales from worker productivity tools like Office and the LinkedIn social network as well as its cloud businesses -- namely the lucrative Azure hosting unit. The success in these businesses -- LinkedIn revenues were up 33% in Microsoft's last quarter while Azure sales surged 76% -- validates Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella's strategy to reinvent Microsoft as...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Army wants Microsoft's HoloLens headsets for battlefield - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/0410c795242447948d1734defed38c0c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMu0ul7Fc6ayDKtM2ordvG0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvqGdAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 21:36:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/0410c795242447948d1734defed38c0c" target="_blank"&gt;Army wants Microsoft's HoloLens headsets for battlefield&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Virtual- and augmented-reality headsets haven't had much traction in the consumer market, but they're finding a place on the battlefield. The U.S. Army said Thursday that it has awarded Microsoft a $480 million contract to supply its HoloLens headsets to soldiers. The head-mounted displays use augmented reality, which means viewers can see virtual imagery superimposed over the real-world scenery in front of them. Microsoft says the technology will provide troops with better information to make decisions. The Redmond, Washington, company says the new work extends its longstanding relationshi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Microsoft’s tussle for top spot highlights its transformation - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/619d0834-f1ed-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFnZ3z3zDqZkYifAzOe39vMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/619d0834-f1ed-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft’s tussle for top spot highlights its transformation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last time that Microsoft rose to be the world’s most valuable company, in 1998, Bill Clinton had yet to be impeached, Boris Yeltsin was still president of Russia, and Google was less than a month old. On Tuesday, the company that dominated the PC era of computing reclaimed that title, albeit only for a few moments near the close of the trading day. Microsoft has undergone a transformation from the days when the US was threatening to break it up for abusing its monopoly over PC software. It is no longer seen as the bully of the tech world. But with power concentrating again, some observe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>The Windows 10 October Update Is Still Breaking Things. You Can Deal With It Or Opt For A Chromebook - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/27/the-windows-10-october-update-is-still-breaking-things-you-can-deal-with-it-or-opt-for-a-chromebook/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ3MlTRfF3prlq6QcqqC3hgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 15:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/27/the-windows-10-october-update-is-still-breaking-things-you-can-deal-with-it-or-opt-for-a-chromebook/" target="_blank"&gt;The Windows 10 October Update Is Still Breaking Things. You Can Deal With It Or Opt For A Chromebook&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The October Update for Windows 10 has been a non-stop nightmare for Microsoft. Windows 10 is always getting small-scale updates that have to be rescheduled so they don’t interrupt your work. In addition, Microsoft adds large collections of new features to Windows 10 with major updates that roll out in the spring and fall. The October Update, also known as version 1809, is this year’s big fall update. It’s been a disaster from day one. Watching Microsoft continue to struggle and fail to fix the October Update has been like watching a slow-motion train wreck. Unless there’s a Windows 10 progr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>When I searched ‘vasectomy’, I didn’t realise how many companies would hear about it - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-23/health-data-shared-with-tech-companies/10521456</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKnEtRJJ0LWUp92tLYH1Gb0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 19:08:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-23/health-data-shared-with-tech-companies/10521456" target="_blank"&gt;When I searched ‘vasectomy’, I didn’t realise how many companies would hear about it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Simon Elvery, with technology reporter Ariel Bogle And it wasn't just search engines sharing my health-related web browsing — I even found a Victorian Government website delivering data directly to two of the world's biggest tech companies. And when I asked them about it, they re-wrote large chunks of their privacy policy overnight. Earlier this month I did a little research into vasectomies. For, ahem, the obvious reason. Sorry if this is a little TMI for you, but it provides a clear example of how something you think of as private can be scooped up by advertising companies. Using my fa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Apple's stock sours, Microsoft's soars. Say what?! - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/86b8b9e7ebc2452aa496cd75fc5c6d61</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHey5Xri0lhTSPUE8TMhg7AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvqGdAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:27:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/86b8b9e7ebc2452aa496cd75fc5c6d61" target="_blank"&gt;Apple's stock sours, Microsoft's soars. Say what?!&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wall Street investors are enamored with a newly emergent tech company. It has nothing to do with posting selfies or finding a soul mate. The company is instead making billions of dollars selling cloud-computing and other technical services to offices around the world. Say hello to Microsoft, the 1990s home-computing powerhouse that is having a renaissance moment - eclipsing Facebook, Google, Amazon and the other tech darlings of the late decade. And now it is close to surpassing Apple as the world's most valuable publicly traded company. Yes, that Microsoft. As other tech giants stumble, it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Monday: Disc-Free Xbox One Rumor, Windows 10 October 2018 Update Re-Release, Black Friday - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/11/19/microsoft-monday-disc-free-xbox-one-rumor-windows-10-october-2018-update-re-release-black-friday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMuXqOupCGHxKHqRinigaxcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/11/19/microsoft-monday-disc-free-xbox-one-rumor-windows-10-october-2018-update-re-release-black-friday/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Monday: Disc-Free Xbox One Rumor, Windows 10 October 2018 Update Re-Release, Black Friday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pedestrians walking in front of the Microsoft store in New York. Photographer: Mark Kauzlarich/Bloomberg “Microsoft Monday” is a weekly column that focuses on all things Microsoft. This week “Microsoft Monday” features news about Windows 10 quality initiatives, the re-release of the Windows October 2018 Update, a rumor about a disc-free Xbox One, Xbox Black Friday deals, the Cortana redesign for iOS, LinkedIn Pages, LinkedIn Sales Navigator improvements, the XOXCO and FSLogix acquisitions and much more! Focus On Windows 10 Quality Initiatives Microsoft hit several speed bumps after rolling ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft, Nielsen Partner To Make Personalized Data A Closer Reality For The CPG Industry - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andriacheng/2018/11/14/microsoft-nielsen-join-forces-to-make-personalized-data-a-closer-reality-to-the-cpg-industry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOWAzXwZgNvJeRFySlqGu-gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andriacheng/2018/11/14/microsoft-nielsen-join-forces-to-make-personalized-data-a-closer-reality-to-the-cpg-industry/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft, Nielsen Partner To Make Personalized Data A Closer Reality For The CPG Industry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nielsen and Microsoft unveiled Nielsen Connect that stores various Nielsen and third-party data for the first time in the Microsoft Azure cloud for the CPG industry. By now, you have probably taken for granted your own personalized playlists from Spotify music streaming and other entertainment services. Imagine the possibility of retailers and your familiar household brands know your preferences down to the same individual level as well. That’s what market research firm Nielsen and Microsoft aim to achieve with their new partnership behind Nielsen Connect, which brings different types of CP...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Resumes Windows 10 October 2018 Update Rollout Along With Renewed Quality Initiatives - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tonybradley/2018/11/13/microsoft-resumes-windows-10-october-2018-update-rollout-along-with-renewed-quality-initiatives/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6eDzfPKpx-E6A55iAbf4IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tonybradley/2018/11/13/microsoft-resumes-windows-10-october-2018-update-rollout-along-with-renewed-quality-initiatives/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Resumes Windows 10 October 2018 Update Rollout Along With Renewed Quality Initiatives&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Satya Nadella speaks about Windows 10. (AP Photo/Elaine Thompson, File) Today is Patch Tuesday for November. It’s not just your average Microsoft Patch Tuesday, though. Today, Microsoft is also renewing availability of the Windows 10 October 2018 Update, which was launched but quickly pulled when issues were reported about data being deleted. Microsoft has addressed the issues with the update—and it is also addressing the larger issues of quality and transparency in general to improve customer confidence and ensure issues like this don’t occur again in the future. Windows 10 October 2018 Up...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Israel renews licensing agreement with Microsoft - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-microsoft/israel-renews-licensing-agreement-with-microsoft-idUSKCN1NI1V5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOKT9xxg9iug53HXLQljszYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 15:01:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-microsoft/israel-renews-licensing-agreement-with-microsoft-idUSKCN1NI1V5" target="_blank"&gt;Israel renews licensing agreement with Microsoft&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel's government signed a new software supply deal with Microsoft on Tuesday, three months after saying it would not renew its contract with the firm due to a change in license terms that would have doubled its price. In a statement, the Finance Ministry did not disclose financial details. In August, it had said that under its current framework agreement with Microsoft, Israel pays more than 100 million shekels ($27 million) for the procurement of Office desktop software, Windows and server software for ministries and government offices. The ministry said its new deal meets the governmen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>You Can Grab The Xbox One X At An All-Time Low Price With Microsoft's 'Black Friday' Sale - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/12/you-can-grab-the-xbox-one-x-at-an-all-time-low-price-with-microsofts-black-friday-sale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBj8soBv9Cx2PjGBcA1_-qEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 15:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/12/you-can-grab-the-xbox-one-x-at-an-all-time-low-price-with-microsofts-black-friday-sale/" target="_blank"&gt;You Can Grab The Xbox One X At An All-Time Low Price With Microsoft's 'Black Friday' Sale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xbox One X. Microsoft wants you to buy an Xbox One X, and in recent weeks it’s been fairly aggressive about convincing you to do so. The super-powerful little box is currently the most capable machine on the market from a technical perspective, and we just recently had the opportunity to get $100 off when we bought it alongside Red Dead Redemption 2. And now that Black Friday deals are starting to roll in, we’re starting to see that that’s the number we’re working with for Xbox One X sales in fall 2018. Microsoft just unveiled its Black Friday deals, and it includes the Xbox One X at its lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>eBay Pre-Black Friday 2018: Best Deals On Gaming Consoles And Accessories - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/15/ebay-pre-black-friday-2018-best-deals-on-gaming-consoles-and-accessories/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOnReOg5UUujuvJwIcY8xQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/15/ebay-pre-black-friday-2018-best-deals-on-gaming-consoles-and-accessories/" target="_blank"&gt;eBay Pre-Black Friday 2018: Best Deals On Gaming Consoles And Accessories&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re ready to go shopping online and want to find some deals, eBay is an outstanding destination. Over the years, eBay has evolved into a desirable destination for online shoppers. The marketplace has a variety of products new and old, new and used, and offers some of the best prices on the market. Best of all, eBay has solidified itself as a place where you can find the products you desire at prices you’d be surprised to get. It’s against that backdrop that we recently evaluated eBay for deals on video game products. From the latest and greatest consoles to the best games, eBay has so...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best Buy Pre-Black Friday 2018: Best Deals On Laptops - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/13/best-buy-pre-black-friday-2018-todays-best-deals-on-laptops/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP0fHp_cOitcPxHl8WI8VBwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 21:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/13/best-buy-pre-black-friday-2018-todays-best-deals-on-laptops/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy Pre-Black Friday 2018: Best Deals On Laptops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The massive Black Friday sales at Best Buy may begin at 5 p.m. on Thanksgiving Day, but that doesn’t mean you need to wait to get doorbuster deals on the best tech. Especially when it comes to big ticket items like laptops, the retailer is offering incredible deals leading up to November 22. These include discounts up to $300 on laptops from Microsoft (which is quite comparable to what we expect to see on Black Friday). As long as you’re spending $35 or more (which you will be if you purchase a laptop), Best Buy offers free shipping. So not only can you skip the busy stores and lines on Bla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>