<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Samsung Galaxy - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR2h1WW5OdU14SUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:25:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECs8OiMwxPuwcZzcG4cRAdMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes no notch in the Galaxy S10, the 5G S10 confirmed for America, the OnePlus 5G heading to the UK, three new Nokia handsets, a review of the Pocophone F1, Huawei’s ongoing security issues, and an innovation award for the Pixel 3 and 3XL. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). No Notch, But There Will Be A Hole, In The New Galaxy S10 Samsung appe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Massive Galaxy S10 Upgrade Suddenly 'Confirmed' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/samsung-galaxy-s10-upgrade-release-date-cost-ultrasonic-fingerprint-reader-5g/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMyiu30uk6R3WMra7ewUJnIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/samsung-galaxy-s10-upgrade-release-date-cost-ultrasonic-fingerprint-reader-5g/" target="_blank"&gt;Massive Galaxy S10 Upgrade Suddenly 'Confirmed'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10 inadvertently became official following high-profile announcements by major US carriers. The news locked in a 5G upgrade for at least one of the four models Samsung will release. But now Samsung has confirmed what I consider to be an even bigger upgrade… Samsung has taken to the stage with chipset partner Qualcomm for the formal announcement of a ‘3D Sonic Sensor’, the world’s first commercial ultrasonic in-display fingerprint reader. And it is going to give the Galaxy S10 a massive advantage over rivals. Samsung Galaxy S10 concept What we h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy S10 Details Confirm Powerful Features - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-5g-qualcomm-snapdragon-855-confirmed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBfJb5891KEyjYbQeeJek7wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-5g-qualcomm-snapdragon-855-confirmed/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy S10 Details Confirm Powerful Features&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has confirmed its continuing partnership with Qualcomm will see the South Korean company use the new SnapDragon 855 system on chip inside 2019′s Galaxy smartphones, starting with its first 5G device for US market. Both Verizon and AT&amp;T have confirmed a 5G Galaxy smartphone will arrive in the first half of next year. While the connection was not explicitly made, Samsung’s VP of Product Marketing and Strategy, Justin Denison, confirmed that the upcoming US 5G smartphone from the South Korean company would be powered by Qualcomm’s SnapDragon 855 system on chip. The only handset we’re a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Plans Radical Update On Foldable Galaxy F - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/12/05/samsung-plans-radical-update-on-foldable-galaxy-f/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGlmI4by5kNOZuBLztkYrgsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/12/05/samsung-plans-radical-update-on-foldable-galaxy-f/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Plans Radical Update On Foldable Galaxy F&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung debuts its foldable phone technology at its developer conference. Photographer: David Paul Morris/Bloomberg Samsung could be planning to update its upcoming foldable phone lineup with a new concept, according to a recently filed patent. The proposed device, spotted by Patently Mobile, has a display that rolls up like a piece of paper into a cylindrical housing unit. With the screen being withdrawn and retracted when necessary. The patent details how a rollable OLED display will have to be sandwiched by several substrates to protect the durability of the panel, as is the case with an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Suddenly 'Confirms' Radical 5G Galaxy S10 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-5g-release-date-price-cost-verizon-att-upgrade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzHJ9vIrddPWJnbbQDtf0oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-5g-release-date-price-cost-verizon-att-upgrade/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Suddenly 'Confirms' Radical 5G Galaxy S10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We already know Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10 is the biggest shake-up of the Galaxy range in years. There will be four models (including a new, more affordable version), up to six cameras, massive displays and ‘gradient’ colour schemes. And now Samsung isn’t even trying to hide its biggest upgrade of all… In a pair of official announcements which are about as subtle as a brick, both Verizon and AT&amp;T have announced a partnership with Samsung to deliver a ‘5G Galaxy smartphone’ in the first half of 2019. And yes, we know exactly what this is. Galaxy S10 Plus Concept “5G is going to b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy Leak Reveals Samsung's Spectacular S10 Plus - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/03/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-specifications-camera-design-notch-release-date/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFfT-5cLrw0yi53UeU63QAoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/03/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-specifications-camera-design-notch-release-date/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy Leak Reveals Samsung's Spectacular S10 Plus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More details are coming out around Samsung’s family of Galaxy S10 devices. With the attention is now on the S10 Plus the latest information give us the clearest idea yet of the upcoming South Korean flagship. The S10 Plus is the third of four handsets, lying just behind the powerful Galaxy S10 Ultra (which is expected to be the ‘specs monster’ with multiple cameras and potentially 5G connectivity), just ahead of the standard Galaxy S10, and well ahead of the entry-level S10 model. The Plus likely denotes a larger screen size (much as it does with the S9 and S9 Plus). The latest leaked detai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm unveils new chip to power 5G smartphones - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-samsung-elec/qualcomm-unveils-new-chip-to-power-5g-smartphones-idUSKBN1O32P1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMecw1wB_A6sq8OQSIV_45wqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:51:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-samsung-elec/qualcomm-unveils-new-chip-to-power-5g-smartphones-idUSKBN1O32P1" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm unveils new chip to power 5G smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chip supplier Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) on Tuesday unveiled a new generation of mobile phone processor chips that will power 5G smartphones in the United States as soon as next year. The key feature of the Snapdragon 855 chip, launched at an event in Hawaii, is a so-called modem for phones to connect to 5G wireless data networks with mobile data speeds of up to 50 or 100 times faster than current 4G networks. Mobile carriers are investing in 5G networks and are eager to sell 5G phones and data plans to recoup investment costs. Qualcomm, the largest supplier...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Samsung Leak Suddenly Exposes Radical Galaxy S10 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/02/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-design-release-date-cost-price-upgrade-galaxy-s9-note9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENwpZru7pfpwX2Q2_ZX42pEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/02/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-design-release-date-cost-price-upgrade-galaxy-s9-note9/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Leak Suddenly Exposes Radical Galaxy S10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For its 10th-anniversary, Samsung is shaking up the Galaxy range. There will be no less than four Galaxy S10 models, and they will come with up to six cameras, 5G carrier support and the biggest phone displays Samsung has ever made. But there are also some controversial compromises (1,2) and arguably the most controversial of them all has just been confirmed… Having already successfully leaked the Galaxy S9 and Note 9 this year, the ever-prolific, ever mysterious Ice Universe has confirmed every model of Galaxy S10 will cut a hole into their displays: “The Galaxy S10 Lite, S10, and S10+ ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm Launches 5G With The Snapdragon 855 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/05/qualcomm-launches-5g-with-the-snapdragon-855/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEE9eii9TsBtzbZk2FeOQjMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/05/qualcomm-launches-5g-with-the-snapdragon-855/" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm Launches 5G With The Snapdragon 855&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Qualcomm Snapdragon 855 platform supports 5G applications and connectivity We have all become accustomed to new, faster, and more efficient mobile processors, or more appropriately called System-on-Chips or SoCs, every year as the mobile industry continues to push performance and functionality to new levels. With the slowing of Moore’s Law, one would expect the performance enhancements to mobile SoCs to slow, but as Qualcomm demonstrated with the new Snapdragon 855, that is not the case. Dubbed the first 5G chipset by Qualcomm, the Snapdragon 855 is a significant increase in performance...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>5G smartphones are coming in 2019. What does that mean? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/samsung-verizon-5g/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBg7H2jCZlAeINu5jVJYwXUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:58:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/samsung-verizon-5g/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;5G smartphones are coming in 2019. What does that mean?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;5G is already here, but you can't do much to access those super-fast speeds unless you live in a specific place with a particular piece of technology. That's about to change. Samsung and Verizon (VZ) jointly announced Monday the companies would sell a 5G smartphone in the first half of 2019. Although they didn't say which phone would support 5G, Samsung usually announces its latest Galaxy S smartphone in the spring. The mystery phone may not be the first 5G smartphone to hit the market. Unsure of other companies' plans, Verizon and Samsung hedged by saying it would be "one of the first." Bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S10 Leak Exposes Controversial New Cancellation - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/29/samsung-galaxy-s10-design-camera-display-notch-release-date-price-cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAUa90LdOMwpsR0rqXOd7r8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/29/samsung-galaxy-s10-design-camera-display-notch-release-date-price-cost/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S10 Leak Exposes Controversial New Cancellation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10 will be its most exciting upgrade in years. Not only does it promise a radical new design, but a flagship model with six cameras which openly taunts the iPhone X. That said, these changes come with some controversial compromises and another one has just been exposed… Following new leaks from historically accurate Korean site The Bell about the Galaxy S10’s camera systems, research from BGR has shown it is almost certain Samsung has been forced to scrap facial recognition on all four models. And this is a blow as Samsung was understood to be on the ver...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Living With An Always Connected PC (Part II) -- It Changed How I Use A PC - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/04/living-with-an-always-connected-pc-part-ii-it-changed-how-i-use-a-pc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEwu-cZIUbGfGnnFOCc5v7QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 07:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/04/living-with-an-always-connected-pc-part-ii-it-changed-how-i-use-a-pc/" target="_blank"&gt;Living With An Always Connected PC (Part II) -- It Changed How I Use A PC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ASUS NovaGo always-connected PC I wrote a few months ago about my experience with the ASUS NovaGo, one of the first Always-Connected PCs (ACPCs) introduced earlier this year. But after making it my primary PC, I felt it was worth providing a little more insight into the platform. The ACPC is not a new platform, but the combination of longer battery life achieved using the Qualcomm Snapdragon SoC and seamless connectivity that switches between integrated Wi-Fi and cellular modems accomplishes something the PC segment has lacked for the past decade–new usage models. ASUS NovaGo convertibl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENR6R3fi9qwUs_y2cSw6FUgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:42:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2" target="_blank"&gt;Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verizon Communications Inc and Samsung Electronics Co Ltd on Monday confirmed long-held industry expectations they would seek to steal a march on Apple Inc by launching U.S. 5G smartphones in the first half of 2019. The two companies said in a statement they would unveil a prototype, using Qualcomm Inc's modem chips, at the chipmaker's annual Snapdragon Technology Summit in Maui, Hawaii this week. While Verizon is leading the charge to trial 5G in some cities next year, industry analysts say the higher-speed networks are unlikely to be widely available until the middle of the next decade. A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy Leak Reveals Samsung's Stunning S10 Plus - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/28/samsung-galaxy-s10-ultra-memory-storage-specifications/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJLlnvR2O0TmqNII8H9Fq3MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 23:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/28/samsung-galaxy-s10-ultra-memory-storage-specifications/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy Leak Reveals Samsung's Stunning S10 Plus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung is planning a number of handsets in the Galaxy S10 family, from an entry-level device, through the workhorse standard models, to a high-end flagship model that will pack in the hardware. It now looks like this top model will feature some killer specifications when it is released. DJ Koh, president of mobile communications business at Samsung, holds up the new Samsung Galaxy Note (Photo by Drew Angerer/Getty Images) Reported by GF Securities in China (via ITHome), one model of the Galaxy S10 will feature an eye-watering 12 GB of RAM and 1 TB of storage. Given what we know of the S10 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: Stunning Galaxy S10 Specs Leak, Nokia 7.1 Surprise, New OnePlus Flagship Confirmed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/30/android-google-headlies-samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-ultra-nokia-7-oneplus-6t-mclaren-pixel-3/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAcdcKexKURpUBExoYltvt8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/30/android-google-headlies-samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-ultra-nokia-7-oneplus-6t-mclaren-pixel-3/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: Stunning Galaxy S10 Specs Leak, Nokia 7.1 Surprise, New OnePlus Flagship Confirmed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes the latest leaked Galaxy S10 specifications, a dual-sim Galaxy S10 for Russia, OnePlus partnering with McLaren, Nokia 7.1 getting a specs bump, HTC starting the rollout of Android Pie, and how Google’s portrait mode used machine learning. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). Pushing The Limit With Leaked S10 Plus Specifications Rather than ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S10 Leak Exposes Potential Cancellation - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/27/samsung-galaxy-s10-cancellation-release-date-price-upgrade-galaxy-s9-active/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFBfAsVAKiVLNYmHil3jGbEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/27/samsung-galaxy-s10-cancellation-release-date-price-upgrade-galaxy-s9-active/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S10 Leak Exposes Potential Cancellation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Galaxy S10 may be getting more controversial with each passing day, but it remains Samsung’s biggest upgrade in years. Leaks tell us the flagship 10th-anniversary device will be the largest phone the company has ever made, sport an all-new design and six cameras. But, worryingly, new information suggests it might be vapourware… Picked up by the eagle-eyed bloggers at TechieRide, Samsung has quietly confirmed its new Galaxy S10 range by submitting it for certification in Russia. But the flagship is missing. Samsung Galaxy S10 and S10 Plus concept What Samsung certified was the ‘SM-G973...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung's Galaxy S10 Will Get Unusual New Display - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/27/samsungs-galaxy-s10-will-get-unusual-new-display/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdWlRu3JHtMCXje5I2gJm4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 15:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/27/samsungs-galaxy-s10-will-get-unusual-new-display/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung's Galaxy S10 Will Get Unusual New Display&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung’s Galaxy S10 could have virtual no bezels thanks to the new Infinity-O display. Photographer: SeongJoon Cho/Bloomberg Samsung’s upcoming Galaxy 10 will finally sport a display notch, but it won’t be like anything we’ve seen before. At this year’s developer conference (at 1 hour 22 minutes in), Samsung confirmed that it’s working on new display styles that further shrink the bezel of its smartphones. But a new leak from Korean outlet ETnews suggests that Samsung might bring that technology to the Galaxy S10. In essence, the new “Infinity-O” display removes the top and bottom bezels –...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>South Korea charges 9 people with selling Samsung secrets to China - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/29/south-korea-charges-9-people-selling-samsung-secrets-china/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED4ait6Ynt0JTi82dikPusMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 18:59:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/29/south-korea-charges-9-people-selling-samsung-secrets-china/" target="_blank"&gt;South Korea charges 9 people with selling Samsung secrets to China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Korea has indicted nine people and two companies on suspicion of leaking Samsung smartphone technology to China. The Suwon District Prosecutors’ Office said on Thursday that it had charged the chief executive and eight employees of Toptec, an equipment manufacturer engaged in the production of smartphone displays, with selling on confidential Samsung technology. The nine people are accused of receiving 15.5bn won (£10.8m) in exchange for providing information about Samsung’s flexible screen technology. The hardware that is alleged to have been stolen is used to create the curved scree...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Best Buy Cyber Monday 2018: Here Are The Best Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/26/best-buy-cyber-monday-2018-sale-iphone-samsung-galaxy-s9-note-9-tv-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJpEENJynr0ExrUieEy5vs8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 16:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/26/best-buy-cyber-monday-2018-sale-iphone-samsung-galaxy-s9-note-9-tv-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy Cyber Monday 2018: Here Are The Best Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. Cyber Monday 2018 sales have intensified with Target’s additional discounts cranking up the pressure on Amazon’s sizeable sales and Walmart’s consistently popular deals. So how does Best Buy fight back? Thanks to store’s extensive 53-page Cyber Monday ad scan we know. And there are genuine Star Buys among them… My Cyber Monday 2018 store gu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best Buy's 15 Best Cyber Monday Phone Deals: Apple, Samsung &amp; Google - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/26/best-buys-15-best-cyber-monday-phone-deals-apple-samsung-google/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIwFK-01E79gKvtMeeLw974qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/26/best-buys-15-best-cyber-monday-phone-deals-apple-samsung-google/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy's 15 Best Cyber Monday Phone Deals: Apple, Samsung &amp; Google&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Best Buy has a huge range of Cyber Monday phone deals this year. Best Buy has hit the ground running with its Cyber Monday sale this year. It looks like hundreds of deals went live last night, and after picking through the best, there at least 10 that are worth taking a look at. Don’t forget to check out my Cyber Monday deals for Amazon, Target, Newegg and Walmart. Some of these deals are actually better than what was on offer at Best Buy during the Black Friday weekend, which is a surprise. This Galaxy S9, for example, is $120 with a two year contract ($5 a month with Sprint). That’s $672...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 3 Best And Worst Things About The LG V40 ThinQ - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ryanwhitwam/2018/11/28/the-3-best-and-worst-things-about-the-lg-v40-thinq/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENrWVVsYYltCMpvvKq4DTzIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ryanwhitwam/2018/11/28/the-3-best-and-worst-things-about-the-lg-v40-thinq/" target="_blank"&gt;The 3 Best And Worst Things About The LG V40 ThinQ&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The V40 from the back. LG has fallen behind hometown rival Samsung in the Android ecosystem as its mobile losses continue to mount quarter after quarter. However, the company isn’t giving up. In fact, LG has released what is probably its best phone ever in the V40 ThinQ. There are some things to like here that might entice you to buy the V40 over a Samsung phone, but there are some notable drawbacks as well. Let’s break it down. The Best - The display: LG’s OLED panels have gotten considerably better over the last year. Compared to the V30, the V40′s screen is brighter, more accurate, and s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung apologises to workers who developed cancer after exposure to toxic chemicals - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/23/samsung-apologises-workers-developed-cancer-exposure-toxic-chemicals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBN4gh0QGtZyTQbf16cfn2EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:12:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/23/samsung-apologises-workers-developed-cancer-exposure-toxic-chemicals/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung apologises to workers who developed cancer after exposure to toxic chemicals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has apologised to employees who developed cancer at one of its computer chip manufacturing facilities following a ten-year legal battle. The announcement comes after the company and a group representing ailing Samsung workers agreed to accept compensation terms and end a highly-publicised standoff. The company's apology was part of the settlement. Kim Ki-nam, the head of Samsung’s semiconductor business, said: "We sincerely apologise to the workers who suffered from illness and their families. We have failed to properly manage health risks at our semiconductor and LCD factories.” Ca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>10 Best Cyber Monday Phone &amp; Tablet Deals: Walmart, Target, Google &amp; Amazon - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/26/10-best-cyber-monday-phone-tablet-deals-walmart-target-google-amazon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAKxiZqRbgi-7E63WccazGsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 15:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/26/10-best-cyber-monday-phone-tablet-deals-walmart-target-google-amazon/" target="_blank"&gt;10 Best Cyber Monday Phone &amp; Tablet Deals: Walmart, Target, Google &amp; Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best Cyber Monday deals in 2018. Today is the last day to pick up some discounted tech as retailers end their Black Friday and Cyber Monday deals. But which shop has the best phone and tablet offers? Here are my top 10 picks. Don’t forget to check out my Cyber Monday deals for Amazon, Target, NeweggWalmart and Best Buy. One of the better tablet deals around this Cyber Monday is Microsoft’s Surface Pro 6 (i5, 8GB), which gets a decent $259 off, bringing the total price down to $799 at Amazon. This may go quickly, though. Apple’s 2017 iPad Pro (10.5”) is $549.99 at Target, with $100 off ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>6 Best Amazon Cyber Monday Phone, Laptop &amp; Tablet Deals: Microsoft, Sony &amp; Samsung - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/25/6-best-amazon-cyber-monday-phone-laptop-tablet-deals-microsoft-sony-samsung/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECzHnGy5iuhsJNKm9YFb8HEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 14:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/25/6-best-amazon-cyber-monday-phone-laptop-tablet-deals-microsoft-sony-samsung/" target="_blank"&gt;6 Best Amazon Cyber Monday Phone, Laptop &amp; Tablet Deals: Microsoft, Sony &amp; Samsung&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google’s Pixelbook is on sale this Cyber Monday. Amazon kicked off its Cyber Monday deals yesterday, and it’s releasing more over the weekend and throughout the course of the week. Here are the best phone, tablet and laptop Cyber Monday deals on Amazon so far. Don’t forget to check out the best Cyber Monday deals for Newegg and Walmart too. Whilst Sony’s TV range is popular during the holiday shopping season, its smartphones have barely featured. Amazon has one of the few discounts you’ll find for the Xperia devices this Cyber Monday, with the XZ1 getting a $100 price reduction – bringing t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>10 Best Target Cyber Monday Phone &amp; Tablet Deals: Apple, Samsung &amp; Google - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/25/10-best-target-cyber-monday-phone-tablet-deals-apple-samsung-google/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBhOjy1It_VRyxVERl0Jt1QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 13:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/25/10-best-target-cyber-monday-phone-tablet-deals-apple-samsung-google/" target="_blank"&gt;10 Best Target Cyber Monday Phone &amp; Tablet Deals: Apple, Samsung &amp; Google&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Target’s smartphone Black Friday deals are still available. Target has kicked off its Cyber Monday deals early. Whilst the sale isn’t into full swing yet, some of early deals are worth taking a look at. Today is also the last day to take advantage of the retailer’s Black Friday deals before they disappear for another year. Here are the 10 best Cyber Monday and final Black Friday deals at Target. Don’t forget to check out the best phone Cyber Monday deals for Newegg &amp; Walmart too. Apple’s 2017 iPad Pro (10.5”) is $549.99 at Target, with $100 off the full price. It’s also the only iPad for sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>5 Best Walmart Black Friday Phone Deals: Apple, LG &amp; Samsung - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/22/5-best-walmart-black-friday-phone-deals-apple-lg-samsung/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMN72LROnFpC-PTeyHMPnTMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/22/5-best-walmart-black-friday-phone-deals-apple-lg-samsung/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Best Walmart Black Friday Phone Deals: Apple, LG &amp; Samsung&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walmart’s iPhone XS Black Friday deals 2018. If you’re looking to upgrade your phone this Black Friday, then there are some genuinely decent deals floating around. Discounts directly from Samsung and Google are the best right now, but don’t ignore the big retailers. Here are the five best phone deals at Walmart right now. The best deal that Walmart is offering right now is a $400 gift card with the purchase of an iPhone 8, 8+ or iPhone X. But that also comes with a 24-month Verizon, Sprint or AT&amp;T contract, which is something you should avoid if possible. For the latest Samsung and Apple p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Target Vs Best Buy Sales: Biggest Black Friday 2018 Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/19/target-black-friday-2018-best-buy-sales-iphone-galaxy-xbox-deals-shipping-times-redcard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEPJefItXNcGAw-Wj-gBEzQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/19/target-black-friday-2018-best-buy-sales-iphone-galaxy-xbox-deals-shipping-times-redcard/" target="_blank"&gt;Target Vs Best Buy Sales: Biggest Black Friday 2018 Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. What are the best Black Friday deals? With just four days to go, Best Buy’s impressive 52-page ad and Target’s bold 47-page ad confirm these retailers have many of them. But who comes out on top? There are some big differences and some easy mistakes to make. So let’s make sure you know where you shop. This is the fifth in my Black Friday Vs Series. Working alongside ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Latest Galaxy S10 Leak Uncovers New Case Design - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/21/samsung-galaxy-s10-ceramic-case-new-leak-rumor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKWASIMcLbAa6yGVFykOgp0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/21/samsung-galaxy-s10-ceramic-case-new-leak-rumor/" target="_blank"&gt;Latest Galaxy S10 Leak Uncovers New Case Design&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung continues to prepare the ground for the release of the Galaxy S10 family, and new details are leaking out to excite and engage the fans. The latest is the inclusion of a ceramic back to the handsets. DJ Koh, president and CEO of Samsung Electronics, introduces the new Samsung Galaxy Note 9 smartphone at the Barclays Center, in Brooklyn (Photo by Drew Angerer/Getty Images) Samsung is expected to announce four different Galaxy S10 models in early 2019. The top-end model could be a monster of a camera phone with a total of six lenses (four at the back, and two at the front). There’s al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Walmart Early Black Friday 2018: Best Deals On Tablets - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/16/walmart-early-black-friday-2018-best-deals-on-tablets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFS8gF431sq3YqTGQMyCkdMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/16/walmart-early-black-friday-2018-best-deals-on-tablets/" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart Early Black Friday 2018: Best Deals On Tablets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black Friday is a big business. 30% of yearly retail sales occur between the Friday following Thanksgiving and Christmas. Considering how hard it is for retailers of any size to enter ‘into the black’ (the reason it’s called Black Friday, incidentally) in this competitive, convoluted business world, retailers can’t afford to miss out on the holiday shopping market. As one of the biggest retailers in the world, Walmart’s all too keenly aware of this. They’ve been rolling out big holiday savings starting on Nov. 1 in a bid to win shopper’s devotion early and often. Sam Walton’s brainchild has...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S10 will have a hole not a notch, patent suggests - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s10-leaks-rumours-release-date-price-patent-notch-a8637101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIqAAX7uVPkWWbc79qHHkpoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 15:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s10-leaks-rumours-release-date-price-patent-notch-a8637101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S10 will have a hole not a notch, patent suggests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung may have figured out a way to make its forthcoming flagship smartphone, presumably called the Galaxy S10, a completely full-screen device that doesn't feature a notch design. A new patent submission shows a phone design that uses a small circle in the top left of the screen in order to incorporate a front-facing camera. The patent, first spotted by Dutch website LetsGoDigital, shows what the South Korean electronics giant may have in mind for its 2019 flagship phone. Slightly different design iterations both featured a small hole in the corner of the screen (LetsGoDigital) When Appl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>5 Best Best Buy Black Friday Phone Deals: Galaxy S9+, LG &amp; iPhone XS - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/23/5-best-best-buy-black-friday-phone-deals-galaxy-s9-lg-iphone-xs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4BUbMcDIIOqMvJknK1FrEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 15:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/23/5-best-best-buy-black-friday-phone-deals-galaxy-s9-lg-iphone-xs/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Best Best Buy Black Friday Phone Deals: Galaxy S9+, LG &amp; iPhone XS&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Best Buy has some of the best Black Friday phone deals this year. Black Friday is officially in full swing and retailers and making their final discounts available before Cyber Monday. If you’re on the hunt for a new smartphone, Best Buy has some good deals that are worth checking out. Don’t forget to check out the 5 best deals for Target and Walmart this Black Friday too. As ever, let’s start with the big guns. For the latest iPhone XS and XS Max, Best Buy (and Sprint) are offering $150 off the total price of a 24 or 18 month contract, which is discounted in monthly instalments. There’s ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Galaxy S10 Leak Suddenly Exposes Samsung's Radical Smartphone - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/20/samsung-galaxy-s10-leak-display-notch-camera-battery-life-release-date-cost-price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8WOcakR1kdyjYKb2zu2vkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/20/samsung-galaxy-s10-leak-display-notch-camera-battery-life-release-date-cost-price/" target="_blank"&gt;Galaxy S10 Leak Suddenly Exposes Samsung's Radical Smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Galaxy S10 is a smartphone worth getting excited about. We already know Samsung’s 10th-anniversary flagship will sport triple rear cameras, the world’s first ’ultrasonic’ in-display reader, new gradient color schemes and a dramatic redesign. But now a major new report reveals Samsung will go a lot further than this… In its exclusive, The Wall Street Journal reveals Samsung is planning to launch an even more radical flagship Galaxy S10 which will push boundaries beyond anything with have seen from the smartphone maker. Suitably, it’s codenamed the ‘Beyond X’. Galaxy S10 concept render Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>5 Best Target Black Friday Phone Deals: iPhone XS, Pixel 3 &amp; Note 9 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/22/5-best-target-black-friday-phone-deals-iphone-xs-pixel-3-note-9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO_v3O0MHTvxF524boc34iIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/22/5-best-target-black-friday-phone-deals-iphone-xs-pixel-3-note-9/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Best Target Black Friday Phone Deals: iPhone XS, Pixel 3 &amp; Note 9&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Target’s smartphone Black Friday deals. Target’s Black Friday sale kicks off tomorrow and if you’re hunting for a new smartphone, the retailer has a few worthwhile discounts. Here are the five best smartphone deals at Target right now. Don’t forget to check out Walmart’s best 5 smartphone Black Friday deals too. Let’s start with the important stuff. Like other retailers, Target is offering a $250 gift card alongside the purchase of an iPhone XS, iPhone XS Max and a $150 gift card with an iPhone X, 8 or 8 Plus. The caveat, of course, is that these deals come with a 24 month contract with Sp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Scouted: These iPad-Alternative Tablets Are On Sale For Cyber Monday - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/these-ipad-alternative-tablets-are-on-sale-for-cyber-monday</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEPFkGxOkA15HqCEgqW8qDcqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/these-ipad-alternative-tablets-are-on-sale-for-cyber-monday" target="_blank"&gt;Scouted: These iPad-Alternative Tablets Are On Sale For Cyber Monday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cyber Monday is creeping up and there is a ton to look through. If you've had your eye on a tablet, look no further than this sale on all the tablets that Samsung offer. The Samsung Galaxy Tab may not run Apple software, but it's just as good when it comes to what it offers as a tablet, and it comes in a ton of different sizes (in both storage and shape). And, unlike iPads, the Samsung Galaxy Tab comes with its own smart pen, the S Pen, to turn any idea into a rendering. The full HD screen, up to 14 hours of battery, and the Multi Window feature, the Galaxy can do everything the iPad can, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Best Buy 'Cyber Monday' 2018 Sales: What We Know So Far - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/17/best-buy-cyber-monday-2018-sales-iphone-xbox-ps4-galaxy-phone-sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPGPgcDYRNflZM3f7WpvuFsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/17/best-buy-cyber-monday-2018-sales-iphone-xbox-ps4-galaxy-phone-sales/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy 'Cyber Monday' 2018 Sales: What We Know So Far&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. As Black Friday 2018 approaches, doubts emerge: Will there be a better deal on Cyber Monday? Since this sales holiday is growing even faster than Black Friday, that’s a valid question. So do you wait? When it comes to Best Buy (52-page Black Friday ad scan), we have a very good idea… This is the second in my Cyber Monday 2018 preview series, following my Walmart Cybe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S10 will have six cameras and 5G support, latest rumours hint - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s10-cameras-5g-latest-features-rumours-a8644691.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFYRUhvi19p0FJpH75h6nh8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s10-cameras-5g-latest-features-rumours-a8644691.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S10 will have six cameras and 5G support, latest rumours hint&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next flagship Samsung, presumably called the Galaxy S10, will feature twice as many cameras as Apple's latest iPhone, according to reports. Set to launch on the 10th anniversary of its first flagship smartphone, the Galaxy S10 will pack four cameras on the rear of the device and two on the front, according to The Wall Street Journal. The Galaxy S10 will also reportedly feature a 6.7-inch screen and will come with 5G support, though this may only be available in South Korea and the US. Its expected release date is February 2019. The latest rumours come just a month after Samsung unveiled...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>5 Best Amazon Black Friday Phone Deals: OnePlus 6, Apple &amp; Samsung - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/23/5-best-amazon-black-friday-phone-deals-oneplus-6-apple-samsung/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK2FJJIbDjfSiInoFhPSHpEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/23/5-best-amazon-black-friday-phone-deals-oneplus-6-apple-samsung/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Best Amazon Black Friday Phone Deals: OnePlus 6, Apple &amp; Samsung&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon’s Black Friday smartphone deals. One of the best reasons to buy smartphones from Amazon is that they are typically sold unlocked. Unlike other big retailers like Target, Walmart and Best Buy, you won’t find a gift card in exchange for a two year contract deal here. Here are the 5 best Amazon smartphone deals. Don’t forget to check out the 5 best smartphone deals for Target,Walmart and Best Buy this Black Friday too. One of the best deals is LG’s ThinQ (unlocked), which comes with a huge $340 discount, bringing the total price down to $549. It has to be said though, Best Buy’s contra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Leak, Samsung Folding Phone Images, Xiaomi Mi8 Pro Fights OnePlus 6T - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/16/android-news-headlines-samsung-galaxy-s10-galaxy-x-oneplus-6t-siaomi-mi8-pro-nokia71-revlew/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOz_ZZJEm5clsJ511wu8sFUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 00:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/16/android-news-headlines-samsung-galaxy-s10-galaxy-x-oneplus-6t-siaomi-mi8-pro-nokia71-revlew/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Leak, Samsung Folding Phone Images, Xiaomi Mi8 Pro Fights OnePlus 6T&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes new leaked details on the Galaxy S10, release date and rendered images of the folding Galaxy smartphone, hints of a new OnePlus 5G handset, the OnePlus 6T vs the Xiaomi Mi 8 Pro, a review of the Nokia 7.1, and what is happening to Google Maps. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). Visitors get a look at Samsung Galaxy Note9 smartphone at the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>5 Best Newegg Cyber Monday Phone Deals: Samsung, LG &amp; Huawei - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/24/5-best-newegg-cyber-monday-phone-deals-samsung-lg-huawei/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMKYSVy8Xr5HYP1x55oPz7AqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 15:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/24/5-best-newegg-cyber-monday-phone-deals-samsung-lg-huawei/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Best Newegg Cyber Monday Phone Deals: Samsung, LG &amp; Huawei&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Newegg’s Cyber Monday deals. Newegg may not be a household name, but it’s a regular during the Black Friday and Cyber Monday shopping season. Whilst this year’s deals aren’t as good as 2017’s, there’s still a few Cyber Monday smartphone savings that are worth your attention. Don’t forget to check out the 5 best deals for Target ,Walmart &amp; Amazon this Black Friday/Cyber Monday too LG’s ThinQ, which has been a battleground for Black Friday retailers, gets a good $230 discount at Newegg, bringing the price down to $519. This is cheaper than Amazon’s impressive deal (which is still live), but n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung doubles down on virtual assistant in growth push - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b23334e2-ec90-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHNyaNdnxtGCreiStF9lmUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 09:37:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b23334e2-ec90-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung doubles down on virtual assistant in growth push&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung Electronics is doubling down on Bixby, its voice assistant, with a plan to install the artificial intelligence platform on all of its electronics products by 2020 as it makes connected technologies a central part of its growth strategy. The digital voice assistant, which was launched last year, has featured only on Samsung’s premium smartphones so far, but will be extended to other mobile devices and home appliances such as televisions, refrigerators and air conditioners. According to the South Korean technology group it sells 500m units of electronics products a year, meaning Bixby...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>5 Best Walmart Black Friday Weekend Tablet Deals: Microsoft Surface, iPad &amp; Samsung Galaxy - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/24/5-best-walmart-black-friday-cyber-monday-tablet-deals-microsoft-surface-ipad-samsung-galaxy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAaTA5XmUcD7KpABW8z1U60qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 15:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/24/5-best-walmart-black-friday-cyber-monday-tablet-deals-microsoft-surface-ipad-samsung-galaxy/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Best Walmart Black Friday Weekend Tablet Deals: Microsoft Surface, iPad &amp; Samsung Galaxy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Microsoft Surface Pro. Walmart has extended its Black Friday deals until Sunday evening as it prepares for Cyber Monday. If you missed out on a good deal during the madness on Friday, then now is your chance to pick up a discounted tablet before they go. Here are the five best Black Friday Weekend Walmart deals. Don’t forget to check out the 5 best deals for Target ,Walmart, Amazon &amp; Newegg this Black Friday/Cyber Monday too Possibly one of the most sought-after and least discounted tablets this Black Friday is Microsoft’s Surface range. Walmart, though, has some good deals for the powe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Walmart's Worst Black Friday 2018 Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/16/walmart-black-friday-2018-sales-iphone-apple-samsung-galaxy-xbox-ps4-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFLJpICSufl0Gve-glUHR4MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 01:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/16/walmart-black-friday-2018-sales-iphone-apple-samsung-galaxy-xbox-ps4-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart's Worst Black Friday 2018 Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. Walmart released its coveted 32-page Black Friday ad last week with sales on TVs, Apple iPhones, Samsung Galaxy smartphones and tablets, and the Xbox One, PS4 and Nintendo Switch. The ad contains some great deals, but there are also some very high profile ones you need to know should be avoided… Note: While I call these Walmart’s “worst” deals that doesn’t mean they ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy Images Reveal Samsung's Radical Folding Design - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/14/samsung-galaxy-f-folding-smartphone-render-images-design/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBWTqiHV5Fu-kldDGFjKkYgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/14/samsung-galaxy-f-folding-smartphone-render-images-design/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy Images Reveal Samsung's Radical Folding Design&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with a glance at a bright screen in a dark room, Samsung’s folding smartphone – the presumptively named Galaxy F – has caught the attention of the smartphone ecosystem. As well as the tantalising shots from the stage, enough details and descriptions of the technology are around to put together the look of the tablet/smartphone hybrid. Samsung Galaxy F 3rd Party Render (Lets Go Digital) With all this information, the team at Lets Go Digital has put together a digital render of what they believe the Galaxy F will look like: Samsung has already revealed that the foldable smartphone will h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Galaxy S10 Leak 'Confirms' Samsung's Nasty Surprise - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/11/samsung-galaxy-s10-leak-design-display-notch-camera-release-date-price-cost-5g/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHpfm7ACKou6ivBc1eYOstEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 01:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/11/samsung-galaxy-s10-leak-design-display-notch-camera-release-date-price-cost-5g/" target="_blank"&gt;Galaxy S10 Leak 'Confirms' Samsung's Nasty Surprise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excited about Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10? You should be. Leaks have revealed it has triple rear cameras, an ’ultrasonic’ in-display reader, gradient color schemes and a 5G option. That said, there’s a very good chance many will not like the new design… ‘Great Secret Features’ and ‘Nasty Surprises’ are my regular columns investigating the best features / biggest problems hidden behind the headlines. Samsung Galaxy S10 concept Following Samsung’s admission that it will embrace display notches in new Galaxy smartphones, the assumption was this would not be the case for the Galaxy S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung foldable phone: Price and release date revealed in leak - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-foldable-phone-price-release-date-new-galaxy-f-2018-leak-a8629886.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVd7F0GkyfFFreP6hsth0kqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 13:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-foldable-phone-price-release-date-new-galaxy-f-2018-leak-a8629886.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung foldable phone: Price and release date revealed in leak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The name, price and release date of Samsung's mysterious foldable smartphone have finally been revealed, according to a South Korean news agency. Samsung teased the device at its annual developer conference last week, saying it will serve as the "foundation of the smartphone of tomorrow" – though few details about the phone were actually revealed. The so-called Galaxy F will be released in March 2019 and is expected to cost 2 million won (£1,370), the Seoul-based Yonhap News Agency reported. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 42 show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/42 5G wireless...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>eBay Pre-Black Friday 2018: 5 Best Deals On Smartphones - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/12/ebay-pre-black-friday-2018-5-best-deals-on-smartphones/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH-684CMwyqo2eaMa58MTMAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/12/ebay-pre-black-friday-2018-5-best-deals-on-smartphones/" target="_blank"&gt;eBay Pre-Black Friday 2018: 5 Best Deals On Smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re in the market for some outstanding deals on smartphones, turning to eBay might be the best move you can make. Thanks to a community of sellers all vying for your attention, eBay has become a popular destination for people seeking deals on devices. A quick search on the company’s website reveals a slew of offers on just about any product you want. And although you do need to be careful finding the right seller, eBay offers a handy set of tools to ensure you’re buying from a reputable source. In an effort to find you the best deals on smartphones, we’ve cut through listings across t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung unveils foldable phone as it tries to regain edge on Apple - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/08/samsung-unveils-foldable-phone-as-it-tries-to-regain-edge-on-apple</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDRdSQdEbnXt89-gQCRxYlUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 04:23:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/08/samsung-unveils-foldable-phone-as-it-tries-to-regain-edge-on-apple" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung unveils foldable phone as it tries to regain edge on Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has unveiled its much-anticipated foldable phone and urged Android developers to start writing apps for the new device. The South Korean tech company needs to perfect the foldable phone to reverse steep declines in profit for its mobile division and restore some of the cachet its brand has lost to Apple. Foldable phones promise the screen of a small tablet in a pocket-sized device. Related: Apple and Samsung fined for deliberately slowing down phones At the unveiling in San francisco, Justin Denison, a senior vice president of mobile product marketing, showed a prototype with a scre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How Your Galaxy Note 9 Can Hold More Power - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/07/samsung-galaxy-note-9-battery-pack-power-wireless-charging-case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSVfPA3cBXZYMcR_7-lYzYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/07/samsung-galaxy-note-9-battery-pack-power-wireless-charging-case/" target="_blank"&gt;How Your Galaxy Note 9 Can Hold More Power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In tests against the iPhone XS, the Galaxy Note 9 came out on top in terms of battery life. Of course that performance test drew some heat from Apple’s geekerati, who were quick to point out that the Note 9 was running at its default screen resolution, rather than the higher options available. Even with the extra drawn the Note 9 should still be regarded as an ‘all-day battery’ device, albeit the margins would be a lot smaller. So how about another 2525mAh? Galaxy Note 9 Juice Pack by Mophie (mophie.com) That’s the size of the new slimline battery case from the powerful peripheral manufactu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>With new One UI, Samsung shows some empathy for smartphone users - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90264362/with-new-one-ui-samsung-shows-some-empathy-for-smartphone-users</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFuV0ZYXcKfosTD_FGGWEx4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 18:13:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90264362/with-new-one-ui-samsung-shows-some-empathy-for-smartphone-users" target="_blank"&gt;With new One UI, Samsung shows some empathy for smartphone users&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research says we’re spending more than 3.5 hours a day looking at our smartphones. So the presentation of stuff on that little square of glass matters. Samsung has been a little slow getting hip to that. Its user interfaces over the years have betrayed a focus on what Samsung wants to present there, rather than what the user wants and/or needs to see. That’s been changing, however, and Samsung made perhaps its biggest leap yet into human-centric design today with the announcement of a new UX called One UI. Where Samsung once famously cluttered the UX with clunky icons, too much data, an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Samsung Takes Its 1.5 to 2.5B Unit Opportunity To Developers At SDC 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickmoorhead/2018/11/11/samsung-takes-its-1-5-to-2-5b-unit-opportunity-to-developers-at-sdc-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIkMyVVRydQrYGWkC3jLu-wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 18:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickmoorhead/2018/11/11/samsung-takes-its-1-5-to-2-5b-unit-opportunity-to-developers-at-sdc-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Takes Its 1.5 to 2.5B Unit Opportunity To Developers At SDC 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung’s DJ Koh kicks off SDC 2018. Last week, I attended SDC 2018, Samsung’s sixth annual Developer Conference, in San Francisco, along with 5,000 other attendees. The event was a great chance to catch a glimpse of the technology that will power the coming generations of Samsung devices and services, and the company did not disappoint. SDC is a must-attend for anyone who closely follows the electronics giant and for developers who want access to future home IoT, mobile, and automotive markets. While Samsung wasn’t the first mover with IoT or mobile software developers,Samsung commands dev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung's Foldable Galaxy X Has Two Big Hurdles - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/08/samsungs-foldable-galaxy-x-has-two-big-hurdles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO42xraSnM5IXbtJLEToJj8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jaymcgregor/2018/11/08/samsungs-foldable-galaxy-x-has-two-big-hurdles/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung's Foldable Galaxy X Has Two Big Hurdles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung’s Foldable phone. Samsung finally, officially, confirmed what has been speculated for some time - it’s releasing a foldable phone imminently. If you’ve been following the development of the Korean company’s first foldable smartphone – dubbed the Galaxy X – then you’ll be aware of the yearly launch delays. The competition from LG, Lenovo, Apple and smaller Chinese companies that have actually launched devices likely forced Samsung’s hand into yesterday’s preview. There are, however, at least two areas that make me sceptical about how popular this device will be. Firstly, software. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung foldable phone finally announced, teasing release date and breakthrough new features - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-foldable-phone-infinity-flex-display-latest-release-date-features-details-a8622956.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAuLv9tdNssIMcqKXcSpwtIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-foldable-phone-infinity-flex-display-latest-release-date-features-details-a8622956.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung foldable phone finally announced, teasing release date and breakthrough new features&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has finally unveiled its foldable phone, after years of teasing and rumours. The handset, with a screen known as the Infinity Flex Display, can be folded out into a tablet or bent in to make it smaller and suitable for use as a phone or fitting into people's pockets. The company says the technology powering the new phone will serve as the "foundation of the smartphone of tomorrow". Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 42 show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/42 5G wireless internet is expected to launch in 2019, with the potential to reach speeds of 50mb/s Getty - 2/42 Uber ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Samsung unveils breakthrough folding smartphone - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/07/samsung-unveils-breakthrough-folding-smartphone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjDnWkWe8MHfNtcZcezEbUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 19:59:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/07/samsung-unveils-breakthrough-folding-smartphone/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung unveils breakthrough folding smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has become the first major smartphone manufacturer to unveil a folding phone as it seeks to reboot a stagnant mobile market. The Korean company, the world’s biggest mobile phone maker, said its bendy screen technology would usher in “a new generation of smartphones” as it unveiled a prototype handset at an event in San Francisco. The device is the size of a tablet computer and features a large 7.3-inch screen, but can fold in on itself, shutting like a book. When folded in half, a second screen on the outside means it can operate like a pocket-friendly smartphone. Phone displays hav...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Samsung shows off bendy tablet that folds down to a smartphone - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-08/samsung-shows-off-bendy-tablet-that-folds-down-to-phone/10478508</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENWODO_Tcd5WX8garMw6EH0qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 07:38:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-08/samsung-shows-off-bendy-tablet-that-folds-down-to-phone/10478508" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung shows off bendy tablet that folds down to a smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While flip phones are considered relics of the past, foldable phones appear to be the future of smart devices. Samsung today offered a first look at its new smartphone tablet hybrid, which folds down to the size of a regular mobile phone. It was displayed at the Samsung Developers Conference in San Francisco, with mobile product marketing executive Justin Denison demonstrating the folding features on stage. The lights dimmed as he took the device from his pocket and unfolded it to reveal the 18cm tablet-style screen. Users will be able to run three different apps at the same time. Mr Deniso...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Samsung 'Galaxy X' foldable phone tablet is finally ready to be unveiled - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-x-foldable-phone-release-date-new-smartphone-technology-a8619796.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFbvR-f1o8BvOIPfrNZrWeMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 11:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-x-foldable-phone-release-date-new-smartphone-technology-a8619796.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung 'Galaxy X' foldable phone tablet is finally ready to be unveiled&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung will reveal details of its much-anticipated foldable smartphone at its developer conference this week, an official at the South Korean electronics giant has revealed. The disruptive device, potentially named the Galaxy X or Galaxy F, was first teased in 2014 but details of the project have remained secret in the years since. In a break with its usual policy of keeping new products under wraps until they're ready to launch, Samsung plans to share some of the phone's features at the Samsung Developer Conference 2018, taking place in San Francisco from 7-8 November. Samsung shared an i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Changing tack: Samsung to reveal some features of foldable phone this week - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-samsung-elec-phones/changing-tack-samsung-to-reveal-some-features-of-foldable-phone-this-week-idUSKCN1NB0AJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOY4YddlUZi_PCchbSxOM0cqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 03:44:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-samsung-elec-phones/changing-tack-samsung-to-reveal-some-features-of-foldable-phone-this-week-idUSKCN1NB0AJ" target="_blank"&gt;Changing tack: Samsung to reveal some features of foldable phone this week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keen to make its foldable smartphone the next big thing, Samsung Electronics Co will depart from its usual policy of keeping product plans highly secret and provide some details of the phone's key features for app developers this week. The goal is garnering critical feedback as new technologies will require developers to tweak apps to make sure they run smoothly when the phone folds out into tablet form. Samsung needs to get the foldable phone right - hoping it will reverse steep declines in profit for its mobile division and restore some of the premium cachet its brand has lost to Apple In...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Smartphone makers bet on foldable screens as next big thing - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/e3cb8474411c43aa83efa562febc89b3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPUczssJNFGXnoulROz8EYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 22:46:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/e3cb8474411c43aa83efa562febc89b3" target="_blank"&gt;Smartphone makers bet on foldable screens as next big thing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — For the past few years, the smartphone industry has been searching for a breakthrough to revive a market mired in an innovation lull and a sales slump. A potential catalyst is on the horizon in the form of flexible screens that can be folded in half without breaking. Samsung and several rivals are preparing to roll out such screens to make devices more versatile for work and pleasure. The foldable screens could increase display space to the size of a mini-tablet, but fold like a wallet so they revert to the size of regular phones. But there are questions about price and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Samsung unveils much-hyped foldable phone - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/08/samsung-unveils-much-hyped-foldable-phon?videoId=481040953</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDhipb1QemI6OlyAMcDJ3XYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 16:25:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/11/08/samsung-unveils-much-hyped-foldable-phon?videoId=481040953" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung unveils much-hyped foldable phone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung unveiled its heavily anticipated foldable phone to developers in San Francisco on Wednesday, urging Android programmers to start writing apps for the product it expects to deliver in the new year. Jane Lanhee Lee reports.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Samsung 'Black Friday' 2018 Leaks: Best Galaxy S9, Note 9, 4K HDTV Deals So Far - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/03/samsung-black-friday-2018-leaks-best-galaxy-s9-note-9-4k-hdtv-deals-so-far/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECMw1QYMpsMSZ3JddlNuS2kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/03/samsung-black-friday-2018-leaks-best-galaxy-s9-note-9-4k-hdtv-deals-so-far/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung 'Black Friday' 2018 Leaks: Best Galaxy S9, Note 9, 4K HDTV Deals So Far&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. Black Friday 2018 leaks have already given away Apple’s best deals and we now know a lot about Samsung sales as well. My holiday season sales partner BestBlackFriday.com has attained leaked Black Friday scans from Costco, Kohl’s, Sam’s Club, Shopko and Target. Consequently, these are the best Black Friday Galaxy S9, Note 9, Galaxy Tablet and HDTV deals so far… Note: ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Galaxy S10 Leak Reveals Samsung's Nasty Surprise - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-design-in-display-fingerprint-scanner-release-date-cost-upgrade-s9-note9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMy08aWRU4Wv3ON9a9YYfBUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 23:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-design-in-display-fingerprint-scanner-release-date-cost-upgrade-s9-note9/" target="_blank"&gt;Galaxy S10 Leak Reveals Samsung's Nasty Surprise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are many reasons why everyone is excited about Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10. Most notably the leaked triple rear cameras, ’ultrasonic’ in-display reader, new gradient color schemes and 5G option. Even Samsung is bragging about the Galaxy S10. But now there is news which will come as a nasty surprise to many… ‘Great Secret Features’ and ‘Nasty Surprises’ are my regular columns investigating the best features / biggest problems hidden behind the headlines. Samsung Galaxy S10 concept Leaked by Ice Universe, arguably the industry’s top Samsung insider right now, we learn the Gal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Black Friday 2018 Ads: Walmart's Biggest Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/08/walmart-black-friday-2018-ad-the-best-deals-iphone-galaxy-xbox-one-x-ps4-pro-ipad-hdtv-sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPeHNdzezUhOR1-PtyD1MoQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 05:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/08/walmart-black-friday-2018-ad-the-best-deals-iphone-galaxy-xbox-one-x-ps4-pro-ipad-hdtv-sales/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Friday 2018 Ads: Walmart's Biggest Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. The king has arrived. The official Walmart Black Friday 2018 36-page ad is here and it brings some of the biggest and most anticipated deals of the entire holiday season. Spotted by my holiday season sales partner BestBlackFriday.com, we now know all Walmart’s Black Friday 2018 plans… You can browse the full Walmart complete ad scan on BestBlackFriday, which also rev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>LG V40 Review: Video Capabilities Set It Apart - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/08/lg-v40-review-video-capabilities-set-it-apart/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMs9YKYmoWut6VIMug4q1RgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 06:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/08/lg-v40-review-video-capabilities-set-it-apart/" target="_blank"&gt;LG V40 Review: Video Capabilities Set It Apart&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The LG V40 with its frosted glass back that looks and feels like metal. LG’s V series began as a rugged, “manly” phone built for content creators. And while the line has moved away from the heavy duty masculine vibe in favor of a more mainstream look, it has not lost its video-centric creative roots. This was why during my week of testing the LG V40 ThinQ, I was constantly reminded of my film buff roots and wanna-be filmmaker aspirations. The V40′s camera app offers so many different video recording options, I found myself shooting random footage on the street just for the sake of it. After...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung shows off new smartphone with foldable screen - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/samsung-shows-off-new-smartphone-with-foldable-screen-2018-11-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIcq9vKaAs_kGU7cQZeYbvEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/samsung-shows-off-new-smartphone-with-foldable-screen-2018-11-07" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung shows off new smartphone with foldable screen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WALL STREET JOURNAL By Timothy W. Martin Device with 7.3-inch screen should be ready for mass production in the coming months Samsung executive Justin Denison holds the new foldable Infinity Flex smartphone Wednesday in San Francisco. Bloomberg News SAN FRANCISCO — Samsung Electronics Co., suffering a handset sales slide, revealed a foldable-screen smartphone that folds like a book and opens up to tablet size. At a developer showcase event on Wednesday, Samsung (KR:005930) said the phone, which is 7.3 inches when opened, would be ready for mass production in the coming months. It boas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Walmart 'Black Friday' 2018 Ad Preview: Expected iPhone, Galaxy, Switch, Xbox One Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/04/walmart-black-friday-2018-ad-preview-sales-apple-iphone-samsung-galaxy-microsoft-xbox-one-x-nintendo-switch-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKFpKrll1NOb98MfEE4-AyMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 21:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/04/walmart-black-friday-2018-ad-preview-sales-apple-iphone-samsung-galaxy-microsoft-xbox-one-x-nintendo-switch-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart 'Black Friday' 2018 Ad Preview: Expected iPhone, Galaxy, Switch, Xbox One Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. Black Friday 2018 already seems to be breaking records and the most sought-after deals from Walmart’s big circular have yet to be revealed. But, now that we have seen the 13-page Dell Black Friday ad, the 77-page JCPenney Black Friday ad, the 20-page Sam’s Club One-Day Sale ad and the 47-page Target Black Friday ad all leak, the picture for Walmart’s hottest items is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy S10 Images Reveal Exciting Concept - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/10/31/samsung-galaxy-s10-leak-new-render-images-concept-notch-selfie/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFazx1jvtOIRI4rJnJQKgEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 23:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/10/31/samsung-galaxy-s10-leak-new-render-images-concept-notch-selfie/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy S10 Images Reveal Exciting Concept&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike most smartphone manufacturers, Samsung has been very reluctant to pus a notched display into its handsets. Instead it has retained two distinctive chins at the top and bottom of the displays to accommodate the required forward facing hardware. Samsung president of mobile communications business DJ Koh presents the new Samsung Galaxy S9 (Photo:Lluis Gene/AFP/Getty Images) The upcoming Galaxy S10 looks set to continue that trend, but it’s also going to move towards a much more expansive display. How is it going to do that without a notch? The answer looks limey to be with some discrete...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: Galaxy S10 Kills Key Feature, Samsung Confirms Folding Screen, OnePlus 6T Reviewed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/02/android-google-news-samsung-galaxy-s10-note9-nokia-oneplus-6t-review/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHo3jr85_qDFoKMTyjLWKW0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/02/android-google-news-samsung-galaxy-s10-note9-nokia-oneplus-6t-review/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: Galaxy S10 Kills Key Feature, Samsung Confirms Folding Screen, OnePlus 6T Reviewed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes a major change to the Galaxy S10, Samsung confirming its folding screen plans, the first reviews of the OnePlus 6T, the Note 9’s Fortnite exclusive, Android Pie for the Nokia 6.1, the first review of Red’s Hydrogen One smartphone, and the disappearance of Android tablets. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). Galaxy S10 To Remove Headphone ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung reports 3rd-quarter profit surge on demand for chips - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/7c3599a7cdd34e5898b357c9a7c808c4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHyBLnqtQKplE3I5WSxEFfkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 06:32:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/7c3599a7cdd34e5898b357c9a7c808c4" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung reports 3rd-quarter profit surge on demand for chips&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — Samsung Electronics Co. has posted a record operating profit for the last quarter with robust demand for its mainstay memory chips compensating for a slowdown in its smartphone business. The South Korean technology giant on Wednesday said its operating profit during the July-September quarter grew at nearly a 21 percent annual pace to 17.6 trillion won ($15.4 billion). Samsung's previous high in quarterly profit was the 15.6 trillion won it posted during the first quarter. Third-quarter sales grew 5.5 percent year-on-year to reach 65.4 trillion won ($57 billion) wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Samsung Suddenly Teases Radical New Galaxy Smartphone - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/10/30/samsung-galaxy-f-folding-smartphone-upgrade-release-date-cost-galaxy-s9-note9-s10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKGYtsm1qAhG0gFg4XfGcBIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/10/30/samsung-galaxy-f-folding-smartphone-upgrade-release-date-cost-galaxy-s9-note9-s10/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Suddenly Teases Radical New Galaxy Smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung is rightly getting a lot of attention for its 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10. That’s not surprising when leaks have revealed its truly bezel-less design, ’ultrasonic’ in-display fingerprint reader, triple rear cameras, gradient colors and 5G. It sounds like a dream, one controversial flaw aside. But now Samsung has suddenly teased a phone which promises to be an even bigger game-changer… Having subtly hinted (not once, but twice) that it plans to announce the screen bending Galaxy F early next month, Samsung has now chosen to ‘accidentally’ confirm another key part of the puzzle on Ap...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Black Friday 2018 Ad Sales: Target's Biggest Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/06/black-friday-2018-ad-deals-apple-iphone-samsung-galaxy-nintendo-switch-sony-ps4-pro-sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFOJ7dpob8OcverlyAFX7boqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/06/black-friday-2018-ad-deals-apple-iphone-samsung-galaxy-nintendo-switch-sony-ps4-pro-sales/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Friday 2018 Ad Sales: Target's Biggest Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. Black Friday 2018 really hit its stride when the 47-page Target Black Friday ad surfaced last week. Thanks to a tip-off from my holiday season sales partner, BestBlackFriday.com, I now know all about Target’s biggest deals… You can browse the full Target ad scan on BestBlackFriday which also reveals the store’s holiday opening hours, improved shipping plans and more....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Week In Wearables: Apple Watch Record Sales, Samsung Galaxy Watch, Bose Sleepbuds - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/01/week-in-wearables-apple-watch-record-sales-samsung-galaxy-watch-bose-sleepbuds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH_cZXlMuRiyjZ5HiJqgCH4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/01/week-in-wearables-apple-watch-record-sales-samsung-galaxy-watch-bose-sleepbuds/" target="_blank"&gt;Week In Wearables: Apple Watch Record Sales, Samsung Galaxy Watch, Bose Sleepbuds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week in wearable news saw Apple claiming strong wearables sales as one analyst predicted soaring growth, Samsung’s 4G version of the Galaxy Watch to go on sale and Bose Sleepbuds being tested. The Week in Wearables is a news digest, out each week, focused on some of the things that have happened in the world of tech you can wear on your wrist, perch on your head, stick in your ear, sling around your waist, tuck into the small of your back or, well, you get the idea. Apple Watch Series 4 with the Infographic Watch face. Apple Watch record sales and predicted to grow 40% Analyst firm UBS...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>