<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Epic Games - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREp5Wm1aMEVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:15:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Is 'Fortnite' Teasing Swords And The Infinity Blade For Season 7? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/07/is-fortnite-teasing-swords-and-the-infinity-blade-for-season-7/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOImANARyUqXWIfO732Yo8kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/07/is-fortnite-teasing-swords-and-the-infinity-blade-for-season-7/" target="_blank"&gt;Is 'Fortnite' Teasing Swords And The Infinity Blade For Season 7?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite, as it usually does, kicked Season 7 off with a little movie. Christmas-themed this time, with stop-motion Rankin and Bass-style movie showcasing a pleasant little winter scene before everything goes south. A glacier crashes into the island and Santa leads an invading army of savage snowmen, raining death upon the unsuspecting elf skins from above. It was a pretty good one, as far as Fortnite cinematics go, but there was one little detail that people immediately noticed. Let’s take a look: Fortnite Santa is wielding a pretty slick looking sword there, a weapon class that’s been in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Creative Mode: What Is Fortnite's Big New Mode, And How Do You Play It? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/access-battle-royale-creative-mode-what-is-fortnites-big-new-mode-and-how-do-you-play-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPud_LyDPsa2l80mTsrjTscqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/access-battle-royale-creative-mode-what-is-fortnites-big-new-mode-and-how-do-you-play-it/" target="_blank"&gt;Creative Mode: What Is Fortnite's Big New Mode, And How Do You Play It?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite You might be zipping around in the new ice biome, testing out a plane or just beginning to level up your battle pass, but none of those things are the biggest changes that developer Epic Games dumped on Fortnite today. Fortnite: Battle Royale got a huge update, as it always does at the start of the season, but the biggest update to the wider Fortnite property is Creative Mode, a third mode for the game to stand alongside Save the World and Battle Royale. That top-level billing should give you a sense of how important this is to the game and its developer. So what is it? Epic detail...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Season 7 start time and downtime confirmed as release hints at new planes - everything we know so far - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fortnite-season-7-teaser-battle-pass-release-date-map-changes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEGiAnt4EZvwgGAeO6zkHuAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:54:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fortnite-season-7-teaser-battle-pass-release-date-map-changes/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Season 7 start time and downtime confirmed as release hints at new planes - everything we know so far&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Season 6 of Fortnite coming to its conclusion, Epic Games has confirmed the arrival of Fortnite Season 7 today. The developer has confirmed that Fortnite will go down at 9am UK time (4am ET) on 6 December as the new season is implemented. The downtime will likely last a few hour as the new Battle Pass, skins and features are added to the hit game. Patch notes detailing the changes and a new trailer will likely be released as the game updates. Epic first starting teasing the new season at the start of this week, with a tweet from the official Fortnite Twitter account that featured an im...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>There's A Big 'Fortnite' Announcement At The Game Awards Tonight, But It's Not What You Think - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/theres-a-big-fortnite-announcement-at-the-game-awards-tonight-but-its-not-what-you-think/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFx_4hkGV0WvjHfenD2tDskqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/theres-a-big-fortnite-announcement-at-the-game-awards-tonight-but-its-not-what-you-think/" target="_blank"&gt;There's A Big 'Fortnite' Announcement At The Game Awards Tonight, But It's Not What You Think&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite It’s a big day for battle royale fans. For one thing, Fortnite Season 7 just launched as Epic Games continues to top itself when it comes to totally transforming its map to match the current season: right now we’ve got a wide-ranging winter wonderland, airplanes, and a ton of other stuff. It’s also The Game Awards tonight, the annual celebration that’s gradually emerging as the most important awards show in the world of video games. The Game Awards are known not only for the awards themselves but also for the announcements, surprises and trailers that have a way of worming their wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Season 7: Creative mode confirmed by Epic following leak - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-leak-reveals-major-new-minecraft-style-fortnite-creative/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBOIPKDiMCBtWnzPxMH8rYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:13:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-leak-reveals-major-new-minecraft-style-fortnite-creative/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Season 7: Creative mode confirmed by Epic following leak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gaming sensation Fortnite will be getting a brand new third 'Creative' mode when Season 7 launches this week. In addition to the phenomenally popular Battle Royale mode and co-op survival game Save the World, Fortnite Creative is a Minecraft style building tool that allows players to create their own private islands and minigames with unlimited resources and a slew of rule options. Developer Epic Games confirmed the existence of the mode on its official site, saying that Fortnite Creative will initially be available for buyers of the Season 7 Battle Pass when it releases tomorrow 6 December...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Brooklyn rapper sues makers of Fortnite over claims video game stole his moves - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/dec/05/brooklyn-rapper-sues-fortnite-video-game-stole-dance</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELmDK_f2HoPCT0xvtTLuiB0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:43:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/dec/05/brooklyn-rapper-sues-fortnite-video-game-stole-dance" target="_blank"&gt;Brooklyn rapper sues makers of Fortnite over claims video game stole his moves&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rapper 2 Milly filed a lawsuit Wednesday against the makers of Fortnite, saying they were illegally using a dance he created in their wildly popular video game. The Brooklyn-based rapper, whose real name is Terrence Ferguson, alleges that the North Carolina-based Epic Games misappropriated his moves without compensation or credit in the lawsuit, filed in federal court in Los Angeles. The lawsuit states that the dance known on Fortnite as “Swipe It”, one of many that players can buy for their characters, is taken from the “Milly Rock”, a dance he came up with in 2011 that caught on as a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Fortnite developer Epic looking to take on Steam with its own digital games store - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-developer-epic-looking-take-steam-digital-games-store/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJQo0utUppKaY180gNDQa5UqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 16:57:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-developer-epic-looking-take-steam-digital-games-store/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite developer Epic looking to take on Steam with its own digital games store&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Epic Games has announced that it will be opening up its Epic Games Store to other developers as it looks to take on Valve's Steam platform on PC. The Fortnite developer has said that the new digital storefront will offer developers 88% of revenue made on game purchases, with Epic taking just a 12% cut. Epic will also waive the 5% royalty it takes for use of its Unreal Engine if the games are sold on the Epic Store. In comparison, developers selling their games on Steam have a 70/30 split with platform holder Valve. Valve has recently announced that it plans to reduce its cut on games that m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Everything You Need To Know About 'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Season 7: Theme, Battle Pass And More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/everything-you-need-to-know-about-fortnite-battle-royale-season-7-theme-battle-pass-and-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFZWj30O-KG1BbN4_A1Ub6wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/everything-you-need-to-know-about-fortnite-battle-royale-season-7-theme-battle-pass-and-more/" target="_blank"&gt;Everything You Need To Know About 'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Season 7: Theme, Battle Pass And More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;fortnite It’s time for another season in Fortnite: Battle Royale, that juggernaut of a cultural phenomenon that recently hit 200 million players. You may have been reading a lot about it recent days, but you might be a little bit confused if you’re still new to the game and wondering what exactly this ice king fellow has to do with a multiplayer shooter. Here’s what you need to know about Fortnite: Battle Royale Season 7. What Is It? A season in Fortnite refers to when the developer releases a new battle pass, which is a $10 purchase that unlocks more and more cosmetic items as you play, in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Rapper 2 Milly files lawsuit against Fortnite creators for 'stolen' dance - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/rapper-2-milly-files-lawsuit-against-fortnite-creators-stolen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2UeDqNwEk6fp4T2ATyVR8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:00:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/rapper-2-milly-files-lawsuit-against-fortnite-creators-stolen/" target="_blank"&gt;Rapper 2 Milly files lawsuit against Fortnite creators for 'stolen' dance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;American rapper 2 Milly has confirmed that he has filed a lawsuit in California against Fortnite creator Epic Games over the apparent use of his 'Milly Rock' dance in the smash video game. The lawsuit, was filed on Wednesday over the alleged 'misappropriation, use and sale' of the dance. The rapper alleges that the Fortnite emote dubbed 'Swipe It', available during Season 5 of the hugely successful game, was an unauthorised recreation of his dance. Epic games sold the 'Swipe It' emote for around $5 (£3.95), which allowed players to perform the dance in-game. The Swipe It emote is no longer ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Season 7 Battle Pass Revealed, Here's What's In It: Weapon Skins, Airplanes, More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/fortnite-season-7-battle-pass-revealed-early-heres-whats-in-it-weapon-skins-airplanes-and-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENSzx_uTEn7HtmWMUtkwkhwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/fortnite-season-7-battle-pass-revealed-early-heres-whats-in-it-weapon-skins-airplanes-and-more/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Season 7 Battle Pass Revealed, Here's What's In It: Weapon Skins, Airplanes, More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Fortnite’s Season 7 Battle Pass is here: we got a bit of an early look this morning due to an early reveal from Fortnite Korea, which dropped both the official trailer and the battle pass trailer a little bit early. It’s a Winter Wonderland for Season 7, with a bunch of snow and ice-themed skins as well as a new pet, new weapons and vehicle skins and even a glimpse of the new airplanes, which look like they’re set to go live when downtime ends later today. The full pass is live now, so let’s check out what’s on offer, from skins to back blings, gliders and more. The full video is n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Season 7 live with new planes, ziplines, custom weapons and an expanded snowy island - all you need to know - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fortnite-season-7-start-time-downtime-confirmed-patch-notes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGflv_75y1muG4nSxKHraXoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:13:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fortnite-season-7-start-time-downtime-confirmed-patch-notes/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Season 7 live with new planes, ziplines, custom weapons and an expanded snowy island - all you need to know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Season 6 of Fortnite coming to its conclusion, Fortnite Season 7 is now live for the Battle Royale behemoth's 200 million players. The new season brings brand new 'Stormwing', machine-gun equipped biplanes for combatants to fly, ziplines to get around the (now bigger) Fortnite island quicker and a new locations in the form of 'Frosty Flights' and Expedition outposts. The iceberg that was travelling towards the map has shunted into the south-west corner of Fortnite island, growing the map considerably, while that particular quadrant of the map is now covered in snow. Season 7 also bring...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fortnite to enter Minecraft territory with new Creative mode - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/dec/05/fortnite-to-launch-creative-mode</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBbM7Jw2PWHMnSMWxixI8qkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:29:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/dec/05/fortnite-to-launch-creative-mode" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite to enter Minecraft territory with new Creative mode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hit video game Fortnite is to get a Creative mode, allowing players to design and play on their own islands. In a major addition to the title, the new mode lets players fly freely around the environment, placing scenic elements, then designing their own mini-games to play with friends. Developer Epic Games is launching the new option, named Fortnite Creative, on 6 December. Best known for its free online multiplayer mode, Battle Royale, in which 100 players land on an island and shoot each other until only one remains, Fortnite has become one of the most successful video games of the la...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Developer Epic Is Launching A Huge Steam Competitor With A Better Cut For Devs - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/04/fortnite-developer-epic-is-launching-a-huge-steam-competitor-with-a-better-cut-for-devs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKEOTyDwd4Ae5_BJ3Hl4TCAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/04/fortnite-developer-epic-is-launching-a-huge-steam-competitor-with-a-better-cut-for-devs/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Developer Epic Is Launching A Huge Steam Competitor With A Better Cut For Devs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Epic Store Split Big, big news in the PC gaming landscape today as all that Fortnite cash has propelled Epic to launch a truly massive project. Epic has announced the Epic Store, a direct competitor to Steam that undercuts the rate Valve’s service gives to developers. That’s the biggest news about this storefront without question. While Steam takes a 30% cut while leaving the developer 70%, the Epic store will take just a 12% cut while leaving 88% for the developer. And if your game is using Epic’s Unreal Engine, that 5% royalty fee will be taken out of Epic’s side, not yours. The timin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite's Big Announcement Leaks Early: Check Out The Brand-New Creative Mode In Action - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/fortnites-big-announcement-leaks-early-check-out-the-brand-new-creative-mode-in-action/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDK4cQP_TL8cTBmFV5zRND8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/fortnites-big-announcement-leaks-early-check-out-the-brand-new-creative-mode-in-action/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite's Big Announcement Leaks Early: Check Out The Brand-New Creative Mode In Action&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Playground in Fortnite. We knew there was a big announcement coming for Fortnite at the Game Awards on Thursday, and it looks like someone just broke embargo on it. Notice that I say Fortnite and not Fortnite: Battle Royale, though I do sometimes use the terms interchangeably. That’s because this new announcement looks to be a complete third mode for the rapidly expanding game, designed to stand beside Battle Royale and Save the World as something entirely different. It’s called Creative Mode, and it looks We first got a look at this thanks to a Youtuber who got an early peek at the game an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Check Out Fortnite's First Season 7 Teaser: A Terrifying New Winter Skin - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/03/check-out-fortnites-first-season-7-teaser-a-terrifying-new-winter-skin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEB6j6XVdf-OC3qq1_lu1LoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/03/check-out-fortnites-first-season-7-teaser-a-terrifying-new-winter-skin/" target="_blank"&gt;Check Out Fortnite's First Season 7 Teaser: A Terrifying New Winter Skin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Epic Games just revealed the first teaser for ‘Fortnite: Battle Royale’ Season 7. And it’s scary. Epic Games just dropped the first teaser for Season 7, which is slated for a likely full reveal this Thursday at the Game Awards. The first teaser, which Epic tweeted earlier this morning, shows off a surprisingly ominous new winter-themed character/outfit, and includes the phrase: “A bitter ice spreads…3 days to Season 7.” If you were expecting a cheery Christmas-themed Season 7, you couldn’t be further off the mark. A bitter ice spreading sounds rather dark—something George R.R. Martin might ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Is Likely Dropping Big Season 7 News At The Game Awards - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/03/fortnite-is-likely-dropping-big-season-7-news-at-the-game-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKDh0Twe17EMAWJOAd7mNtIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/03/fortnite-is-likely-dropping-big-season-7-news-at-the-game-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Is Likely Dropping Big Season 7 News At The Game Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite The Game Awards has not only secured itself as the closest thing we’re going to get to video game Oscars, but also, essentially, as Winter E3, where game companies drop news and trailers for their upcoming 2019 releases and beyond. We’re getting a bunch of world premieres, but also something else. Both host Geoff Keighley and Epic have confirmed that there will be Fortnite news at the December 5 event. Fortnite is nominated for a few Game Awards, and seems likely to win best ongoing game and possibly best multiplayer, given the year it’s had. But the timing of the Game Awards just ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite player count rises 60pc in six months to reach 200 million - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-player-count-rises-60-six-months-reach-200-million/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENH9FOQOqTUZR5-MhsDowq8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:46:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-player-count-rises-60-six-months-reach-200-million/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite player count rises 60pc in six months to reach 200 million&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The popularity of Battle Royale phenomenon Fortnite shows no signs of abating. In another arresting milestone, the developer of the smash video game Epic Games has said that Fortnite now has 200 million registered users. This makes for a 60pc jump on the 125 million player-count Epic revealed in June. While many of those 200 million registered users will not be playing the game regularly, Epic also said that Fortnite also recently achieved a record concurrent player count of 8.3 million. This particular figure is one of the clearest indicators of the gaming's extraordinarily successful year...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite: The Story So Far' Is A Must-Watch Video That Took Eight Months To Film - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/27/fortnite-the-story-so-far-is-a-must-watch-video-that-took-eight-months-to-film/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQ_lJWIHmAZDB6JPwg04kIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/27/fortnite-the-story-so-far-is-a-must-watch-video-that-took-eight-months-to-film/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite: The Story So Far' Is A Must-Watch Video That Took Eight Months To Film&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Fortnite remains one of the most strangely fascinating games out there with an engaging story that…is barely a story at all. There are characters, but few have names and literally no one talks. There are big moments that take place in the game that has the community buzzing, yet almost no one truly understands what’s going on. From seasons 3-6, Fortnite has been telling effectively one story, with one event leading into another the seems to have culminated, and possibly ended, midway through season 6. YouTuber LaffenGas has been filming for eight months now, capturing every major e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 'Fortnite' Monster: 200 Million Players, 8.3 Million Concurrents - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/28/the-fortnite-monster-200-million-players-8-3-million-concurrents/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBPX8lIsAbEqiyHpacdL0ykqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/28/the-fortnite-monster-200-million-players-8-3-million-concurrents/" target="_blank"&gt;The 'Fortnite' Monster: 200 Million Players, 8.3 Million Concurrents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite The era of Fortnite is far from over, as Epic has hit enough new milestones to start talking publicly about them again. Fortnite now has 200 million registered players, a 60% increase from June alone, when it last clocked in at 125 million. It also now has 8.3 million concurrent players on a regular basis, another huge jump from the last time we got these stats, 4.3 million in February. I mean, what else can even be said about Fortnite at this point? It’s a global gaming trend that I’ve rarely seen on this scale, not since Pokémon GO took over the world, but Fortnite has done that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Has Bridged the Gap Between E-Sports and Traditional Sports - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/leighsteinberg/2018/11/30/fortnite-has-bridged-the-gap-between-e-sports-and-traditional-sports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBOE41XJpt_uir7-bAM7bbAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 18:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/leighsteinberg/2018/11/30/fortnite-has-bridged-the-gap-between-e-sports-and-traditional-sports/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Has Bridged the Gap Between E-Sports and Traditional Sports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cross convergence of sports and video games just accelerated with the recent announcement that the NFL and Fortnite are doing a deal to feature jerseys from each of the 32 teams in gameplay. This is the first major deal between a video game company and a major sports league. Fortnite is an action video game which has become a sensation, especially among athletes. Professional athletes in football, soccer, and other sports have broken out in Fortnite celebration dances during real-world sporting events. NFL players like Colts TE Eric Ebron have been mimicking Fortnite dances and other an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite facing legal threats over 'stolen' dances, but can you copyright choreography? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/fortnite-facing-legal-threats-stolen-dances-can-copyright-choreography/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPsIwPxxDagDm_l0u8dR3gqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 07:18:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/fortnite-facing-legal-threats-stolen-dances-can-copyright-choreography/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite facing legal threats over 'stolen' dances, but can you copyright choreography?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can you copyright a dance move? What exactly are my legal rights over my uncoordinated Saturday night fever? Do I have a case if, say, a video game creates a dance move called ‘flailing water butt’ and charges its players money to be able to use it in game? Probably not. But more coordinated and famous dance artists just might. Earlier this week, the thorny issue of Epic Games allegedly 'stealing' dances from the real world in its phenomenally popular Fortnite Battle Royale game reared its head again. If you have missed the memo on Fortnite’s ‘emotes’, they are actions, flourishes and dance...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>A New 'Fortnite' Awaits In Blockchain Gaming - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidpetersson/2018/11/16/a-new-fortnite-awaits-in-blockchain-gaming/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGSanBzD24AmJpvtCu9LpFQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidpetersson/2018/11/16/a-new-fortnite-awaits-in-blockchain-gaming/" target="_blank"&gt;A New 'Fortnite' Awaits In Blockchain Gaming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fortnite Effect The Epic Games Inc. Fortnite: Battle Royale video game is displayed for a photograph on an Apple Inc. iPhone in Washington, D.C., U.S., on Thursday, May 10, 2018. Fortnite, the hit game that’s denting the stock prices of video-game makers after signing up 45 million players, didn’t really take off until it became free and a free-for-all. Photographer: Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg Fortnite is one of the most profitable games in history—and growing. Since launch, the free-to-play game has brought in more than $1.2 billion in revenue. I also holds the record for most revenues in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Has Let Ghoul Trooper Remain One Of Its Rarest Skins Ever - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/12/fortnite-has-let-ghoul-trooper-remain-one-of-its-rarest-skins-ever/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENf8nhV39Ws8aL4eu5cRDgIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 14:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/12/fortnite-has-let-ghoul-trooper-remain-one-of-its-rarest-skins-ever/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Has Let Ghoul Trooper Remain One Of Its Rarest Skins Ever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite We are now moving rapidly toward Thanksgiving and deep into season 6 of Fortnite. The game’s Halloween event, Fortnitemares, has come and gone with the Cube explosion, but one significant aspect of the season remains a mystery. Why did Ghoul Trooper never make a return, in any form, to the store? Ghoul Trooper and Skull Trooper were a pair of Halloween skins that were released a year ago in 2017 before Fortnite: BR was the global phenomenon it is now. As such, they became two of the most sought after skins in the game, because they were not sold again after that point, so only “OG”...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite partners with NFL to bring American Football outfits for all 32 teams - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-nfl-outfits-new-skins-american-football-teams-epic-games-v-bucks-a8619951.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBStg1XRtaY6j30JKwC6DLIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-nfl-outfits-new-skins-american-football-teams-epic-games-v-bucks-a8619951.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite partners with NFL to bring American Football outfits for all 32 teams&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a first-of-its-kind partnership, Fortnite developer Epic Games has partnered with the National Football League (NFL) in order to bring team outfits to the hugely popular video game. From 9 November, Fortnite players will be able to get hold of outfits from all 32 teams in the NFL, as well as other American Football-themed items from the game's Battle Royale Item Shop. "We see the popularity of Fortnite every day at the NFL as many of our players are passionate about this game," said Brian Rolapp, chief media and business officer at the NFL. "This partnership represents a great opportunit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Here Are All The Awesome Leaked Skins And Cosmetics In Fortnite's v6.21 Patch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/01/here-are-all-the-awesome-leaked-skins-and-cosmetics-in-fortnites-v6-21-patch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF6BmTXHCB3oQ2cjXwPE8tYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 11:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/01/here-are-all-the-awesome-leaked-skins-and-cosmetics-in-fortnites-v6-21-patch/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are All The Awesome Leaked Skins And Cosmetics In Fortnite's v6.21 Patch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Fortnite has arrived with a new patch today in addition to challenge rotation for week 6, and there’s a whole lot of stuff being extracted from the data as we speak. The army of leakers who dissects this stuff has already found a new, giant treasure trove of cosmetics that should be heading to the store shortly, with at least one skin already live right now. We are mostly moving past the Halloween theme now that we’re in November, and some players will be enthused to see that at least a pair of these appear to be Borderlands-inspired, or at least generically post-apocalyptic at wor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Everything You Need To Know About Fortnite's Big One Time Cube Event - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/03/fortnitemares-explosion-everything-you-need-to-know-about-fortnites-big-one-time-cube-event/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOfVbwRHU470Z0uUgCE2ZMQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/03/fortnitemares-explosion-everything-you-need-to-know-about-fortnites-big-one-time-cube-event/" target="_blank"&gt;Everything You Need To Know About Fortnite's Big One Time Cube Event&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite If you want to unlock the Dark Engine glider in Fortnite: Battle Royale, you better do so today. The Halloween ‘Fortnitemares’ ends tomorrow, November 4th, so after that we can say goodbye to the legions of cube monsters as well as the challenges and rewards that go along with them. But things aren’t going to end with a simple deactivation: developer Epic Games has something a little more involved in mind. Fortnitemares will end with a special one-time event this Sunday, the developer announced the other day. But what does that mean? Read on for everything you need to know about Su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Tencent's Epic Games, Developer Of Fortnite, Now Valued At More Than $15 Billion - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ljkelly/2018/10/29/tencents-epic-games-developer-of-fortnite-now-valued-at-more-than-15-billion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH9PBLq46xuQ9LCJDaRccaoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ljkelly/2018/10/29/tencents-epic-games-developer-of-fortnite-now-valued-at-more-than-15-billion/" target="_blank"&gt;Tencent's Epic Games, Developer Of Fortnite, Now Valued At More Than $15 Billion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A gamer plays the video game ‘Fortnite Battle Royale’ developed by Epic Games on a Samsung Galaxy Note 9 smartphone. (Photo by Chesnot/Getty Images) Epic Games, the studio behind gaming sensation Fortnite, has been valued at more than $15 billion in its latest funding round that was led by private equity firm KKR. Majority-owned by Tencent, Epic Games received a $1.25 billion cash boost aimed at expanding the company’s efforts in esports and live events. North Carolina-based Epic Games, which also develops titles such as Gears of War and Unreal Tournament, was valued at just $660 million wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite company Epic Games valued at nearly $15bn after cash boost - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/oct/28/fortnite-company-epic-games-valued-15bn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG5amgzfGuX7927f1dKpB4AqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 17:52:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/oct/28/fortnite-company-epic-games-valued-15bn" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite company Epic Games valued at nearly $15bn after cash boost&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company behind the Fortnite video game has been valued at almost $15bn (£11.7bn) after receiving a $1.25bn cash injection led by the private equity firm KKR. The game, which has been described as a cross between The Hunger Games and Minecraft, has proved hugely popular since its release last year by Epic Games. The game is free to download, making money by charging players for costumes and other embellishments in virtual in-game currency. Fortnite, which in “battle royale” mode involves 100 characters fighting for survival on a dystopian island, has been played by more than 125 million ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Fortnite developer Epic Games raises $1.25bn from KKR - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/27/fortnite-developer-epic-games-raises-125bn-kkr/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECfSg6stjlmp2xNzr7j4f_4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 12:48:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/27/fortnite-developer-epic-games-raises-125bn-kkr/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite developer Epic Games raises $1.25bn from KKR&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The developer of online gaming free-for-all Fortnite has raised $1.25bn (£1bn) from private equity backers as it looks to expand into esports and live gaming events. Fortnite has proved an addictive hit drawing in more than 78 million players each month with fans including football star Dele Alli and the rapper Drake. Its developer, Epic Games, secured the funding from private equity giant KKR. The firm joins current investors Tencent and Disney, taking a minority stake. Epic continues to be controlled by chief executive Tim Sweeney. Mr Sweeney said: "We’re excited to partner with the fines...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' creator Epic Games raises $1.25 bln from KKR, others - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-epic-games-funding/fortnite-creator-epic-games-raises-1-25-bln-from-kkr-others-idUSKCN1N0277</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKELkltokoLU1qjTteCUfTUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 20:35:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-epic-games-funding/fortnite-creator-epic-games-raises-1-25-bln-from-kkr-others-idUSKCN1N0277" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' creator Epic Games raises $1.25 bln from KKR, others&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Epic Games, the creator of video game sensation "Fortnite", said on Friday it received $1.25 billion in funding from investors, including KKR &amp; Co Inc (KKR.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), Iconiq Capital and Smash Ventures. "Fortnite," a sort of hybrid of "The Hunger Games" and "Minecraft," drops 100 people onto an island to fight each other for survival. The tactical tournament game, whose first version was released in 2017, has been called an industry "game-changer" by analysts as it signed up tens of millions of users for its last-player-standing "Battle Royale" format. Epic Gam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Fortnite developer Epic Games raises $1.25bn - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e9876162-d934-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJYCYW3VXPIUQPqEHYdsOeEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 15:48:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e9876162-d934-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite developer Epic Games raises $1.25bn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite’s developer Epic Games has received a huge new power-up in the form of a $1.25bn investment led by private equity group KKR. The North Carolina-based creator of the video gaming phenomenon of the summer said the investment would help it to expand into esports and live events, as well as developing its Unreal Engine platform, which underpins many 3D games. KKR is joined in the round by ICONIQ Capital, Smash Ventures, aXiomatic, Vulcan Capital, Kleiner Perkins and Lightspeed Venture Partners. “We’re excited to partner with the finest minds in the financial, sports, and entertainment ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Six Shooter, Cube Monsters And More: Everything In Fortnite's Huge v6.20 'Fortnitemares' Patch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/24/six-shooter-cube-monsters-and-more-everything-in-fortnites-huge-v6-2-fortnitemares-patch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIINh1Ah2q_piMOB4aDp5z8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 10:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/24/six-shooter-cube-monsters-and-more-everything-in-fortnites-huge-v6-2-fortnitemares-patch/" target="_blank"&gt;Six Shooter, Cube Monsters And More: Everything In Fortnite's Huge v6.20 'Fortnitemares' Patch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Fortnitemares is here, and it’s a big one. Epic Games has been teasing this for days, and it’s far and away the biggest update we’ve ever seen save a new season: we’ve got challenges, new map elements, weapons and spooky battle bus decorations: there’s a lot to work with here. It’s funny to think that last year we saw a Halloween event with little more than a few skins and a pumpkin launcher, but, well, this game has come a long way since then. Here’s everything that’s in Fortnite: Battle Royale’s massive Fortnitemares update. To start with: Cube Island has been destroyed and is no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Skins Are Too Expensive, Even For A Free-To-Play Game - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/22/fortnite-battle-royale-skins-are-too-expensive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJoXOeMYXLPXNkTPFfHQyIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/22/fortnite-battle-royale-skins-are-too-expensive/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Skins Are Too Expensive, Even For A Free-To-Play Game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite: Battle Royale is a free-to-play game and you don’t need to spend a single penny to play it, but Epic Games sells both a $10 ten-week Battle Pass and various rotating cosmetics in the game’s Item Shop, so there are plenty of ways to part with your cash. Epic Games has gotten better when it comes to cosmetic design since the game first launched. Compare last year’s Halloween skins to this year’s spooky Outfits to see what I mean: Ghoul Trooper and Skull Trooper The classic Fortnite Halloween skins, Ghoul Trooper and Skull Trooper, are beloved Outfits because they’re classics (as muc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Halloween update: Latest patch brings hordes of 'Cube Monsters' to the map– but just don't call them zombies - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-halloween-update-latest-patch-notes-zombies-cube-monsters-map-location-skins-epic-games-a8600696.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVkOxbKglPLLi1g-Z_BlOUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 11:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-halloween-update-latest-patch-notes-zombies-cube-monsters-map-location-skins-epic-games-a8600696.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Halloween update: Latest patch brings hordes of 'Cube Monsters' to the map– but just don't call them zombies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest update for Fortnite: Battle Royale has come just in time for Halloween, introducing new weapons with which to defeat an onslaught of new monsters. The Halloween event comes as part of the patch v6.20 for Fortnite Season 6, which represents one of the biggest patches ever introduced to the game. Fortnite developer Epic Games dubbed the Halloween event "Fortnitemares" and plans to introduce a new set of challenges every few days as part of the patch. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/43 Designed by Pierpaolo Lazzarini from Italian ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Testing 'Soaring' Mechanic In All Game Modes - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/23/fortnite-battle-royale-testing-soaring-mechanic-in-all-game-modes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGEKJViQKh7MU8S2Pr5V-H8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 19:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/23/fortnite-battle-royale-testing-soaring-mechanic-in-all-game-modes/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Testing 'Soaring' Mechanic In All Game Modes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting tomorrow you’ll be able to redeploy your glider in all Fortnite’s game modes. I loved Soaring 50s when it was added to Fortnite a few weeks ago. The limited-time mode is currently unavailable, but the soaring mechanic is alive and well in Disco Domination. Being able to redeploy your glider when leaping off of tall buildings, ramps or cliffs allows players to move about the map much more quickly. It also means fewer deaths via fall damage, and just makes the whole game a bit faster and more mobile. In other words, being able to soar in Fortnite makes the game better and more fun. W...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here Are All The (Amazing) Leaked Skins And Cosmetics Found In Fortnite's v6.10 Patch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/16/here-are-all-the-amazing-leaked-skins-and-cosmetics-found-in-fortnites-v6-10-patch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENs0XOhAnM9FCWe0JMmWw4MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 15:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/16/here-are-all-the-amazing-leaked-skins-and-cosmetics-found-in-fortnites-v6-10-patch/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are All The (Amazing) Leaked Skins And Cosmetics Found In Fortnite's v6.10 Patch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are all the amazing leaked skins and other cosmetics just leaked in Fortnite’s v6.10 patch. Fortnite: Battle Royale was updated to patch v6.10 this morning. You can read the patch notes here, including the addition of the new Quadcrasher vehicle which I’m excited to take for a spin. As usual, along with the update come the leaks. This week we have a bunch of leaked Outfits and other cosmetics and, in keeping with the spooky Halloween spirit, a couple of these are creepily amazing. Let’s take a look at all the cosmetics leaked in the v6.10 patch: Outfits/Skins Spider Knight (Legendary) ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Season 6, Week 4 'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Challenges Leak Online, But There's A Catch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/17/season-6-week-4-fortnite-battle-royale-challenges-leak-online-but-theres-a-catch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEECX9W46Qe5uQNLjdtVUB7kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 13:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/17/season-6-week-4-fortnite-battle-royale-challenges-leak-online-but-theres-a-catch/" target="_blank"&gt;Season 6, Week 4 'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Challenges Leak Online, But There's A Catch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A corrupted zone in Fortnite: Battle Royale Epic is making life a little bit harder for dataminers this season of Fortnite: Battle Royale. It used to be that we’d see new challenges leaked on a regular basis, and that they would line up pretty well with the challenges that actually showed up in game. Not so anymore: the lists are further diverging from reality, whether that’s intentional obfuscation or just the need to shift things around for whatever reason. That doesn’t mean they don’t offer us any information, however, so let’s take a look at the leaked challenges that dataminers have fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New In-Game 'Tournaments' Coming To 'Fortnite' Tomorrow: Here's How They Work - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/15/new-tournaments-mode-coming-to-fortnite-tomorrow-heres-how-it-works/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGfNVn5_nVVdJzg5QoffZCsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/15/new-tournaments-mode-coming-to-fortnite-tomorrow-heres-how-it-works/" target="_blank"&gt;New In-Game 'Tournaments' Coming To 'Fortnite' Tomorrow: Here's How They Work&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In-game Tournaments arrive in Fortnite tomorrow. Here’s how to join the fun. Epic Games has announced that new in-game Tournaments will be coming to Fortnite: Battle Royale beginning tomorrow, October 16th. There will be a new Events section in the game’s menu which will allow you to access the Tournaments. Unlike major eSports events, these in-game Tournaments will be available to everyone. That means all you have to do is join a Tournament to start competing in order to win a shiny pin. According to Epic, winning said shiny pin in the future will open up new Tournaments to compete in. Her...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>‘Black Ops 4’: How ‘Call of Duty’s’ New Battle Royale Mode Outshines ‘Fortnite’ - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/black-ops-4-how-call-of-dutys-new-battle-royale-mode-outshines-fortnite</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAA0ExkETb8buqJExvR0TYIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 08:47:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/black-ops-4-how-call-of-dutys-new-battle-royale-mode-outshines-fortnite" target="_blank"&gt;‘Black Ops 4’: How ‘Call of Duty’s’ New Battle Royale Mode Outshines ‘Fortnite’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activision Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 is the most significant release in the wildly successful first-person shooter franchise in over a decade. Maybe there’s something about fourths, because it was Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare that changed what the series was and could be in 2007. The critically acclaimed single-player campaign made a splash, but the waves that its multiplayer version left behind are still being felt all these years later. Ever since, the online modes have been many players’ real draw to the games. Now, they’re all that they have. Black Ops 4 may not change gaming, but it ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Ghoul Trooper Probably Coming After Skull Trooper For 'Fortnite' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/12/ghoul-trooper-probably-coming-after-skull-trooper-for-fortnite/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFcbkdNJx4otcmo4HS9VVCgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 13:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/12/ghoul-trooper-probably-coming-after-skull-trooper-for-fortnite/" target="_blank"&gt;Ghoul Trooper Probably Coming After Skull Trooper For 'Fortnite'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite: Battle Royale Consider this: it’s only October 12, and Epic Games has already dropped arguably its most in-demand Halloween Skin. Skull Trooper hit Fortnite: Battle Royale earlier this week, marking the return of what had been one the rarest and most coveted skins in the game. It’s neither so rare nor so coveted now, but those who had it last year still get a special piece of flair so they can flaunt their original ghoul status. But like I said, it’s only October 12. And that means there’s plenty of Halloween left for a game that’s so far not shy about slapping spiderwebs and ghos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here's When 'Fortnite' Servers Go Offline Ahead Of Epic's Next Big Update - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/15/heres-when-fortnite-servers-go-offline-ahead-of-epics-next-big-update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIpKI29V9kLBtokEbLUbMFMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 21:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/15/heres-when-fortnite-servers-go-offline-ahead-of-epics-next-big-update/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's When 'Fortnite' Servers Go Offline Ahead Of Epic's Next Big Update&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s when downtime starts for Fortnite’s next big update. Fortnite: Battle Royale servers are going offline to make way for Epic’s big v6.10 patch. The patch will usher in the new in-game Tournaments, which you can read about here. We’ll also likely see the arrival of a brand new vehicle, the Quadcrasher, which looks pretty sweet. Epic Games announced the exact time servers will go offline: 4 am ET, tomorrow October 16th. That’s 1 am PT, 8 am GMT. Downtime usually lasts for an hour or two at most. Patch notes will go live once the downtime begins, so we’ll know for sure what tweaks Epic i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite cheats on YouTube spark Epic Games lawsuit in attempt to stop people getting special abilities - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/fortnite-cheat-sheet-season-6-codes-youtube-epic-games-lawsuit-a8586941.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAMGndDIEYNAaMOws-K_Iq0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/fortnite-cheat-sheet-season-6-codes-youtube-epic-games-lawsuit-a8586941.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite cheats on YouTube spark Epic Games lawsuit in attempt to stop people getting special abilities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The developers of the popular video game Fortnite have filed a lawsuit against two YouTube personalities for allegedly selling cheat codes to their viewers. Popular YouTuber Golden Modz, who boasts more than 1.7 million subscribers on the video-sharing platform, shared videos that showcased "magical powers" to help Fortnite players defeat their opponents. A second YouTuber who goes by the name Exentric is also accused of directing viewers to a website selling cheats for the game. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/43 Designed by Pierpaolo La...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Epic Games Just Totally Nerfed Fortnite's Skull Trooper Back Bling Challenges - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/11/epic-games-just-majorly-nerfed-fortnites-skull-trooper-back-bling-challenges/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDU91QcaBuW_ANzz31ceoeQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 21:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/11/epic-games-just-majorly-nerfed-fortnites-skull-trooper-back-bling-challenges/" target="_blank"&gt;Epic Games Just Totally Nerfed Fortnite's Skull Trooper Back Bling Challenges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well the Ghost Portal Back Bling challenges just got a lot easier and less interesting. Epic Games has apparently taken flak for the very challenging Skull Trooper “Ghost Portal” Back Bling challenges. When those challenges were first revealed, we were all a little surprised by how hard they were. They included getting eliminations in 14 matches, playing a total of 50 matches, and dealing 1000 damage to opponents in a single match (among others which you can read about at the link above.) For high-level players like Ninja these aren’t too difficult. For mere mortals like yours truly, dealin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Enters Open Beta On Android, Now Available To Everyone - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/11/fortnite-battle-royale-enters-open-beta-on-android-now-available-to-everyone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFyhd1-GP2s236R2Eabfj7AqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 15:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/11/fortnite-battle-royale-enters-open-beta-on-android-now-available-to-everyone/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Enters Open Beta On Android, Now Available To Everyone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite is now available to everyone on Android, so long as you have a compatible device. Fortnite: Battle Royale has left closed beta on Android and is now open to everyone with a compatible device. You can see which devices are compatible with the free-to-play battle royale game here. Previously gamers had to sign up for an invitation to play the game on Android devices. Now you can simply go to Epic’s website and download the game. I haven’t played Fortnite on my Galaxy S8+ since it first came out. At the time it was laggy and not great, similar to when I first played the game on my iPa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>This chart suggests that we’ve reached peak Fortnite - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-chart-shows-weve-reached-peak-fortnite-2018-10-06</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPe7QSH0426k9kJhiwlbDKYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 17:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-chart-shows-weve-reached-peak-fortnite-2018-10-06" target="_blank"&gt;This chart suggests that we’ve reached peak Fortnite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN ONE CHART By Emily Bary Social-media mentions of Fortnite Season 6 are down considerably from past seasons, good news for EA and Activision Bloomberg There has been substantially less social-media chatter about the latest season of Fortnite than there was in past seasons, and that bodes well for big videogame publishers Activision Blizzard Inc., Electronic Arts Inc., and Take-Two Interactive Software Inc. Usually significant social-media buzz accompanies the introduction of new Fortnite seasons, but launch day for Season 6, which made its debut Sept. 27, was fairly tame in terms of Twitt...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Deep Freeze retail bundle targeting Christmas crowd - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-deep-freeze-retail-bundle-targeting-christmas-crowd/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_x8GE3N8FC62GaCrHEI5sqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 15:22:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-deep-freeze-retail-bundle-targeting-christmas-crowd/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Deep Freeze retail bundle targeting Christmas crowd&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Epic Games has teamed up with Warner Bros. Interactive to produce a physical retail version of Fortnite Battle Royale, the phenomenally popular video game that continues to take the world by storm. Fortnite: Deep Freeze will appear on shelves from 16 November for PS4, Xbox One and Switch. It will cost £25 and includes a copy of Fortnite Battle Royale, skins for a Frostbite Outfit, Cold Front Glider, Chill-Axe Pickaxe and Freezing Point Back Bling. The bundle will also include 1000 V-Bucks, the currency used within Fortnite to purchase new outfits, emotes and weapon skins. The bundle will al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Call Of Duty's 'Blackout' Doesn't Truly Compete With 'Fortnite' For Two Simple Reasons - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/12/call-of-dutys-blackout-doesnt-really-compete-with-fortnite-for-two-simple-reasons/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJovaDEJZfCz5JhtC2XROdsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 15:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/12/call-of-dutys-blackout-doesnt-really-compete-with-fortnite-for-two-simple-reasons/" target="_blank"&gt;Call Of Duty's 'Blackout' Doesn't Truly Compete With 'Fortnite' For Two Simple Reasons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Here’s a small indication of what publisher Activision thinks about Blackout, the new battle royale mode for Call of Duty: Black Ops 4, out today. As with all games, there’s a minimum amount you need to download before you can start playing Black Ops 4. And if you boot up the game at that minimum viable moment, you’ll notice something on the mode select screen. You won’t be able to play zombies and you won’t be able to play traditional multiplayer, because Blackout is the first thing the game downloaded. And why wouldn’t it be? Blackout has already made a splash in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How To Get Paid With Fortnite's New 'Support-A-Creator' Program - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/06/how-to-get-paid-with-fortnites-new-support-a-creator-program/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO6uMyf9d2sIhpP3f8E5HQ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 12:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/06/how-to-get-paid-with-fortnites-new-support-a-creator-program/" target="_blank"&gt;How To Get Paid With Fortnite's New 'Support-A-Creator' Program&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Fortnite would not be where it is today without its legions of creators blowing up the game on Twitch and YouTube, and Epic certainly seems to realize that. That’s why they’ve launched a new program that runs from next week through the end of the year where, if you’re a creator, you can get free money whenever any of your friends or fans spend V-Bucks in the game. If you want to support a creator yourself, next week you will enter their Epic name into the game and every 14 days, either reselect them or pick someone new. After that, your V-Buck purchases, whether they be paid or ear...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite patch notes 6.02 update: New skins and LTM Disco Domination is now live - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-patch-notes-602-update-new-skins-ltm-disco-domination/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGJOkSzhgXzbUz3vzWXNRtoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 12:28:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-patch-notes-602-update-new-skins-ltm-disco-domination/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite patch notes 6.02 update: New skins and LTM Disco Domination is now live&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest update for Fortnite Battle Royale is now live, and it's a significant one, bringing with it a fresh limited time game mode, a chunky new special weapon and Skull Trooper skins. Patch 6.02, the second of Fortnite Season 6's mean that new mode Disco Domination is available to play now. It is a combination of Fortnite's sprawling multiplayer hijinks and the dancing emotes that have also helped bring the game to widespread attention. In the King of the Hill style mode two teams of fifty players drop into the map and must attack five dance floors scattered around the map. How the Fort...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fortnite season 6 review: is the world's most popular game keeping up the pace? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/oct/05/fortnite-season-six-review</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPAa2U0AOL1Z72Z1iK9aNuoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 13:20:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/oct/05/fortnite-season-six-review" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite season 6 review: is the world's most popular game keeping up the pace?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite developer Epic Games certainly lived up to its name with the launch of season six. Arriving last Thursday, the latest instalment of the Battle Royale juggernaut saw a great chunk of land being ripped from Loot Lake and re-forming as a floating sky island supported by the purple interdimensional cube that’s been hovering over the map for weeks. But that wasn’t the only major change to either the map or the weird mythology that seems to underpin everything that happens in the game. These are the key new places to explore and features to play with. The floating island (of course) The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>What To Expect From Fortnite's Halloween Event - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/02/what-to-expect-from-fortnites-halloween-event/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPKea3fKaaNnGln2xaIA3m4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 13:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/02/what-to-expect-from-fortnites-halloween-event/" target="_blank"&gt;What To Expect From Fortnite's Halloween Event&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite: Battle Royale So, here’s one thing that we can assume beyond a reasonable doubt: Fortnite: Battle Royale is going to have a Halloween event. No, developer Epic Games has not announced one yet, but in the world of unannounced announcements, this one feels about as assured as you can get. For one thing, Halloween decorations are already popping up in-game. For another, the entire battle pass is “spooky” themed for Season 6, not to mention the shadow stones, haunted castle, otherworldly floating island and other Halloween-adjacent items. Also, Ninja said something to that effect last...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite's Floating Island Is Its Most Impressive Map Change Yet - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/27/fortnites-loot-lake-floating-island-is-its-most-impressive-map-change-yet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKJSKMz-EwR_n6vTc5z8UkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 15:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/27/fortnites-loot-lake-floating-island-is-its-most-impressive-map-change-yet/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite's Floating Island Is Its Most Impressive Map Change Yet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost exactly a year ago, Player Unknown’s Battlegrounds was on top of the world and Epic Games was testing the waters with a battle royale game of its own, for which it used its zombie survival game Fortnite as a template. At the time, it looked something like a PUBG clone, though it was one of the first of such clones to hit the market. It took place on a largely barren map with some small buildings and the occasional larger subdivision or farm, and we wondered how it would distinguish itself from PUBG. A year later, we’re staring this thing in the face: Fortnite Season 6 has arrived in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Season 6: Shadow Stones Are Already Disabled - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/28/fortnite-season-6-shadow-stones-are-already-disabled/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENmVbqZt-J_MJ0UjhbF_ZSQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 13:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/28/fortnite-season-6-shadow-stones-are-already-disabled/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Season 6: Shadow Stones Are Already Disabled&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;fortnite Season 6 hit Fortnite: Battle Royale yesterday, bringing with it a new battle pass along with a raft of map changes and new gameplay to match the new spooky/Halloween theme. Perhaps the most striking item developer Epic Games introduced has to be the Shadow Stone: a new consumable that turns you into a wraith for a limited time, during which you’re mostly invisible if you stand still, but more visible if you move. You also can’t use weapons and can phase through walls by an ability. It’s the sort of item that has the ability to totally upend what we expect out of encounters, but we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Profiting Off Dance Moves: Is It Legal? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/legalentertainment/2018/09/28/fortnite-profiting-off-dance-moves-is-it-legal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENzqmBhhtSe-1OyrpuEbXVEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 00:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/legalentertainment/2018/09/28/fortnite-profiting-off-dance-moves-is-it-legal/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Profiting Off Dance Moves: Is It Legal?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Epic Games Inc. Fortnite: Battle Royale video game is displayed for a photograph on an Apple Inc. iPhone in Washington, D.C., U.S., on Thursday, May 10, 2018. Photographer: Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg Fortnite, an online third-person shooter game released by Epic Games, has become one of the most popular online games in the industry. However, it has also recently come under fire for allegedly stealing dance moves from hip-hop artists. While no lawsuit has been filed yet, the growing controversy begs the question: are dance moves protected under copyright? In Fortnite, players have the abili...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite season 6 update now live: Battle Pass, challenges and patch notes revealed - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fortnite-season-6-update-now-live-battle-pass-challenges-patch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF96HAglFkNpGv2Ki5vBnZ0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 11:40:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fortnite-season-6-update-now-live-battle-pass-challenges-patch/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite season 6 update now live: Battle Pass, challenges and patch notes revealed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Season 6 is now live and the Battle Royale phenomenon's players are getting their first taste of a changed map that features a new location in the Wailing Woods to the north-east and a floating island complete with haunted castle above Loot Lake. In a blog post detailing the patch notes for Fortnite version 6.0, Epic said that fans will be able to explore a changed map with floating islands and new corrupted areas, players will now be able to take pets and there is the new Shadow Stones, a new consumable that allows you to 'become one with the shadows'. However, shadow stones are t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The clever UX that made Fortnite a $1.2 billion sensation - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90241691/the-clever-ux-that-made-fortnite-a-1-2-billion-sensation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_dKHB11_NlDC85n-E10Z4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 09:00:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90241691/the-clever-ux-that-made-fortnite-a-1-2-billion-sensation" target="_blank"&gt;The clever UX that made Fortnite a $1.2 billion sensation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The online videogame Fortnite Battle Royale was launched just a year ago in September 2017. Since then the game had amassed 125 million active players by June and made $1.2 billion for its developer Epic Games. It has also been linked to 200 divorces and a case of aggravated harassment where a 45-year-old man threatened to kill an 11-year-old boy after losing to him in the game. Love it or hate it, the question is: How has Epic Games created a game with such enormous social, economic, and psychological impact? Fusing elements from recent hits such as Minecraft, PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Nintendo: over Mario - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/878a3e64-c24e-11e8-8d55-54197280d3f7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMErbtCCh4_ptBMkWuUMcBEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 15:05:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/878a3e64-c24e-11e8-8d55-54197280d3f7" target="_blank"&gt;Nintendo: over Mario&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Accepting Super Mario can fail is distressing for ageing fans of the endearing plumber. Yet the release of role-playing computer game Dragalia Lost shows Nintendo is aware of his weaknesses. Super Mario Run flopped last year, punishing the Japanese computer games group for its reliance on the character. The new game — swords and sorcery with hints of Shinto — indicates a welcome departure from this conservatism. The games industry is tilting towards the huge Asian market. UBS expects gaming revenues in Asia to grow 9.5 per cent a year to $200bn in 2030. Asian gamers play lengthily on their ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>How 'Fortnite' Can Avoid Getting Stale In Season 6 And Beyond - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/09/25/how-fortnite-can-avoid-getting-stale-in-season-6-and-beyond/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL1E6S5jCsRThXXrxczA8ikqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 14:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/09/25/how-fortnite-can-avoid-getting-stale-in-season-6-and-beyond/" target="_blank"&gt;How 'Fortnite' Can Avoid Getting Stale In Season 6 And Beyond&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Fortnite is approaching its sixth season this Thursday, putting out yet another teaser for it earlier today. Season 3 is about when the game started rocketing to be a truly global phenomenon, and now here in season 6, many are wondering if the game has peaked after a summer of utter madness. It probably has. I mean, that was bound to happen eventually, as no game could sustain that level of popularity indefinitely, be it League of Legends or Pokémon GO. But just because Fortnite has peaked doesn’t mean it’s irrelevant. It’s still the biggest game in the world right now raking in lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sony Relents, Will Allow Cross-Play With PS4, Xbox One and Switch For 'Fortnite,' Other Games - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/26/sony-relents-will-allow-cross-play-with-ps4-xbox-one-and-switch-for-fortnite-other-games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcMjaCPLPeyncMk1ntHziYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 13:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/26/sony-relents-will-allow-cross-play-with-ps4-xbox-one-and-switch-for-fortnite-other-games/" target="_blank"&gt;Sony Relents, Will Allow Cross-Play With PS4, Xbox One and Switch For 'Fortnite,' Other Games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Fortnite: Battle Royale’ And the walls come tumbling down. Or chipping away slowly, but still. Just three months after the issue came to a head at e3, Sony is relenting on its restrictionist policies and beginning an “extended cross-play beta” for Fortnite, beginning today. That means that PS4 players will be able to play Fortnite with those on Xbox One and Nintendo Switch in addition to the mobile and PC users they could already play with, and a blog post from Sony indicates that they’ll be able to share progression between platforms going forward, as well. It’s a big step from the bigges...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Season 6: Teaser hints at cube fate and gives sneak peak ahead of imminent release date - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/fortnite-season-6-release-date-when-teaser-trailer-leaks-cube-skins-loot-lake-map-a8552776.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI4g0ZB5PCYugClPyABKfNEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 15:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/fortnite-season-6-release-date-when-teaser-trailer-leaks-cube-skins-loot-lake-map-a8552776.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Season 6: Teaser hints at cube fate and gives sneak peak ahead of imminent release date&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Season 6 is almost here, with Epic Games formally announcing that the latest version of the battle royale phenomenon will launch on 27 September. A teaser image showing a robotic lama was published by the official social media channels of Fortnite's developer on Monday, though it is not clear what this signifies. A short message accompanied the image: "All great parties need a DJ. 3 days to Season 6." A teaser image for Fortnite Season 6 depicts a purple robot lama (Epic Games) Players of the game can expect new skins, challenges and updates to the map, which has already begun to c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>If you think Fortnite is just a video game, you’re missing the big picture - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90227475/if-you-think-fortnite-is-just-a-video-game-youre-missing-the-big-picture</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIttQFscOpyQYav-aWGEzPEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 07:00:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90227475/if-you-think-fortnite-is-just-a-video-game-youre-missing-the-big-picture" target="_blank"&gt;If you think Fortnite is just a video game, you’re missing the big picture&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With mere seconds to go before 1:30 p.m. ET, on a mountaintop overlooking Snobby Shores, Muselk scrambled up a makeshift ramp, lowered his sniper rifle, and peered down at the launchpad below. Like everyone else, he was here to see the rocket. An alarm sounded. Boosters rumbled. Fiery orange jets began pushing the missile skyward. “Oh. My. God. Yaaaaaaaaow! It’s going, boys, it’s going!” Muselk shouted to his friend LachyDachy. He peered through his rifle’s scope to get a better look as the rocket disappeared into the night sky. For a moment: silence. But then the rocket returned, first as ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Leak Reveals Psycho Clown Skins, Valkyrie With Ice Dragon Glider - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/09/18/fortnite-leak-reveals-psycho-clown-skins-valkyrie-with-ice-dragon-glider/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOABgAh2TqGtG1XAeR78rrcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 11:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/09/18/fortnite-leak-reveals-psycho-clown-skins-valkyrie-with-ice-dragon-glider/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Leak Reveals Psycho Clown Skins, Valkyrie With Ice Dragon Glider&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite We are sort of in a weird limbo in Fortnite, pretty much in week 11 of a 10 week season, as season 5 is about to end but season 6 doesn’t start until next week. As such, there are minor patches, minor CUBE movements and minor leaks that have come with today’s patch. Today’s leak is a handful of skins that seem like they’re going to be closing out season 5 sometime in the next week. Usually we see at least twice this many, but it seems season 6 skins are being kept full under wraps, so these last season 5 morsels are all we get. So, what do we have here? Nite Nite (Epic) Fortnite Ah...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Port-A-Fortress And Spiky Stadium Added To 'Fortnite: Battle Royale' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/18/port-a-fortress-and-spiky-stadium-added-to-fortnite-battle-royale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOFEnWk1yDKlr27yvrYyM_MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/18/port-a-fortress-and-spiky-stadium-added-to-fortnite-battle-royale/" target="_blank"&gt;Port-A-Fortress And Spiky Stadium Added To 'Fortnite: Battle Royale'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Port-a-Fortress is truly massive. Epic Games just released Patch v5.41 for Fortnite: Battle Royale Tuesday morning and while there’s not a ton of new content in the game this morning, there are some cool new items and a brand new limited-time mode. Probably the most exciting new item in the free-to-play game is the Port-a-Fortress. It’s essentially a massive Port-a-Fort that should make 50 vs 50 mode a little bit crazier. Here’s the new Port-a-Fortress trailer: Here’s how the Legendary Port-a-Fortress works: Port-a-Fortress - It’s huge! - Builds instantly. - Includes built-in Bouncers f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>When Do The 'High Stakes' Events And Challenges End In 'Fortnite: Battle Royale?' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/17/when-do-the-high-stakes-events-and-challenges-end-in-fortnite-battle-royale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjeShvunpN99A9Okw7hPWAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 13:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/17/when-do-the-high-stakes-events-and-challenges-end-in-fortnite-battle-royale/" target="_blank"&gt;When Do The 'High Stakes' Events And Challenges End In 'Fortnite: Battle Royale?'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite: Battle Royale This month, Fortnite tried something a little bit different. For the last little while we’ve been playing High Stakes, a heist-themed limited time event centered around a special limited time mode called “Getaway,” along with one slick customizable skin. It comes with special challenges that allow you to kit that skin out with some extra cosmetics to really give it that bank robber flair, but you’ve only got a little bit left to unlock them. Epic has announced that the High Stakes event will end with the next update, which will be coming this week. It could be as lat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' For Switch Suddenly Drops Popular Feature To Boost Performance - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2018/09/12/fortnite-for-switch-suddenly-drops-popular-feature-to-boost-performance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMcy9UDQvzY5KKG4qmsBREMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 08:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2018/09/12/fortnite-for-switch-suddenly-drops-popular-feature-to-boost-performance/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' For Switch Suddenly Drops Popular Feature To Boost Performance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re playing Fortnite on the Nintendo Switch, you may have noticed the sudden absence of a cool feature present in many other Switch titles. With the v5.40.2 update, developer Epic has decided to patch out the ability to capture and share 30-second video clips in an effort to improve overall game performance. While the Switch version of Fortnite is mostly feature-complete, it does lack the ability to view replays, making the removal of the ability to record 30-second highlights disappointing for many. It hasn’t been determined what kind of performance impact it had other than crashes, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Battle Royale: Kirstie Allsopp's iPad smashing puts child gaming addiction under the microscope - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/fortnite-battle-royale-ipad-smash-kirstie-allsopp-gaming-addiction-a8532626.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDbfQFqEhqNcnnbjh8gf4WcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 18:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/fortnite-battle-royale-ipad-smash-kirstie-allsopp-gaming-addiction-a8532626.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Battle Royale: Kirstie Allsopp's iPad smashing puts child gaming addiction under the microscope&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three months after a 9-year-old girl was reportedly sent to therapy for Fortnite addiction that caused her to wet herself, a parent has taken the drastic step of smashing her children’s iPads to prevent them from playing the popular game. TV presenter Kirstie Allsopp has been widely criticised for her parenting methods, however her frustration once again draws attention to the issue of video game addiction among children. Since launching last year, Fortnite has amassed more than 125 million players around the world, together with a fair amount of controversy. Its developer, Epic Games, has ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Battle Royale: Drum Gun banned for being too powerful - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-battle-royale-drum-gun-best-weapons-season-6-release-date-a8533326.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEETiJ6GiDi33KT9Kuk9bK_8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 08:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-battle-royale-drum-gun-best-weapons-season-6-release-date-a8533326.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Battle Royale: Drum Gun banned for being too powerful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just two months after it was released on Fortnite: Battle Royale, Epic Games has retired the ultra-effective Drum Gun. The weapon had proved controversial among some players of the popular game, who argued that its 50-round capacity meant that whoever had the gun had an unfair advantage. The Drum Gun joins a list of other "vaulted" weapons, which includes the temporary removal of guided missiles. Epic Games eventually brought back the guided missiles after modifying them. The gun's removal comes just over a week before the anticipated release date for Season 6, which has been tipped for Thu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Season 6: Leaks explain purple cube mystery and likely release date revealed - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-season-6-leaks-release-date-purple-box-challenges-map-skins-cube-a8537766.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJH5l5Cr9QlU449XKjZYUvMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-season-6-leaks-release-date-purple-box-challenges-map-skins-cube-a8537766.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Season 6: Leaks explain purple cube mystery and likely release date revealed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Season 6 of Fortnite: Battle Royale is nearly upon us, with the final Week 10 challenges for Season 5 released this week. So what surprises lay in store for players of the wildly popular game? Various leaks have sprung up online, revealing possible new skins, new map features, and new challenges. When is Season 6 launching? No official announcement has been made about the release date of Season 6, with Fortnite developers Epic Games preferring to keep people guessing. Based on past launches of new seasons, the next one can be expected one week after the launch of the Week 10 challenges. The...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Battle Royale Fall Skirmish offers $10m in prize money in game's biggest ever tournament - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-battle-royale-fall-skirmish-play-rules-format-teams-prize-money-twitchcon-a8538086.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECkuvCKmZATYbWI_JGU_3_wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-battle-royale-fall-skirmish-play-rules-format-teams-prize-money-twitchcon-a8538086.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Battle Royale Fall Skirmish offers $10m in prize money in game's biggest ever tournament&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Epic Games, the developer of Fortnite: Battle Royale, has announced the launch of its Fall Skirmish competition, which will give players of the popular game the chance to win a share of $10 million. The six-week series will begin next weekend (22 September) and conclude at the Twitchcon gaming conference in California on 26 October. "The new approach for Fall Skirmish will include both Competitive and Entertainment play formats. We’re looking to incorporate some of these new formats into our large-scale events in 2019," Epic Games said in a blog post. "During Fall Skirmish, players will pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout beta will experiment with new game modes, player count may increase - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/call-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-beta-will-experiment-new-game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB5_pqX-UHpXXg60FGefybQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 08:41:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/call-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-beta-will-experiment-new-game/" target="_blank"&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout beta will experiment with new game modes, player count may increase&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Players of the Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout beta will this week see developer Treyarch experimenting with new game-types for its Fortnite-challenging Battle Royale mode. The Blackout beta started on Monday, with players impressed at how developer Treyarch have translated Call of Duty’s slick first-person-shooting into a Battle Royale setting. The test-run started with just the base game-mode, where 80 players dive into a large map tasked with finding equipment and weapons to eliminate other combatants. The last player (or squad) left standing is the winner. However, Treyarch are looki...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item></channel></rss>