<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Fallout 76 - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZtTmpjNWJHSmtiaElDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:21:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Bethesda Responds To The 'Fallout 76' Support Glitch That Exposed Customer Data - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/bethesda-responds-to-the-fallout-76-support-glitch-that-exposed-customer-data/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_lZzx3tbgSpyrhNYJ_2BoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/bethesda-responds-to-the-fallout-76-support-glitch-that-exposed-customer-data/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda Responds To The 'Fallout 76' Support Glitch That Exposed Customer Data&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bethesda explains what happened in the support ticket fiasco. I’ve already written at length about the crazy glitch that allowed Fallout 76 players to accidentally gain access to other players’ personal information and support tickets. It was quite an astonishing technical error, even for Bethesda. Now the publisher has responded with a lengthy email sent out to the press yesterday afternoon. Here’s the full statement: As previously reported, onDecember 5, 2018, we experienced an error with our Customer Support website that resulted in the exposure of a limited number of customer support ti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'The Outer Worlds' Is The 'Fallout' Game We've All Been Waiting For - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/the-outer-worlds-is-the-fallout-game-weve-all-been-waiting-for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGjPrtVHWOtdZJjl-xuPCsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/the-outer-worlds-is-the-fallout-game-weve-all-been-waiting-for/" target="_blank"&gt;'The Outer Worlds' Is The 'Fallout' Game We've All Been Waiting For&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Outer Worlds looks great. I imagine the developers at Obsidian have been watching the Fallout 76 with grim wonder and more than a little schadenfreude. After all, this is a studio who missed out on a bonus from publisher Bethesda because their game, Fallout: New Vegas, didn’t top 85 on Metacritic. Fallout 76 hasn’t even come close to that number. While New Vegas had its problems—Obsidian, like Bethesda, isn’t known for bug-free projects—it was an instant classic and a much-beloved entry into the franchise. Fallout 76 is a disaster. So it must have been rather serendipitous for Obsidian ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>A 'Fallout 76' Support Ticket Glitch Gave Players Access To Everyone's Personal Information - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/05/a-fallout-76-support-glitch-leaked-players-personal-information-for-all-the-world-to-see/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQTdTWvDuUMEgrxC4uQ1doqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/05/a-fallout-76-support-glitch-leaked-players-personal-information-for-all-the-world-to-see/" target="_blank"&gt;A 'Fallout 76' Support Ticket Glitch Gave Players Access To Everyone's Personal Information&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the most shocking twist yet, Fallout 76 players’ private information was just revealed to the whole world. In what may very well be the most bizarre and unsettling twist in the ongoing saga that is Fallout 76, players reported Wednesday that they inadvertently gained access to the support tickets of fellow Fallout 76 players. Not only did other gamers gain access to these tickets, they were able to see personal information such as addresses, phone numbers and credit card information. It gets weirder, of course—I’m not sure it could get any worse—because not only could players see this in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 5 Biggest Problems With 'Fallout 76' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/05/the-5-biggest-problems-with-fallout-76/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgaube4gkhPC4VU4mY_GPIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/05/the-5-biggest-problems-with-fallout-76/" target="_blank"&gt;The 5 Biggest Problems With 'Fallout 76'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 is riddled with problems. Here are five of them. Well, I hate to tell you “I told you so.” But I told you so. When I wrote an article about Fallout 76 and how dubious I was that it would be a good game ready for a release in 2018, I received tons of backlash from angry fans. Now the game is rocking a 49/100 Metacritic score (on Xbox One, it’s slightly higher on PC and PS4) with a 2.7 user score. That’s just about the worst-reviewed AAA game of the year, and one of the worst-reviewed AAA games in recent memory, and certainly of this console generation. Ouch. Forbes Games writer Pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda Is Sending 'Fallout 76' Power Armor Edition Customers Canvas Bags, After All - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/04/bethesda-is-sending-fallout-76-power-armor-edition-customers-canvas-bags-after-all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-W8AGxQHvSVdfxTRLNozoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/04/bethesda-is-sending-fallout-76-power-armor-edition-customers-canvas-bags-after-all/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda Is Sending 'Fallout 76' Power Armor Edition Customers Canvas Bags, After All&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Power Armor Edition customers will get the bag at last. Bag-gate may soon draw to a close, as Fallout 76 publisher Bethesda is finally doing right by its customers. Following the launch of the game, super-fans who spent $200 on the special Power Armor Edition of the game discovered that instead of the nice canvas bag that was advertised when they pre-ordered, Bethesda had sent out cheap nylon bags instead. This revelation was made worse when Bethesda’s customer service responded in a less-than-helpful manner, sparking more outrage and frustration among players and some severe articles in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>It's Hard To Imagine How 'Fallout 76' Ever Goes Free-To-Play - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/04/its-hard-to-imagine-how-fallout-76-ever-goes-free-to-play/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBqDydoO9xJnVNvRsuwiQdUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/04/its-hard-to-imagine-how-fallout-76-ever-goes-free-to-play/" target="_blank"&gt;It's Hard To Imagine How 'Fallout 76' Ever Goes Free-To-Play&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Fans watched the price of Fallout 76 dip all the way down to around $35 just a week or two after launch around Black Friday sale time, and that combined with its myriad issues caused an old refrain to start up again. “Well, it’s only a matter of time until it goes free-to-play.” It’s the go-to for any struggling game when they realize it’s the best way to bulk up their playerbase, as they’ll hope to make money in other ways. But you do not usually hear this when talking about an enormous, just-released triple A product like Fallout 76, which should tell you what dire straits it’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda Gave 'Influencers' Nice 'Fallout 76' Canvas Bags Instead Of Fans Who Spent $200 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/03/bethesda-gave-influencers-nice-fallout-76-canvas-bags-just-not-customers-who-paid-200/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIEeO5uyyDof8dbkj316-IQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/03/bethesda-gave-influencers-nice-fallout-76-canvas-bags-just-not-customers-who-paid-200/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda Gave 'Influencers' Nice 'Fallout 76' Canvas Bags Instead Of Fans Who Spent $200&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76′s ‘bag-gate’ controversy deepens. In many ways, at least for those of us who comment on the video game industry’s many foibles, Fallout 76 is the gift that keeps on giving. Not so much, however, if you spent $200 on the game’s Power Armor Edition, thought you’d get a nice canvas bag, and were sent a cheap nylon bag instead. This on top of the game being a hot pile of steaming garbage, riddled with performance issues, bland combat and recycled assets. Of course, the story only gets better—or worse, depending on where you’re sitting. If you’re me, writing about just how low and scu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Red Dead Online,' 'Fallout 76' And The Convoluted Nature Of 'Betas' In 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/02/red-dead-online-fallout-76-and-the-convoluted-nature-of-betas-in-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN58Yuu5xULY5POS9HkD3dcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 15:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/02/red-dead-online-fallout-76-and-the-convoluted-nature-of-betas-in-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'Red Dead Online,' 'Fallout 76' And The Convoluted Nature Of 'Betas' In 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red Dead Online Yesterday, I wrote an article criticizing the current state of the economy in Red Dead Online, as it feels so unrewarding and geared toward potential microtransactions, that it seems like it runs the risk of turning off the millions of players that turned GTA Online into a billion dollar cash cow from the outset. While I know a number of players agree with me, there was a large contingent that showed up after reading to say some variant of “dude, it’s a beta!” I hear this a lot now when I criticize any game’s beta, be it this one, or Fallout 76, or really anything. First off...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda Offers Players $5 In Microtransactions For Issue With $200 'Fallout 76' Power Armor Edition - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/29/bethesda-offers-players-5-in-microtransactions-for-issue-with-200-fallout-76-power-armor-edition/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAh4K22PNLPCNAQqnEZ45l8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 12:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/29/bethesda-offers-players-5-in-microtransactions-for-issue-with-200-fallout-76-power-armor-edition/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda Offers Players $5 In Microtransactions For Issue With $200 'Fallout 76' Power Armor Edition&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After somehow managing to shoehorn Fallout 76 into my review of Red Dead Online yesterday, I swore I was going to take a break for a while. But Bethesda is just the gift that keeps on giving, this time thanks to their handling of a rather ridiculous issue with the $200 Fallout 76 Power Armor Edition. And now players are not especially happy with the $5 in microtransaction currency they’re being given for their troubles. While I’m sure plenty of people have buyer’s remorse for that just because of the state of the game itself, a further issue has been discovered as players have been shipped ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76 review | A lonely post-apocalyptic world of little consequence - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/fallout-76-review-lonely-post-apocalyptic-world-little-consequence/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM1U089I7ZhT7y5k42QZnakqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 09:19:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/fallout-76-review-lonely-post-apocalyptic-world-little-consequence/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76 review | A lonely post-apocalyptic world of little consequence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the dawn of Reclamation Day I left Vault 76, weary eyed and slightly optimistic about the journey that laid ahead of me in West Virginia. Despite all the doom and gloom that had been directed towards Fallout 76, this divergent multiplayer instalment of Bethesda's post-apocalyptic series, moving from single-player immersion to an online playground. As a Fallout fan I had faith that Bethesda’s ambitious idea could pay-off. But the more hours I gave, the more that faith was drained and the worse the experience became. I did a piece about what Bethesda should change to the game after the bet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Bethesda's Silence Of The State Of 'Fallout 76' At Launch Is Deafening - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/27/bethesdas-silence-of-the-state-of-fallout-76-at-launch-is-deafening/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEnR7z_v_SR0d1dXnRLjvzIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 14:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/27/bethesdas-silence-of-the-state-of-fallout-76-at-launch-is-deafening/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda's Silence Of The State Of 'Fallout 76' At Launch Is Deafening&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Fallout 76 is a unique disaster in the gaming industry. A huge game based on a huge IP that took years to craft, and yet its arrival has been marked by some of the lowest critic and user scores in modern gaming history. While Bethesda has often been given free passes for buggy titles, Fallout 76 has taken things to a new level on that front, and its technical issues are compounded by the core design problems of a multiplayer, survivalist Fallout experience few people asked for, or if they did, this is definitely not what they had in mind. And yet we have heard practically nothing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Red Dead Online' Has Two Significant Problems To Overcome - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/30/red-dead-online-has-two-significant-problems-to-overcome/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAb94k1_PoC6qUnbYzUrYUIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/30/red-dead-online-has-two-significant-problems-to-overcome/" target="_blank"&gt;'Red Dead Online' Has Two Significant Problems To Overcome&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red Dead Online Today the Red Dead Online beta launches for everyone, and while I’ve put in a solid chunk of time into it so far, I think my time with it is drawing to a close, particularly since we have no idea at all if beta progress will carry over to the full release, and all that’s ahead of me now is a grind that may not end up saving my rank or currency. As I’ve played Red Dead Online, I think it can be a lot of fun, but also two glaring problems seem to keep presenting themselves to me at every turn. No, this isn’t a Fallout 76 glitch fest, and while the economy doesn’t seem great, t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here Are Some Short-Term (Non-Bug) Fixes 'Fallout 76' Needs ASAP - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/24/here-are-some-short-term-non-bug-fixes-fallout-76-needs-asap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIwot1TduNlzdOumlIw7Fc8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 13:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/24/here-are-some-short-term-non-bug-fixes-fallout-76-needs-asap/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are Some Short-Term (Non-Bug) Fixes 'Fallout 76' Needs ASAP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Much ink has been spilled about what ails Fallout 76, whether it be its litany of bugs or problems with its core concept, but for this piece, I wanted to focus on things that were hopefully more realistic than total revamps of the entire concept of the game, and less obvious than things that need to be addressed like “get the server to stop kicking people” or “patch bugs that are causing players to become immortal god kings longing for death.” Rather, I wanted to focus on what I think would be a number of short-term fixes for Fallout 76 that could hopefully be rolled out soon-ish...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Is Already $20 Off For Black Friday, But It Still Might Be Overpriced - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/23/fallout-76-is-already-20-off-for-black-friday-but-it-still-might-be-overpriced/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsAsZivq-zR5Uz-A2UvF_MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 14:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/23/fallout-76-is-already-20-off-for-black-friday-but-it-still-might-be-overpriced/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Is Already $20 Off For Black Friday, But It Still Might Be Overpriced&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 It’s rare to see big discounts on recently-released AAA games for Black Friday, at least those that came out in the past month or so. Red Dead Redemption 2 is still basically sitting at the MSRP of $60 at most retailers, despite some little collectible pack-ins to make it look a little more like a deal. Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 is seeing a couple of discounts, but the game was released just long enough to go for that to make a little more sense. And then we’ve got Fallout 76, a game that was released just one week ago and yet is already seeing some pretty steep discounts across ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>After A Historically Bad Launch, Is 'Fallout 76' Worth Saving? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/23/after-a-historically-bad-launch-is-fallout-76-worth-saving/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPnbkn257L0IlVVcQihm4SYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 14:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/23/after-a-historically-bad-launch-is-fallout-76-worth-saving/" target="_blank"&gt;After A Historically Bad Launch, Is 'Fallout 76' Worth Saving?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 While I did not particularly enjoy my time with Fallout 76, I was not expecting the critical and public reaction to it to be quite this harsh. Fallout 76 may be the highest profile release with the lowest review scores I can remember seeing in at least a decade, or really since metascores became a thing. It’s Bethesda’s lowest rated game by a huge margin, it’s scoring worse than No Man’s Sky, Mass Effect Andromeda, vanilla Destiny and all those other big titles that were high profile critical disappointments at launch. It’s hovering around Duke Nukem Forever territory in terms of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Red Dead Online' Day One: Well It Sure Ain't 'Fallout 76' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/28/red-dead-online-day-one-well-it-sure-aint-fallout-76/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsc0v29mvXvyevY_Byt4ZwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/28/red-dead-online-day-one-well-it-sure-aint-fallout-76/" target="_blank"&gt;'Red Dead Online' Day One: Well It Sure Ain't 'Fallout 76'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red Dead Online The beta for Red Dead Online kicked off yesterday, allowing Ultimate Edition players into the world while gradually rolling out to everyone else in the next few days. I put a solid chunk of time into it yesterday thanks to a code from Rockstar, enough to form at least a few first impressions of what the publisher is hoping is going to be their next GTA Online cash cow. As someone who never really got into GTA Online, I was hoping that Red Dead Online might be more my speed instead. And while I’ve had fun in these initial hours, I’m still not convinced this is going to be som...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>It Sure Is Interesting To Rewatch That 'Fallout 76' Todd Howard E3 Reveal Now - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/21/it-sure-is-interesting-to-rewatch-that-fallout-76-todd-howard-e3-reveal-now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECEyVrWuOgMxqIf3Ci_DWEEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/21/it-sure-is-interesting-to-rewatch-that-fallout-76-todd-howard-e3-reveal-now/" target="_blank"&gt;It Sure Is Interesting To Rewatch That 'Fallout 76' Todd Howard E3 Reveal Now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo by Christian Petersen/Getty Images Fallout 76 has arrived not just as a middling title in a storied franchise, but as possibly the worst-reviewed major release of the year. Of the last few years, in fact, with a current Metascore current hovering around Duke Nukem Forever low-50s levels, a smidge of irony for Bethesda, who once famously denied Obsidian bonuses because Fallout: New Vegas was one point below an 85. I posted my own review yesterday, which did little to bring its average up, and I thought it might be appropriate to go back to where this all starter, to 2018’s E3 reveal of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76 review – a pointless walk in the post-apocalypse - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/19/fallout-76-review-playstation-xbox-pc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIy3KURyac766-mZ_o2sO8UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 13:45:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/19/fallout-76-review-playstation-xbox-pc" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76 review – a pointless walk in the post-apocalypse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Fallout 76’s opening moments, you are urged to leave your underground vault and remake America after a nuclear apocalypse, adventuring through Appalachia collecting scrap to build with and weapons and armour to help survive the irradiated environment and the monsters, super mutants and robots that now call it home. You’re not alone in this endeavour: online, you can team up with, or attack, your fellow former vault-dwellers – or you can ignore them completely, treating the game as a solo experience (that nonetheless requires a constant internet connection). Rebuilding the world with stra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76': 5 Things That Could Have Saved It From Total Disaster - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/23/fallout-76-5-things-that-could-have-saved-it-from-total-disaster/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHKllbnsz0ncebFc0rTudxQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/23/fallout-76-5-things-that-could-have-saved-it-from-total-disaster/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76': 5 Things That Could Have Saved It From Total Disaster&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The release of Fallout 76 hasn’t been a success. PARIS, FRANCE – OCTOBER 27: Visitors queue to play the video game ‘Fallout 76′ developed and published by Bethesda Softworks during the ‘Paris Games Week’ on October 27, 2018 in Paris, France. ‘Paris Games Week’ is an international trade fair for video games and runs from October 26 to 31, 2018. (Photo by Chesnot/Getty Images) The reviews have been brutal and the game currently has Metacritic scores of 49, 50 and 55 on Xbox One, PS4, and PC, respectively. Despite a recent patch that measured 47 GB in size, it doesn’t appear as though most of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ten Things I Wish I Knew When I Started 'Fallout 76' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/16/ten-things-i-wish-i-knew-when-i-started-fallout-76/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBigLuq_u05LKZE2hCsSfikqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 13:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/16/ten-things-i-wish-i-knew-when-i-started-fallout-76/" target="_blank"&gt;Ten Things I Wish I Knew When I Started 'Fallout 76'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Fallout 76 has arrived as one of the final few big games of the holiday season, and it’s drawn some measure of controversy for both its buggy release and online multiplayer concept. It does have its fans, however, and I am occasionally among them when I’m not being frustrated in some way or another. In order to try and make all of you who are just starting out less frustrated, I thought it was time to write one of my advice posts. I did not put a ton of hours into the betas, where progress was carried over to release, but I did a decent amount then and have been playing more or l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Don't Trust 'Fallout 76' Reviews Today - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/14/dont-trust-fallout-76-reviews-today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENSsrJegqQ7nqccphloVtroqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/14/dont-trust-fallout-76-reviews-today/" target="_blank"&gt;Don't Trust 'Fallout 76' Reviews Today&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 It’s that time again: there’s a new multiplayer-focused AAA game out in the world, and it’s a controversial one. Fallout 76 officially went live today, giving us all an opportunity to re-interpret the idea of a Fallout experience in an online setting. And because this game works the way it does, there were no early copies or no real chance to experience the finished product for review. So if you see reviews floating around the internet today, or even tomorrow and Friday, don’t trust them. At this point, reviewers have only had their hands on the game for less than a day, maybe a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Review (Xbox One X): Look Upon My Works And Despair - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2018/11/20/fallout-76-review-xbox-one-x-look-upon-my-works-and-despair/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM9pxtsq2vJmeacljSDjtEkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 13:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2018/11/20/fallout-76-review-xbox-one-x-look-upon-my-works-and-despair/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Review (Xbox One X): Look Upon My Works And Despair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 When is the right time to review a deeply flawed, clearly unfinished game? Is it when more bugs are patched? When the servers stabilize? When the player population becomes more engaged? When the content is bolstered by enough new stuff to pump life into the world? Perhaps, so maybe a week and 35-40 hours with Fallout 76 isn’t giving it enough of a fair shake, and yet I think the line has to be drawn somewhere when it comes to the state of new games at launch. I’m drawing it here. Fallout 76 feels like a shell of a game. It looks, sounds and acts like a Fallout title, but undernea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>I'll Say It Again: 'Fallout 76' Needs An Offline Mode - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/18/ill-say-it-again-fallout-76-needs-an-offline-mode/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMgDhvAWa4Fyv0WhbmsXCxcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 14:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/18/ill-say-it-again-fallout-76-needs-an-offline-mode/" target="_blank"&gt;I'll Say It Again: 'Fallout 76' Needs An Offline Mode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 I don’t particularly enjoy essentially rewriting an article I’ve already written, as I said this exact thing before Fallout 76 was released. And yet spending a full 24 hours with the game (as an in-game challenge completion pop-up helpfully told me), I have evolving thoughts on this. Namely, I still very much believe that Fallout 76 needs an offline mode. I thought one of two things could happen when I got to play the full release of Fallout 76: 1) I would see the light and understand that yes, this game really is better on live servers with other people. or 2) The game is so bad...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Vs. 'Red Dead Redemption 2': How To Make 'Survival' Not Irritating - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/17/fallout-76-vs-red-dead-redemption-2-how-to-make-survival-not-irritating/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBDlpgQM-fgunUVuqQ2_az4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 14:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/17/fallout-76-vs-red-dead-redemption-2-how-to-make-survival-not-irritating/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Vs. 'Red Dead Redemption 2': How To Make 'Survival' Not Irritating&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 I feel like my time with Fallout 76 is probably drawing to a close. I am not even close to max level, but after 20-30 hours or so, the game has revealed itself to be an endless series of not particularly interesting fetch quests, and even if exploration has been fun, it’s running its course. Not to mention the game seems determined to make me hate it at all times. Fallout has always been a “survival-lite” game to some extent, flirting with character maintenance mechanics that make it seem like you’re trying to survive in a nuclear wasteland. This manifests itself mainly in the fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>‘Fallout 76’ Brings Players Together for a Crushingly Lonely Experience - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fallout-76-brings-players-together-for-a-crushingly-lonely-experience</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIf7hBDDvsSzBtri1CdDAB8qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMKv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 09:55:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/fallout-76-brings-players-together-for-a-crushingly-lonely-experience" target="_blank"&gt;‘Fallout 76’ Brings Players Together for a Crushingly Lonely Experience&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bethesda “Nobody helps anybody anymore.” So says an audio recording pulled off a dead body sitting on the porch of a small shack that has seen better days. The body had been “Sophie,” and in her final days, she wasn’t too happy about her situation. She had survived the bomb dropping, the one that irradiated the Appalachian world in which Fallout 76 exists. But in the apocalypse, things went from bad to worse and she, I assume, sat on the porch and waited to die of blight or radiation poisoning or something equally horrific. These audio recordings have been around in games for a long time—no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76': The 5 Harshest Critical Quotes From Respected Reviewers - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/22/fallout-76-the-5-harshest-critical-quotes-from-respected-reviewers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAJmHWY8Q45G1IKTrUDmxysqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/22/fallout-76-the-5-harshest-critical-quotes-from-respected-reviewers/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76': The 5 Harshest Critical Quotes From Respected Reviewers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Game development is difficult. Studios are celebrated when they come up with innovative concepts that step outside the box when the results are fun and engaging experiences. Unfortunately, new-fangled ideas don’t always pan out, and that seems to be the problem with Bethesda’s Fallout 76. Fallout 76 Most of the major publications have weighed in on the latest edition from the successful series and let’s just say the review scores haven’t been favorable. Fallout 76 [PS4 - 50] https://t.co/p31OUPH9zx [PC - 55] https://t.co/cc16KEpLfP [XONE - 53] https://t.co/c7cdWeGIf1 IGN: “The rich wastelan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Hitman 2' Is A Great Game That No One Is Talking About - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/24/hitman-2-is-a-great-game-that-no-one-is-talking-about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPWTU3mfqyrSisu0uL9bmKwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/24/hitman-2-is-a-great-game-that-no-one-is-talking-about/" target="_blank"&gt;'Hitman 2' Is A Great Game That No One Is Talking About&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gaming world is submerged in discussions about the excellence of Red Dead Redemption 2 and Call of Duty Black Ops 4. It is still coming to grips with the good, bad and incomplete of Battlefield V, and the mess that is Fallout 76. Hitman 47 Meanwhile, IO Interactive’s Hitman 2 is quietly one of the better games of the year. If you take a look at the most predominant gaming publications, on YouTube and other sources of information in the industry, and almost no one is talking about Hitman 2. Unfortunately, it’s release date was sandwiched between the aforementioned behemoths, but if you’r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sam's Club Black Friday 2018 Ad Has Nasty Expensive Surprises - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/22/sams-club-black-friday-2018-ad-microsoft-xbox-one-x-sony-playstation-4-slim-ps4-nintendo-switch-sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFz6SL3pdNJPO8ejl8VIyq4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 03:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/22/sams-club-black-friday-2018-ad-microsoft-xbox-one-x-sony-playstation-4-slim-ps4-nintendo-switch-sales/" target="_blank"&gt;Sam's Club Black Friday 2018 Ad Has Nasty Expensive Surprises&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. While I have already ranked the Best Black Friday deals, the big Sam’s Club Black Friday sale (ad scan) has flown under the radar. Is this because the competition is so strong? Sadly, yes. If you’re hoping to land a bargain on many of the most popular products, you’re in for a nasty surprise… This is the ninth article in my Black Friday ‘...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Is Indeed Channeling 'No Man's Sky,' For Better And Worse - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/15/fallout-76-is-indeed-channeling-no-mans-sky-for-better-and-worse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIJkS8dGLgldIMnbojKVnKwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/15/fallout-76-is-indeed-channeling-no-mans-sky-for-better-and-worse/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Is Indeed Channeling 'No Man's Sky,' For Better And Worse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 As he usually is, my colleague Erik Kain was right. A few weeks ago, he predicted that Fallout 76 would end up being the No Man’s Sky of 2018. This notion was mostly based around the idea that this was a high profile, but ultimate unfinished game releasing in what was more or less an early access state. But the reality? The games are actually more alike than I imagined they would be in terms of how they actually feel and play, which is something I was not expecting. This can be either a good or bad thing, depending on how you look at it, and I think there are positive and negativ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Is A Success In Spite Of All Its Pointless Online Nonsense - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/14/fallout-76-is-a-success-in-spite-of-all-its-pointless-online-nonsense/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHJcDdHv5YvrDOYvVDFiMcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 15:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/14/fallout-76-is-a-success-in-spite-of-all-its-pointless-online-nonsense/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Is A Success In Spite Of All Its Pointless Online Nonsense&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Today is officially launch day for Fallout 76, but in an endless parade of Bethesda’s ongoing bugs with the game, it launched in some regions and some platforms early yesterday. This also comes after a number of limited time betas, so many players, myself included, have gotten our hands on the game for a good while now. God help me, overall, I like it. While I have been almost relentlessly negative about many aspects of Fallout 76 since its inception, playing the game so far has been a…mostly enjoyable experience. But with one big caveat. The reason I’m enjoying Fallout 76 is bec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Xbox Makes A Quiet Change That Could Be A Huge Leap Forward For Backward Compatibility - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/20/xbox-makes-a-quiet-change-that-could-be-a-huge-leap-forward-for-backward-compatibility/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFN77-QvMK6IdaFrD_h0Q9cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/20/xbox-makes-a-quiet-change-that-could-be-a-huge-leap-forward-for-backward-compatibility/" target="_blank"&gt;Xbox Makes A Quiet Change That Could Be A Huge Leap Forward For Backward Compatibility&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Final Fantasy XIII’ Xbox just changed the backward compatibility game and the consequences could be huge. For the first time, a backward compatibility title enhanced for the XBox One X, Final Fantasy XIII, has assets that were not in the original Xbox 360 release. The One X enhanced version of FF13 looks more like a remaster than a straightforward resolution boost. If it can be done for Final Fantasy XIII, it may be possible for other titles as well. A 3 x 3 grid of 720p renders of Halo 5. Xbox uses a simple resolution-boosting technique to enhance backward compatibility titles for the One...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>I Feel Like I Already Know Everything That's Going To Happen With The 'Fallout 76' Launch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/12/i-feel-like-i-already-know-everything-thats-going-to-happen-with-the-fallout-76-launch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBDi36lLpeiSYdih9dr4gQUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/12/i-feel-like-i-already-know-everything-thats-going-to-happen-with-the-fallout-76-launch/" target="_blank"&gt;I Feel Like I Already Know Everything That's Going To Happen With The 'Fallout 76' Launch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76765 I don’t like judging a game before its technically released, but sometimes, it’s hard not to. Fallout 76 is out tomorrow, and it’s going to be buggy. I feel I can say this with 99% confidence. For one thing, Bethesda games are always buggy. For another, the beta had some bugs in it, and it wasn’t all that long ago. For another, Bethesda basically told us that things were going to be a little rough in the early stages. If you’re playing this game at launch, that’s the first thing you should have on your mind. The thing about this release, however, is that I have this strange se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76: Server Launch Times, Day-One Patch And What You Need To Know - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/12/fallout-76-server-launch-times-day-one-patch-and-what-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwl5Y3Ck-2U0P8snWfr5YsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/12/fallout-76-server-launch-times-day-one-patch-and-what-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76: Server Launch Times, Day-One Patch And What You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 We’ve all been screwing around in the beta for a few days, but it’s time to finally dive into West Virginia with both feet. Bethesda’s ambitious, odd and controversial Fallout 76 launches tomorrow, marking arguably the most interesting AAA release of the fall season. It’s a Fallout game, make no mistake about that. It’s just a very strange Fallout game, one that both fits the mold of previous titles and totally turns the idea on its head. First things first, however: this is an online game, and so we’re not playing until servers go live and the developer lets us loose into the wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Release Date And 10 Things You Should Know Before You Buy The Game - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/12/fallout-76-release-date-and-10-things-you-should-know-before-you-buy-the-game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0-Kzxwor7kUecvnOnPbZ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 15:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/12/fallout-76-release-date-and-10-things-you-should-know-before-you-buy-the-game/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Release Date And 10 Things You Should Know Before You Buy The Game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next piece of Bethesda’s post-apocalyptic Fallout franchise will be available on November 14 for PC, Xbox One and PlayStation 4. It’s called Fallout 76, and by all accounts, it is a noticeably different experience than the previous versions of the series. Fallout 76 With a larger map, a new twist on the core plot and a different approach to gameplay, Fallout 76 figures to be one of the more memorable releases in the series’ history. Let’s take a look at the 10 things you should know about Fallout 76. It’s Thin On Pre-Order Bonuses The biggest pre-order bonus has already expired. Gamers ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76 beta: 6 things for Bethesda to address at release - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fallout-76-beta-review-6-things-bethesda-address-release-date/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRh4iXBfJCau_YqlH4-QsQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 13:36:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fallout-76-beta-review-6-things-bethesda-address-release-date/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76 beta: 6 things for Bethesda to address at release&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 will release on Wednesday 14 November, but we have already been given a good idea of how the game plays from a series of beta sessions, that have happened sporadically over the last couple of weeks. As this is the first time Bethesda has taken an post-apocalyptic world online the Fallout 76 Beta, for people who had pre-ordered and downloaded the game set in West Virginia, allowed the US-based video game publisher to stress test its servers. And see what changes it has to make to fix glitches before the game’s full release next week. With the Fallout 76 Beta over ahead of the full...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Will Fix One Of Its Most Annoying Problems After Beta Feedback - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/08/fallout-76-will-fix-one-of-its-most-annoying-problems-after-beta-feedback/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELuv0drXCL5m438q2AMlp6MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 14:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/08/fallout-76-will-fix-one-of-its-most-annoying-problems-after-beta-feedback/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Will Fix One Of Its Most Annoying Problems After Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 The Fallout 76 beta (I refused to write B.E.T.A.) is coming to a close, and Bethesda is absorbing feedback for potential changes to a game that comes out in uh, six days. Not a lot you can really do in that window, but at least one thing is being changed sometime in the “near future” that was annoying fans during the beta. One common complaint, especially on PC, was the prevalence of open world chat being on by default in the beta, meaning that you could hear the voice of anyone with a microphone on nearby. Bethesda’s explanation for this was “Our goal with voice chat being on by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Premier RPG Developers inXile And Obsidian Acquired By Xbox - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/12/premier-rpg-developers-inxile-and-obsidian-acquired-by-xbox/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZVXSuwf_6--UvweMDzlZYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 19:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/12/premier-rpg-developers-inxile-and-obsidian-acquired-by-xbox/" target="_blank"&gt;Premier RPG Developers inXile And Obsidian Acquired By Xbox&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Wasteland 3′ Last month it was rumored that Microsoft was set to acquire acclaimed RPG developer Obsidian Entertainment. The rumor was confirmed on Saturday during Xbox’s XO18 event in Mexico City. But Obsidian isn’t the only renowned RPG development studio coming to Xbox. XO18 also brought the announcement that Microsoft has acquired inXile Entertainment. Obsidian and inXile have played a central role in the resurgence of classical RPGs that has taken place over the past few years. Obsidian recently developed Pillars of Eternity and Pillars of Eternity 2: Deadfire, South Park: The Stick o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>A New Nebula Award Category Honors Writing For Science Fiction And Fantasy Games - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/13/a-new-nebula-award-category-honors-writing-for-science-fiction-and-fantasy-games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELEFd_UfTSDQaivc9RMEyX0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/13/a-new-nebula-award-category-honors-writing-for-science-fiction-and-fantasy-games/" target="_blank"&gt;A New Nebula Award Category Honors Writing For Science Fiction And Fantasy Games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nebula Awards The Board of Directors of the Science Fiction and Fantasy Writers of America (SWFA) has voted to add Game Writing as a new Nebula Award category. The Nebulas and Hugos are the most prestigious awards in the science fiction and fantasy genres and the new Nebula award category recognizes the important contributions game writers make to both fields. This is a great development for video game writers who often labor in obscurity while producing some of the most compelling narratives that can be found in popular entertainment. Here’s what the SWFA has to say about the Game Writ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Beta Feels Like A Total Mess, But I Sort Of Love It Anyways - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/03/fallout-76-beta-feels-like-a-total-mess-but-i-sort-of-love-it-anyways/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMXlsY4fzDbH7kdAc-9yyfQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/03/fallout-76-beta-feels-like-a-total-mess-but-i-sort-of-love-it-anyways/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Beta Feels Like A Total Mess, But I Sort Of Love It Anyways&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 As a rule, I try not to be too critical of betas. It’s a beta, after all, and theoretically, the developer is here to present us with an unfinished product that it hopes to improve through testing. The lines get all muddy when betas are semi-commercial products through pre-order bonuses, or when they’re deployed shortly before launch as more or less finished products and designed as demos more than anything else. But again, this is just a general rule: if its a beta, it gets a little leeway in my book. Fallout 76, however, comes out in two weeks. There’s still plenty to be fixed,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Shows Bethesda's Engine Has Gone From Meme To Liability - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/02/fallout-76-shows-bethesdas-engine-has-gone-from-meme-to-liability/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMbFBipBfuB6g-6G-8yb-pUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/02/fallout-76-shows-bethesdas-engine-has-gone-from-meme-to-liability/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Shows Bethesda's Engine Has Gone From Meme To Liability&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 The Fallout 76 beta has opened up past just Xbox One, and players are flooding into the West Virginia wasteland to see what’s up ahead of the game’s release on November 14. Reactions feel…mixed, but I don’t want to debate the concept of Fallout 76 again as I’ve done that enough for now. To reiterate, I’m not a huge fan of this weird PvPvE blend that seems to have both bad PvP and lifeless PvE with an NPC-less sprawling map where every quest is given by holotape. But what I need to address is just how badly aged this game feels in the current video game landscape, and that’s due t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>A Simple Way To Make The 'Fallout 76' Beta Less Depressing - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/02/a-simple-way-to-make-the-fallout-76-beta-less-depressing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDgIcpDfQXhxclCfBd_4vpAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 14:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/02/a-simple-way-to-make-the-fallout-76-beta-less-depressing/" target="_blank"&gt;A Simple Way To Make The 'Fallout 76' Beta Less Depressing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 I’ve played the Fallout 76 Beta for two hours now, which is an hour longer than I planned to. That’s always a good sign, though the constant crashing and other bugs was a decidedly bad sign. If there’s one feeling that overwhelms the game, however, it’s a kind of sadness. The story is told through audio logs from the people who died trying to save the world before you, and there’s one long questline that so far has me listening to a woman visiting the dead and destroyed memories of her former life. Fun! Luckily, there’s something to be done about that. Playing Red Dead Redemptio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here Are Walmarts's Black Friday 2018 Gaming Deals: Nintendo Switch, Xbox, PS4 And More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/08/here-are-walmartss-black-friday-2018-gaming-deals-nintendo-switch-xbox-ps4-and-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELs8HGwrIjxrOMe4EX2mEGEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 14:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/08/here-are-walmartss-black-friday-2018-gaming-deals-nintendo-switch-xbox-ps4-and-more/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are Walmarts's Black Friday 2018 Gaming Deals: Nintendo Switch, Xbox, PS4 And More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mario Kart 8. And here’s the big one. Walmart is the largest retailer in America, the largest retailer in the world, and reliably one of the largest loci of all things Black Friday. You can get essentially anything here that you can possibly imagine, but we’re here to talk about gaming, where Walmart is often an excellent place to get discounts along with discounts on everything else under the sun. Let’s take a look at Walmart’s gaming deals for Black Friday 2018, with discounts on Xbox One X, Nintendo Switch, PS4 Pro and more. To take a look at Walmart’s entire Black Friday ad, check out B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Hackers Have Already Found A Way To Cheat In The 'Fallout 76' Beta - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/01/hackers-have-already-found-a-way-to-cheat-in-the-fallout-76-beta/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG-w1BfTXuPUgYgTwkLTNgwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 14:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/01/hackers-have-already-found-a-way-to-cheat-in-the-fallout-76-beta/" target="_blank"&gt;Hackers Have Already Found A Way To Cheat In The 'Fallout 76' Beta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 It’s a beta test, even if it’s a beta test for a game that comes out very soon. But Bethesda warned us about all sorts of problems that might crop up in the Fallout 76 beta, and we’re not short on them so far. One particularly interesting one straight-up deleted the entire beta file for PC players, forcing them to re-download the massive file and hope for the best. This one here isn’t a bug so much as an exploit, though it might even rise to the level of “hack.” Whatever we call it, it’s clearly an early issue here. It’s called “speed hacking”, and it essentially has to do with t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76's PC Beta Suffered From The Most Hilarious Game-Eating Bug - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/31/fallout-76s-pc-beta-suffered-from-the-most-hilarious-game-eating-bug/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL9For1LT-Y9rj6HKIxBY7cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 16:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/31/fallout-76s-pc-beta-suffered-from-the-most-hilarious-game-eating-bug/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76's PC Beta Suffered From The Most Hilarious Game-Eating Bug&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76′s PC beta ran into a terrible snag. Oh Bethesda, never change. The studio behind such glitchy masterpieces as The Elder Scrolls V: Skryim,The Elder Scrolls IV: Oblivion, Fallout 3 and Fallout 4 ran another truncated beta for online-only survival game Fallout 76 last night. This time, not only were Xbox One players let into the game, but also PS4 and PC players. Well, in theory at least. Not all PC players were able to join in the fun. Some discovered that when they opened the game’s launcher and pressed a button the game was wiped from their computers. Simply pressing a button de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' PS4/PC Beta: Start And End Times, How To Get A Code And What You Need To Know - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/29/fallout-76-ps4pc-beta-start-and-end-times-how-to-get-a-code-and-what-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC3jq0HAn33zCcQnYvZWmtgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 13:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/29/fallout-76-ps4pc-beta-start-and-end-times-how-to-get-a-code-and-what-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' PS4/PC Beta: Start And End Times, How To Get A Code And What You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 It’s time to hop back into the world of Fallout 76–for Xbox One owners, this will be the second or third time they’ve had the opportunity to see just what sort of strangeness Bethesda Softworks is cooking up for its first online-focused game. PS4 and PC owners are getting their first chance, however, though at this point it’s clear that there’s something to see there in the wastes of post-apocalyptic West Virginia. Here’s when you’ll want to login, and note the brevity of each window. As with previous beta sessions, Bethesda is doing these in short, four-hour bursts in an effort ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here Are The Role Playing Games That Are Coming In November - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/30/here-are-the-role-playing-games-that-are-coming-in-november/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKLk1uLbjmHJf6YLus8kOL0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/30/here-are-the-role-playing-games-that-are-coming-in-november/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are The Role Playing Games That Are Coming In November&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Fallout 76′ The role-playing landscape in November is dominated by two mainstream, A-list games. Fallout 76 is running frequent beta sessions in preparation for the game’s mid-month launch and the Elder Scrolls Online has two in-game events and a new DLC pack on its schedule. The Switch is getting its version of a blockbuster title along with an intriguing game from an indie developer that mixes shopkeeping by day with dungeon crawling at night. JRPG fans have a pair of games to look forward to and a true classic is reimagined by many of the same people who created the original. Here are t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Amazon Has The Best Red Dead Redemption 2/Xbox One X Deal Out There - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/30/amazon-has-the-best-red-dead-redemption-2-xbox-one-x-deal-out-there/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELovm8pJn8B-LAGRn1cwPtkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 15:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/30/amazon-has-the-best-red-dead-redemption-2-xbox-one-x-deal-out-there/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Has The Best Red Dead Redemption 2/Xbox One X Deal Out There&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red Dead Redemption 2 The Xbox One X is, on a technical level, hands-down the best place to play Rockstar Games’ Red Dead Redemption 2. Which is a big deal, because Red Dead Redemption 2 is arguably the best-looking AAA game ever made (comparing with lower-res games is tough, of course). So that’s a big score right now: at this moment in time, the Xbox One X can give you the prettiest AAA experience on the market, and everyone else can just look on in envy. It’s clear, also, that Microsoft wants you to know it. There’s a broad-based deal that gives you $100 a new Xbox One X when you buy it ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here's When The 'Fallout 76' Xbox One Beta Starts Back Up - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/26/heres-when-the-fallout-76-xbox-one-beta-starts-back-up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBia5bVW73aXeD3nxBXZVZMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/26/heres-when-the-fallout-76-xbox-one-beta-starts-back-up/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's When The 'Fallout 76' Xbox One Beta Starts Back Up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s when the Fallout 76 beta starts back up on Xbox One. Gamers only got a very small time window to play Fallout 76′s Xbox One beta this week. After just a few hours, feelings were decidedly mixed. The game’s subreddit seemed largely positive, and I personally was bombarded with fans angry at me expressing skepticism toward the game without playing it first. But others were dismayed by the game’s lack of NPCs and repetitiveness. I actually wrote the offending piece prior to the beta going live (but scheduled it for the next morning) and then wrongly assumed that Bethesda would be runnin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Could Double Its Sales And Playerbase With An Offline Mode - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/25/fallout-76-could-double-its-sales-and-playerbase-with-an-offline-mode/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJGtb9K1PtY_syPtq8VXCN0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/25/fallout-76-could-double-its-sales-and-playerbase-with-an-offline-mode/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Could Double Its Sales And Playerbase With An Offline Mode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 As we sit and wait for the next Fallout 76 beta to begin (this Saturday for two hours, in another ultra-brief stress test), I’ve been thinking about the issues I have with the game, and how they could be solved. Polygon recently ran a piece about how they wished the game had private servers, because while it’s fun to play with friends, playing with strangers, either griefers or those just that are flat out irritating in voice chat, can be exhausting, and you can’t block everyone in every session indefinitely. While I agree that private servers are a great idea (and it seems they ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 'Fallout 76' Beta Makes Me Sad - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/24/the-fallout-76-beta-makes-me-sad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKAsrw3I77Yz1jfM7TNTwQcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/24/the-fallout-76-beta-makes-me-sad/" target="_blank"&gt;The 'Fallout 76' Beta Makes Me Sad&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 I just wrapped up almost four full hours with the Fallout 76 beta, live for only a short while yesterday for an Xbox One stress test. Bethesda very much emphasized how many things would inevitably be wrong with the beta, standard for a “true” early test, but still somewhat worrying with official release just three weeks away. I’m happy to report that on the technical side, it actually wasn’t a disaster. Sure, there were a good amount of framerate drops pretty much everywhere, and my character kept sleeping two feet in the air and getting up speared through the middle of the mattr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Nintendo Switch Is Running Into A Predictable Nintendo Problem - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/31/the-nintendo-switch-is-running-into-a-predictable-nintendo-problem/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMx87OvJz2fpAZ7Uqi5SkmwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 12:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/31/the-nintendo-switch-is-running-into-a-predictable-nintendo-problem/" target="_blank"&gt;The Nintendo Switch Is Running Into A Predictable Nintendo Problem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smash While the Nintendo Switch is certainly a hit, and a radical departure from the clear failure of the Wii U, we are starting to see signs that Nintendo is once again dealing with an old problem specific to the company in the last few console races. In a recent earnings report, we learned that Nintendo has sold 22.8 million Switches at this point, roughly on par or a bit below the pace of the PS4. Nintendo has forecast they will sell 20 million Switches during this current fiscal year, but right now they’re only at 5.07 million, halfway through. But this is “in line” with expectations, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Login Failed: Here's Why You Can't Get Into The 'Fallout 76' Beta - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/23/login-failed-heres-why-you-cant-get-into-the-fallout-76-beta/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBCrzsF6DafEAov7rFEv4g0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 13:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/23/login-failed-heres-why-you-cant-get-into-the-fallout-76-beta/" target="_blank"&gt;Login Failed: Here's Why You Can't Get Into The 'Fallout 76' Beta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 I thought I was going to finish up writing early today and jump into the Fallout 76 beta, but it turns out, I’m going to have to wait a while. Despite my pre-order of the game, I was hit with a few different errors trying to get into the beta this morning. The first was an endless loading screen that would appear when I entered my Bethesda.net username/password wrong that I had to force quit to escape. Then there was another error message when I finally got my login info right: “Login failed. This account lacks the required entitlements.” I thought this may have been a problem wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>It Sure Seems Like 'Fallout 76' Will Be The 'No Man's Sky' Of 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/24/it-sure-seems-like-fallout-76-will-be-the-no-mans-sky-of-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEiT2SaX2vBnXqpGRpI6-2QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/24/it-sure-seems-like-fallout-76-will-be-the-no-mans-sky-of-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;It Sure Seems Like 'Fallout 76' Will Be The 'No Man's Sky' Of 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is Fallout 76 ready for the big leagues? Just before the launch of No Man’s Sky back in August of 2016, Hello Games chief Sean Murray released an open letter to fans. There was something just a tiny bit odd about the note. After all, it opened with this line: I feel sick writing this. You are about to play ‘No Man’s Sky’ and I don’t know what you’ll think. “Believe the hype” this was decidedly not. And sure enough, upon its release the gaming community descended into that place only the gaming community really can: Collective fury, a sense of betrayal, and feckless outrage all mixed into a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Xbox One Beta: Start/End Times, How To Get A Code And What You Need To Know - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/22/fallout-76-xbox-one-beta-startend-times-how-to-get-a-code-and-what-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB8IEPlxkXv7KFheEGBDnTcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 17:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/22/fallout-76-xbox-one-beta-startend-times-how-to-get-a-code-and-what-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Xbox One Beta: Start/End Times, How To Get A Code And What You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Of all the blockbusters coming out this holiday season, none of them is quite as strange as Fallout 76. Bethesda’s upcoming open-world Fallout game is unlike any Fallout game that’s come before it, and it’s still a little bit of a mystery what it’s actually going to be like to play the thing. It’s a multiplayer survival game, something like Rust or any number of survival games we’ve seen in recent years, but as usual, Bethesda is doing its own thing when it comes to thing like base building, PvP and somewhat concerningly upbeat attitude about nuclear war. Luckily, we’re about to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda's Confusing 'Fallout 76' Note To Fans Is A Perfect Kick-Off To The Beta - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/23/bethesdas-confusing-fallout-76-note-to-fans-is-a-perfect-kick-off-to-the-beta/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECSlJEt_K4_MulNgYR_xRVUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 11:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/23/bethesdas-confusing-fallout-76-note-to-fans-is-a-perfect-kick-off-to-the-beta/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda's Confusing 'Fallout 76' Note To Fans Is A Perfect Kick-Off To The Beta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 I am about to dive into the beta of Fallout 76 which launches today on Xbox One and a week later on PS4 and PC, but a note caught my eye that Bethesda released to fans that feels pretty emblematic of the entire lead-up to this game. Fallout 76 is a strange experiment for Bethesda, a fact that they fully acknowledge in this note to fans. Here are a few of the key passages: “Once the idea of ‘Fallout-Online-Survival-Game’ stuck, there was not running back, but still some worry and questions. Will people want this from Fallout? Will they want it from us? How the hell are we going to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Xbox One X Reaches New Heights In 'Red Dead Redemption II' Console Comparison - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/27/the-xbox-one-x-reaches-new-heights-in-red-dead-redemption-ii-console-comparison/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIKfdi3M-0JjrE96kYtNp74qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/27/the-xbox-one-x-reaches-new-heights-in-red-dead-redemption-ii-console-comparison/" target="_blank"&gt;The Xbox One X Reaches New Heights In 'Red Dead Redemption II' Console Comparison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Red Dead Redemption II’ Review after review, including David Their’s thoughtful and balanced analysis of Red Dead Redemption II here on Forbes, has praised the game’s fully realized and beautifully rendered world. This doesn’t come as a complete surprise as Rockstar is renowned for it’s ability to create rich and immersive open worlds and the gameplay trailers that preceded RDR2’s release are strikingly beautiful. The surprise is that the PS4 Pro footage seen in the trailers is far from the best looking version of the game. Red Dead Redemption II on the Xbox One X stands head and shoulders...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Target Offers Early Pick-Up On Thursday Night For 'Red Dead Redemption II' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/22/target-offers-early-pick-up-on-thursday-night-for-red-dead-redemption-ii/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO0_OKBnZA49v2fFeBcY6tgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/22/target-offers-early-pick-up-on-thursday-night-for-red-dead-redemption-ii/" target="_blank"&gt;Target Offers Early Pick-Up On Thursday Night For 'Red Dead Redemption II'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Red Dead Redemption II’ is almost here. Target has a solution if you want to score a physical copy of Red Dead Redemption II and don’t want to wait in one of the long lines that are sure to form before midnight on Friday. The store’s weekly ad says both the regular $59.99 and special $79.99 editions of the game will be available for in-store pick-up at 9:00 PM on Thursday. Target is also offering a good deal on an RDR2 bundle that includes the game and a 1 TB PS4 Pro for $399 which is the standard cost of the console alone. You’ll have to wait until Friday to buy the bundle, however. An RD...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>PS4's First 'Spider-Man' DLC Is Out Today, But So Far It's Missing In Action - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/23/ps4s-first-spider-man-dlc-is-out-today-but-so-far-its-missing-in-action/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI_v3BP90IOc1MHOPApc1CIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/23/ps4s-first-spider-man-dlc-is-out-today-but-so-far-its-missing-in-action/" target="_blank"&gt;PS4's First 'Spider-Man' DLC Is Out Today, But So Far It's Missing In Action&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black Cat With Spider-Man being the PlayStation 4’s fastest-selling exclusive ever, it stands to reason that a fair amount of players are going to be diving in to the first DLC for the game, Black Cat’s ‘The Heist’ storyline, which is out today just a month and a half after the original release. Unfortunately, if you stayed up late to play it at midnight, you were disappointed. And if you woke up early to play it now, you’re also disappointed. For some reason, despite the game itself saying The Heist DLC is available now, it’s not showing up in the store. Clicking the “get DLC” button in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda And Xbox Drop The Hammer On Player Who Breaks The 'Fallout 76' NDA - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/16/bethesda-and-xbox-drop-the-hammer-on-player-who-breaks-the-fallout-76-nda/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELobHPvaTW3fhOI_1Qzd4u0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/16/bethesda-and-xbox-drop-the-hammer-on-player-who-breaks-the-fallout-76-nda/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda And Xbox Drop The Hammer On Player Who Breaks The 'Fallout 76' NDA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guy breaks ”Fallout 76′ NDA. Bethesda and Xbox break guy. Technology and video game companies take NDAs and embargoes seriously. You don’t break them. Apparently, a player who participated in last Saturday’s stress test for Fallout 76 on the Xbox One either didn’t get the message or thought he could get away with it. He didn’t, and both Bethesda and Xbox dropped the hammer on him. Players who signed up for the stress test were required to click-to-agree to an NDA that prohibited taking or sharing photos, videos or audio recordings, describing the game online or offline, allowing people to w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76 release date, beta and everything you need to know before you don your power armour - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fallout-76-release-date-beta-everything-need-know-don-power/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJAnVDxlfvb-eKjTP45Gpu4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 12:29:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fallout-76-release-date-beta-everything-need-know-don-power/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76 release date, beta and everything you need to know before you don your power armour&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nuclear annihilation survivors will soon be able to step out of the vault in Fallout 76, the latest in Bethesda Games Studios sprawling sci-fi RPG. But for the first time, this is Fallout online, with a huge multiplayer map populated with other players as you explore the scorched earth of West Virginia. Bethesda has confirmed the release date for both the full game and a beta, allowing players to pre-test Fallout 76’s servers. More information has been trickling out since Fallout 76’s reveal at E3 2018, so here is everything you need to know. Fallout 76 release date and platforms Fallout 76...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Bethesda Explains 'Fallout 76' Microtransactions (Sort Of) - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/10/bethesda-explains-fallout-76-microtransactions-sort-of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIPmUzOO1s-9ggDcy_7sRVUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/10/bethesda-explains-fallout-76-microtransactions-sort-of/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda Explains 'Fallout 76' Microtransactions (Sort Of)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 will sell gamers ‘Atoms’ in order to purchase in-game cosmetics. Bethesda has revealed what we all knew was coming: Micro-transactions will be a part of Fallout 76. Specifically, players will be able to purchase Atoms which they can then use to buy cosmetic items like skins. Atoms will also be available to earn in-game, meaning you won’t have to spend any money on these cosmetics if you don’t want to. According to Bethesda chief Pete Hines, the game will “throw them at you all the time.” “Atoms are thing that we use and hand out as you play the game–quite honestly we throw them a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Boy, Does Fallout 76's Real-Time VATS System Look Terrible - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/09/boy-does-fallout-76s-real-time-vats-system-look-terrible/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJDLHPFivOuAu_qMzp8rz10qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 13:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/09/boy-does-fallout-76s-real-time-vats-system-look-terrible/" target="_blank"&gt;Boy, Does Fallout 76's Real-Time VATS System Look Terrible&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 Yesterday, an embargo lifted for a Fallout 76 preview event that many game journalists attended, myself not among them. The result was that we got hours and hours of preview footage from select areas of the game, and pages and pages of impressions pieces about what was played. I have watched the videos, I have read the previews, and while I still have to limit my judgement not having played the game myself, I have to say I have seen literally nothing to convince me that this game isn’t exactly as weird and not-for-me as I anticipate, given Bethesda’s confusing explanation about h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fallout 76' Beta Start Dates, Platforms And Everything You Need To Know - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/27/fallout-76-beta-start-dates-platforms-and-everything-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEElPzkOFtZYBbBZUq7poGuIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 15:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/27/fallout-76-beta-start-dates-platforms-and-everything-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fallout 76' Beta Start Dates, Platforms And Everything You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s everything you need to know about the ‘Fallout 76′ beta. Bethesda has revealed the starting dates, platforms and other information about the upcoming Fallout 76 beta landing later this month. The beta, which in this instance is being referred to as the Break It Early Test Application, comes just weeks before the game’s November launch. Fallout 76 is a multiplayer spinoff of the main Fallout series, and we’re still a little unsure of what exactly to expect from the game. In fact, that’s one reason we’re so excited for the upcoming beta: We need to know what it is this game is trying t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76 beta release date announced for Xbox One, PS4 and PC - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fallout-76-beta-release-date-announced-xbox-one-ps4-pc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELDfaToVzsDRmWhR6lhGCikqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 14:34:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fallout-76-beta-release-date-announced-xbox-one-ps4-pc/" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76 beta release date announced for Xbox One, PS4 and PC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bethesdahas announced that the beta for Fallout 76, the upcoming apocalyptic online survival game, will start on 23 October for Xbox One players and 30 October on PS4 and PC. The only way to access the beta is through pre-ordering the game. The beta (or 'Break-It Early Test Application' in Fallout terms) will run from its release up until a few days before the game's release date of 14 November. However, in a Q&amp;A on the Fallout website, Bethesda has said that the beta servers will not be live 24/7, but will run during 'targeted timeframes' in order to get as many players playing at the sam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Here Are The Role Playing Games That Are Coming In October - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/09/29/here-are-the-role-playing-games-that-are-coming-in-october/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKMtA-DInRxngA9cLUKd3JcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/09/29/here-are-the-role-playing-games-that-are-coming-in-october/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are The Role Playing Games That Are Coming In October&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Fallout 76′ October’s seven RPGs may not match the volume of September’s twelve, but the quality of the games on offer more than makes up the difference. Two of the most anticipated games—let alone RPGs— of the Fall season, Assassin’s Creed Odyssey and the beta for Fallout 76, bookend the month. The remaining releases include a DLC pack that brings exo-suit clad fighters to the Wild West, a Souls-like action RPG where you get weaker as the game progresses, a sequel to a much loved MMORPG and a graphical remaster of a game that launched a mini-industry. If that isn’t enough, October also fe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sony enables Fortnite PS4 crossplay with Xbox, Switch, PC and mobile - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/sony-enables-fortnite-ps4-crossplay-xbox-switch-pc-mobile/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFN4P_0s19HanY1rHrFk62cqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 14:59:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/sony-enables-fortnite-ps4-crossplay-xbox-switch-pc-mobile/" target="_blank"&gt;Sony enables Fortnite PS4 crossplay with Xbox, Switch, PC and mobile&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sony has relented on its heavily criticised refusal to allow cross platform play between its PS4 console and other video game platforms. In a statement made by Sony Interactive Entertainment CEO John Kodera, it was announced that the hugely popular Battle Royale game Fortnite will allow PS4 players to play with Xbox One, Nintendo Switch, PC and mobile device players for the first time in an 'extended open beta'. The feature is live now in time for the release of Fortnite Season 6 tomorrow. Up until now, cross-play had been enabled between other platforms, but Sony policy meant that cross-pl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Bethesda's Pete Hines on Fallout 76, next-gen and The Elder Scrolls 6 - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/bethesdas-pete-hines-fallout-76-next-gen-elder-scrolls-6/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKzrCcJedqMKgEoW4MMUIf0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 16:00:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/bethesdas-pete-hines-fallout-76-next-gen-elder-scrolls-6/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda's Pete Hines on Fallout 76, next-gen and The Elder Scrolls 6&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bethesda Softworks continues its march as one of the most bankable video game companies on the planet. The Washington-based publisher has cultivated a passionate following with RPGs both post-apocalyptic and medieval fantasy in Fallout and The Elder Scrolls. With fast-paced, furiously named shooters like Doom, Rage and Wolfenstein. The company has had a significant period of growth to put them at the top table. At an E3 press conference earlier this year, they announced a slew of games, including the eagerly anticipated The Elder Scrolls VI and new sci-fi adventure Starfield. This in additi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>From 'Fortnite' To 'Fallout 76,' Publishers Are Sick Of Google, Apple And Steam's Store Cuts - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/08/13/from-fortnite-to-fallout-76-publishers-are-sick-of-google-apple-and-steams-store-cuts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELuRAelpSkTBzCkonP9B2L0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/08/13/from-fortnite-to-fallout-76-publishers-are-sick-of-google-apple-and-steams-store-cuts/" target="_blank"&gt;From 'Fortnite' To 'Fallout 76,' Publishers Are Sick Of Google, Apple And Steam's Store Cuts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 If I was to highlight one gaming industry trend in 2018, it would be how publishers are doing their best to absolutely flee from loot boxes like they’re some sort of contagious disease after going overboard with them in previous years. But if there’s a second narrative emerging, it’s that major publishers are getting tired of platform holders taking enormous cuts of their revenue in order to use their storefronts. The most high profile examples of this have both happened recently. Epic announced that Fortnite would indeed be coming to Android, but it would not be sold through the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>The Elder Scrolls VI, Starfield and the future of video game giant Bethesda - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/jul/18/bethesda-games-interview-todd-howard-pete-hines-elder-scrolls-starfield</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJvsZGjae4j1lnvFPhAxhooqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 06:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/jul/18/bethesda-games-interview-todd-howard-pete-hines-elder-scrolls-starfield" target="_blank"&gt;The Elder Scrolls VI, Starfield and the future of video game giant Bethesda&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the early 2000s, game publisher Bethesda was best known for its Elder Scrolls series of technologically ambitious fantasy games. In the last 15 years, however, it has expanded greatly, snapping up several legendary video game franchises as well as starting an original series of its own. The company now produces the Fallout post-apocalyptic role-playing games; the iconic, hellish shooter Doom; tongue-in-cheek Nazi-killing romp Wolfenstein; supernatural steampunk assassin sim Dishonoured; and Rage, a Mad Max-style romp around a devastated world. At its E3 press conference last month, after...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76: what you need to know about one of the biggest games of the year - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/jul/17/fallout-76-bethesda-todd-howard-interview</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMFt7tGqPtYF6R0Dz9Xh7c0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 06:00:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/jul/17/fallout-76-bethesda-todd-howard-interview" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76: what you need to know about one of the biggest games of the year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While billionaires buy up property in New Zealand and pay technologists huge sums of money for advice on how to keep their staff in check after “the event” – that is, whatever it is that wipes out enough of the planet to justify living in bunkers – the rest of us are left to deal with the looming threat of catastrophe by playing video games. Bethesda Game Studios’ Fallout series offers a very American take on the post-apocalypse: humans, ghouls and mutants protect their respective corners of the wasteland with big guns and power armour, in a retro future with sci-fi technology and a 1950s a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item></channel></rss>