<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Stranger Things - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV6TVd4dU4za1NBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:02:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Doctor Who season 12: Jodie Whittaker confirms she will return as the Time Lord - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/doctor-who-season-12-jodie-whittaker-role-reprise-return-time-lord-new-series-a8672466.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC_lg61kxFCC_HtBHDpqmJ4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/doctor-who-season-12-jodie-whittaker-role-reprise-return-time-lord-new-series-a8672466.html" target="_blank"&gt;Doctor Who season 12: Jodie Whittaker confirms she will return as the Time Lord&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jodie Whittaker is set to go on more adventures aboard the Tardis. The Doctor Who star has confirmed she will return as the Time Lord in season 12 of the BCC's iconic sci-fi series. "I really can’t wait to step back in and get to work again," Whittaker told The Hollywood Reporter. "It’s such an incredible role. It's been an extraordinary journey so far and I'm not quite ready to hand it over yet." It was announced in July 2017 that Whittaker had been picked as the 13th Doctor, succeeding to Peter Capaldi. The casting decision was met with excitement as Whittaker was the first woman to ever ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Narcos: Mexico season 2: Netflix renews Diego Luna and Michael Peña series - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/narcos-mexico-season-2-netflix-diego-luna-michael-pena-a8668836.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOQLsJZvo9ONQe9StlfrVT0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/narcos-mexico-season-2-netflix-diego-luna-michael-pena-a8668836.html" target="_blank"&gt;Narcos: Mexico season 2: Netflix renews Diego Luna and Michael Peña series&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix has renewed Narcos: Mexico for a second season. The sequel series – set in the 1980s – stars Diego Luna and Michael Peña as the Mexican drug-lord Félix Gallardo and DEA agent Kiki Camarena, respectively. The story sees Kiki garner intelligence on Félix, eventually becoming more entangled in his mission and a tragic chain of events unfolding. Both actors will assumably return for the second series, which itself will be the fifth overall season of Narcos. The first three revolved around the kingpin Pablo Escobar and the aftermath of his death, taking place primarily in Columbia. The 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Daredevil cancelled by Netflix despite being one of the most streamed shows across America - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/daredevil-netflix-cancelled-season-3-most-streamed-on-demand-handmaids-tale-house-of-cards-a8667981.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH8h6U18h8dNRsuvkvR9R38qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/daredevil-netflix-cancelled-season-3-most-streamed-on-demand-handmaids-tale-house-of-cards-a8667981.html" target="_blank"&gt;Daredevil cancelled by Netflix despite being one of the most streamed shows across America&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix has begun cancelling all their Marvel content, beginning with Iron Fist and recently culminating in Daredevil. The latter came as a particular surprise, as the Charlie Cox-led series has picked up rave reviews and seemingly had a large fan-base. According to the latest numbers from Parrot Analytics, as published by Deadline, the series was indeed hugely popular with streamers: the company claims Daredevil was the fourth most-demanded show among all digital original programmes in the US last week. The three series that beat the superhero show were Narcos, The Chilling Adventures of S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Friends: Netflix confirms Friends will stay on US and UK version of streaming service until 2020 - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/friends-netflix-us-uk-episodes-watch-leave-date-a8666146.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIi6OPHmg1ggHhIJIbrA80kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 09:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/friends-netflix-us-uk-episodes-watch-leave-date-a8666146.html" target="_blank"&gt;Friends: Netflix confirms Friends will stay on US and UK version of streaming service until 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix has confirmed that the world's most beloved sitcom is remaining on the streaming service. Fans of Friends – who are currently able to watch all 10 seasons on Netflix – were worried that their supply would get cut off after a message on the streamer's website made it look like the entire show could soon be taken down. Netflix's homepage stated on Monday morning that Friends would be available only until 1 January 2019, implying that all 236 episodes would disappear come the new year. Both the UK and US versions of Netflix have now assuaged subscribers' fears, confirming that Friends ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Doctor Who actors reject claims the show has become too politically correct - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/doctor-who-politically-correct-mandip-gill-tosin-col-jodie-whittaker-a8664436.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEErp-lzAUAEguLc8UOb0ztcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 08:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/doctor-who-politically-correct-mandip-gill-tosin-col-jodie-whittaker-a8664436.html" target="_blank"&gt;Doctor Who actors reject claims the show has become too politically correct&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cast of Doctor Who have laughed off suggestions that the iconic science fiction show has become too politically correct. Mandip Gill and Tosin Cole – who play Yaz and Ryan alongside Jodie Whittaker’s Doctor – have rejected the idea the series has become overly politicised and believe it is an “entertaining reminder” of important issues. Speaking in Radio Times, the pair said that the show can provoke “extreme opinions” in some viewers who comment online. In being too politically correct, Gill said: “It makes me laugh, because having the words ‘too’ and ‘correct’ in the same sentence is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Stranger Things season 3: Everything we know so far from cast and plot to spoilers - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/features/stranger-things-season-3-latest-cast-release-date-trailer-plot-spoilers-a8618601.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO_TFHgewT7PeI74l7IAaqEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 17:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/features/stranger-things-season-3-latest-cast-release-date-trailer-plot-spoilers-a8618601.html" target="_blank"&gt;Stranger Things season 3: Everything we know so far from cast and plot to spoilers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It feels like we’ve been waiting forever for a return to Hawkins, Indiana. Unfortunately, there’s still longer to wait, as season three of Stranger Things will debut outside of its usual Halloween slot. However, in return, expect new characters, new thrills, a major new location, and some of the biggest special effects yet. Here’s everything you need to know. What year does it take place? Season three will take place in the summer of 1985, a little bit less than a year since the events of season 2, which took place in October 1984. As has now become standard with the series, expect referenc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Daredevil cancelled: Cast ‘heartbroken’ after Netflix ends Marvel series - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/daredevil-cancelled-cast-react-netflix-disney-plus-iron-fist-charlie-cox-jessica-jones-a8660286.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBIiw4ZrqAzAcJqjZatpe0wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 07:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/daredevil-cancelled-cast-react-netflix-disney-plus-iron-fist-charlie-cox-jessica-jones-a8660286.html" target="_blank"&gt;Daredevil cancelled: Cast ‘heartbroken’ after Netflix ends Marvel series&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix has cancelled Daredevil after three seasons, leaving the cast “heartbroken and surprised”. The streaming service won’t be bringing its original Marvel series back for a fourth season, confirming in a statement: “Although it’s painful for the fans, we feel it best to close this chapter on a high note”. Fans may be surprised but it’s the cast who are truly devastated, with many expressing difficulties processing the news despite the cancellation of Iron Fist and Luke Cage. Rahul Nadeem star Jay Ali wrote: “So Sad to hear the end of @Daredevil. I was so lucky and fortunate to be a part...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Netflix TV shows: The 25 best series to watch in the UK - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/features/best-netflix-tv-shows-what-to-watch-tonight-black-mirror-the-crown-stranger-things-narcos-rick-and-a8548846.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIT8h9X9a9xCYmg0MNTdvlIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 16:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/features/best-netflix-tv-shows-what-to-watch-tonight-black-mirror-the-crown-stranger-things-narcos-rick-and-a8548846.html" target="_blank"&gt;Netflix TV shows: The 25 best series to watch in the UK&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix's televised revolution began in earnest in February 2013, when the machiavellian political schemer Frank Underwood looked straight into the camera and casually snapped a dog’s neck. It was the first episode of House of Cards – a $100 million TV series that would only be available on the Internet. The show represented a huge risk for the streaming service as it sought to make the leap from tech start-up to entertainment industry goliath. Five years on and the gamble has paid off. Netflix was a major winner at the Emmys, its haul of 23 awards attesting to its power-player status. And ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Luther season 5 trailer: Idris Elba and Ruth Wilson return in brutal promo - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/luther-season-5-trailer-video-idris-elba-ruth-wilson-bbc-series-5-return-date-christmas-tv-a8657466.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSSddMkVCsutVbCpSK3IFEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/luther-season-5-trailer-video-idris-elba-ruth-wilson-bbc-series-5-return-date-christmas-tv-a8657466.html" target="_blank"&gt;Luther season 5 trailer: Idris Elba and Ruth Wilson return in brutal promo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trailer for the forthcoming fifth series of Luther has been released ahead of its premiere this Christmas. It was announced in June 2017 that series co-creator Neil Cross had signed up Idris Elba to return as the grizzled detective for four brand new episodes of the crime series following its apparent “climax” in 2015. But sure enough, DCI Luther is back in a trailer that’s capped with a blink-and-you’ll-miss-it cameo from none other than Ruth Wilson’s fan favourite, Alice Morgan, which you can watch below. Other returning cast members include Dermot Crowley, Michael Smiley and Patrick ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>BBC Christmas schedule revealed: From Watership Down, The ABC Murders, Luther season 5 to Les Misérables - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/bbc-christmas-schedule-full-list-les-miserables-abc-murders-luther-season-5-malkovich-a8653651.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENOzbrqL3IN5FJq16-ftRv8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 09:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/bbc-christmas-schedule-full-list-les-miserables-abc-murders-luther-season-5-malkovich-a8653651.html" target="_blank"&gt;BBC Christmas schedule revealed: From Watership Down, The ABC Murders, Luther season 5 to Les Misérables&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The BBC has unveiled their Christmas TV schedule for 2018, revealing a line-up that features iconic detectives, animated rabbits, and 19th century classics. John Malkovich’s Poirot leads the way, the actor starring as the iconic character alongside Harry Potter’s Rupert Grint in an adaptation of Agatha Christie’s The ABC Murders. A star-studded version of Watership Down – featuring the voices of James McAvoy, Nicolas Hoult, John Boyega, Olivia Coleman, Ben Kingsley, Gemma Arterton, and Peter Capaldi – will also debut on BBC One, as will a six-part version of Les Misérables starring Dominic ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Dynasties: BBC crew responsible for calling vets on poisoned lion cub - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/dynasties-bbc-poisoned-lion-cub-vets-crew-call-africa-a8651726.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGHv3vkQfsNE5p-OvojGs8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 08:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/dynasties-bbc-poisoned-lion-cub-vets-crew-call-africa-a8651726.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dynasties: BBC crew responsible for calling vets on poisoned lion cub&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The third episode of David Attenborough's latest series Dynasties was a heartbreaking look at how humans are negatively affecting the lives of lions. Viewers witnessed a pride being poisoned by neighbouring farmers after some bait was laced with poison. A group of vets were soon on scene, hoping to save a young lion cub as he struggled to keep up with the others. Reports have since revealed that the medical crew who attempted to help the cub were alerted by the BBC crew filming th pride. The Mara Mobile Veterinary Unit filed an incident report, which notes the lions “were seen during the mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Bodyguard actor Richard Madden confirms talks for season 2 are happening - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/bodyguard-season-2-start-sequel-richard-madden-julia-montague-bbc-a8640546.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDNqfwXyiUrZ3v58iRO9KywqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/bodyguard-season-2-start-sequel-richard-madden-julia-montague-bbc-a8640546.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bodyguard actor Richard Madden confirms talks for season 2 are happening&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following the astronomical success of Bodyguard, talks of a sequel were inevitable. Richard Madden – who played the eponymous bodyguard in the series – has since confirmed that talks with showrunner Jed Mercurio about a follow-up are taking place. “I’m having a conversation with him (Mercurio) in about 10 days or something, when I’m back in the country, and we are just going to chat through some ideas,” he said. “We never intended to make another one and I don’t know, I’m excited to see what he’s got, especially because David (Budd, his character) had quite a busy couple of months. “So what...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Luther season 5: New clip shows how much trouble Idris Elba's detective is in - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/luther-season-5-trailer-clip-bbc-one-idris-elba-broadcast-date-alice-a8626296.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELrY8OEXYEd4IQF3Z72ytmgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/luther-season-5-trailer-clip-bbc-one-idris-elba-broadcast-date-alice-a8626296.html" target="_blank"&gt;Luther season 5: New clip shows how much trouble Idris Elba's detective is in&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The BBC has released a new clip from the upcoming series 5 of Luther. The scene sees Idris Elba‘s grizzled detective being interrogated by George, as he demands Luther reveals the location of his son Alistair, who appears to have been kidnapped. It was announced in June 2017 that series co-creator Neil Cross had signed up Elba to return for four brand new episodes of the crime series. The character was last seen on screen in 2015. - Read more Idris Elba returns as Luther in new teaser trailer While plot details remain sparse, the first look at the series came with one bold warning: “This wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Rick &amp; Morty has more deaths per episode than any other show on streaming, report claims - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/rick-and-morty-deaths-episode-season-streaming-netflix-justin-roiland-dan-harmon-a8623446.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHQGkc88kgwJrwV9v_pQuvwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 08:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/rick-and-morty-deaths-episode-season-streaming-netflix-justin-roiland-dan-harmon-a8623446.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rick &amp; Morty has more deaths per episode than any other show on streaming, report claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rick and Morty has been named the deadliest TV show currently available on streaming. According to a study by BuzzBingo, the animated series outnumbers even The Walking Dead in its number of onscreen deaths, with an average of 26.1 deaths per episode. That equates to 808 deaths across its three seasons and 31 episodes. Westworld, however, is only just behind with 25.9 deaths per episode, while The Walking Dead averages 23.2. Read more - Dan Harmon deletes his Twitter after ‘distasteful’ video resurfaces - Rick and Morty creator announces 70 more episodes will be made - Rick and Morty creato...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Kelsey Grammer hopes to bring back old co-stars for Frasier reboot - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/kelsey-grammer-frasier-reboot-co-stars-cast-return-david-hyde-pierce-john-mahony-a8617926.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAssQj5T63_Ta8WiTie8jQgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 09:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/kelsey-grammer-frasier-reboot-co-stars-cast-return-david-hyde-pierce-john-mahony-a8617926.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kelsey Grammer hopes to bring back old co-stars for Frasier reboot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether the world really needs a Frasier reboot remains up for debate, but that has not stopped leading star Kelsey Grammer pursuing the idea. Speaking at the USC Comedy Festival alongside co-star David Hyde Pierce (Niles), the Emmy-winning actor told an audience thatno premise has yet been set in stone. “No, there’s been no premise that has come along that has the necessary fire,” Deadline reports Grammer saying. "A lot of us are quite committed to the concept that you would never try to redo what we once had.” Asked about whether Pierce and other co-stars would return, Grammer said: "In m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Penny Dreadful is returning to TV - with new cast - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/penny-dreadful-tv-return-new-cast-latest-sky-a8618111.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIjVbM-mkX4FHhpSfMHIbFMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 10:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/penny-dreadful-tv-return-new-cast-latest-sky-a8618111.html" target="_blank"&gt;Penny Dreadful is returning to TV - with new cast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Penny Dreadful will return to Showtime for a revival series, two years after its dramatic conclusion. A new chapter called City of Angels will serve as “spiritual descendant” of the original three-season story set in Victorian-era London, says The Hollywood Reporter. The series will take place in Los Angeles in 1938 which, according to Showtime, is “a time and place deeply infused with Mexican-American folklore and social tension”. The conflict of the series will be rooted between characters connected to the deity Santa Muerte and others allied with the devil, using the supernatural set aga...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Javier Bardem revealed as highest-paid actor on TV - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/tv/2018/10/31/javier-bardem-revealed-highest-paid-actor-tv/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGUkAopQL2xsMBUWLqz_qQYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTD51N8D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:51:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/tv/2018/10/31/javier-bardem-revealed-highest-paid-actor-tv/" target="_blank"&gt;Javier Bardem revealed as highest-paid actor on TV&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Javier Bardem is the highest-paid star in TV, according to a Variety investigation. He will earn $1.2million for each episode of Amazon’s forthcoming series about Hernán Cortés. In joint second place on the list are Reese Witherspoon and Jennifer Aniston, who are each being paid $1.1m for their untitled morning show drama for Apple. The top 10 per episode salaries are: - $1.2m, Javier Bardem (untitled series, Amazon) - (=) $1.1m, Reese Witherspoon and Jennifer Aniston (untitled series, Apple) - (=) $1m, Elisabeth Moss (The Handmaid’s Tale, Hulu); Norman Reedus (The Walking Dead, AMC) - (=) ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Highest-paid TV stars 2018: Salaries of the biggest names in US television revealed, from Reese Witherspoon to Javier Bardem - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/highest-paid-tv-stars-salaries-jennifer-aniston-reese-witherspoon-javier-bardem-walking-dead-a8609931.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2MUQvEyV58C9I6zluDpOsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/highest-paid-tv-stars-salaries-jennifer-aniston-reese-witherspoon-javier-bardem-walking-dead-a8609931.html" target="_blank"&gt;Highest-paid TV stars 2018: Salaries of the biggest names in US television revealed, from Reese Witherspoon to Javier Bardem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The salaries of TV’s highest-paid actors have been revealed. Split into three categories – comedy, unscripted and drama – the new report comes from Variety and reveals just how much stars earn per episode. The highest-paid actor in a US drama is Javier Bardem who will earn $1.2m for his role in a forthcoming Amazon series based on “legendary conqueror” Hernan Cortes from Traffic writer, Steven Zaillian. Following close behind are Hollywood stars Reese Witherspoon and Jennifer Aniston who’ll each earn $1.1m per episode for their roles in a new series from Apple. Their co-star, Steve Carell, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>BoJack Horseman renewed for season 6 by Netflix - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/bojack-horseman-season-6-netflix-will-arnett-animation-a8609926.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEocdT6xWwtvWqK4bvQPq2gqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/bojack-horseman-season-6-netflix-will-arnett-animation-a8609926.html" target="_blank"&gt;BoJack Horseman renewed for season 6 by Netflix&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix's best show about a depressed animated horse will return for another season. The streaming service has confirmed that a sixth season of BoJack Horseman, which follows the struggles of a washed up alcoholic actor, has been commissioned. A tweet from the BoJack Twitter page confirmed the news with a message reading: "Woooowwwwwwwwwwwwwww lets all forget about the fact that theres going to b a season 6 and focus on this inedible arrangement Netflix sent me just woww." woooowwwwwwwwwwwwwww lets all forget about the fact that theres going to b a season 6 and focus on this inedible arrang...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>House of Cards: Netflix scraps Doug Stamper spinoff series - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/house-of-cards-netflix-season-6-doug-stamper-michael-kelly-spinoff-robin-wright-kevin-spacey-a8610191.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPfYZn3ha6GZlhyIe0il3mIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/house-of-cards-netflix-season-6-doug-stamper-michael-kelly-spinoff-robin-wright-kevin-spacey-a8610191.html" target="_blank"&gt;House of Cards: Netflix scraps Doug Stamper spinoff series&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix has cancelled plans to make a House of Cards spinoff series focused on character Doug Stamper. The series was confirmed to be in the works at the streaming service after Kevin Spacey was fired following multiple allegations of sexual assault. However, actor Michael Kelly has confirmed the project will not proceed. “There was talk of a spinoff for a while, and we went well down the road on that. And I would’ve liked to have played him more, but when they decided not to do that, I was okay,” he told Variety. “I was really okay with it. I felt like I had done him justice, and it was an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Legend of Zelda: Castlevania creator in talks to bring Nintendo classic to Netflix - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/legend-of-zelda-netflix-series-castlevania-adi-shankar-nintendo-game-link-release-a8608306.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM8GP22xC4L-6IttkbPBx3wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 09:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/legend-of-zelda-netflix-series-castlevania-adi-shankar-nintendo-game-link-release-a8608306.html" target="_blank"&gt;Legend of Zelda: Castlevania creator in talks to bring Nintendo classic to Netflix&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Castlevania showrunner Adi Shankar has entered into talks with Netflix to produce a TV series based on the video-game series The Legend of Zelda. Shankar previously Tweeted he was “working with an iconic Japanese gaming company to adapt one of their iconic video game series into a series.” The Wrap has since confirmed that the producer hopes to bring the long-running Nintendo series to the streaming service. Netflix already produces Shankar’s Castlevania, an animated show based on the game of the same name, the second season of which was released on Friday (26 October). The 25 best TV shows...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The Walking Dead season 9 episode 4 sees Norman Reedus drop show's first F-word - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/the-walking-dead-season-9-episode-4-f-word-swear-word-daryl-rick-dies-a8605981.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEWtleTMEinSXOloOco2cRwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 05:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/the-walking-dead-season-9-episode-4-f-word-swear-word-daryl-rick-dies-a8605981.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Walking Dead season 9 episode 4 sees Norman Reedus drop show's first F-word&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Walking Dead just dropped its first ever F-word. Strict rules placed on the AMC series have meant it's had to censor the word “f*ck” from every episode in the past, however, guidelines were reportedly “relaxed” ahead of the show’s eighth season. meaning Rick Grimes (Andrew Lincoln) and the gang could use the expletive up to twice throughout a season. Despite this, The Walking Dead kept the word from the entirety of season eight – however, the show’s latest episode saw Daryl Dixon (Norman Reedus) utter the word in one of its more emotional moments. Major spoilers follow for episode four,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Sarah Scott accuses actor Kip Pardue of sexually assaulting her during and after filming sex scene - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/sarah-scott-kip-pardue-sexual-assault-claim-metoo-mogulettes-sex-scene-penis-a8606146.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEshWHQDn_LrhwjKMTO5idMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 09:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/sarah-scott-kip-pardue-sexual-assault-claim-metoo-mogulettes-sex-scene-penis-a8606146.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sarah Scott accuses actor Kip Pardue of sexually assaulting her during and after filming sex scene&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sarah Scott has accused fellow actor Kip Pardue of masturbating in front of her after filming a sex scene, and accused SAG-AFTRA [Screen Actors Guild – American Federation of Television and Radio Artists] of failing to respond quickly to her claims. Scott, who has appeared in TV shows including True Blood and Castle, alleges that the incident involving Pardue happened on 16 May when they filmed a post-coital scene together for a pilot series called Mogulettes. She claims Pardue became aroused while they were under a bedsheet waiting for the scene to begin. He allegedly put her hand on his g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Chilling Adventures of Sabrina review round-up: Critics hail ‘spooky as hell’ Netflix show - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/sabrina-chilling-adventures-reviews-round-up-netflix-kiernan-shipka-a8602526.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBwv3faBD6KKeIm0nH8TXNsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 10:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/sabrina-chilling-adventures-reviews-round-up-netflix-kiernan-shipka-a8602526.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chilling Adventures of Sabrina review round-up: Critics hail ‘spooky as hell’ Netflix show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chilling Adventures of Sabrina has just arrived on Netflix bringing the Archie Comics character back to the small screen. This time around, Mad Men star Kiernan Shipka plays the eponymous teenage witch in an altogether darker show than the version starring Melissa Joan Hart in the 1990s. Critics have weighed in on the reboot – and it’s unanimous praise all round for the series which has been devised by Riverdale‘s Roberto Aguirre-Sacasa. Find out what they’re saying below. - Read more How Sabrina the Teenage Witch is symbolic of feminism through the ages Digital Spy If Riverdale occasio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Another Life: what to know about Selma Blair's new Netflix series - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/tv/2018/10/22/another-life-know-selma-blairs-new-netflix-series/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPWz0RaKGhStaQARXml2Ru8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTD51N8D</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 14:51:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/tv/2018/10/22/another-life-know-selma-blairs-new-netflix-series/" target="_blank"&gt;Another Life: what to know about Selma Blair's new Netflix series&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selma Blair received an outpouring of sympathy over the weekend after revealing she had been diagnosed with Multiple Sclerosis. The actress made her name during the late Nineties and early Noughties with films such as Cruel Intentions and Guillermo Del Toro’s Hellboy films, but as Blair explained in her enlightening Instagram post, will be returning to the small screen with Netflix sci-fi drama series, Another Life. The news has caused interest to pique in the sci-fi drama; here’s what you need to know: Blair’s involvement in Another Life marks yet another instance of an actress who has ch...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Crown season 3: Emerald Fennell cast as Camilla Parker Bowles - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/the-crown-season-3-emerald-fennell-camilla-parker-bowles-netflix-trailer-a8598801.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAZY331pTYsPBQV7k5GMo7gqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 07:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/the-crown-season-3-emerald-fennell-camilla-parker-bowles-netflix-trailer-a8598801.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Crown season 3: Emerald Fennell cast as Camilla Parker Bowles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix has confirmed who will play Camilla Parker Bowles in The Crown season three. Emerald Fennell will star as the Duchess of Cornwall in the Emmy Award-winning series that has recast its characters as it enters a new era. Fennell, who is best known for BBC series Call the Midwife, said: “I’m absolutely over the moon, and completely terrified, to be joining so many hugely talented people on The Crown. I absolutely love Camilla, and am very grateful that my teenage years have well prepared me for playing a chain-smoking serial snogger with a pudding bowl haircut.” - Read more The Crown ep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Bodyguard finale was most watched drama tv episode since records began with 17m viewers - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/bodyguard-viewing-figures-record-tv-drama-episode-bbc-season-2-a8597681.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECla5FJZSfobnlElUEqHBbcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 12:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/bodyguard-viewing-figures-record-tv-drama-episode-bbc-season-2-a8597681.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bodyguard finale was most watched drama tv episode since records began with 17m viewers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the proliferation of streaming services, the summer of 2018 saw the nation brought together by three major televised events: the World Cup, Love Island and Bodyguard. All three have been record breaking (England vs Tunisia at the World Cup is the most-watched live event of the year so far; Love Island broke ITV2 viewership records), with the Bodyguard finale only now breaking another: most-watched episode of a drama since records began in 2002. According to the BBC, 17.1 million people across the UK watched the finale over the course of 28 days. The consolidated figure was calculate...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Daredevil season 4: Showrunner discusses whether possible in wake of Iron Fist and Luke Cage cancellation - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/daredevil-season-4-launch-date-netflix-iron-fist-luke-cage-charlie-cox-a8595396.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKy4R3Z4W9n7ka5FhGad9MkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 06:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/daredevil-season-4-launch-date-netflix-iron-fist-luke-cage-charlie-cox-a8595396.html" target="_blank"&gt;Daredevil season 4: Showrunner discusses whether possible in wake of Iron Fist and Luke Cage cancellation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Netflix having cancelled both Iron Fist and Luke Cage within a week of each other, fans have begun to question the future of their fellow Defenders. Jessica Jones and The Punisher have already been renewed for their third and second seasons, respectively, but Daredevil has not had another run commissioned. Following the third season’s debut on the streaming service, showrunner Erik Oleson spoke to Entertainment Weekly about the current status of the show. “I can tell you that I’m very hopeful to go do a season four,” he told the publication. “There has not yet been any kind of an offic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Orange Is the New Black to end with season 7 on Netflix - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/orange-is-the-new-black-season-7-netflix-cancelled-taylor-schilling-jenji-kohan-when-a8589546.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPbZT9vGI_qckt0g6ogXBrgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 07:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/orange-is-the-new-black-season-7-netflix-cancelled-taylor-schilling-jenji-kohan-when-a8589546.html" target="_blank"&gt;Orange Is the New Black to end with season 7 on Netflix&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Netflix's first original shows is officially drawing to a close. The streaming service has announced that prison series Orange Is the New Black, which stars Taylor Schilling and Laverne Cox, will end with its forthcoming seventh season. Responding to the news, creator Jenji Kohan said: “After seven seasons, it’s time to be released from prison. I will miss all the badass ladies of Litchfield and the incredible crew we’ve worked with. My heart is orange but fade to black.” Vice President of Original Content for Netflix Cindy Holland reflected on the series' legacy in a statement which...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Netflix's 3Q subscriber growth gets rave reviews on Wall St. - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/77477af824004b6897a93d35780dfced</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3ZLL_ZGT8r50bb1Q1eeVAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvqGdAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 22:04:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/77477af824004b6897a93d35780dfced" target="_blank"&gt;Netflix's 3Q subscriber growth gets rave reviews on Wall St.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Netflix regained its stride with surprisingly strong subscriber growth in the third quarter, after an unexpected springtime stumble triggered fears that it was losing its allure. The video-streaming service added 7 million subscribers worldwide from July through September, far above the company's target of 5 million and exceeding analyst projections. Netflix fell well shy of its subscriber goals for the April-to-June period, raising fears that fiercer competition from Amazon, Hulu, HBO and other streaming services was siphoning away viewers. In a show of confidence, Net...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The Walking Dead: Andrew Lincoln is leaving season 8 sooner than expected - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/the-walking-dead-season-8-andrew-lincoln-rick-grimes-leaving-episode-synopsis-a8590151.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN23VMdLkJAsjge-ajcoroQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 12:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/the-walking-dead-season-8-andrew-lincoln-rick-grimes-leaving-episode-synopsis-a8590151.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Walking Dead: Andrew Lincoln is leaving season 8 sooner than expected&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The synopses for the next five episodes of The Walking Dead have been released – and it seems Andrew Lincoln is leaving the show sooner than expected. Which episode exactly will mark the departure of Rick Grimes remains to be seen, but AMC’s decision to release a synopsis for every episode bar the ninth season’s sixth outing hints that it could arrive as early as three weeks. The synopsis for episode 9x05 – titled “What Comes After” – reads: “Rick is forced to face the past as he struggles to maintain the safety of the communities and protect the future he and Carl envisioned.” - Read more ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Streaming’s greatest hits: the best TV shows from Netflix and Amazon - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/oct/14/netflix-v-amazon-streaming-tv-top-shows</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELQluwFHg43G0ONeU80o7LMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 06:00:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2018/oct/14/netflix-v-amazon-streaming-tv-top-shows" target="_blank"&gt;Streaming’s greatest hits: the best TV shows from Netflix and Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix and Amazon have invested billions of dollars in producing original content for their streaming platforms. Here are some of their most notable shows. Netflix House of Cards A remake of a British classic, the streaming site’s first original showed its competitors that it meant business. The accusations surrounding Kevin Spacey’s alleged behaviour on set saw him fired from the show and leave its final season – which starts on 2 November – in the hands of his co-star Robin Wright. Stranger Things The Duffer Brothers pastiche-athon was a massive sleeper hit for Netflix. Released in the s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Roseanne Barr hits back at The Connors premiere, calling it 'grim and morbid' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/roseanne-barr-the-connors-first-episode-review-fired-racist-tweets-a8587841.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBiVYU945SI6xut4jYrlpcwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 09:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/roseanne-barr-the-connors-first-episode-review-fired-racist-tweets-a8587841.html" target="_blank"&gt;Roseanne Barr hits back at The Connors premiere, calling it 'grim and morbid'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Conners’ family returned to television screens last night (17 October), and Roseanne Barr was not amused. Barr was infamously fired from the sitcom Roseanne earlier this year after posting racist messages on Twitter, with the show continuing without her under a new name, The Connors. The fate of her character had been kept heavily under wraps by the series’ network ABC and was revealed during the first episode, titled “Keep on Trucking”. At first, the audience are led to believe that she died of a heart attack following knee surgery, until a coroner’s report reveals she died from an opi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Informer, episode one review: New BBC terrorism thriller is as nonsensical as Bodyguard - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/reviews/informer-bbc-episode-one-review-plot-cast-paddy-considine-bodyguard-a8586371.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJpBVLuK1T54wS-gL9MXCZkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/reviews/informer-bbc-episode-one-review-plot-cast-paddy-considine-bodyguard-a8586371.html" target="_blank"&gt;Informer, episode one review: New BBC terrorism thriller is as nonsensical as Bodyguard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is weird to have Informer (BBC1) on so soon after Bodyguard (BBC1). The two series are so alike that only their mother – or perhaps Auntie – could tell them apart. Where Bodyguard was a six-part thriller about a caring but troubled police officer (Richard Madden) fighting sophisticated terrorists in London, Informer is a six-part thriller about a caring but troubled counter-terrorism officer (Paddy Considine) fighting sophisticated terrorists in London. The obvious defence of the scheduling is that they are to be seen as companion pieces. Rather than close-protection, Informer’s premise ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Sherlock season 5 delayed as creators confirm new Dracula series for BBC - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/sherlock-season-5-dracula-mark-gatiss-steven-moffat-bbc-netflix-martin-freeman-a8584971.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEo8n1_KK99FCz2peJYCFsoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 15:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/sherlock-season-5-dracula-mark-gatiss-steven-moffat-bbc-netflix-martin-freeman-a8584971.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sherlock season 5 delayed as creators confirm new Dracula series for BBC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The creators of Sherlock are officially adapting Dracula for the BBC. As first reported by Variety, Mark Gatiss and Steven Moffat are currently working on a fresh version of Bram Stoker's tale. It'll run for three 90-minute instalments and will be broadcast on Netflix outside of the UK. The series, set in 1897, will revolve around the blood-drinking vampire from Transylvania who targets residents of London. The 25 best TV shows on Netflix UK - 25 show all The 25 best TV shows on Netflix UK - 1/25 Bojack Horseman A cartoon about a talking horse, starring the goofy older brother from Arrested...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The Walking Dead season 9: Did episode 2 reveal how Maggie will leave the series? - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/the-walking-dead-season-9-episode-3-maggie-lauren-cohan-leave-how-when-georgie-a8584156.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB0NXjofW1r-bol9loWR4OsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 07:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/the-walking-dead-season-9-episode-3-maggie-lauren-cohan-leave-how-when-georgie-a8584156.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Walking Dead season 9: Did episode 2 reveal how Maggie will leave the series?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's a shadow hanging over The Walking Dead season 9 in the form of the forthcoming departures of lead stars Andrew Lincoln and Lauren Cohan. By the time the midseason finale airs in December, both actors will have exited the show although details on what will happen to their characters - Rick Grimes and Maggie Rhee - are currently unclear. While it seems likely that Lincoln is definitively done with the series, a return for Cohan seems more likely - and tonight's episode, titled “The Bridge,” proved just that, One moment sees Maggie taking some much-needed time off from hanging people a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>South Park labels The Simpsons as racist in Brett Kavanaugh episode - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/south-park-simpsons-apu-mr-hankey-brett-kavanaugh-episode-season-22-a8578501.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMhQPjzno1bDitxBF-RBtrQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 09:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/south-park-simpsons-apu-mr-hankey-brett-kavanaugh-episode-season-22-a8578501.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Park labels The Simpsons as racist in Brett Kavanaugh episode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Park has taken aim at The Simpsons in its latest episode, which saw Brett Kavanaugh referenced in the form of famous character, Mr Hankey. Despite maintaining a respectful relationship with its animated rival throughout its 22 seasons, creators Trey Parker and Matt Stone removed the gloves for the latest episode 'The Problem with a Poo' - a play on the title of the documentary The Problem with Apu which detailed how the long-running character, voiced by white actor Hank Azaria, was used as a device to bully stand-up comedian Hari Kondabolu when growing up in New York. The Simpsons was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ozark season 3: Netflix renew Jason Bateman-starring series - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/ozark-season-3-netflix-renew-release-date-jason-bateman-cast-series-a8577871.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBg8YvJUzX-voLlLaLdnCUoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/ozark-season-3-netflix-renew-release-date-jason-bateman-cast-series-a8577871.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ozark season 3: Netflix renew Jason Bateman-starring series&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix has renewed the Jason Bateman-starring series Ozark for a third season. The streaming service has confirmed that the third series will consist of 10 episodes, the same as the first two seasons. Centred on a former accountant who becomes entwined with a dangerous drug cartel, the series has quickly become a favourite among critics and viewers, with one survey finding that the show was the Netflix’s most-watched title during the summer of 2017. A release date for season three has not been announced, but considering season one arrived 21 July, 2017, and season 2 following on 31 August,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The Romanoffs episode 1 review: Mad Men creator's new show opens with a slightly sappy modern-day fairytale - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/reviews/the-romanoffs-season-1-episode-1-amazon-prime-matthew-weiner-hajar-a8578016.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECFTA2TIXOe0f1Kc7GUxF3sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 11:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/reviews/the-romanoffs-season-1-episode-1-amazon-prime-matthew-weiner-hajar-a8578016.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Romanoffs episode 1 review: Mad Men creator's new show opens with a slightly sappy modern-day fairytale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What a great time it is to be making television. Deep-pocketed streaming services are commissioning more shows than one could ever hope to find the time to watch, and the creators of them are rhapsodising – with no small amount of surprise – about the level of control they’re being given. Take this extravagant new approach, add the creator of the revered Mad Men, and you get The Romanoffs: a lavish anthology series in seven languages, revolving around Russian royal family imposters, and with a budget of $70 million. Matthew Weiner’s new drama is a bold and slightly risky proposition, this f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Making a Murderer season 2 trailer: Netflix documentary following Steven Avery's case returns - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/making-a-murderer-season-2-netflix-trailer-start-date-steven-avery-murder-brendan-dassey-a8575966.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN1UKfMhhHsKcM-NZ9evs-4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/making-a-murderer-season-2-netflix-trailer-start-date-steven-avery-murder-brendan-dassey-a8575966.html" target="_blank"&gt;Making a Murderer season 2 trailer: Netflix documentary following Steven Avery's case returns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three years ago, Steven Avery – the salvage yard worker convicted of murdering Teresa Halbach ​– became an internationally recognised name thanks to Making a Murderer. Everyone who watched the acclaimed Netflix series had an opinion on Avery’s case, some people finding believing him to be guilty, others being swayed by the series. Since then, the case has moved on. Attorney Kathleen Zellner has begun representing Avery, hoping to overturn the conviction. Brendan Dasey, who was also convicted, was almost freed before his appeal was overturned. Making a Murderer’s second season will document ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Black Mirror season 5: New series will feature 'choose your own adventure' episode - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/black-mirror-season-5-netflix-start-date-interactive-episode-charlie-brooker-a8566231.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFfbhtU_xdxo9JHUHwUJIj8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 10:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/black-mirror-season-5-netflix-start-date-interactive-episode-charlie-brooker-a8566231.html" target="_blank"&gt;Black Mirror season 5: New series will feature 'choose your own adventure' episode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A “choose-your-own-adventure” episode of the Netflix series Black Mirror is reportedly on its way. Plot details are scarce, though Bloomberg says the episode will be part of the show’s fifth season, which is expected to debut before the end of 2018. Netflix has experimented with interactive episodes of television before, but only on children’s shows such as the Shrek spin-off Puss in Boots and animated series Buddy Thunderstruck. Those behind the streaming service hope to expand the feature into more adult television – starting with Black Mirror – in the near future. The 25 best TV shows on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The Crown episode Queen Elizabeth 'hated' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/the-crown-queen-elizabeth-netflix-prince-philip-charles-school-season-2-a8557711.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO4eGuq5bYWzJOa_OtTtrNwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 11:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/the-crown-queen-elizabeth-netflix-prince-philip-charles-school-season-2-a8557711.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Crown episode Queen Elizabeth 'hated'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Queen Elizabeth was reportedly left “sad and annoyed” by one particular episode of Netflix's hit series The Crown. The offending scene appears in the second season's ninth episode, titled "Paterfamilias", in which the Queen is shown arguing with Prince Philip about which school to send Prince Charles to. They eventually settle on Philip's old education centre Gordonstoun School, despite the Queen's preference of Eton. Later in the episode, viewers see Charles subjected to tough school life, including running in the bitter cold, receiving no sympathy from his father. - Read more The Crown se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Stranger Things star Millie Bobby Brown says Drake texts her 'boy advice' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/drake-millie-bobby-brown-texting-age-gap-stranger-things-emmys-2018-a8544406.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPrMhOJcnn4kkp8XgTMRH48qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 09:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/drake-millie-bobby-brown-texting-age-gap-stranger-things-emmys-2018-a8544406.html" target="_blank"&gt;Stranger Things star Millie Bobby Brown says Drake texts her 'boy advice'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stranger Things star Millie Bobby Brown has revealed that she gets advice "about boys" from her friend Drake. Asked about Drake, who is 31, during a red carpet interview for the Emmy Awards in LA, the 14-year-old actress revealed that she and Drake have formed a friendship after meeting in Australia. "We just texted each other and he was like, 'I miss you so much' and I was like 'I miss you too!'" she told Access Hollywood. Asked about what advice he gives her she replied: "About boys, he helps me" but added any detail "stays in the text messages". Brown met Drake when he attended the Brisb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Emmys 2018: Claire Foy and Thandie Newton among winners on night of British success - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/emmys-2018-claire-foy-thandie-newton-crown-stranger-things-westworld-black-mirror-a8544086.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIxnH2jNfEVx14jelEkGv00qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 23:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/emmys-2018-claire-foy-thandie-newton-crown-stranger-things-westworld-black-mirror-a8544086.html" target="_blank"&gt;Emmys 2018: Claire Foy and Thandie Newton among winners on night of British success&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claire Foy, Thandie Newton and Charlie Brooker were among the winners on a triumphant night for Britons at the Emmys. Amazon’s The Marvelous Mrs Maisel also won bigat the most prestigious awards in US television, scooping five prizes in quick succession in a ceremony which demonstrated the growing strength of streaming services. It was the first streamed series to win the Emmy for best comedy. - Read more The 7 most heartwarming Emmy moments The Marvelous Mrs Maisel, which features a housewife in 1950s New York City who discovers she has a talent for stand-up comedy, scooped further prizes ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Emmy nominee Millie Bobby Brown rises above the online hate - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/83a047862b1344be88efca7719ae2c90</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE1433xuOWvFBpX0Lu1gziQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 18:06:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/83a047862b1344be88efca7719ae2c90" target="_blank"&gt;Emmy nominee Millie Bobby Brown rises above the online hate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Emmy nominee Millie Bobby Brown continues to show wisdom beyond her years. The 14-year old "Stranger Things" star is no stranger to social media trolls. She hopes young people can "rise above the hate" and "not let anyone change you." Earlier this summer, Brown deactivated her Twitter account after being harassed online. She no longer looks at online comments and remains active on Instagram. Brown received a supporting actress nod for her role as Eleven in "Stranger Things." Though the Netflix series won't return until next summer, Brown provided a shred about the third seas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Stranger Things star Charlie Heaton to play Elephant Man in BBC drama - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/elephant-man-charlie-heaton-stranger-things-bbc-joseph-merrick-a8502191.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIFfBF193zjpx7nsl8EBClgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 09:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/elephant-man-charlie-heaton-stranger-things-bbc-joseph-merrick-a8502191.html" target="_blank"&gt;Stranger Things star Charlie Heaton to play Elephant Man in BBC drama&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The extraordinary life of Joseph Merrick, better known as "The Elephant Man", will be brought to the screen once more, thanks to a new BBC drama. The role has been tackled by major names in the past: Bernard Pomerance's 1979 play The Elephant Man has seen the likes of David Bowie, Mark Hamill, and Bradley Cooper in the role of Merrick, with John Hurt also memorably starring in David Lynch's 1980 film of the same name. However, the task now comes down to Stranger Things' own Charlie Heaton, in a two-part drama that marks a fresh take on Merrick's legacy, written by Neil McKay. - Read more St...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Stranger Things season 3 release date delayed - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/stranger-things-season-3-release-date-delayed-netflix-2019-a8469266.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZGZdevU6BNzLvEjeXbapYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 08:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/stranger-things-season-3-release-date-delayed-netflix-2019-a8469266.html" target="_blank"&gt;Stranger Things season 3 release date delayed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wait for the third season of Stranger Things just got a little longer. Netflix programming executive Cindy Holland has confirmed that the science-fiction smash will return next Summer, rather than early next year as presumed by fans. “It’s a handcrafted show,” Holland said, speaking at the Television Critics Association’s press tour, according to EW. “[Showrunnners] The Duffer Brothers and Shawn Levy, they understand the stakes are high. They want to deliver something bigger and better than last year. I think it’s going to be a fantastic season. It will be worth the wait.” Holland also ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Stranger Things,' other terrors at Universal for Halloween - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/74b5c9ae18f849d0835c7f63cbbc3833</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB2Odbcr-qvhIpnTBCCyuA4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 20:12:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/74b5c9ae18f849d0835c7f63cbbc3833" target="_blank"&gt;'Stranger Things,' other terrors at Universal for Halloween&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — You won't have to travel to Hawkins, Indiana, to visit the Upside Down. Universal Studios' theme parks in Orlando, Los Angeles and Singapore are bringing the scary dimension from Netflix's "Stranger Things" to their Halloween Horror Nights. Each park will have a "Stranger Things" maze complete with a Demogorgon creature to terrify visitors from September through early November. The "Stranger Things" maze is one of several haunted houses at the parks' Halloween Horror Nights fright fests. For the first time, the Orlando park will have 10 houses, several recalling slasher...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>All the Netflix news that you need to know from its summer critics presentation - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90210688/all-the-netflix-news-that-you-need-to-know-from-its-summer-critics-presentation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECB35gse7syPZQTd0RijRiAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 13:00:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90210688/all-the-netflix-news-that-you-need-to-know-from-its-summer-critics-presentation" target="_blank"&gt;All the Netflix news that you need to know from its summer critics presentation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You won’t see some giant volume play,” new Amazon Studio chief Jennifer Salke said of her streaming strategy during a Television Critics Association panel last week. “I think of us as an alternative to some of those places.” By “some of those places,” of course, Salke was referring to Netflix, the current king of streamers, whose approach famously involves releasing an almost oppressive amount of content on a weekly basis. In 2017, Netflix chief creative officer Ted Sarandos announced the company would be spending somewhere between $7 billion and $8 billion on programming for the following...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Netflix Exec Breaks Silence Over Aziz Ansari Controversy: ‘Happy’ to Keep Making ‘Master of None’ - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/netflix-exec-breaks-silence-over-aziz-ansari-controversy-happy-to-keep-making-master-of-none</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF5bvabeG_jUq-SuMubWPVsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 21:07:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/netflix-exec-breaks-silence-over-aziz-ansari-controversy-happy-to-keep-making-master-of-none" target="_blank"&gt;Netflix Exec Breaks Silence Over Aziz Ansari Controversy: ‘Happy’ to Keep Making ‘Master of None’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix Beverly Hills, CALIFORNIA — “I don’t have anything to share with you today.” That was the most common refrain from Netflix vice president of original series Cindy Holland as TV critics and journalists grilled her about some of the biggest names the streaming service recently wooed, including the Obamas and black-ish creator Kenya Barris. With respect to Barack and Michelle Obama, who signed a deal in May to produce shows and deals for Netflix, Holland said it is too early in the deal to have an update on what their content might look like. When the deal was announced, it was vaguely...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>How the ingredients of Netflix’s success could trigger its downfall - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/features/netflix-hit-tv-streaming-subscribers-drop-share-value-a8450701.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO6Z9rBKcyxVqRjCQ3XtqS0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/features/netflix-hit-tv-streaming-subscribers-drop-share-value-a8450701.html" target="_blank"&gt;How the ingredients of Netflix’s success could trigger its downfall&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Panic gripped Netflix on Monday. Its shares dropped 13 per cent overnight after the streaming giant posted disappointing results for the first half of the year. When this is the reaction to adding five million subscribers in three months – taking your total to 130 million across the world – it certainly tells you something. In the past 12 months the company’s stock skyrocketed from $158 (£121) to $396, light years ahead of the market index S&amp;P 500’s average. This was partly driven by a stellar quarterly earnings report in April, which raised analysts’ and investors’ expectations about wheth...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Stranger Things 3’ Teaser Reveals New Character, Setting And Possible Release Date - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/stranger-things-3-teaser-reveals-new-character-setting-and-possible-release-date_us_5b4ce6b6e4b0bc69a78a3685</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcXQE_vZT9TOkWZnI_kGWIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 22:54:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/stranger-things-3-teaser-reveals-new-character-setting-and-possible-release-date_us_5b4ce6b6e4b0bc69a78a3685" target="_blank"&gt;'Stranger Things 3’ Teaser Reveals New Character, Setting And Possible Release Date&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hawkins, Indiana, is about to get a rad new addition. On Monday Netflix released a teaser for the third season of “Stranger Things” in the form of a totally ’80s commercial for the new Starcourt Mall — “one of the finest shopping facilities in America and beyond.” Ahoy! Something is coming... to Hawkins, Indiana! pic.twitter.com/BI4wFRVzvB — Stranger Things (@Stranger_Things) July 16, 2018 According to the nearly 90-second video, the new mall “opens next summer” —a possible hint that the show’s third season will be released in summer 2019. Among the attractions at the town’s tubular new spo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Stranger Things season 3 teaser reveals ultra-'80s new location - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/stranger-things-series-3-trailer-teaser-starcourt-mall-steve-harrington-robin-location-a8449966.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB9pKn3zdrYodhlc0EC701IqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 15:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/stranger-things-series-3-trailer-teaser-starcourt-mall-steve-harrington-robin-location-a8449966.html" target="_blank"&gt;Stranger Things season 3 teaser reveals ultra-'80s new location&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stranger Things season 3 is venturing into new territory, though not too far from home. The latest teaser for the hit Netflix show centres on a new setting, Starcourt Mall, thanks to a delightfully retro, ‘80s-style fake commercial highlighting all the delights on offer. The Gap! A food court! Sam Goody! A large fountain! It also gives us a glimpse at what Steve Harrington (Joe Keery) is up to; namely, working in an ice cream store called Scoops Ahoy, alongside new character Robin (Maya Hawke). Read more - See the full list of winners from the 2018 MTV Movie &amp; TV Awards - Stranger Things pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The Secret of Marrowbone review – plot holes the diameter of Jupiter - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/jul/13/the-secret-of-marrowbone-review</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPvUZU0UR8VjGYHyyFvoSM0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 07:00:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/jul/13/the-secret-of-marrowbone-review" target="_blank"&gt;The Secret of Marrowbone review – plot holes the diameter of Jupiter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s rare to get such a strong taste of turkey with Christmas so far off – unusual to get that piercing tang of cranberry sauce without a double-issue of the Radio Times to hand. This distinctively terrible film is a hideous hotchpotch of shouty overacting and muddled storytelling, unable to make up its mind if it’s a family drama, a supernatural chiller or a psychological mystery. It’s got plot holes the diameter of the planet Jupiter and is abjectly reliant on narrative elements which have to be initially withheld under cover of a clunking “six months later” transition, and then disclosed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Tiffany Haddish and more react to their Emmy nominations - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/12/entertainment/emmy-nominations-reactions-2018/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJDgdfwyC8teuZZ_MzFEsH0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 21:11:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/12/entertainment/emmy-nominations-reactions-2018/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tiffany Haddish and more react to their Emmy nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nominations for the 70th Primetime Emmy Awards were announced Thursday morning and the nominees are feeling the love. Here's a roundup of some of the best reactions: Jeff Daniels, outstanding limited Series for "Godless" "My genuine gratitude to the Emmy Voters. 'GODLESS' was Scott Frank's triumph. Thrilled to be a part of it. Plus I got to ride a horse." Sarah Paulson, outstanding lead actress in a limited series or TV movie for "American Horror Story: Cult" "I am incredibly honored to have been recognized by the Television Academy, and want to thank Ryan Murphy and the entire cast and cre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>How 'Stranger Things' helps Eggo sales - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2018/06/20/stranger-things-eggo-sales-orig.cnnmoney</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOP0vO4Nl13gYT43dQwzTSEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 21:55:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2018/06/20/stranger-things-eggo-sales-orig.cnnmoney" target="_blank"&gt;How 'Stranger Things' helps Eggo sales&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the popularity of Netflix's "Stranger Things," sales of Eggo waffles have gotten a boost. But one analyst says the gap between seasons has sent some Eggo sales to the upside down. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Netflix Teams With Dark Horse To Bring 'Stranger Things' To Comics - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/robsalkowitz/2018/06/19/netflix-teams-with-dark-horse-to-bring-stranger-things-to-comics/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG85vD1sGshzlk8c88ByYgkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 17:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/robsalkowitz/2018/06/19/netflix-teams-with-dark-horse-to-bring-stranger-things-to-comics/" target="_blank"&gt;Netflix Teams With Dark Horse To Bring 'Stranger Things' To Comics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dark Horse Comics will adapt the hit Netflix series Stranger Things starting in fall, 2018. The breakout Netflix series Stranger Things has kept fans spellbound through two seasons with its mixture of supernatural suspense and skillful evocation of cheesy 1980s popcorn movie ambiance. Now Netflix is bringing the extended story world of Stranger Things to comics through a multi-year partnership with top-tier independent publisher Dark Horse Comics, announced yesterday. The agreement calls for Dark Horse to publish a line of comics and graphic novels expanding the world of Hawkins, Indiana an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>MTV Movie &amp; TV Awards 2018 winners: Stranger Things and Black Panther dominate - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/mtv-movie-tv-awards-2018-winners-black-panther-stranger-things-a8405521.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECbqldXMVq60Timm5dANRRgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 08:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/mtv-movie-tv-awards-2018-winners-black-panther-stranger-things-a8405521.html" target="_blank"&gt;MTV Movie &amp; TV Awards 2018 winners: Stranger Things and Black Panther dominate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black Panther and Stranger Things dominated the 2018 MTV Movie &amp; TV Awards with widespread Wakanda pride and '80s nostalgia as Black Panther won the most film awards and Stranger Things took home the most prizes in television. Black Panther took home four awards, including Best Movie, and actor Chadwick Boseman earned two trophies for Best Hero and Best Movie Performance. Boseman even gave his Best Hero award to real-life hero James Shaw Jr., who fought off a gunman at the Tennessee Waffle House shooting earlier this year. - Read more Black Panther's Chadwick Boseman gives MTV Award to Waff...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Westworld: Top 10 science-fiction shows to try next as season 2 draws to a close - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/westword-season-2-best-sci-fi-shows-star-trek-doctor-who-x-files-a8408031.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtMEx4kVdhw4SCgm1rk7akqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 07:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/westword-season-2-best-sci-fi-shows-star-trek-doctor-who-x-files-a8408031.html" target="_blank"&gt;Westworld: Top 10 science-fiction shows to try next as season 2 draws to a close&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the second series of HBO's acclaimed science-fiction series Westworld draws to a close, fans are already bracing themselves for the withdrawal symptoms. But never fear, here's our guide to 10 alternative shows you could try to stave off the cold turkey. 10. Stranger Things (2016-) Netflix's acclaimed series from the Duffer Brothers, packed with 80s nostalgia and drawing on the teen-centric adventures of early Stephen Spielberg and Stephen King, absolutely lives up to the (considerable) hype. Seamlessly merging extraterrestrial horror with coming-of-age drama, the tale of a group of frien...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Stranger Things' star leaves Twitter - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2018/06/15/millie-bobby-brown-twitter-cyberbullying.hln</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMJafVTrwkzY389bNKGgDoUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 08:34:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2018/06/15/millie-bobby-brown-twitter-cyberbullying.hln" target="_blank"&gt;'Stranger Things' star leaves Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Stranger Things" actress Millie Bobby Brown has deactivated her Twitter account after becoming the target of a cruel hashtag and meme. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Millie Bobby Brown quits Twitter after being turned into an 'anti-gay' meme - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/millie-bobby-brown-twitter-deleted-anti-gay-meme-homophobic-stranger-things-a8398101.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAxLCv3nrNu7yxE1sXivXxwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 08:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/millie-bobby-brown-twitter-deleted-anti-gay-meme-homophobic-stranger-things-a8398101.html" target="_blank"&gt;Millie Bobby Brown quits Twitter after being turned into an 'anti-gay' meme&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stranger Things star Millie Bobby Brown has quit Twitter after she was made the subject of a bizarre series of memes. The 14-year-old actor appears to have left the social media platform in reaction to hundreds of posts that misattributed homophobic or racist comments to her. Brown has been a vocal advocate of LGBT+ rights for some time. According to Vulture, the meme was first shared by members of the LGBT+ community in an apparent attempt at satirical humour; however the theme was quickly adopted by mainstream social media users. Stranger Things 2 in pictures - 5 show all Stranger Things ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Millie Bobby Brown deletes Twitter account over memes - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/32a86282f6ef4b5eb3c146dd1de95976</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKKbEnyyYd9NCQ-4YEBNTVkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 11:45:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/32a86282f6ef4b5eb3c146dd1de95976" target="_blank"&gt;Millie Bobby Brown deletes Twitter account over memes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — "Stranger Things" actress Millie Bobby Brown has deleted her Twitter account after users posted memes depicting her as homophobic. The memes featured photos of the 14-year-old with homophobic slurs. It is not clear why she was targeted. The actress' publicist did not immediately respond to an email seeking comment Thursday. Brown has been a supporter of LGBTQ rights and created a secondary Twitter account Milliestopshate last summer that remains active. Brown is set to return for the third season of the Netflix series.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Black Panther star gives his MTV Award away to a 'real hero' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/2018/06/19/black-panther-triumphs-mtvmovie-tv-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBugnOfbg2JBG9R01ZEGNsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDf2rcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 06:44:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/2018/06/19/black-panther-triumphs-mtvmovie-tv-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Panther star gives his MTV Award away to a 'real hero'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The MTV Movie &amp; TV Awards gave Black Panther its first taste of awards glory, with Marvel's blockbuster taking home four honours including two awards for its star, Chadwick Boseman. Boseman quickly handed off his best hero award to James Shaw Jr, who wrestled an assault-style rifle away from a gunman in a Tennessee Waffle House in April. "This is going to live at your house," Boseman told Shaw, giving him the show's golden popcorn award. The actor said while it was an honour to be recognized for playing a superhero, it was more important to "acknowledge the heroes we have in real life." Bos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Millie Bobby Brown leaves Twitter amid cyberbullying - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/14/entertainment/millie-bobby-brown-twitter/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPHX2jKUq-9oTt3oIHRM04UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 17:34:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/14/entertainment/millie-bobby-brown-twitter/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Millie Bobby Brown leaves Twitter amid cyberbullying&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Millie Bobby Brown has deactivated her Twitter account after becoming the target of a cruel hashtag and meme. The 14 year-old "Stranger Things" star deleted her @milliebbrown account Wednesday. The hashtag #TakeDownMillieBobbyBrown started last year, according to one Twitter user, when someone claimed in a tweet that the actress refused to take a picture with her unless she removed her hijab. When the woman refused, she alleges Brown then pulled off the hijab for her. There is no evidence the incident actually occurred. The hashtag was used to spread stories -- many of them with outrageous ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Stranger Things: Millie Bobby Brown wants Leonardo DiCaprio to play her long-lost brother - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/stranger-things-millie-bobby-brown-leonardo-dicaprio-brother-casting-a8360211.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK4YVGdk6DT2PBwfp_RyjhoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 12:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/stranger-things-millie-bobby-brown-leonardo-dicaprio-brother-casting-a8360211.html" target="_blank"&gt;Stranger Things: Millie Bobby Brown wants Leonardo DiCaprio to play her long-lost brother&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Millie Bobby Brown has an idea for the perfect guest role for an upcoming season of Stranger Things: Oscar winner Leonardo DiCaprio. She told the Press Association she’d love to see DiCaprio on the show as “Eleven’s long-lost brother”, adding: “I have already made a storyline. Leo, if you want to be in Stranger Things, here’s the contract.” Season 3 of the show will already have its fair share of celebrity guest stars: Cary Elwes and Jake Busey will feature as the mayor of Hawkins, Indiana and a morally questionable journalist for The Hawkins Post. Read more - Cary Elwes and Jake Busey join...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>‘Stranger Things’ Announces Season 3 Now In Production With A Cool, New Teaser - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/stranger-things-3-announces-its-now-in-production-with-a-cool-new-teaser_us_5ae35cc8e4b04aa23f22f815</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVv9Zd8JmmI0_6MnVUmOlEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 19:25:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/stranger-things-3-announces-its-now-in-production-with-a-cool-new-teaser_us_5ae35cc8e4b04aa23f22f815" target="_blank"&gt;‘Stranger Things’ Announces Season 3 Now In Production With A Cool, New Teaser&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here ya go, nerds! Netflix turned “Stranger Things” fans’ emotions upside down Friday when it announced that the third season is now in production by releasing a behind-the-scenes teaser. The video shows the series’ established stars and a few newcomers sitting down for a table read. It also features fan-favorite Erica, played by Priah Ferguson, who we can expect to get a bigger role in the series. Joining the cast for season three are a few notable and exciting names joining the cast including Cary Elwes Of “The Princess Bride” fame, Jake Busey who slayed an electric violin performance in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Millie Bobby Brown becomes youngest person ever on Time 100 list - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/millie-bobby-brown-time-100-list-stranger-things-influence-youngest-person-ever-a8313671.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJNYyQ3zlE59D9Xl9lEDOr0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 09:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/millie-bobby-brown-time-100-list-stranger-things-influence-youngest-person-ever-a8313671.html" target="_blank"&gt;Millie Bobby Brown becomes youngest person ever on Time 100 list&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Millie Bobby Brown has become the youngest person ever to be included on Time magazine's list of the world's most 100 influential people. With good reason: the 14-year-old star of Stranger Things has not only become a global name thanks to her role as the enigmatic, super-powered Eleven, but has mastered an ability to control and shape her own career and work. She's set to become one of the youngest Hollywood stars ever to land a producer credit on a feature film, working on an adaptation of Nancy Springer's Enola Holmes Mysteries, recounting the adventures of Sherlock Holmes' younger siste...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Stranger Things' Creators Accused Of Stealing Netflix Show's Concept - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/legalentertainment/2018/04/19/stranger-things-creators-accused-of-stealing-netflix-shows-concept/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIDwt0ZYAvH7Smy_gVWjwWoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/legalentertainment/2018/04/19/stranger-things-creators-accused-of-stealing-netflix-shows-concept/" target="_blank"&gt;'Stranger Things' Creators Accused Of Stealing Netflix Show's Concept&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES, CA – JANUARY 05: Ross Duffer and Matt Duffer attend the 18th Annual AFI Awards at Four Seasons Hotel Los Angeles at Beverly Hills on January 5, 2018 in Los Angeles, California. (Photo by Frazer Harrison/Getty Images for AFI) The Duffer Brothers, creators of the massively successful Netflix series “Stranger Things,” are being sued by filmmaker Charlie Kessler for allegedly stealing the idea of the show from his 2012 short film “Montauk” and script “The Montauk Project.” Allegedly, Kessler pitched the concept to the brothers in 2014 and, coincidentally, when Netflix first announc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Time 100: Stranger Things' Millie Bobby Brown becomes youngest person to be named on list - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/2018/04/19/time-100-stranger-things-millie-bobby-brown-becomes-youngest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBNytpaFOO79MoQy2qaYBMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDf2rcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 09:59:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/2018/04/19/time-100-stranger-things-millie-bobby-brown-becomes-youngest/" target="_blank"&gt;Time 100: Stranger Things' Millie Bobby Brown becomes youngest person to be named on list&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stranger Things star Millie Bobby Brown has become the youngest person to be named by Time magazine as one of its 100 most influential people of 2018. The 14-year-old British actress is enjoying a meteoric rise in Hollywood after rising to fame with her role as Eleven in the popular sci-fi TV show. US actor Aaron Paul called her an "extraordinary" actress. "She may have been 12 in years, but her spirit and mind were timeless," Paul wrote in a profile of Brown for the magazine, speaking of first meeting the teenager in New York. "A wise woman was speaking from her cherubic face. "It was like...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Cary Elwes Of ‘The Princess Bride’ To Join ‘Stranger Things’ Season 3 - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cary-elwes-of-the-princess-bride-to-join-stranger-things-season-3_us_5ad7a140e4b029ebe0209029</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENL3gR1JmtMg6LmZ1CRiuS8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 21:38:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cary-elwes-of-the-princess-bride-to-join-stranger-things-season-3_us_5ad7a140e4b029ebe0209029" target="_blank"&gt;Cary Elwes Of ‘The Princess Bride’ To Join ‘Stranger Things’ Season 3&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Did you want to see another famous face from the ’80s in the next season of “Stranger Things”? As you wish. Cary Elwes, who played Wesley in the beloved 1987 fantasy adventure film “The Princess Bride,” has signed on for the third season of Netflix’s sci-fi smash, the streaming service announced Wednesday. The 55-year-old actor will play Mayor Kline, a character described as “handsome, slick and sleazy” and a “classic ’80s politician” who cares more about himself than the fictional town of Hawkins, Indiana, that he governs. Since his swashbuckling turn as the Dread Pirate Roberts, Elwes sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item></channel></rss>