<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Ariana Grande - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRGxuYTJSNU5CSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:31:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Even for young, socially aware readers, there is such a thing as too woke - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/wokeness-pc-minorities-left-wing-snowflake-campaign-brand-baby-its-cold-outside-ariana-grande-latest-a8673691.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG2swdvtIJeqVqfY-Z1_PM8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/wokeness-pc-minorities-left-wing-snowflake-campaign-brand-baby-its-cold-outside-ariana-grande-latest-a8673691.html" target="_blank"&gt;Even for young, socially aware readers, there is such a thing as too woke&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Too woke, or not too woke, that is the question. Shakespeare might find more profound issues to ponder if he were alive today, but that’s hardly going to stop me. If you’re looking at your screen in a confused manner, “woke” is an adjective, a verb and an outlook. The political term refers to a perceived awareness of social justice issues, particularly those affecting minority groups. The expression “stay woke" originated in African-American culture and its widespread use since 2014 is a result of the Black Lives Matter movement. A typical example of “wokeness” is an acknowledgement or unde...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>This year’s Spotify and YouTube stats reveal how little we value female work - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/youtube-spotify-2018-highest-paid-stars-vloggers-women-gender-jake-paul-zoe-sugg-a8672916.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED0wANxSN519fqvlJoKDxkEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/youtube-spotify-2018-highest-paid-stars-vloggers-women-gender-jake-paul-zoe-sugg-a8672916.html" target="_blank"&gt;This year’s Spotify and YouTube stats reveal how little we value female work&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to feel sorry for Ariana Grande, Taylor Swift or Zoe Sugg for being just that tiny bit less successful than their male counterparts, isn’t it? After all, what’s a few million pounds for people who live in mansions, fly first class and sell out live shows within minutes? Not much, on the face of it. But it speaks a lot to the world we live in. This week, two lists were released: the highest paid YouTube stars and the most streamed artists on Spotify. They have two things in common: firstly, that they offer a slice of the entertainment zeitgeist of 2018; secondly, that they are comp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande On Love Life: 'I Really Have No Idea What The F**k I’m Doing' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-billboard-speech_us_5c0a53fbe4b0b6cdaf5df976</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENAwAFPn1kmbDzzdk_86WAgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:39:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-billboard-speech_us_5c0a53fbe4b0b6cdaf5df976" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande On Love Life: 'I Really Have No Idea What The F**k I’m Doing'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande offered a harsh assessment of her love life on Thursday. “I really have no idea what the fuck I’m doing,” she admitted at Billboard’s Women In Music event in New York City. She said she’s trying to redirect some of “the love and forgiveness that I’ve given away so frivolously and easily to men” to herself. In her speech to receive the Woman of the Year award, which can be seen in the clip above, the “thank u, next” singer said she has her professional act together. Offstage, not so much. “I want to say that I find it interesting that this has been one of the best years of my c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>After a year full of tears, Ariana Grande comes out on top - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/cbb687ca6a1f41049b993ffbdbbddfd3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECsZNn4Qccgov5StaPqSiZoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:57:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/cbb687ca6a1f41049b993ffbdbbddfd3" target="_blank"&gt;After a year full of tears, Ariana Grande comes out on top&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ariana Grande capped off a successful year as a pop star — but a trying one as a maturing young woman — at the 13th annual Billboard Women in Music event, where she was named Woman of the Year. The 25-year-old singer was teary-eyed at times during her acceptance speech as she reflected on her year, which included the end of her relationship with comedian-actor Pete Davidson and the death of her former boyfriend, the rapper Mac Miller. Last year, a bombing at her concert in Manchester, England killed 22 people. "I want to say that I find it interesting that this has been one ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Drake and Lamar lead but women shine through in Grammy nods - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-grammys-nominations/drake-and-lamar-lead-but-women-shine-through-in-grammy-nods-idUSKBN1O61LJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOZzcHmAdaGSEzl12SKoc2YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:48:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-grammys-nominations/drake-and-lamar-lead-but-women-shine-through-in-grammy-nods-idUSKBN1O61LJ" target="_blank"&gt;Drake and Lamar lead but women shine through in Grammy nods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rappers Kendrick Lamar and Drake led Grammy Award nominations on Friday, but Cardi B, Lady Gaga, Brandi Carlile and American newcomer H.E.R helped make it a female-dominated line-up for the year's top prizes in the music industry. Ten-time Grammy winner Taylor Swift, Beyonce, Ariana Grande and Camila Cabello were among the biggest snubs in top categories that were dominated by hip-hop and R&amp;B. Canada's Drake, the most-streamed artist of 2018, won eight nominations, including album of the year for "Scorpion," and both song and record of the year for his single "God's Plan." Five of the expan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Grammy nominations 2019: Cardi B, Kendrick Lamar and Drake lead the pack - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/dec/07/grammy-nominations-2019-cardi-b-kendrick-lamar-drake-lead</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIlVuvKfjcfFvCwBWElA-EUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:31:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/dec/07/grammy-nominations-2019-cardi-b-kendrick-lamar-drake-lead" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy nominations 2019: Cardi B, Kendrick Lamar and Drake lead the pack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After controversy about the Grammys’ failure to recognise women’s achievements at the 2018 ceremony, female artists dominate key categories in the nominations for the 2019 awards. Country stars Maren Morris and Kacey Musgraves, rapper Cardi B, pop futurist Janelle Monáe and Lady Gaga could all take home major awards at the 61st Grammy award ceremony in Los Angeles next February. Elsewhere, Kendrick Lamar and Drake dominate proceedings, with eight and seven nominations respectively. Along with Childish Gambino, AKA Donald Glover, they could rectify the other dispute that emerged from this ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>James Corden channels Ariana Grande for Thank U, Jeff video paying homage to Jeff Goldblum - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/james-corden-thank-u-jeff-goldbum-ariana-grande-parody-video-watch-late-show-cbs-a8669866.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEJ3bZhN8fKhB70QV5SSRlUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/james-corden-thank-u-jeff-goldbum-ariana-grande-parody-video-watch-late-show-cbs-a8669866.html" target="_blank"&gt;James Corden channels Ariana Grande for Thank U, Jeff video paying homage to Jeff Goldblum&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;James Corden has shared a parody of Ariana Grande's hit single "thank u, next", which pays tribute to Jurassic Park star Jeff Goldblum. The Late Late Show host opened the skit by walking into Goldblum's dressing room and profusely thanking him. The opening notes to Grande's song then begin and the scene cuts to Corden in the bedroom from the film Mean Girls, looking through a book showing pictures of Goldblum in his various roles. Read more - Ariana Grande responds to Pete Davidson's post on online bullying - Rebel Wilson joins cast of Cats movie adaptation starring Taylor Swift - James Cor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Grammy nominations: Three talking points, from album of the year snubs to new artist contenders - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/grammy-nominations-list-kendrick-lamar-drake-best-album-snubs-taylor-swift-ariana-grande-a8672541.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHx1sqcDkw5eJYdFAOETdjsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/grammy-nominations-list-kendrick-lamar-drake-best-album-snubs-taylor-swift-ariana-grande-a8672541.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy nominations: Three talking points, from album of the year snubs to new artist contenders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nominees for the 2019 Grammy Awards were announced this afternoon, with Cardi B, Kacey Musgraves and Janelle Monae amongst the nominees for the most prestigious category: Album of the Year. Here are the biggest talking points ahead of the ceremony, which takes place in Los Angeles on 10 February. 1) The Albums of the Year category is one of the strongest in years Janelle Monae (PA) There have been some questionable winners in the Album of the Year category of late. Last year, Bruno Mars’s 24K Magic beat out Kendrick Lamar, Lorde and Childish Gambino, all of whom made arguably better alb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Grindr's LGBTQ News Site Apologizes For Controversial Ariana Grande Critique - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/grindr-into-ariana-grande-critique_us_5c07d5b2e4b0680a7ecb1942</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN9p-rl-WbBbwjgT0Wos9WUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:54:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/grindr-into-ariana-grande-critique_us_5c07d5b2e4b0680a7ecb1942" target="_blank"&gt;Grindr's LGBTQ News Site Apologizes For Controversial Ariana Grande Critique&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A digital news site owned by the gay dating app Grindr has apologized after running a controversial critique of Ariana Grande’s “thank u, next” video that sparked online vitriol and alleged threats of violence against the writer. Zach Stafford, who is the editor-in-chief of Grindr’s INTO, issued a statement Tuesday saying he was “personally sorry” for having allowed his team to publish the widely derided article that appeared on the site a day prior. “We as editors failed the writer by not working with her to ensure the piece met our standards,” Stafford wrote. “Moving forward, I am working...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Bests Adele to Fastest 100 Million Views - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/grande-s-thank-u-next-bests-adele-to-fastest-100-million-views/4686757.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM0128FPNiLduT73tRsNK_4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwmp0i</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:38:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/grande-s-thank-u-next-bests-adele-to-fastest-100-million-views/4686757.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Bests Adele to Fastest 100 Million Views&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande's breakup anthem "Thank U, Next" has become the fastest music video to reach 100 million views, video hosting service Vevo said on Tuesday. The single, released after the 25-year-old singer's much publicized breakup with fiance Pete Davidson, has also topped the Billboard charts for three weeks, giving Grande the biggest hit of her seven-year career. Vevo said the "Thank U, Next" video, in which Grande recreates scenes from popular women's empowerment movies "Legally Blonde" and "Mean Girls," reached 100 million views in under four days following its Nov. 30 release. The previ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Meet Hannah Lux Davis, The Record-Breaking Director Behind "Thank U, Next" - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/janeclairehervey/2018/12/04/meet-hannah-lux-davis-the-record-breaking-director-behind-thank-u-next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF0xFHV28Ze0UrKdmJJNt8QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/janeclairehervey/2018/12/04/meet-hannah-lux-davis-the-record-breaking-director-behind-thank-u-next/" target="_blank"&gt;Meet Hannah Lux Davis, The Record-Breaking Director Behind "Thank U, Next"&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s it like to shatter two records on YouTube? Music video director Hannah Lux Davis can tell you. Over five days, the long-time creative’s latest project with pop singer Ariana Grande, the music video for “Thank U, Next,” has swept the Internet with more than 100 million views, breaking YouTube’s record for most-watched video premiere and most viewers within 24 hours (50.3 million, to be exact). With clever 2000s references, sourced from feature films like “Mean Girls,” “Legally Blonde” and “Thirteen Going on Thirty,” as well as casual subplots around Ariana Grande’s recent break-ups an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Grammy nominations 2019 could be surprising - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/grammy-nominations-2019-look-ahead/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECAIW7IXMZSqhvCtgSndL3sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:41:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/grammy-nominations-2019-look-ahead/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy nominations 2019 could be surprising&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We may not know who will be nominated, but there's already controversy over who won't be. Both Cardi B and Post Malone have had breakout years in music, but neither is eligible to be nominated in the best new artist category at the Grammys. Nominations will be announced Friday, but it was reported months ago that the pair had been knocked out of new-artist contention -- Cardi, because her nominations last year disqualified her, and Post Malone, because Recording Academy voters reportedly decided he didn't fit the requirements for new artists. Jason Lipshutz, editorial director at Billboard,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Pop goes the fantasy: how Vox Lux shows the darker side of music - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/05/vox-lux-natalie-portman-brady-corbet-analysis</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZaL3tYWj3af26fFz2JJPgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/dec/05/vox-lux-natalie-portman-brady-corbet-analysis" target="_blank"&gt;Pop goes the fantasy: how Vox Lux shows the darker side of music&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who’d be a pop star, eh? If there’s one thing we’ve learned from cinema in 2018 – A Star is Born, Vox Lux, even the PG-rated neutering of Freddie Mercury’s legend in Bohemian Rhapsody – it’s that the gleaming lights of the music industry can emit a pretty harsh glow when you’re under them, that the warm embrace of a crowd can turn to a stranglehold in the blink of a heavily made-up eye. That fame comes at a price is, admittedly, not the hottest of takes: in the movies, it goes back at least as, well, 1932’s What Price Hollywood?, the film that directly bore one of this year’s grit-amid-the-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Begs Fans To Leave Pete Davidson Alone: 'I Care Deeply About Pete' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-pete-davidson-fans_us_5c06894be4b07aec5752b379</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEODFb47XaY8BmvOFgM6Dg3EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:44:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-pete-davidson-fans_us_5c06894be4b07aec5752b379" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Begs Fans To Leave Pete Davidson Alone: 'I Care Deeply About Pete'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hell hath no fury like an Ariana Grande stan scorned. Drunk off the power of Grande’s No. 1 single “thank u, next,” some of her fans who believe ex-boyfriend Pete Davidson wronged her (for no apparent reason, we might add) have resorted to relentlessly attacking him on social media. The “Saturday Night Live” comedian released an open letter on Monday, detailing how damaging the negative messages have been but pledging that “no matter how hard the internet or anyone tries to make me kill myself” he won’t give in. Grande and her team have repeatedly tried to stamp out toxic behavior in her fa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande And Drake Top Spotify's 2018 Most-Streamed Artists List - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adriennegibbs/2018/12/04/ariana-grande-and-drake-top-spotifys-2018-most-streamed-artists-list/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-PjaB_2sTBLvPS0-J6ST0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/adriennegibbs/2018/12/04/ariana-grande-and-drake-top-spotifys-2018-most-streamed-artists-list/" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande And Drake Top Spotify's 2018 Most-Streamed Artists List&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande performing on Broadway. Photo by: Eric Liebowitz/NBC/NBCU Photo Bank via Getty Images Ariana Grande and Drake have done it again. For the global stage, they both top Spotify’s list of the most-streamed female and male artists of 2018. This information and other tantalizing tidbits about Spotify user habits and likes will be revealed in full when the Wrapped microsite run by Spotify is released later this week with a new look. Meanwhile, here are some of Spotify’s global stats. Drake’s Scorpion has been the talk of every teen since it dropped in June, and since then the Canadia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Sums Up Her Feelings About Barack Obama With 3 Little Letters - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-barack-obama_us_5c067475e4b066b5cfa5aa3c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI4pzT4h3b_wmFeb0n_VGFsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:38:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-barack-obama_us_5c067475e4b066b5cfa5aa3c" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Sums Up Her Feelings About Barack Obama With 3 Little Letters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande kept it short and sweet on Monday with a message for former President Barack Obama. The pop star responded to Obama’s celebratory Hanukkah tweet with three little letters: “imy,” which is online slang for “I miss you.” imy https://t.co/9aJ52D4chj — Ariana Grande (@ArianaGrande) December 3, 2018 It was widely interpreted by her fans as a lament that Obama was no longer in the White House. Some even called for the singer to run for president: Grande 2028 — diane alston (@dianelyssa) December 3, 2018 cover baby come back and dedicate it to the obama administration — BRIstmas (@sc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande calls on fans to be 'gentler to others' after Pete Davidson shares emotional post about online bullying - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ariana-grande-pete-davidson-online-bullying-fans-fiance-instagram-a8666156.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjrgNudG419_GIZdfBEREUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 09:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ariana-grande-pete-davidson-online-bullying-fans-fiance-instagram-a8666156.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande calls on fans to be 'gentler to others' after Pete Davidson shares emotional post about online bullying&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande responded to Pete Davidson’s social media post about online bullying, calling on her fans to be “gentler to others”. The pair were engaged for four months before calling things off in October, the split appearing to be amicable. However – just days after being referenced in the singer’s latest music video “Thank U, Next” – Davidson released a statement about the horrible abuse he has received. “I’ve spoken about BPD [borderline personality disorder] and being suicidal publicly only in the hopes that it will help bring awareness and help kids like myself who don’t want to be on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Jesy Nelson fans defend the Little Mix singer’s decision to get gun tattoo - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/jesy-nelson-gun-tattoo-little-mix-face-piers-morgan-a8667761.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0LV-7Wr1Pd5yFhasD8NQkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 08:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/jesy-nelson-gun-tattoo-little-mix-face-piers-morgan-a8667761.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jesy Nelson fans defend the Little Mix singer’s decision to get gun tattoo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fans of Jesy Nelson are rushing to defend the Little Mix singer after she uploaded images on Instagram of her new tattoos, which include the letter “Q” on her face and a gun on her rib cage. The photograph of the latter, which was accompanied by a caption thanking the tattoo artist, has sparked outrage online, with critics accusing the musician of glorifying gun crime to her young and impressionable fan base. But many have been quick to stand up for the 27-year-old, who has yet to explain the meaning behind her new body art. View this post on Instagram Thank you @zayahastra for always givin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande explains Mac Miller's absence from her burn book in 'thank u, next' video - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ariana-grande-thank-u-next-video-mac-miller-burn-book-mean-girls-pete-davidson-ex-boyfriends-a8665031.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG41BPXzUk3KBOvVEr3mIUUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ariana-grande-thank-u-next-video-mac-miller-burn-book-mean-girls-pete-davidson-ex-boyfriends-a8665031.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande explains Mac Miller's absence from her burn book in 'thank u, next' video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande's Mean-Girls-themed video for her song "thank u, next"is filled with references to the beloved 2004 teen comedy – down to the "burn book" kept by Regina George and her posse to archive rumours and gossip about other students at their high school. The singer's version, however, is filled not with demeaning comments but with affectionate feedback about several of her exes, from Big Sean to Pete Davidson, with one notable absence. Mac Miller, whom Grande dated for almost two years before their break-up was announced in May, isn't named in the scrapbook. Miller died September this...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The top 100 songs of 2018 - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/dec/03/the-top-100-tracks-of-2018-playlist</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAmsLOnYcUOebyOxE4iyr9UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 06:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/dec/03/the-top-100-tracks-of-2018-playlist" target="_blank"&gt;The top 100 songs of 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kicking off our roundups of the best music of 2018, polled from votes by more than 50 Guardian music writers, we count down our favourite tracks of the year – topped by a man who managed to unpick US racial politics, launch a thousand thinkpieces and reach No 1 in the US charts, all with a single track. Read about the top 20 below, and hear the whole top 100 in playlists on Spotify and Apple Music. We’ll be counting down the albums of the year throughout the rest of the month, with No 1 announced on 21 December. 20. Rolling Blackouts Coastal Fever – Mainland There are only two bands in this...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Drake Is The King Of Spotify And Apple Music As Top Streaming 2018 Artist - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/drake-is-the-king-of-spotify-and-apple-musics-as-top-streaming-2018-artist_us_5c06b665e4b066b5cfa6875f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFx1hDn-hJgErtE_BD2f8zkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 19:22:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/drake-is-the-king-of-spotify-and-apple-musics-as-top-streaming-2018-artist_us_5c06b665e4b066b5cfa6875f" target="_blank"&gt;Drake Is The King Of Spotify And Apple Music As Top Streaming 2018 Artist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Started From The Bottom, now Drake is the most-streamed artist of 2018. Every year, streaming services reveal the top reigning artist, and with viral hits such as “In My Feelings” and “God’s Plan,” it shouldn’t surprise that the Toronto-born rapper is king. Drake has dominated both the Spotify and Apple Music’s end of the year lists as the top-streaming artist of 2018 thanks to his fifth studio album “Scorpion,” which dropped in June. The Grammy winner scored 8.2 billion streams on Spotify in 2018, making him the most-streamed artist ever on the platform. Post Malone, the late rapper XXXTEN...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Says 'True Love Doesn't Exist' And Tries To Take It Back - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-true-love-doesnt-exist_us_5c050486e4b0a173c024bd48</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILJNEmEkYfYU8sioM8-75QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 11:44:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-true-love-doesnt-exist_us_5c050486e4b0a173c024bd48" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Says 'True Love Doesn't Exist' And Tries To Take It Back&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’re bitter when you’re hungry, Ariana Grande. The pop star tweeted her feelings about romance over the weekend following the release of her “Thank U, Next” video. The song includes shoutouts to ex-boyfriends, including former fiance Pete Davidson. “Actually ... I don’t want no ‘next,’ ” she wrote, peroutlets. “True love doesn’t exist. Hope you’re having a great day!” Grande deleted the post, tweeting a funny excuse for her lovelorn self. “True love might exist i was just hungry,” she wrote. “But still, fuck that,” she added. true love might exist i was just hungry — Ariana Grande (@Aria...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Spotify most streamed music 2018: What were the year's favourite albums, artists and tracks - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/spotify-most-streamed-music-2018-album-artist-tracks-ariana-grande-drake-xxxtentacion-a8666011.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOSnAK09ayg8rUeF_wsVdogqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 07:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/spotify-most-streamed-music-2018-album-artist-tracks-ariana-grande-drake-xxxtentacion-a8666011.html" target="_blank"&gt;Spotify most streamed music 2018: What were the year's favourite albums, artists and tracks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spotify has shared its annual end of year music figures, which reveal the top artists, tracks and albums on the streaming service. Unsurprisingly, it was Drake who dominated as the most streamed artist in the UK and globally thanks to the release of his album Scorpion. His single "God's Plan" was the most listened-to track of the year, with over 1.1bn streams. Ariana Grande achieved the highest number of streams for a female artist, following the release of her anticipated fourth album Sweetener in August, and the success of her new single "thank u, next" – the video for which broke several...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pete Davidson addresses bullying after Ariana Grande breakup - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/2d789e0b9dfe4cd8963045fa434e785d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENhMEUrl3SuqOeTylXSQrVYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:42:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/2d789e0b9dfe4cd8963045fa434e785d" target="_blank"&gt;Pete Davidson addresses bullying after Ariana Grande breakup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Pete Davidson says he's not going to "kill myself." Davidson is breaking his silence in an Instagram post following his short-lived engagement with Ariana Grande. The 25-year-old "Saturday Night Live" cast member says he's been getting bullied online and in public for nine months. But Davidson says he's spoken about being suicidal publicly "only in the hopes that it will bring awareness and help kids like myself who don't want to be on this earth." Davidson writes, "No matter how hard the internet or anyone tries to make me kill myself, I won't." Grande responded that she ca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Drake, Post Malone and XXXTentacion are most-streamed artists of 2018 on Spotify - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/dec/04/drake-post-malone-and-xxxtentacion-are-most-streamed-artists-of-2018-on-spotify</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGYzg6tmXkMoSf6YZ63NjmIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:01:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/dec/04/drake-post-malone-and-xxxtentacion-are-most-streamed-artists-of-2018-on-spotify" target="_blank"&gt;Drake, Post Malone and XXXTentacion are most-streamed artists of 2018 on Spotify&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three North American rappers – Drake, Post Malone and XXXTentacion – have been named as the most streamed artists of the year on Spotify. Canadian rapper Drake topped the list of total global streams, with his tracks being played 8.2bn times. He had 2018’s most streamed album and track, with Scorpion and God’s Plan respectively. Another track, In My Feelings, which sparked a hugely popular viral dance challenge on social media, was the fifth most streamed. Twenty-three-year-old Post Malone had two tracks in the Top five, with Rockstar and Psycho at No 3 and No 4, with his album Beerbongs &amp; ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Pete Davidson Spotted Dining At NYC Restaurant While 'Thank U, Next' Plays - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pete-davidson-dining-new-york-thank-u-next_us_5c053df3e4b0cd916fae4ade</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGqxgAGS-h3OlJkaXUjTKZ4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:06:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pete-davidson-dining-new-york-thank-u-next_us_5c053df3e4b0cd916fae4ade" target="_blank"&gt;Pete Davidson Spotted Dining At NYC Restaurant While 'Thank U, Next' Plays&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A viral video of Pete Davidson dining at a New York City restaurant while his ex-fiancée Ariana Grande’s song breakup song, “thank u, next” played on the speakers. The “Saturday Night Live” star was seen eating at Cafeteria in Chelsea after his performance on the show over the weekend. Fellow patron Steven Thomas captured a video of Davidson while “thank u, next” blared on the sound system: The Waiters at Cafeteria just did Pete Davidson so dirty. pic.twitter.com/jsUdNMf9bq — Steven Thomas (@stevendotthomas) December 2, 2018 Davidson appears unshaken in the video and it’s unclear whom he wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Pete Davidson shares personal note about mental health and online bullying - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/pete-davidson-instagram-mental-health-ariana-grande-bpd-borderline-personality-disorder-bullying-a8665751.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFCbQ6s31Zo-2D_HhOdthPgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 20:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/pete-davidson-instagram-mental-health-ariana-grande-bpd-borderline-personality-disorder-bullying-a8665751.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pete Davidson shares personal note about mental health and online bullying&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pete Davidson shared a personal note broaching the topic of mental health on his Instagram account on Monday. The comedian, who has previously opened up about being diagnosed with borderline personality disorder, said he has been bullied online and in public "for the past nine months". "I've kept my mouth shut. Never mentioned any names, never said a word about anyone or anything," he wrote. "I'm just trying to understand how when something happens to a guy the whole entire world just trashes him without any facts or frame of reference." - Read more Ariana Grande explains Mac Miller's absen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pete Davidson gets candid about mental health and bullying - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/entertainment/pete-davidson-mental-health-bullying/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENw7hKn4HGk_xuK5WRhh3bUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 02:51:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/entertainment/pete-davidson-mental-health-bullying/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pete Davidson gets candid about mental health and bullying&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Saturday Night Live" performer Pete Davidson isn't laughing about the public harassment he's faced during and after his relationship with singer Ariana Grande. On Monday, the comedian took to Instagam to address bullying he's endured for the last nine months, roughly the length of his relationship with former fianceé Grande, which ended in October. "I'm trying to understand how when something happens to a guy the whole entire world just trashes him without any facts or frame of reference," Davidson wrote. The bullying, he said, has occurred both online and in public. "I've spoken about BPD...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Drake tops Spotify's 2018 list with 8.2 billion streams - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/b8c1d83e81be43e2a8d083f59ebdd713</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECkm8ZgRicQJfIZAHL-ffIMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 05:07:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/b8c1d83e81be43e2a8d083f59ebdd713" target="_blank"&gt;Drake tops Spotify's 2018 list with 8.2 billion streams&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — It's no surprise, but Drake is the king of Spotify: He is the platform's most-streamed artist of the year globally. Spotify announced Tuesday that the rapper earned 8.2 billion streams in 2018. He also has the year's most-streamed album and song with "Scorpion" and "God's Plan." Drake is also Spotify's most-streamed artist of all-time. Following Drake on the 2018 list of top artists are Post Malone, XXXTentacion, J Balvin and Ed Sheeran, who was Spotify's most-streamed artist last year. No women made the Top 5, but Ariana Grande ranks first among female artists globally on S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Grammy Predictions 2019: Taylor, Beyonce And Jay-Z And Ariana Grande For Album Of The Year - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/28/grammy-predictions-2019-taylor-beyonce-and-jay-z-and-ariana-grande-for-album-of-the-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF9BIVL-Luxv9gCfmO8Rc5wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/28/grammy-predictions-2019-taylor-beyonce-and-jay-z-and-ariana-grande-for-album-of-the-year/" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy Predictions 2019: Taylor, Beyonce And Jay-Z And Ariana Grande For Album Of The Year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARLINGTON, TX – OCTOBER 05: Taylor Swift performs onstage during the reputation Stadium Tour at AT&amp;T Stadium on October 5, 2018, in Arlington, Texas. (Photo by Matt Winkelmeyer/TAS18/Getty Images for TAS) While some might argue that Record of the Year is more important in a world that doesn’t focus on albums like it used to, winning Album of the Year remains the high point of any artist’s career. As with all of the “Big Four” categories (Album, Record, Song of the Year and Best New Artist), the field is opening up to eight potential nominees for the first time, and that could certainly make...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Panic! At The Disco Hits A New Career High While Ariana Grande Rules For A Third Week - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/26/panic-at-the-disco-hits-a-new-career-high-while-ariana-grande-rules-for-a-third-week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMM7x6InH-YrydFM-TodsAUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 22:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/26/panic-at-the-disco-hits-a-new-career-high-while-ariana-grande-rules-for-a-third-week/" target="_blank"&gt;Panic! At The Disco Hits A New Career High While Ariana Grande Rules For A Third Week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TODAY — Pictured: Brendon Urie of Panic! At the Disco on Friday, June 29, 2018 — (Photo by: Nathan Congleton/NBC/NBCU Photo Bank via Getty Images) Almost everywhere in the world, Ariana Grande continues to rule the charts with her instantly popular new single “Thank U, Next,” which is in charge of the Hot 100 songs listing for the third consecutive turn. The track, which fronts her upcoming new album of the same name, debuted at the peak earlier this month, becoming her first leader on the all-genre tally and one of fewer than 40 songs in history to start as high as a cut can climb. Grande...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Jennifer Garner Says Ariana Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Video Brightened Her Day - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/jennifer-garner-ariana-grande-thank-u-next_us_5c030064e4b0a173c0239a2e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKiB2HskREscBY-I_U7MGPoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 22:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/jennifer-garner-ariana-grande-thank-u-next_us_5c030064e4b0a173c0239a2e" target="_blank"&gt;Jennifer Garner Says Ariana Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Video Brightened Her Day&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande released the highly anticipated video for her song “Thank U, Next” on Friday, and one admirer is now thanking her. Jennifer Garner responded on social media to the new video, inspired by early-2000s romantic comedies. The video for “Thank U, Next” included references to Garner’s 2004 film “13 Going on 30.” “Every now and then something comes along and just brightens your day,” Garner wrote on Instagram. “[Ariana] you’re adorable. Thank you, pretty girl.” View this post on Instagram Every now and then something comes along and just brightens your day. @arianagrande you’re adora...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Pete Davidson Reflects On Harassment In Emotional Post: 'I've Kept My Mouth Shut' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pete-davidson-borderline-personality-disorder_us_5c056d8fe4b066b5cfa48695</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBQnavMz7kLL1v4oLihTMEYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 18:28:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pete-davidson-borderline-personality-disorder_us_5c056d8fe4b066b5cfa48695" target="_blank"&gt;Pete Davidson Reflects On Harassment In Emotional Post: 'I've Kept My Mouth Shut'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pete Davidson shared an open letter to his fans on Monday, promising them that “no matter how hard the internet or anyone tries to make me kill myself. I won’t.” “I’m upset I even have to say this,” he wrote in the heartfelt Instagram post. “To all those holding me down and seeing this for what it is - I see you and I love you.” View this post on Instagram A post shared by Pete Davidson (@petedavidson) on Dec 3, 2018 at 9:30am PST The “Saturday Night Live” comedian said that he has kept his “mouth shut” and “never mentioned any names” but wanted to let fans know that he’s “trying to underst...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Hootie &amp; the Blowfish to reunite for new album and tour in 2019 - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/hootie-and-the-blowfish-tour-tickets-reunion-new-album-group-therapy-release-date-presale-barenaked-a8665281.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGSXTOsxPjInpgNZjDQThFcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/hootie-and-the-blowfish-tour-tickets-reunion-new-album-group-therapy-release-date-presale-barenaked-a8665281.html" target="_blank"&gt;Hootie &amp; the Blowfish to reunite for new album and tour in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hootie &amp; the Blowfish are getting back together, 13 years after the release of their last studio album. The American rock band, which formed in 1986 and found fame in the Nineties, announced its upcoming return Monday morning on the Today show. Darius Rucker, Mark Bryan, Dean Felber, and Jim Sonefeld told Craig Melvin they're getting the band back together for a new album and a new tour in 2019. You can sign up here for access to the pre-sale. - Read more Ariana Grande explains Mac Miller's absence from 'thank u, next' video All four members looked back on their humble beginnings, during wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Video Breaks The Vevo Record For Most Views In 24 Hours - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/01/ariana-grandes-thank-u-next-video-breaks-the-vevo-record-for-most-views-in-24-hours/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAvWr1o56rNpG-qYaqGmHUYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/01/ariana-grandes-thank-u-next-video-breaks-the-vevo-record-for-most-views-in-24-hours/" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Video Breaks The Vevo Record For Most Views In 24 Hours&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOSTON, MA – DECEMBER 11: Singer Ariana Grande performs on stage during KISS 108′s Jingle Ball 2016 at TD Garden on December 11, 2016, in Boston, Massachusetts. (Photo by Dave Kotinsky/Getty Images for iHeart) It hasn’t even been a full 24 hours since Ariana Grande released the highly-anticipated video for her new single “Thank U, Next,” but it has already broken an important record with an eye-popping view count. According to a representative for music video platform Vevo, the internationally-adored pop singer’s latest smash has broken the record for the most plays on the site in one day…o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Tops The U.K. Singles Chart Again While Newcomer Ava Max Enters The Top 10 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/01/ariana-grande-tops-the-u-k-singles-chart-again-while-newcomer-ava-max-enters-the-top-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM9xBZCpqGmY8plwDzEwHaUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 14:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/01/ariana-grande-tops-the-u-k-singles-chart-again-while-newcomer-ava-max-enters-the-top-10/" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Tops The U.K. Singles Chart Again While Newcomer Ava Max Enters The Top 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, NY – AUGUST 20: American Express and Ariana Grande present ‘The Sweetener Sessions’ at Irving Plaza on August 20, 2018, in New York City. (Photo by Kevin Mazur/Getty Images for American Express) Once again, Ariana Grande is in charge of the singles chart in the U.K. with her new song “Thank U, Next,” which debuted on the throne and hasn’t left in the four weeks since.Grande recently just released the highly-anticipated music video for her new single, and all the streams it racks up could keep it at No. 1 in the U.K. for some time to come. Behind her, only one new tune breaks into ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande's 'thank u, next' music video breaks YouTube record with break-up clues and romcom nods - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ariana-grande-thank-u-next-music-video-youtube-pete-davidson-big-sean-ricky-alverez-mean-girls-a8662441.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELEBjnYXbGPAkTHBVEXzLKYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 10:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ariana-grande-thank-u-next-music-video-youtube-pete-davidson-big-sean-ricky-alverez-mean-girls-a8662441.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande's 'thank u, next' music video breaks YouTube record with break-up clues and romcom nods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there are two things at a premium on the internet, it’s gossip and nostalgia. Ariana Grande’s new music video mines both of them, helping it on the way to a YouTube record as it reached one million views in less than 34 minutes. The video pays tribute to beloved early 2000s romcoms, including Mean Girls, Legally Blonde, Bring It On and 13 Going On 30. Mean Girls actor Jonathan Bennett (Aaron Samuels) makes a cameo, with Kris Jenner stepping in as Amy Poehler’s “cool mom” character. “thank u, next”, which has been top of the Billboard Hot 100 since it was released three weeks ago, is a so...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The Posthumous Career Of Mac Miller Begins - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonbisnoff/2018/11/30/the-posthumous-career-of-mac-miller-begins/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGSYaeHOCHNdFD3OEndX9rcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonbisnoff/2018/11/30/the-posthumous-career-of-mac-miller-begins/" target="_blank"&gt;The Posthumous Career Of Mac Miller Begins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jason Bisnoff With the recent debut of two previously-unreleased singles by Mac Miller, his posthumous career has begun. There are some clues from Mac’s career and previous artists who passed prematurely that give clues to how an artists career after death can take shape. The aforementioned pair of releases came from Spotify, which, as part of their “Spotify Sessions” series, had Mac in their studio in New York City. That August session would, unfortunately, be one of his last recordings. An email to users that announced the release said: ”In August, Mac Miller came to our Spotify Studio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande releases star-studded music video for Thank U, Next - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/music/what-to-listen-to/ariana-grande-releases-star-studded-music-video-thank-u-next/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChgqGOPmP0l2QElyRA5MnkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDW0bcF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/music/what-to-listen-to/ariana-grande-releases-star-studded-music-video-thank-u-next/" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande releases star-studded music video for Thank U, Next&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande has released the star-studded music video for her latest hit single, Thank U, Next. The highly anticipated video paid homage to teen movies such as Mean Girls, Bring It on, 13 Going on 30 and Legally Blonde. Many of the films' stars - including Jennifer Coolidge and Jonathan Bennett - made appearances, as did Grande's own celebrity friends. Coolidge reprised her role from Legally Blonde opposite Grande's reimagining of Reese Witherspoon's Elle Woods. #thankunextvideo out now https://t.co/g12C0vVini 🖤 pic.twitter.com/ASST9rmWLs — Ariana Grande (@ArianaGrande) November 30, 2018...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Music Video Is Here With Kris Jenner As Cool Mom - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-thank-u-next-music-video_us_5c014b7ee4b0249dce74433c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJXhFMNyTCl9F_WXzoB-M_MqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:07:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-thank-u-next-music-video_us_5c014b7ee4b0249dce74433c" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Music Video Is Here With Kris Jenner As Cool Mom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please pass along a kind “Thank U, Next” to all other music videos, because Miss Ariana Grande has finally arrived. After toying with us for weeks with star-studded Instagrams, a teaser trailer, behind-the-scenes peeks and more, the singer’s “Thank U, Next” music video is finally here, and it finally made fetch happen. Inspired by “Mean Girls” and other female-driven films of the early 2000s, Grande is front and center in her video for the pettiest empowerment anthem around. The video re-creates iconic moments from the films as Grande muses on past relationships, with callbacks to the scene...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Broke YouTube Viewer Records With Her 'Thank U, Next' Music Video - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/caitlinkelley/2018/11/30/ariana-grande-broke-youtube-records-thank-u-next-premiere/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPswT2weHm8zh5PZZlO9N-gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 01:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/caitlinkelley/2018/11/30/ariana-grande-broke-youtube-records-thank-u-next-premiere/" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Broke YouTube Viewer Records With Her 'Thank U, Next' Music Video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES, CA – JUNE 02: (EDITORIAL USE ONLY. NO COMMERCIAL USE) Ariana Grande performs onstage during the 2018 iHeartRadio Wango Tango by AT&amp;T at Banc of California Stadium on June 2, 2018 in Los Angeles, California. (Photo by Rich Polk/Getty Images for iHeartMedia ) Ariana Grande broke YouTube records on Nov. 30 with the premiere of her “thank u, next” music video. Her memeified self-love anthem became the biggest-ever Premiere on YouTube using the site’s Premiere feature. The pint-sized songstress threw a giant streaming party as a whopping 829,000 viewers tuned in at the same time. A ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande shares Mean Girls themed clip from 'thank u, next' music video - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ariana-grande-mean-girls-thank-u-next-music-video-a8653526.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGcA8u_chhVLvp1QMXmdzbUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 08:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ariana-grande-mean-girls-thank-u-next-music-video-a8653526.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande shares Mean Girls themed clip from 'thank u, next' music video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande is trying to make "fetch" happen. The pop star has shared a teaser on social media giving fans a first look at the forthcoming video for her hit single "thank u, next" – which is massively inspired by the hit movie Mean Girls. Grande has managed to assemble some of the original cast, including Aaron Samuels actor Jonathan D Bennett, to appear in the clip, along with fellow pop star and friend Troye Sivan. Each member of the cast talks to the camera as they reveal a piece of gossip, in the same style as the original Mean Girls movie when the characters talked about Cady Heron a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Releases Rom-Com Inspired ‘Thank U, Next’ Music Video - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ariana-grande-releases-rom-com-inspired-thank-u-next-music-video</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFOh8t4E7Wl-ihs-b-m0CvgqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:49:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/ariana-grande-releases-rom-com-inspired-thank-u-next-music-video" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Releases Rom-Com Inspired ‘Thank U, Next’ Music Video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot/YouTube Singer Ariana Grande on Friday dropped her highly anticipated “thank u, next” music video, which drew inspiration from “girl power” rom-coms like Mean Girls, Legally Blonde, Bring It On, and 13 Going on 30. In the video, Grande transforms into several different female protagonists—donning hot pink to channel the iconic characters of Regina George and Elle Woods, chopping her hair to turn into Jenna Rink, and waving pom-poms around to play Torrance Shipman. Celebrity cameos include Kardashian matriarch Kris Jenner, singer Troye Sivan, and actress Elizabeth Gillies. Jennife...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Viewers criticise trailer of new romance film 'After' for 'glorifying unhealthy relationships' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/after-trailer-movie-film-harry-styles-fanfiction-josephine-langford-hero-fiennes-tiffin-anna-todd-a8653296.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOT7ffL55dkbEnZCAOuCW0MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/after-trailer-movie-film-harry-styles-fanfiction-josephine-langford-hero-fiennes-tiffin-anna-todd-a8653296.html" target="_blank"&gt;Viewers criticise trailer of new romance film 'After' for 'glorifying unhealthy relationships'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An upcoming romance film has been criticised for glorifying toxic relationships following the release of its trailer. After, which is scheduled to be released in April 2019 in the US, is the big screen adaptation of the 2014 novel of the same name by author Anna Todd. The novel itself originated as a popular fan fiction dedicated to One Direction singer Harry Styles, who inspired the character of Hardin Scott in Todd's books. - Read more Harry Styles interviewed Timothée Chalamet – and the internet lost it After has become part of a bestselling, five-book series. Simon &amp; Schuster paid a "mi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Dangerous Woman Diaries, review: Ariana Grande’s new YouTube series is strictly for die-hard fans - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/music/artists/dangerous-woman-diaries-review-ariana-grandes-new-youtube-series/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIFe7Jq8NPL6BSA-3bPkGZ4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDW0bcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:36:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/music/artists/dangerous-woman-diaries-review-ariana-grandes-new-youtube-series/" target="_blank"&gt;Dangerous Woman Diaries, review: Ariana Grande’s new YouTube series is strictly for die-hard fans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At one point during Ariana Grande’s new YouTube documentary series – chronicling Grande’s 2018 world tour and work behind her recent album – the pint-sized pop icon is driven away from a meet-and-greet in New York, only to have one very eager fan sprint after the car to try and flag it down. Grande and her team are left in hysterics, Grande asking, with trademark quit wit, “Am I a Spice Girl?” The way things have gone for Grande in the past four months, the question now sounds prophetic. The star’s fourth album Sweetener, released in August, was a critical and commercial smash that catapult...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Reveals Gut-Wrenching Letter She Wrote After Manchester Bombing - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-letter-manchester_us_5c010dcae4b0b69ed379e53c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJgGDxbfo9hJWaIPMPK7Qy4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 11:38:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-letter-manchester_us_5c010dcae4b0b69ed379e53c" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Reveals Gut-Wrenching Letter She Wrote After Manchester Bombing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande has revealed a heartbreaking letter she wrote to fans about the 2017 bombing attack that killed 22 and injured hundreds at her Manchester Arena concert. In an episode of her docuseries “Dangerous Woman Diaries” that dropped Thursday on YouTube Premium, the 25-year-old pop star revisited the horror of that May night, calling it “heartbreaking in a way that seems impossible to fully recover from.” “I’m writing to you this February 22, 2018,” “The God Is A Woman” singer began the letter. “It’s been eight months since the attack at our show at the Manchester Arena. It’s impossible...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Grammy Predictions 2019: Childish Gambino, Beyonce (Twice) And Bradley Cooper For Record Of The Year - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/29/grammy-predictions-2019-childish-gambino-and-beyonce-twice-might-earn-record-of-the-year-noms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE-VJM_W7gvHYMmH6yCfHQEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 16:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/29/grammy-predictions-2019-childish-gambino-and-beyonce-twice-might-earn-record-of-the-year-noms/" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy Predictions 2019: Childish Gambino, Beyonce (Twice) And Bradley Cooper For Record Of The Year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LAS VEGAS, NV – SEPTEMBER 21: Childish Gambino performs onstage during the iHeartRadio Music Festival at T-Mobile Arena on September 21, 2018, in Las Vegas, Nevada. (Photo by Rich Fury/Getty Images for iHeartMedia) What one song dominated the past year more than all others? Was it a smash No. 1 hit that radio couldn’t stop playing? Was it a track that made history? Was there just one piece that meant so much more than every other single to so many people, thus making it truly the Record of the Year? It’s impossible to say who will win this coveted trophy this year, but ahead of the December...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Zara Larsson: ‘Pop could be a positive force’ - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/189a38a4-ed84-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMX04ep0Mf4vMg6cJAjK3vAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 13:52:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/189a38a4-ed84-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Zara Larsson: ‘Pop could be a positive force’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A decade ago, when she was 10, Zara Larsson marched purposefully on to the stage of a television talent show in her native Sweden and proceeded to sing Whitney Houston’s “Greatest Love of All”. “If I fail, if I succeed/At least I’ll live as I believe,” she belted out in front of a beaming audience. The coin fell on the side of success: she won the talent show. Ten years later, Larsson has yet to experience failure. Her first album, released in Sweden in 2014, topped Scandinavian charts. Her international debut So Good came out in 2017 and made her a global star: it is the second most stream...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande drops 'Thank U, Next' teaser - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/27/entertainment/thank-u-next-teaser/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH-b8zFe6e65roCO354iRZ8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 17:02:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/27/entertainment/thank-u-next-teaser/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande drops 'Thank U, Next' teaser&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande released a sneak peek of her music video for "Thank U, Next" and it's full of delicious throwbacks. The clip shared by Grande on Instagram early Tuesday features the singer dressed as Regina George from the 2004 film "Mean Girls." Jonathan Bennett, who played Aaron Samuels in the film, and Stefanie Drummond, who played Bethany Byrd, make cameos. "Ariana Grande told me my hair looked sexy pushed back," Bennett says in the clip. "She's not wrong!" But "Mean Girls" isn't the only film giving fans major nostalgia. Grande also reenacts scenes from "13 Going on 30," "Bring It On" an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Destroys Rank Misogynist (and Disgraced Journalist) Piers Morgan - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ariana-grande-destroys-rank-misogynist-and-disgraced-journalist-piers-morgan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcZQHb0KrAtQcRQQGR78cUqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMKv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 18:32:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/ariana-grande-destroys-rank-misogynist-and-disgraced-journalist-piers-morgan" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Destroys Rank Misogynist (and Disgraced Journalist) Piers Morgan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast Just in time for Thanksgiving, patron saint of gratitude Ariana Grande is saying thank u, next to Piers Morgan, a crusty old misogynist masquerading as a journalist. In recent years, Morgan has clung to relevancy by “feuding” with celebrities; these spats usually consist of Morgan picking on a star for wearing revealing clothes, with her “clapping back” by saying that she can wear whatever the fuck she wants. The disgraced former tabloid editor’s high-profile targets range from the Kardashians to Chrissy Teigen and Emily Ratajkowski. His triggers includ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Drops Behind-The-Scenes Supercut For 'Thank U, Next' Music Video - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-thank-u-next-behind-scenes_us_5c00336ae4b08506231ad17d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDTEPwoo2H7ZX5C8EJuGQxwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 19:58:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-thank-u-next-behind-scenes_us_5c00336ae4b08506231ad17d" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Drops Behind-The-Scenes Supercut For 'Thank U, Next' Music Video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande dropped a behind-the-scenes supercut on Thursday that depicts the making of her upcoming music video for “Thank U, Next,” and we’re so freakin’ grateful for her. In the teaser, we see Grande reenacting scenes from classic teen movies like “Bring It On,” “Mean Girls,” “13 Going on 30” and “Legally Blonde.” “Legally Blonde” fans will surely be pleased to see that Paulette, played by Jennifer Coolidge, makes an appearance: There’s even the wedding sequence from “13 Going on 30” with Grande as the bride: The pop star released the first teaser trailer for the video on Monday and it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande pens emotional letter about Manchester bombing in new docuseries - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/entertainment/ariana-grande-docuseries-youtube/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMYROPahFG-Dyc0CHKzTXIEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 20:45:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/entertainment/ariana-grande-docuseries-youtube/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande pens emotional letter about Manchester bombing in new docuseries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande is taking her fans behind the scenes of her "Dangerous Woman Tour" in a new docuseries. In it, she addresses the terrifying bombing that took place during her Manchester concert in May 2017, which killed 22 people. In the fourth episode of the docuseries, which dropped Thursday on YouTube Premium, the platform's paid streaming service, Grande writes a letter to her fans about the terrorist attack. "I'm writing to you this February 22, 2018. It's been eight months since the attack at our show at the Manchester Arena. It's impossible to know where to start or to know what to say...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Piers Morgan celebrity feuds: A history of A-listers taking on the TV host - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/piers-morgan-feud-ariana-grande-emily-ratajkowski-jk-rowling-lady-gaga-chrissy-teigen-gmb-tv-a8645826.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKmLnwccRTtb7Lb9ulewI5gqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 22:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/piers-morgan-feud-ariana-grande-emily-ratajkowski-jk-rowling-lady-gaga-chrissy-teigen-gmb-tv-a8645826.html" target="_blank"&gt;Piers Morgan celebrity feuds: A history of A-listers taking on the TV host&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the world of Twitter punditry, Piers Morgan's celebrity feuds have become somewhat of a background noise. His complaints are near-constant, so much so that you may not even notice them anymore. The former CNN host, who hosted his own talk show on the network from 2011 to 2014, now spends a significant amount of his time arguing with A-listers on social media, often generating eye-rolls – and garnering attention – in the process. On Wednesday, Morgan found a new rival in the form of Ariana Grande. The 22-year-old singer criticised the 53-year-old journalist after he accused Little Mix of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande criticises Piers Morgan over nudity comments - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/nov/22/ariana-grande-criticises-piers-morgan-over-nudity-twitter-comments-little-mix</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECChr71XhQEKb7cttMmKR4MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 10:08:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/nov/22/ariana-grande-criticises-piers-morgan-over-nudity-twitter-comments-little-mix" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande criticises Piers Morgan over nudity comments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande has criticised Piers Morgan after he made disparaging comments about a nude photoshoot by the band Little Mix. The group of female musicians posed naked and their bodies were painted with criticisms they had faced, such as “ugly” and “talentless”. It was a similar photoshoot to one in 2003 by the country trio Dixie Chicks. Morgan criticised Little Mix for the similarity, writing on Twitter that they “stole this idea”, and that Jesy Nelson of the group “looks ridiculous … she should put some clothes on”. Ariana Grande’s mother, Joan, first responded to the Good Morning Britain ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande shares letter about Manchester Arena attack: 'It seems impossible to fully recover from' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ariana-grande-manchester-arena-attack-dangerous-woman-diaries-a8660426.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEErCSdZqWpqhZzV9E_5COE4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 09:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/ariana-grande-manchester-arena-attack-dangerous-woman-diaries-a8660426.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande shares letter about Manchester Arena attack: 'It seems impossible to fully recover from'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande has opened up about the Manchester Arena bombing in an open letter. The popstar’s concert – which was part of the Dangerous Woman tour – was attacked in May 2017, when a suicide bomber detonated a homemade explosive device in the arena foyer, killing 22 people. In the fourth episode of her documentary series, entitled Ariana Grande: Dangerous Woman Diaries, she shares a letter about the attack. Grande describes the atrocity, which left hundreds injured, as something “that seems impossible to fully recover from”. “I’m writing to you this February 22, 2018. It’s been eight month...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>How Ariana Grande created a new kind of break up song - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/nov/24/ariana-grande-thank-u-next</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKFtNODc_buvP5kchWyjItsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 11:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/nov/24/ariana-grande-thank-u-next" target="_blank"&gt;How Ariana Grande created a new kind of break up song&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four decades ago, Carly Simon skewered an ex-lover with a song called You’re So Vain. Drawing its power from Simon’s use of the unnamed man’s egotism to take him down a peg, it became a celebrated breakup song. Simon has said the actor Warren Beatty was one inspiration of three – the other two men remain unnamed. In contrast, in this year’s most popular breakup song, Thank U, Next, we know exactly whom Ariana Grande is singing about. Also singing about more than one ex, she identifies them in the opening lyrics. Unlike Simon, her motive is to praise, not condemn. The song discusses therappe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande embroiled in Twitter spat with Piers Morgan over Little Mix criticism - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/music/news/ariana-grande-embroiled-twitter-spat-piers-morgan-little-mix/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL-rqBeBhy6gP0zO_VGmp1UqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDW0bcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:15:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/music/news/ariana-grande-embroiled-twitter-spat-piers-morgan-little-mix/" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande embroiled in Twitter spat with Piers Morgan over Little Mix criticism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande and Piers Morgan have become embroiled in a Twitter spat over the TV presenter's recent comments about Little Mix and Ellen DeGeneres. The Good Morning Britain host, 53, sparked controversy when he criticised a nude image of the girl group which was intended to champion body positivity, claiming they had swiped the idea for the shoot from US band Dixie Chicks and were "using sex to sell records". He also had a pop at DeGeneres's chat show, tweeting: "Ellen drooling today over famous men's bodies on £InternationalMensDay2018. Yet I've been abused all day for complimenting @holl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Pete Davidson's New Ruth Bader Ginsberg Tattoo Is Never Getting Covered Up - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pete-davidson-ruth-bader-ginsberg-tattoo_us_5bf6ca03e4b03b230f9f81fb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECEkAa--C6kegDi6ydauHtkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 18:46:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pete-davidson-ruth-bader-ginsberg-tattoo_us_5bf6ca03e4b03b230f9f81fb" target="_blank"&gt;Pete Davidson's New Ruth Bader Ginsberg Tattoo Is Never Getting Covered Up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pete Davidson seems to be on a never-ending mission to cover up old tattoos and get new ones for his collection. Tattoo artist Jon Mesa recently shared a new design he said he inked on the “Saturday Night Live” comedian: a portrait of Supreme Court justice Ruth Bader Ginsberg. The tattoo shows the 85-year-old wearing a crown, of course. “‘The Notorious R.B.G.’ Ruth Bader Ginsburg on @petedavidson,” Mesa wrote in the caption of his Instagram photo, which showed Davidson’s shoulder. Since Ginsburg isn’t one of Davidson’s exes, he’ll never have to worry about covering it up (as he did with his...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande's Manager Defends Pete Davidson: 'Stop The Bulls**t' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grandes-manager-defends-pete-davidson-stop-the-bullshit_us_5c003ad2e4b0864f4f6b7d8f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPGhECAy_kemvom9QPIlWbcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 21:47:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grandes-manager-defends-pete-davidson-stop-the-bullshit_us_5c003ad2e4b0864f4f6b7d8f" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande's Manager Defends Pete Davidson: 'Stop The Bulls**t'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande and Pete Davidson might be ready to say “thank u, next” to their relationship, but some of the pop star’s pettiest fans are still in their feelings about the split. While the former couple has played mostly nice since breaking off their engagement weeks ago, Davidson has been inundated with negative comments since reactivating his Instagram after an extended social media break. The “Saturday Night Live” star returned to the platform on Wednesday to promote his new film “Big Time Adolescence,” and let’s just say his followers wanted a little less conversation about his filmogra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Drags Piers Morgan There And Back Again To Defend Mom - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-drags-piers-morgan-there-and-back-again-to-defend-mom_us_5bf59a93e4b0eb6d930afe5f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwGd3xJv0B6aN2N_bucjSIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 19:26:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-drags-piers-morgan-there-and-back-again-to-defend-mom_us_5bf59a93e4b0eb6d930afe5f" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Drags Piers Morgan There And Back Again To Defend Mom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande has issued a personal “thank you, next” to Piers Morgan. The British TV personality, who spends his days body-shaming and making other derogatory comments toward women, has taken aim at the girl group Little Mix and talk show host Ellen DeGeneres in recent days. After calling DeGeneres a hypocrite for sharing a photo montage of shirtless celebrity men on her show, he moved on, slamming the band for appearing nude in an empowering photoshoot for their latest single “Strip.” Grande’s mother, Joan, was having absolutely none of it, tagging Morgan in a tweet on Wednesday after he ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Holds At No. 1 With 'Thank U, Next' While Panic! At The Disco Hits The Top 10 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/19/ariana-grande-holds-at-no-1-with-thank-u-next-while-panic-at-the-disco-hits-the-top-10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC3LpH8FBZRFdmaiDj28iloqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 19:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/19/ariana-grande-holds-at-no-1-with-thank-u-next-while-panic-at-the-disco-hits-the-top-10/" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Holds At No. 1 With 'Thank U, Next' While Panic! At The Disco Hits The Top 10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BILBAO, SPAIN – NOVEMBER 04: Brendon Urie of Panic! at the Disco attends the MTV EMAs 2018 at Bilbao Exhibition Centre on November 4, 2018 in Bilbao, Spain. (Photo by Jeff Kravitz/FilmMagic) For the second week in a row, Ariana Grande is in charge of the Hot 100 singles listing with her latest catchy tune, “Thank U, Next.” The cut debuted atop the ranking last frame, giving the singer her first leader and making her one of fewer than 30 musicians to start a song at No. 1 on the important chart. Back in the runner-up spot is Travis Scott’s “Sicko Mode,” which has now been stuck in second pla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Posts Moving Thanksgiving Tribute To Mac Miller - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-posts-moving-thanksgiving-tribute-to-mac-miller_us_5bf828f4e4b0eb6d930e2dc8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKRmltsZ_elMQfu3DJp5u8UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 18:02:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-posts-moving-thanksgiving-tribute-to-mac-miller_us_5bf828f4e4b0eb6d930e2dc8" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Posts Moving Thanksgiving Tribute To Mac Miller&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s been nearly three months since rapper and record producer Malcolm James McCormick, better known as Mac Miller, died of a lethal mixture of drugs and alcohol at the age of 26. His ex-girlfriend, pop star Ariana Grande, posted a touching photo Thursday of the two of them taken last Thanksgiving. “You’re v missed,” Grande said in an Instagram story caption. Grande and Miller dated for two years before splitting back in May. Grande then had a highly publicized relationship with “Saturday Night Live” cast member Pete Davidson. The couple got engaged after just a few weeks, but the relations...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>All of the film-inspired fashion from Ariana Grande's 'thank u, next' music video, from Legally Blonde to Bring It On - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/fashion/ariana-grande-thank-u-next-music-video-fashion-films-legally-blonde-mean-girls-bring-it-on-13-going-a8646601.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM75f1p-EmK3r1caaabXoxgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 15:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/fashion/ariana-grande-thank-u-next-music-video-fashion-films-legally-blonde-mean-girls-bring-it-on-13-going-a8646601.html" target="_blank"&gt;All of the film-inspired fashion from Ariana Grande's 'thank u, next' music video, from Legally Blonde to Bring It On&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the release of Ariana Grande’s new single ‘thank u, next’, which pays homage to the singer’s exes and the lessons that they’ve taught her, Arianators across the globe have been eagerly awaiting the launch of the song’s music video. After much anticipation, a few days ago Grande finally started sharing sneak peeks from the video, painting a fuller of the video’s film-inspired concept much to the delight of her fans. In the music video, which hasn't yet been released, Grande places an emphasis on the song’s message of self-love by lovingly recreating looks from popular female-led films,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Chops Off Signature Ponytail, Debuts Post-Breakup Lob - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-chops-off-signature-ponytail_us_5beed327e4b0510a1f30186d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOFhNEY5BvvJZSbOyzo-fkMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 16:05:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grande-chops-off-signature-ponytail_us_5beed327e4b0510a1f30186d" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Chops Off Signature Ponytail, Debuts Post-Breakup Lob&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the grand tradition of Felicity Porter and other women who’ve famously embraced a post-breakup haircut, Ariana Grande has debuted a brand new look weeks after splitting from ex-fiancé Pete Davidson. The “Thank U, Next” singer has seemingly removed her ever-so-famous hair extensions responsible for the power pony she’s been rocking since as long as we can remember. The pop princess shared the first peek at her chic shoulder-length lob on Instagram Thursday with what else but a floral bunny ears filter. View this post on Instagram A post shared by Ariana Grande (@arianagrande) on Nov 15, 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Is The New 'Mean Girl' in Teaser For 'thank u, next' Video - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/cmalone/2018/11/27/ariana-grande-is-the-new-mean-girl-in-teaser-for-thank-u-next-video/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGY95CrQ1_PDgbbE68197SkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 04:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/cmalone/2018/11/27/ariana-grande-is-the-new-mean-girl-in-teaser-for-thank-u-next-video/" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande Is The New 'Mean Girl' in Teaser For 'thank u, next' Video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande performs at Wango Tango at Banc of California Stadium on Saturday, June 2, 2018, in Los Angeles. (Photo by Chris Pizzello/Invision/AP) To say that the entertainment industry has gotten reboot- and sequel-crazy in the last few years is a comical understatement. Sabrina, The Teenage Witch is haunting our screens again, and Tyra Banks is coming out of her box again in less than a week in the premiere of Life-Size 2. Mean Girls received a much-maligned sequel treatment eight years ago (and a polarizing Broadway musical just this year), so fans of the original movie have every righ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Pete Davidson Gets Into Food Fight With Star Not Named Ariana Grande - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pete-davidson-food-fight-snl-preview_us_5bffd4afe4b027f1097b032e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1O6zzHvQ8haDLo3akZQPsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 13:21:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/pete-davidson-food-fight-snl-preview_us_5bffd4afe4b027f1097b032e" target="_blank"&gt;Pete Davidson Gets Into Food Fight With Star Not Named Ariana Grande&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pete Davidson just made a public spectacle of himself ― but this time, it was scripted, and ex-fiancée Ariana Grande wasn’t involved. In a video that dropped Wednesday, the “Saturday Night Live” comedian engaged actress Claire Foy in a food fight to preview her “SNL” guest host appearance this weekend. Davidson set up the “Animal House”-style exchange by telling “First Man” star Foy that it’s a show tradition. But she later discovers that it’s not ― with consequences. Note to Pete: Pasta comes off easily, unlike tattoos inspired by exes and a certain Supreme Court justice. Watch the food fl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>How Scooter Braun Discovers Talent | Fast Company - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KJgTAgEDkZ8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGNagu793499c-bcQf2qvcwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOKbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KJgTAgEDkZ8" target="_blank"&gt;How Scooter Braun Discovers Talent | Fast Company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a candid conversation, the founder of SB Projects (and talent manager for the likes of Ariana Grande, Kanye West, Psy, and Justin Bieber) discusses dealing with difficult clients, standing up for what you believe in, taking big risks, and how getting fired is a good thing. Fast Company is the world's leading progressive business media brand, with a unique editorial focus on innovation in technology, leadership, and design. Follow us on: https://www.facebook.com/FastCompany/ https://twitter.com/FastCompany https://www.instagram.com/fastcompany/ https://www.linkedin.com/company/fast-company/&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Trailer Is All 'Mean Girls' And Pete Davidson Jokes - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grandes-thank-u-next-trailer-is-all-mean-girls-pete-davidson_us_5bfd49d4e4b0771fb6be205e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIVcyV5950eb8YMuEskZQOsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 15:11:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ariana-grandes-thank-u-next-trailer-is-all-mean-girls-pete-davidson_us_5bfd49d4e4b0771fb6be205e" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Trailer Is All 'Mean Girls' And Pete Davidson Jokes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bring on the Ariana Grande extended cinematic universe. Music videos aren’t usually described as blockbusters, but the pop star has been building a superhero-movie level of hype ahead of the release of the music video for her No. 1 smash single “thank u, next.” The singer on Monday night dropped the teaser trailer for the video, which she promised is coming soon, and it’s just as gloriously 2000s and star-studded as we’d hoped. The short clip takes inspiration from a classic “Mean Girls” sequence in which high school students gossip about queen bee Regina George. Except this queen is played...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Donald Trump Singing Ariana Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Is All Kinds Of Unsettling - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/donald-trump-ariana-grande-thank-u-next-parody_us_5c00f821e4b0249dce7388dd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECbYTWaFRYKb3Iu-u43p6HgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 09:19:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/donald-trump-ariana-grande-thank-u-next-parody_us_5c00f821e4b0249dce7388dd" target="_blank"&gt;Donald Trump Singing Ariana Grande's 'Thank U, Next' Is All Kinds Of Unsettling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump may have been “most thankful” for his own work for America this Thanksgiving. But he’s decidedly more generous with his praise in YouTuber Maestro Ziikos’ new spoof video in which the president appears to warble away to pop star Ariana Grande’s latest hit “Thank U, Next.” Check out the clip here: And compare it to Grande’s original audio here:&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item></channel></rss>