<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Qualcomm Snapdragon - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRFJqYzJkdGJCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:31:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>The ACPC Is Transforming Into A Premium &amp; Enterprise PC With The Snapdragon 8cx Platform - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/06/the-acpc-is-transforming-into-a-premium-enterprise-pc-with-the-snapdragon-8cx-platform/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKVZ2ywvozG_Q76s1dqOr6QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/06/the-acpc-is-transforming-into-a-premium-enterprise-pc-with-the-snapdragon-8cx-platform/" target="_blank"&gt;The ACPC Is Transforming Into A Premium &amp; Enterprise PC With The Snapdragon 8cx Platform&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualcomm announces a new family of Snapdragon chipsets for PCs starting with the 8cx I posted yesterday on Qualcomm’s announcement about the Snapdragon 855 platform for 5G smartphones. While that was hard to top, today was just as exciting with the announcement of a new Snapdragon product and roadmap just targeting PCs. Qualcomm, with Microsoft on hand, announced the Snapdragon 8cx (the new nomenclature standards for Compute eXtreme). Qualcomm will have two roadmaps for PCs and mobile devices going forward. The PC roadmap begins with the 8cx. The block diagram for the Qualcomm Snapdragon 8c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECs8OiMwxPuwcZzcG4cRAdMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes no notch in the Galaxy S10, the 5G S10 confirmed for America, the OnePlus 5G heading to the UK, three new Nokia handsets, a review of the Pocophone F1, Huawei’s ongoing security issues, and an innovation award for the Pixel 3 and 3XL. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). No Notch, But There Will Be A Hole, In The New Galaxy S10 Samsung appe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Taking aim at Intel, Qualcomm launches chip for business PCs - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-intel/taking-aim-at-intel-qualcomm-launches-chip-for-business-pcs-idUSKBN1O52EF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMQ8c2KjxC_rzSRxRnY1uL8qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:50:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-intel/taking-aim-at-intel-qualcomm-launches-chip-for-business-pcs-idUSKBN1O52EF" target="_blank"&gt;Taking aim at Intel, Qualcomm launches chip for business PCs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), the biggest supplier of chips for mobile phones, on Thursday pushed further into the PC market with a line of chips designed to power business machines. Qualcomm's "Snapdragon" processor chips historically have been at the heart of mobile phones like Alphabet Inc's (GOOGL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Google Pixel phone and many Samsung Electronics Co Ltd (005930.KS: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) devices. Over the past year, though, Qualcomm adapted its chips to operate PCs running Microsoft Corp's (MSFT.O: Quot...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm Launches 5G With The Snapdragon 855 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/05/qualcomm-launches-5g-with-the-snapdragon-855/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEE9eii9TsBtzbZk2FeOQjMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/05/qualcomm-launches-5g-with-the-snapdragon-855/" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm Launches 5G With The Snapdragon 855&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Qualcomm Snapdragon 855 platform supports 5G applications and connectivity We have all become accustomed to new, faster, and more efficient mobile processors, or more appropriately called System-on-Chips or SoCs, every year as the mobile industry continues to push performance and functionality to new levels. With the slowing of Moore’s Law, one would expect the performance enhancements to mobile SoCs to slow, but as Qualcomm demonstrated with the new Snapdragon 855, that is not the case. Dubbed the first 5G chipset by Qualcomm, the Snapdragon 855 is a significant increase in performance...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy S10 Details Confirm Powerful Features - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-5g-qualcomm-snapdragon-855-confirmed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBfJb5891KEyjYbQeeJek7wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-5g-qualcomm-snapdragon-855-confirmed/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy S10 Details Confirm Powerful Features&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has confirmed its continuing partnership with Qualcomm will see the South Korean company use the new SnapDragon 855 system on chip inside 2019′s Galaxy smartphones, starting with its first 5G device for US market. Both Verizon and AT&amp;T have confirmed a 5G Galaxy smartphone will arrive in the first half of next year. While the connection was not explicitly made, Samsung’s VP of Product Marketing and Strategy, Justin Denison, confirmed that the upcoming US 5G smartphone from the South Korean company would be powered by Qualcomm’s SnapDragon 855 system on chip. The only handset we’re a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm unveils new chip to power 5G smartphones - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-samsung-elec/qualcomm-unveils-new-chip-to-power-5g-smartphones-idUSKBN1O32P1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMecw1wB_A6sq8OQSIV_45wqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:51:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-samsung-elec/qualcomm-unveils-new-chip-to-power-5g-smartphones-idUSKBN1O32P1" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm unveils new chip to power 5G smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chip supplier Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) on Tuesday unveiled a new generation of mobile phone processor chips that will power 5G smartphones in the United States as soon as next year. The key feature of the Snapdragon 855 chip, launched at an event in Hawaii, is a so-called modem for phones to connect to 5G wireless data networks with mobile data speeds of up to 50 or 100 times faster than current 4G networks. Mobile carriers are investing in 5G networks and are eager to sell 5G phones and data plans to recoup investment costs. Qualcomm, the largest supplier...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Living With An Always Connected PC (Part II) -- It Changed How I Use A PC - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/04/living-with-an-always-connected-pc-part-ii-it-changed-how-i-use-a-pc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEwu-cZIUbGfGnnFOCc5v7QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 07:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/04/living-with-an-always-connected-pc-part-ii-it-changed-how-i-use-a-pc/" target="_blank"&gt;Living With An Always Connected PC (Part II) -- It Changed How I Use A PC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ASUS NovaGo always-connected PC I wrote a few months ago about my experience with the ASUS NovaGo, one of the first Always-Connected PCs (ACPCs) introduced earlier this year. But after making it my primary PC, I felt it was worth providing a little more insight into the platform. The ACPC is not a new platform, but the combination of longer battery life achieved using the Qualcomm Snapdragon SoC and seamless connectivity that switches between integrated Wi-Fi and cellular modems accomplishes something the PC segment has lacked for the past decade–new usage models. ASUS NovaGo convertibl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENR6R3fi9qwUs_y2cSw6FUgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:42:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2" target="_blank"&gt;Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verizon Communications Inc and Samsung Electronics Co Ltd on Monday confirmed long-held industry expectations they would seek to steal a march on Apple Inc by launching U.S. 5G smartphones in the first half of 2019. The two companies said in a statement they would unveil a prototype, using Qualcomm Inc's modem chips, at the chipmaker's annual Snapdragon Technology Summit in Maui, Hawaii this week. While Verizon is leading the charge to trial 5G in some cities next year, industry analysts say the higher-speed networks are unlikely to be widely available until the middle of the next decade. A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pixel 3 Lite Leak Reveals Same Camera, Cheaper Price - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/paulmonckton/2018/11/29/pixel-3-lite-camera-cheaper-price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED_mkTRCTTBqfTwoGNAkzmEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 10:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/paulmonckton/2018/11/29/pixel-3-lite-camera-cheaper-price/" target="_blank"&gt;Pixel 3 Lite Leak Reveals Same Camera, Cheaper Price&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both versions of Google’s Pixel 3 handsets offer some of the best camera technology currently available. However, as is the case with all flagship products, it comes with a hefty price tag. Google’s Pixel 3 camera could be coming to a much less-expensive handset. Now, according to perennial leaker @VenyaGeskin1, it seems the much-rumoured simplified Pixel 3 model will soon launch fitted with the same top-of-the-range camera as the current high-end models. More Google Pixel 3 Lite “Sargo” Photos: https://t.co/D9XCuLeQbU pic.twitter.com/XCvHprAugV — Ben Geskin (@VenyaGeskin1) 26 November 2018...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>OnePlus Confirms Updated OnePlus 6T For Christmas - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/27/oneplus-6t-mclaren-salute-speed-new-update-confirmed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFXca_FQxFQvjo4DQy8_XOsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 01:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/27/oneplus-6t-mclaren-salute-speed-new-update-confirmed/" target="_blank"&gt;OnePlus Confirms Updated OnePlus 6T For Christmas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following on from the successful launch of the OnePlus 6T last month, OnePlus are set to launch an update to the critically acclaimed Android-powered smartphone alongside Formula 1 Grand Prix stalwarts McLaren. OnePlus 6T McLaren web page (oneplus.com) The event is taking place at the McLaren Technology Centre in Woking, England, on December 11th. Although no details have been released beyond a short promotional clip featuring memorabilia and archival footage from McLaren’s history, the slogan ‘Salute To Speed’ is intriguing. It might be a little bit too early to announce OnePlus’ first 5G...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>OnePlus 6T Review: Competitors Have Caught Up In Value, But OnePlus Software Still King - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/22/oneplus-6t-review-competition-have-caught-up-in-value-but-oneplus-software-still-king/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECVMFsGN2osEfA5lkyveg1cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 08:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/22/oneplus-6t-review-competition-have-caught-up-in-value-but-oneplus-software-still-king/" target="_blank"&gt;OnePlus 6T Review: Competitors Have Caught Up In Value, But OnePlus Software Still King&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The OnePlus 6T has a 6.4-inch OLED display. The OnePlus 6T is the fifth phone from the upstart brand I’ve tested in a professional capacity, and this is the toughest one to judge. It’s not because the 6T isn’t good, or a step backwards. No, it’s the best OnePlus phone yet. But it’s trickier this time around because circumstances around the phone have changed. For years, OnePlus phones were undoubtedly the best value on the market. Other phones that ran on the same Snapdragon chipset almost always cost several hundred dollars more, and other phones in the mid-tier market were significantly l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What's The Outlook Like For Qualcomm After A Mixed Fiscal 2018? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/08/whats-the-outlook-like-for-qualcomm-after-a-mixed-fiscal-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI6NnDrU2nyV9V5ar1zyo6cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 13:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/08/whats-the-outlook-like-for-qualcomm-after-a-mixed-fiscal-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;What's The Outlook Like For Qualcomm After A Mixed Fiscal 2018?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signage for 5G mobile experiences is seen at the Qualcomm Inc. booth at the Mobile World Congress Shanghai in Shanghai, China, on Thursday, June 28, 2018. Photographer: Qilai Shen/Bloomberg Wireless technology behemoth Qualcomm published its Q4 FY’18 results on Wednesday, November 7, reporting a better than expected set of results that were driven by stronger demand for the company’s chipsets from Chinese smartphone vendors, although this was partially offset by lower revenues from Apple. The company has guided for revenues of $4.5 billion to $5.3 billion for Q1 FY’19, marking a decline of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>OnePlus 6T's Biggest Threat Has Disappeared - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/07/oneplus-6t-opneplus-6-out-of-stock-sale-discount-update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI2abOO_4EWSqFxdi1eGnKMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/07/oneplus-6t-opneplus-6-out-of-stock-sale-discount-update/" target="_blank"&gt;OnePlus 6T's Biggest Threat Has Disappeared&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the OnePlus 6T goes on full release across the world (including a US launch with T-Mobile USA), one of the biggest obstacles to a successful retail launch has been removed. OnePlus 6T (image: Ewan Spence) Thanks to the short product cycle of six months used by the Shenzhen-based company, the handset that the OnePlus 6T is replacing is effectively out of stock around the world. Launched in May this year, the OnePlus 6 also features the same SnapDragon 845, the same 6GB or 8GB RAM choices, and the same camera hardware as the OnePlus 6T. While the latest update to OxygenOS is available ‘out...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Three Stunning Surprises You Can See Inside The New Xiaomi Mi 8 Pro - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/08/xiaomi-mi8-pro-uk-launch-release-date-transparent-android-specifications/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ4g87igYXI7tNO28CnGczQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 18:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/08/xiaomi-mi8-pro-uk-launch-release-date-transparent-android-specifications/" target="_blank"&gt;Three Stunning Surprises You Can See Inside The New Xiaomi Mi 8 Pro&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today saw Xiaomi enter the UK smartphone and consumer electronics with the launch of the flagship Mi 8 Pro smartphone, a solid portfolio of Android-powered handsets, a new store in London, and an electric scooter. How will Western markets take to the strange mix of Xiaomi’s consumer products, smartphones, and impactful branding? The bridgehead into the UK begins with the Mi 8 Pro smartphone. Xiaomi Mi 8 Pro (image: Ewan Spence) High Specifications At A Low Price Let’s face it, the table stakes for a flagship device make for a great phone. The Mi 8 Pro has the requisite SnapDragon 845 system...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What To Expect As Qualcomm Reports Q4 Results - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/05/what-to-expect-as-qualcomm-reports-q4-results/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJaRDUzWCF3xl2emMZdZRqUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 18:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/05/what-to-expect-as-qualcomm-reports-q4-results/" target="_blank"&gt;What To Expect As Qualcomm Reports Q4 Results&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visitors look at monitors in the Qualcomm Inc. booth at the World IT Show 2018 in Seoul, South Korea, on Wednesday, May 23, 2018. Photographer: SeongJoon Cho/Bloomberg Wireless technology behemoth Qualcomm is expected to publish its Q4 FY’18 results on Wednesday, November 7, reporting on a quarter that is likely to see the company post a mixed performance amid slowing global demand for smartphones and the company’s ongoing licensing disputes with Apple. The company has guided for revenues of $5.1 billion to $5.9 billion for the quarter, with earnings projected to come in at $0.75 – $0.85 pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>OnePlus 6T review: you'd have to spend double to get better than this - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/02/oneplus-6t-review-in-display-fingerprint-scanner-speedy-performance-all-screen-design-notch</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_UJv-kTaL5adyhH1QI0_8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 06:00:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/02/oneplus-6t-review-in-display-fingerprint-scanner-speedy-performance-all-screen-design-notch" target="_blank"&gt;OnePlus 6T review: you'd have to spend double to get better than this&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The OnePlus 6T proves that cutting-edge technology doesn’t have to cost the Earth, bringing an in-display fingerprint scanner and a tiny notch for just £500. OnePlus has kept things simple for years, offering top specifications for budget prices. The price has slowly crept up to not-quite-so budget, but the level of refinement and technology has also improved. The OnePlus 6T builds on the already excellent OnePlus 6, by further cutting away anything that isn’t screen. The gorgeous, crisp and colourful OLED display is a smidgen bigger at 6.41in, with a smaller chin at the bottom and a tiny t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>OnePlus 6T: cut-price flagship launches with in-screen fingerprint sensor - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/oct/29/oneplus-6t-cut-price-flagship-android-smartphone-launches-in-screen-fingerprint-sensor</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJwCmDcrKXIRFk-T5eKWwUAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 16:30:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/oct/29/oneplus-6t-cut-price-flagship-android-smartphone-launches-in-screen-fingerprint-sensor" target="_blank"&gt;OnePlus 6T: cut-price flagship launches with in-screen fingerprint sensor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OnePlus is putting a stake in the ground with its latest smartphone, saying cutting-edge technology doesn’t need to cost the best part of £1,000. The new OnePlus 6T, which starts at £499, has an all-screen design and large 6.41in FHD+ OLED display, but this time shrinks the notch at the top to a more bearable tiny teardrop shape, slims the chin at the bottom of the screen and fits a fingerprint scanner directly into the screen. The rest of the metal and glass sandwich matches the OnePlus 6, released six months ago. It has Qualcomm’s top-end Snapdragon 845 processor, a choice of 6 or 8GB of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>China’s OnePlus 6T has an American carrier in T-Mobile - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90258309/chinas-oneplus-6t-has-an-american-carrier-in-t-mobile</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHY2C9TNjDVqjdcEWWVKuNYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 13:24:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90258309/chinas-oneplus-6t-has-an-american-carrier-in-t-mobile" target="_blank"&gt;China’s OnePlus 6T has an American carrier in T-Mobile&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After notching $1 billion in revenue and turning a profit last year, phone maker OnePlus is getting its first U.S. wireless carrier deal with T-Mobile, which will sell the just-announced OnePlus 6T in 5,600 retail stores. The OnePlus 6T bears several similarities to other high-end phones from Vivo and Oppo, which are also owned by parent company BBK, but don’t have wireless carrier deals. Most notably, it has a fingerprint reader built into the display glass–a first for the U.S. market–and just a small camera cutout near the top of the 6.41-inch screen. Other specs include a Qualcomm Snapdr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi Mi Mix 3 Hands-On: The Slider Phone With 10GB of RAM - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/10/25/xiaomi-mi-mix-3-hands-on-the-slider-phone-with-10gb-of-ram/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIXTYu6dM8EZpyatXkx3t3UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 03:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/10/25/xiaomi-mi-mix-3-hands-on-the-slider-phone-with-10gb-of-ram/" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi Mi Mix 3 Hands-On: The Slider Phone With 10GB of RAM&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lei Jun speaks at Xiaomi’s launch event for the Mi Mix 3 at the Palace Museum on Oct. 25 in Beijing, China. (Photo: Liang Shuang/Huanqiu.com/VCG via Getty Images) Xiaomi’s original Mi Mix, released in the fall of 2016, was an industry shaker that ditched several traditional smartphone hardware parts and ignored conventional design cues to achieve its at the time near-bezel-less look. Of course, the competition for jaw-dropping design has gotten much stiffer in 2018, a fact even Xiaomi founder and CEO Lei Jun admitted during yesterday’s launch event of the Mi Mix 3. The Xiaomi Mi Mix 3 (righ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Google's New Hardware Showcases Its AI Capabilities - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/moorinsights/2018/10/23/googles-new-hardware-showcases-its-ai-capabilities/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKUfmORqNiD8Uq5M6UZWS9YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 15:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/moorinsights/2018/10/23/googles-new-hardware-showcases-its-ai-capabilities/" target="_blank"&gt;Google's New Hardware Showcases Its AI Capabilities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google held its annual hardware event in New York City last week. Google’s Pixel 3 launch was possibly one of the most heavily leaked launches in industry history, with virtually all of the specifications of the device unveiled before the event began. Google was very aware of this fact and cobbled together a montage of YouTubers discussing the leaks that played before the event began. However, Google still had some surprises up its sleeves, in regards to the software and AI capabilities of the Pixel 3 and other devices. Like previous Google hardware events, this wasn’t just about showcasing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple's New iPhones Have An Unfixable Problem - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/10/14/apple-new-iphones-iphone-xs-max-battery-life-price-cost-upgrade-xr/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVwV-BFnAQm4TPgVrFvN3cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/10/14/apple-new-iphones-iphone-xs-max-battery-life-price-cost-upgrade-xr/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple's New iPhones Have An Unfixable Problem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While they hide some great secret features, even Apple has been forced to admit its new iPhone XS (details) and iPhone XS Max (details) were shipped with problems. The good news is Apple fixed most of them, but new tests confirm there is one it can do nothing about… Putting to bed questions about real-world performance, popular YouTube site PhoneBuff enlisted the help of robotics and discovered that for all the iPhone XS and iPhone XS Max’s incredible CPU performance, battery life is a mess. Particularly the bigger model. Apple’s iPhone XS (middle) and iPhone XS Max (left) have a battery ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Razer Finally Delivers Chroma Color Excitement To Gamers With Razer Phone 2 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/10/11/razer-phone-2-chroma-color-launch-release-date-specifications/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECc5cSO_hjT1wzcFUJA7118qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 08:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/10/11/razer-phone-2-chroma-color-launch-release-date-specifications/" target="_blank"&gt;Razer Finally Delivers Chroma Color Excitement To Gamers With Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following last year’s almost surprising launch of the Razer Phone, the Singapore-based Razer has updated its smartphone and announced the imaginatively titled Razer Phone 2. Last year’s model put the focus squarely on mobile gaming, and this year’s update carries on that mantle with the promise of “up to thirty percent more power”. That comes from the combination of Qualcomm’s SnapDragon 845 system on chip and the Adreno 630 graphics processing unit; along with improved cooling, the 5.7 inch screen with 120 Hz refresh, and the 4000 mAh battery. Forbes’ Ben Sin has taken a closer look at the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Galaxy S10 Leak Suddenly Exposes Samsung's Radical Smartphone - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/10/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-upgrade-5g-qualcomm-release-date-cost-price-galaxy-s9-note9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBecV07p0vOu_hnLDrw5fNcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/10/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-upgrade-5g-qualcomm-release-date-cost-price-galaxy-s9-note9/" target="_blank"&gt;Galaxy S10 Leak Suddenly Exposes Samsung's Radical Smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung is very excited about the Galaxy S10, and you should be too. The Galaxy range’s 10th-anniversary model will have slimmer bezels, an ’ultrasonic’ in-display reader, triple rear cameras, gradient colors and a 5G option. And now Samsung has accidentally leaked its next-generation chipset… Credit for the spot goes to eagle-eyed XDA Developers’ writer Max Weinbach who discovered it buried deep in Samsung’s code for its upcoming Galaxy S9 Android Pie update, alongside references to the folding Galaxy F. And the wider consequences are significant. The Galaxy S10 will be Samsung’s most amb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Google Pixel 3 XL Early 'Review' Evokes iPhone XS Max - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brookecrothers/2018/10/06/google-pixel-3-xl-early-review-evokes-iphone-xs-max/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDOV4WY0cPkNGDUvmtqLiBkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 21:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brookecrothers/2018/10/06/google-pixel-3-xl-early-review-evokes-iphone-xs-max/" target="_blank"&gt;Google Pixel 3 XL Early 'Review' Evokes iPhone XS Max&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pixel 3 and Pixel 3 XL. A fresh Pixel 3 XL “review” seems to confirm that Google has adopted key design facets of Apple’s biggest phone, as the Pixel’s release date nears. About halfway through a Pixel 3 XL “review” from Unwire.HK* (via Android Police) there is a telling image of the 3 XL next to the iPhone XS Max (see image below). If accurate, the Pixel 3 XL not only has the iPhone’s notch and its bezel-less (mostly) front but is similar in size, sporting a 6.3-inch display (vs the iPhone XS Max’s 6.5-inch), as the Unwire.HK review shows. Those are not trivial features since they pretty m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New OnePlus 6T Leak Reveals Powerful Secret - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/09/29/oneplus-6t-battery-wireless-charging-power-leak/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDCeur3XDOq6qrGIIWTHN1cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 22:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/09/29/oneplus-6t-battery-wireless-charging-power-leak/" target="_blank"&gt;New OnePlus 6T Leak Reveals Powerful Secret&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With just over two weeks to go until its expected launch, the latest OnePlus 6T leak may have revealed a much larger battery to power the flagship smartphone from Shenzhen. The latest details come via social network Weibo, and shows the alleged battery. While the OnePlus 6 has a 3300 mAh battery, the upcoming OnePlus 6T is on course to sport a 3610 mAh battery. We also have a part number – BLP68S – and it should come as no surprise to anyone that the latest Oppo handset (the Oppo R17 Pro) features the same battery. OnePlus 6T pre-launch images (OnePlus) Although different companies, there h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How Qualcomm Escaped A $774 Million Antitrust Fine And Boosted Taiwan's Tech Hub - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphjennings/2018/09/19/how-qualcomm-escaped-a-760-million-antitrust-fine-and-made-tech-hub-taiwan-happy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENNBG4n5O0eKZO2qFCCJXjcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 01:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphjennings/2018/09/19/how-qualcomm-escaped-a-760-million-antitrust-fine-and-made-tech-hub-taiwan-happy/" target="_blank"&gt;How Qualcomm Escaped A $774 Million Antitrust Fine And Boosted Taiwan's Tech Hub&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualcomm Inc. CEO Steve Mollenkopf speaks during a keynote address at CES 2017 at The Venetian Las Vegas in January 2017 in Las Vegas, Nevada. (Photo: Ethan Miller/Getty Images). What a difference a year makes. Last October, Taiwan’s Fair Trade Commission fined American chip developer Qualcomm NT$23.4 billion ($774 million). The commission found that Qualcomm had used its dominant position in the modem chip market to charge unfair royalties and terms for its patents. Taiwan matters because it accounted for 12% of the company’s fiscal revenue in 2016 through its sales to a long list of local...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm's Snapdragon 3100 Platform Ushers In New Era Of Wearables - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/moorinsights/2018/09/11/qualcomms-snapdragon-3100-platform-ushers-in-new-era-of-wearables/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELdErsApnUkhD0pKT3xXAXMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/moorinsights/2018/09/11/qualcomms-snapdragon-3100-platform-ushers-in-new-era-of-wearables/" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm's Snapdragon 3100 Platform Ushers In New Era Of Wearables&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wearables continue to become more functional and fashionable. While some continue to question the viability of the wearables market, each generation of devices is becoming more capable. The success of the Apple watch has certainly helped, along with the growth of companies like Fitbit, Mobvoi, and Garmin. I think we’re closer to the perfect smartwatch than ever before, and a lot of credit goes to Qualcomm, the chipmaker who has managed to effectively corner the market in the last several years. Yesterday, Qualcomm announced its next generation of its Snapdragon Wear processors, the Snapdrag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Can Qualcomm See Wearables Success With The Snapdragon Wear 3100 Chip? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/09/11/can-qualcomm-see-wearables-success-with-the-snapdragon-wear-3100-chip/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENELOpT-c_l6g-EocoK8aGAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/09/11/can-qualcomm-see-wearables-success-with-the-snapdragon-wear-3100-chip/" target="_blank"&gt;Can Qualcomm See Wearables Success With The Snapdragon Wear 3100 Chip?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signage for 5G mobile experiences is seen at the Qualcomm Inc. booth at the Mobile World Congress Shanghai in Shanghai, China, on Thursday, June 28, 2018. Photographer: Qilai Shen/Bloomberg Qualcomm introduced a smartwatch chipset called the Snapdragon Wear 3100 at an event held on Monday, marking its first major smartwatch chip launch in over two years. The chip, which is based on an all-new architecture, will be crucial to driving Qualcomm’s growth in the wearables market, as the company looks for new avenues of expansion, considering its slowing smartphone SoC sales and headwinds at its ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm Demonstrates Performance In Wearables And IoT - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/09/12/qualcomm-demonstrates-performance-in-wearables-and-iot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAW98NwHvEQBvj_Io_xWE0IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 04:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/09/12/qualcomm-demonstrates-performance-in-wearables-and-iot/" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm Demonstrates Performance In Wearables And IoT&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smartwatches are tied to fashion and lifestyle On Monday, Qualcomm announced a new platform for smartwatches dubbed the Snapdragon Wear 3100. Qualcomm first introduced the Snapdragon Wear platform with the Snapdragon Wear 2100 in early 2016 and followed by a series of other products aimed at anything from smart trackers to premium watches. While the market for wearables has been slowly developing compared to the catastrophic growth rate of smartphones, it is still growing, and Qualcomm has become the leader in Android-based smartwatches and other devices. The new platform combines four Arm ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Xiaomi's $300 Pocophone Vs. Samsung's $1,250 Galaxy Note 9: It's Closer Than You'd Think - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/10/xiaomis-300-pocophone-vs-samsungs-1250-galaxy-note-9-its-closer-than-youd-think/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPxab-kyNIoTfnbY3K3e1cIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 06:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/10/xiaomis-300-pocophone-vs-samsungs-1250-galaxy-note-9-its-closer-than-youd-think/" target="_blank"&gt;Xiaomi's $300 Pocophone Vs. Samsung's $1,250 Galaxy Note 9: It's Closer Than You'd Think&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pocophone, left, and the Samsung Galaxy Note 9. Three years ago, Lenovo’s CEO Yang Yuanqing pulled his company out of the high-end smartphone battleground, saying that there were “too many Chinese vendors,” some of whom were “playing irrationally.” He was referring to the price war that saw — and continues to see — Chinese brands push smartphone pricing lower and lower in order to gain an edge. That price war is still going strong three years on. In fact, it may be more irrational than ever. I recently reviewed Samsung’s much-hyped Galaxy Note 9, and though I really liked the phone (so ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Pixel 3: Google Confirms New Smartphones Launch For October 9 In New York - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/09/07/pixel-3-google-confirms-new-smartphones-launch-for-october-9-in-new-york/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBoEQUT3PaVc70R4FUZY9xUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 17:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/09/07/pixel-3-google-confirms-new-smartphones-launch-for-october-9-in-new-york/" target="_blank"&gt;Pixel 3: Google Confirms New Smartphones Launch For October 9 In New York&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next month, Google will unveil its latest flagship smartphone lineup, the Pixel 3, and perhaps an update to the Google Home product family of smart speakers and of the Pixel Buds headsets. (ELIJAH NOUVELAGE/AFP/Getty Images) Google sent out media invitations to its ‘Made by Google’ event which will take place on October 9 at Spring Studios in New York City. As I wrote previously, the tech giant will not announce any smartwatch running its latest Wear OS operating system but instead focus this fall on its flagship smartphone lineup, the Pixel, and perhaps an update of its Google Home product...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Huawei Kirin 980 Looks Good On Paper But AnandTech Benchmarking Accusations Could Indicate Otherwise - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickmoorhead/2018/09/05/huawei-kirin-980-looks-good-on-paper-but-anandtech-benchmarking-accusations-could-indicate-otherwise/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDLM6A7tS-dswyqAVorG6Q8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickmoorhead/2018/09/05/huawei-kirin-980-looks-good-on-paper-but-anandtech-benchmarking-accusations-could-indicate-otherwise/" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei Kirin 980 Looks Good On Paper But AnandTech Benchmarking Accusations Could Indicate Otherwise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei has been on an up and down roller coaster related to smartphones as of late. On one hand, it achieved the number two global smartphone unit market share position surpassing Apple, only second to Samsung. Its premium smartphone market share is up, too, so it’s more than Huawei selling just cheap phones, and based on Moor Insights &amp; Strategy analyst Anshel Sag’s analysis, the company has the best smartphone camera at this moment with the P20 Pro. I love the P20 Pro’s 3X physical zoom lens. Last week at IFA, Huawei announced the Kirin 980 processor and characterized it in its press rel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Samsung Resets The Business Phone Bar Again With The Note9, Three Weeks In Review - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickmoorhead/2018/09/04/samsung-resets-the-business-phone-bar-again-with-the-note9-three-weeks-in-review/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHhu_I0-mHqhOa9etvgoVb4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 17:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickmoorhead/2018/09/04/samsung-resets-the-business-phone-bar-again-with-the-note9-three-weeks-in-review/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Resets The Business Phone Bar Again With The Note9, Three Weeks In Review&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Samsung Galaxy Note9 The Samsung Galaxy Note9 is the next in a series of business and creativity-focused smartphone devices that Samsung has been releasing for many years. Because the Note line has traditionally been a second half of the year release, it comes out with a more refined feel than its “S” and “S+” brother. This year’s model is no exception with the New Samsung Galaxy Note9 shipping with the latest and greatest features and, of course, with a new stylus. This year’s Note9 is by no means a ground-breaking change from the Note8, but it makes many improvements across the board ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Huawei's Kirin 980 Is The World's First 7-Nanometer Mobile Chipset With 5G Support - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/01/huaweis-kirin-980-is-the-worlds-first-7-nanometer-mobile-chipset-with-5g-support/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED2Tat4FFH-2pQKP-oOKFDQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 06:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/09/01/huaweis-kirin-980-is-the-worlds-first-7-nanometer-mobile-chipset-with-5g-support/" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei's Kirin 980 Is The World's First 7-Nanometer Mobile Chipset With 5G Support&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Kirin 980 chipset. The results for the heated race to release the first mainstream 7-nanometer mobile processor are in, and Huawei has edged Apple to come in first. At the IFA trade show in Berlin today, Huawei’s consumer head, Richard Yu, unveiled the company’s next flagship chipset, the Kirin 980, and it is, as rumored, a 7nm SoC (systems-on-a-chip). Apple will almost certainly announce its own 7nm chipset on Sept. 12 during its iPhone launch, but for the record books, Huawei introduced it to the world first. So what is 7nm, and why does it matter? The “nanometer” part refers to the s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple 6.5-inch iPhone XS Vs. Google Pixel 3 XL: Specs, Price, Release Date, Leaks - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brookecrothers/2018/09/01/apple-6-5-inch-iphone-xs-vs-google-pixel-3-xl-specs-price-release-date-leaks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEESMWoPMbQ4-ZO3TQc88ek4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 18:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brookecrothers/2018/09/01/apple-6-5-inch-iphone-xs-vs-google-pixel-3-xl-specs-price-release-date-leaks/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple 6.5-inch iPhone XS Vs. Google Pixel 3 XL: Specs, Price, Release Date, Leaks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘iPhone XS’ via 9to5Mac A fall showdown is set for the next monster flagship phones from two American tech giants. On one side, we have the Pixel 3 XL apparently just landing at the FCC. On the other side, we have the 6.5-inch iPhone with the “XS” branding* scheme. So, it’s time for a (preliminary) side-by-side. 6.5-inch iPhone: - Notch (front): integrates Face ID camera etc. - Display: 6.5-inch diagonal edge-to-edge, 2,688-by-1,242 pixel resolution - Processor: next-gen A12 - Frame: stainless steel - Camera: rear dual 12MP - Battery: extra-large battery (possibly 3,300 to 3,400 mAh) - Wire...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Opinion: Qualcomm claims wireless dominance over Intel and Apple - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/qualcomm-claims-wireless-dominance-over-intel-and-apple-2018-07-23</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECD-t9VbncxNOkg8J23aw40qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 20:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/qualcomm-claims-wireless-dominance-over-intel-and-apple-2018-07-23" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: Qualcomm claims wireless dominance over Intel and Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Ryan Shrout With speed-testing data, Qualcomm is attempting to turn its leadership position into a wave of partner deals and relationships Bloomberg News Qualcomm is going on the offensive in its wireless business, attacking rival products from Intel and the Apple iPhones that integrate them. A collection of new data from Ookla, the largest and most prominent internet-speed-testing service, shows that Android phones integrating Qualcomm (QCOM) modems have significantly better wireless performance than iPhones that are using Intel (INTC) modems. Phones integrating Qualcomm modems show u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Opinion: Intel’s development of 5G is at risk in Apple-Qualcomm lawsuit - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/intels-development-of-5g-is-at-risk-in-apple-qualcomm-lawsuit-2018-06-29</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1GRMA2ybwuT2rDkFD75EcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 15:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/intels-development-of-5g-is-at-risk-in-apple-qualcomm-lawsuit-2018-06-29" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: Intel’s development of 5G is at risk in Apple-Qualcomm lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Ryan Shrout Upholding Qualcomm’s request to prevent Apple from importing iPhones that use Intel modem technology could imperil next-gen technology Reuters An Intel lawyer said the company may have to reduce or remove plans to develop 5G-capable cellular technology if courts held up a Qualcomm request to halt sales of Apple iPhones that included current-generation Intel modems. As part of an ITC (International Trade Commission) patent case filed by Qualcomm (QCOM) against Apple (AAPL) one of several legal disputes between the two companies, Intel technology lawyer Steven Bowers testified...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm extends NXP tender offer yet again - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-nxp-semicondtrs/qualcomm-extends-nxp-tender-offer-yet-again-idUSKBN1JP28D</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKa9nNE_EUtou19Oiw9F-LsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 15:03:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-nxp-semicondtrs/qualcomm-extends-nxp-tender-offer-yet-again-idUSKBN1JP28D" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm extends NXP tender offer yet again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Sonam Rai (Reuters) - U.S. chipmaker Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) on Friday extended the tender offer for its proposed $44 billion deal to buy NXP Semiconductors NV (NXPI.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) for the 29th time as it awaits clearance from the Chinese government. Qualcomm, which supplies chips to Android smartphone makers and Apple (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), will become the leading supplier to the fast-growing automotive chip market if the deal goes through. The biggest-ever deal in the semiconductor industry has faced...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm-NXP deal still waiting for China nod: sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-nxp/qualcomm-nxp-deal-still-waiting-for-china-nod-sources-idUSKBN1JA3AG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN9McvNRFmWeT7QyxXapUgAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 18:48:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-nxp/qualcomm-nxp-deal-still-waiting-for-china-nod-sources-idUSKBN1JA3AG" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm-NXP deal still waiting for China nod: sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING/SHANGHAI (Reuters) - China is yet to approve U.S. chipmaker Qualcomm Inc's (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) proposed $44 billion acquisition of NXP Semiconductors (NXPI.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), three people close to the talks said, dismissing an earlier media report that said Beijing had already greenlit the deal. Chinese clearance would remove a long-running roadblock to the deal that has become entangled with broader trade tensions between the United States and China. The acquisition has already got a nod from eight of the nine required global regula...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm will not exit data center business, chip chief says - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-chips/qualcomm-will-not-exit-data-center-business-chip-chief-says-idUSKBN1J902Z</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMHiN1CcT1rNEqQZ9c0jS9kqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:49:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-chips/qualcomm-will-not-exit-data-center-business-chip-chief-says-idUSKBN1J902Z" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm will not exit data center business, chip chief says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Stephen Nellis (Reuters) - Qualcomm Inc has no plans to abandon its efforts to create processors for data centers, the company's president, who oversees the chip division, said. Qualcomm, the largest maker of chips in mobile phones, last year launched chips that use technology from Softbank Group Corp's ARM Holdings to power the workhorse computer servers behind cloud-based services such as social networks. Qualcomm's push to enter the data center market puts it in direct competition with Intel Corp, which dominates data centers and now draws half of its revenue from servers and other "d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China's markets regulator says still reviewing Qualcomm-NXP deal - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-nxp/chinas-markets-regulator-says-still-reviewing-qualcomm-nxp-deal-idUSKCN1IX3WM?il=0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECAsguhhUvaMRa3OwS0ESG8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 08:42:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-nxp/chinas-markets-regulator-says-still-reviewing-qualcomm-nxp-deal-idUSKCN1IX3WM?il=0" target="_blank"&gt;China's markets regulator says still reviewing Qualcomm-NXP deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (Reuters) - China's markets regulator said on Friday it is still reviewing Qualcomm Inc's (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) proposed $44 billion acquisition of NXP Semiconductors NV (NXPI.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) and is in talks with Qualcomm about ways to eliminate negative impact from the deal. The State Administration for Market Regulation (SAMR) is conducting the antitrust review in a fair and open way, the regulator said in a faxed response to a Reuters request for comment. Clearance for the takeover comes at a time of rising U.S.-China trade tensio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Opinion: Qualcomm’s stock is poised to go from cold to hot - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/qualcomms-stock-is-poised-to-go-from-cold-to-hot-2018-05-31</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKMBpEXDy1ZrLHrW5sD4xYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwqJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/qualcomms-stock-is-poised-to-go-from-cold-to-hot-2018-05-31" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: Qualcomm’s stock is poised to go from cold to hot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OUTSIDE THE BOX By Daniel Newman Prepare for three reasons that could have the stock sizzling Getty Images Qualcomm has been on quite the roller coaster over the past few months. In the wake of President Trump’s extraordinary intervention in March to stop Broadcom (AVGO) from acquiring Qualcomm (QCOM) on national security grounds, the rumor mill about this maker of computer chips and wireless telecom equipment has been spinning at what feels like record speed. There’s been speculation about a takeover bid by former chairman Paul Jacobs and a series of opinion articles that seem to overplay ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm to meet China regulators in push to clear $44 billion NXP deal: sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-nxp/qualcomm-to-meet-china-regulators-in-push-to-clear-44-billion-nxp-deal-sources-idUSKCN1IS04X</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG4hxFhIoCkKlDu2CO_WG4QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 09:33:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-nxp/qualcomm-to-meet-china-regulators-in-push-to-clear-44-billion-nxp-deal-sources-idUSKCN1IS04X" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm to meet China regulators in push to clear $44 billion NXP deal: sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Matthew Miller BEIJING (Reuters) - Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) is expecting to meet this week in Beijing with China's antitrust regulators in a final push to secure clearance for its proposed $44 billion acquisition of NXP Semiconductors NV (NXPI.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), three sources told Reuters. The acquisition has been caught in the crosshairs of rising U.S.-China trade tensions, with sources saying an approval would depend on the progress of broader bilateral talks. The deal has got a nod from eight of the nine required global regulat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Chinese authorities expected to OK Qualcomm’s bid to buy NXP - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/chinese-authorities-expected-to-ok-qualcomms-bid-to-buy-nxp-2018-05-26</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDyFMEkuExcrcB0_X7sxJ3MqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 15:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/chinese-authorities-expected-to-ok-qualcomms-bid-to-buy-nxp-2018-05-26" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese authorities expected to OK Qualcomm’s bid to buy NXP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WALL STREET JOURNAL By Yoko Kubota , Lingling Wei Bloomberg Chinese authorities are set to approve Qualcomm Inc.’s planned $44 billion acquisition of Netherlands-based NXP Semiconductors NV in the next few days, according to people familiar with the matter, in what would be another significant step toward easing frayed U.S.-China trade relations. China’s State Administration for Market Regulation, which has been conducting the antitrust review, will hold a meeting on the matter Monday, according to the people. They said a contingent of Qualcomm’s (QCOM) legal team arrived in Beijing t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Chip-maker stocks notch losing week after Applied Materials outlook slams sector - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/chipmaker-stocks-slammed-by-applied-materials-outlook-2018-05-18</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENs6SFws7DtUaeoL6E8SqZAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 10:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/chipmaker-stocks-slammed-by-applied-materials-outlook-2018-05-18" target="_blank"&gt;Chip-maker stocks notch losing week after Applied Materials outlook slams sector&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RATINGS GAME By Wallace Witkowski AMD, Qualcomm shares break trend, trade higher Friday Applied Materials/Digiman Studio Applied Materials Inc. led semiconductor-related stocks to losses Friday and to a weekly decline after the chip-maker materials supplier’s outlook indicated a possible slowing in the recently hot sector. Applied Materials (AMAT) shares fell 8.3% to close at $49.51, after hitting an intraday low of $48.53, as analysts were split on target price moves after the company’s sales outlook was lighter than Wall Street expected. In comparison, the PHLX Semiconductor Index (S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm to depose Apple services chief Eddy Cue - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-qualcomm/qualcomm-to-depose-apple-services-chief-eddy-cue-idUSKBN1I52I4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPXonI5bAmiB5R47KPWb7HwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 20:52:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-qualcomm/qualcomm-to-depose-apple-services-chief-eddy-cue-idUSKBN1I52I4" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm to depose Apple services chief Eddy Cue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Stephen Nellis (Reuters) - Qualcomm Inc can depose Apple Inc's services chief Eddy Cue in addition to Chief Executive Tim Cook, a magistrate judge in the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of California ruled on Friday, part of the chipmaker's effort to determine whether Apple worked with Samsung to focus regulatory scrutiny on Qualcomm. The access to Cue is important because Qualcomm alleges talks between executives at Apple and its rival Samsung Electronics Co Ltd were central to its decision to cut off Apple from a stream of nearly $1 billion in licensing rebate payments. A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm's patent deals aim to ease Apple, regulator tensions, executive says - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-qualcomm-licensing/qualcomms-patent-deals-aim-to-ease-apple-regulator-tensions-exec-says-idUSKBN1I22IP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4eRykD77q4CKYcNADYRhYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:33:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-qualcomm-licensing/qualcomms-patent-deals-aim-to-ease-apple-regulator-tensions-exec-says-idUSKBN1I22IP" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm's patent deals aim to ease Apple, regulator tensions, executive says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Stephen Nellis (Reuters) - Qualcomm Inc has broadened its use of a lower-cost licensing model for the next generation of mobile data networks, a move that could help in contentious talks with two customers including iPhone maker Apple Inc, the wireless tech company's patent licensing chief said on Monday. The patent business traditionally has supplied much of Qualcomm's profit but has also spurred conflict with Apple, Samsung Electronics Ltd and Huawei Technologies Co Ltd as well as regulators in China, South Korea and the United States. New deals could lower the licensing rate that Qual...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm earnings: Amid takeover drama, what matters most is smartphone-chip sales - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/qualcomm-earnings-amid-takeover-drama-what-matters-most-is-smartphone-chip-sales-2018-04-23</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEODrQReSrFKtpYvnohAY2LUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 13:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/qualcomm-earnings-amid-takeover-drama-what-matters-most-is-smartphone-chip-sales-2018-04-23" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm earnings: Amid takeover drama, what matters most is smartphone-chip sales&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EARNINGS OUTLOOK By Wallace Witkowski Concerns rise that NXP deal may become a trade-war casualty Qualcomm’s Snapdragon 835 processor (center) is displayed next to the Snapdragon 820 processor and a penny. Getty Images Chip sales to smartphone vendors and how Qualcomm Inc. moves forward after fending off a takeover from Broadcom Inc. will be among the main topics of focus for investors as the chipmaker reports its earnings this quarter. Qualcomm (QCOM) is scheduled to report earnings late Wednesday, but company fundamentals have been getting drowned out lately by the Broadcom takeover atte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm chip sales indicate some smartphone strength - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-results/qualcomm-chip-sales-indicate-some-smartphone-strength-idUSKBN1HW2ST</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMUsAy1p3t1iscMEKuSXmAMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 23:55:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-results/qualcomm-chip-sales-indicate-some-smartphone-strength-idUSKBN1HW2ST" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm chip sales indicate some smartphone strength&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Sonam Rai and Stephen Nellis (Reuters) - U.S. chipmaker Qualcomm Inc's (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) quarterly profit and revenue topped Wall Street forecasts, suggesting that a slowdown in the global smartphone business might be less severe than feared after a string of weak forecasts from suppliers. The results announced in Qualcomm's smartphone chip business contrasted to those from major mobile phone components makers in Asia, including TSMC (2330.TW: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) and SK Hynix Inc (000660.KS: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), which have ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm shares tick higher on earnings beat, but outlook disappoints - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/qualcomm-shares-tick-higher-on-earnings-beat-but-outlook-disappoints-2018-04-25</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXpxCuNdBn9T2_dIcAWeKsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/qualcomm-shares-tick-higher-on-earnings-beat-but-outlook-disappoints-2018-04-25" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm shares tick higher on earnings beat, but outlook disappoints&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EARNINGS RESULTS By Wallace Witkowski Muted forecast does not include disputed Apple royalties, NXP deal Bloomberg News Qualcomm Inc. shares rose in the extended session Wednesday after the chipmaker’s quarterly results topped Wall Street estimates but were held in check by a less-than-stellar guidance. Qualcomm (QCOM) shares rose 1.3% after hours, following a 0.4% decline to close at $49.75 in the regular session. At Wednesday’s close, Qualcomm shares are down 22% for the year to date, compared with a 0.9% decline in the PHLX Semiconductor Index (SOX) and a 1.3% decline in the S&amp;P 500 in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Earnings Preview: What To Expect From Qualcomm Today - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamsarhan/2018/04/25/earnings-preview-what-to-expect-from-qualcomm-today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP3XfZaWo4xpTyfXFHG2WG8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamsarhan/2018/04/25/earnings-preview-what-to-expect-from-qualcomm-today/" target="_blank"&gt;Earnings Preview: What To Expect From Qualcomm Today&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualcomm logo, at Qualcomm pavilion, during theMobile World Congress day 3, on February 28, 2018 in Barcelona, Spain. (Photo by Joan Cros/NurPhoto via Getty Images) Qualcomm Inc. is scheduled to report earnings after Wednesday’s close. The stock hit a record high of $100.00/share in 2000 and is trading near $49/share. The stock is prone to big moves after reporting earnings and can easily gap up if the numbers are strong. Conversely, if the numbers disappoint, the stock can easily gap down. To help you prepare, here is what the Street is expecting: Earnings Preview: Qualcomm is expected to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm easing licensing terms in bid to strike deals - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-licensing/qualcomm-easing-licensing-terms-in-bid-to-strike-deals-idUSKBN1HX08K</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIwn8-8d-CGHBUKWKHFFAQMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 04:26:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-licensing/qualcomm-easing-licensing-terms-in-bid-to-strike-deals-idUSKBN1HX08K" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm easing licensing terms in bid to strike deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Stephen Nellis and Sonam Rai SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Qualcomm Inc's earnings call on Wednesday showed just how far the company is willing to go to preserve one of its core business practices of taking a cut of the selling price of phones. The San Diego-based chipmaker posted quarterly profit and revenue that topped Wall Street forecasts, suggesting that a slowdown in the global smartphone business might be less severe than feared after a string of weak forecasts from other industry suppliers. But Qualcomm's other line of business - licensing a trove of patents that help make smart phon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>ZTE tells suppliers China trade row may be factor in U.S. ban: source - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-zte/zte-tells-suppliers-china-trade-row-may-be-factor-in-u-s-ban-source-idUSKBN1HX0BM</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA1zYRbahwV8H240gtiVZt0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 05:32:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-zte/zte-tells-suppliers-china-trade-row-may-be-factor-in-u-s-ban-source-idUSKBN1HX0BM" target="_blank"&gt;ZTE tells suppliers China trade row may be factor in U.S. ban: source&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Karen Freifeld NEW YORK (Reuters) - China's ZTE Corp (000063.SZ: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) held a conference call on Wednesday with major suppliers, during which a company representative suggested the trade dispute with Beijing may have been a factor in last week's U.S. order banning American firms from selling goods to the smartphone maker, according to a person familiar with the call. The Commerce Department last week banned American firms from doing business with ZTE after the company violated an agreement reached after it was caught selling U.S. goods to Iran despite U.S....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm profits bitten by legal battle over iPhone royalties - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e5d68fb8-48af-11e8-8ae9-4b5ddcca99b3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOJlsiKNMuz7LWyEsVV6S4wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 20:38:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e5d68fb8-48af-11e8-8ae9-4b5ddcca99b3" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm profits bitten by legal battle over iPhone royalties&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualcomm saw its profits cut in half as a painful legal dispute with Apple over iPhone royalties drags on, but it still beat Wall Street estimates for the quarter. Earnings of 80 cents per share beat analysts’ estimates of 70 cents as Qualcomm shrugged off wider concerns about the health of the smartphone market. Wednesday saw the mobile chipmaker’s first quarterly earnings report since rival Broadcom abandoned its hostile takeover bid in March, after the deal was blocked by President Donald Trump over national security concerns. The company is now trying to cut $1bn in costs and complete i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm comes under pressure on legal disputes - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/6909e5a0-48ca-11e8-8ee8-cae73aab7ccb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcj5tlpIaSyzTaC7UilZnYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 02:07:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6909e5a0-48ca-11e8-8ee8-cae73aab7ccb" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm comes under pressure on legal disputes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualcomm accumulated a $125m legal bill in the three months to March and the chipmaker warned its costs would rise further in the coming months, as it prepares for a number of courtroom battles against Apple and US regulators. Apple’s legal onslaught against Qualcomm over smartphone patent royalties has already put a huge dent in the chipmaker’s profits. Qualcomm said on Wednesday that its net income fell by 52 per cent to $363m, in large part because Apple and its contract manufacturers have choked off billions of dollars worth of royalty payments since the dispute began more than a year a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm cutting 1,500 jobs at its California offices - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-layoffs/qualcomm-cutting-1500-jobs-at-its-california-offices-idUSKBN1HQ34D</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELJ3wf6m01sxnEGG5nPiC5MqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 22:00:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-layoffs/qualcomm-cutting-1500-jobs-at-its-california-offices-idUSKBN1HQ34D" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm cutting 1,500 jobs at its California offices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Reuters) - Chipmaker Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) is cutting 1,500 jobs across multiple divisions at its offices in California, as part of its promise to investors to cut annual costs by $1 billion. The company, which has about 33,800 employees as of Sept.24, informed about its job cut plans in California in a regulatory notice that was filed with the state on April 18. Qualcomm said it plans to cut 1,231 jobs in its San Diego office and 269 from its San Jose and Santa Clara offices in the state. Though the company first considered cost reductions without lay...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>U.S. strike on China's ZTE another blow for Qualcomm - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-zte-qualcomm-analysis/us-strike-on-chinas-zte-another-blow-for-qualcomm-idUSKBN1HO0XT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKMnpzelbvuqsYLw8h9qUrgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 11:10:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-zte-qualcomm-analysis/us-strike-on-chinas-zte-another-blow-for-qualcomm-idUSKBN1HO0XT" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. strike on China's ZTE another blow for Qualcomm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Adam Jourdan and Cate Cadell SHANGHAI/BEIJING (Reuters) - A move by the United States to ban American firms selling components to the Chinese telecom equipment maker ZTE Corp will also hit a target closer to home: Qualcomm Inc, a U.S. company that is a major supplier of chips for ZTE's phones. The U.S. Department of Commerce slapped a seven-year ban on sales to ZTE on Monday for breaking terms of an agreement reached last year after it was caught illegally shipping goods to Iran. Caught in the crossfire is Qualcomm, whose products account for the lion's share of chips inside ZTE smartpho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm concessions insufficient to clinch NXP deal: commerce ministry - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-antitrust/qualcomm-concessions-insufficient-to-clinch-nxp-deal-commerce-ministry-idUSKBN1HQ1FJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOQmerjNRzhJ3ybr2FkVZ2cqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 11:44:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-antitrust/qualcomm-concessions-insufficient-to-clinch-nxp-deal-commerce-ministry-idUSKBN1HQ1FJ" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm concessions insufficient to clinch NXP deal: commerce ministry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (Reuters) - U.S. chipmaker Qualcomm (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) will have to do more to complete its proposed takeover of NXP Semiconductors (NXPI.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), a commerce ministry spokesman said on Thursday. Qualcomm had submitted a remedy plan to resolve competition issues, but an initial investigation found these to be insufficient, said ministry spokesman Gao Feng. "This deal will have significant influence in the industry and might have a negative impact on competition," he said. "Qualcomm's plan could not easily solve the problems...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm begins layoffs as part of cost cuts - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-layoffs/qualcomm-begins-layoffs-as-part-of-cost-cuts-idUSKBN1HP33L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBW2j8rEml81sohLlSxc4VEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 01:18:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-layoffs/qualcomm-begins-layoffs-as-part-of-cost-cuts-idUSKBN1HP33L" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm begins layoffs as part of cost cuts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Munsif Vengattil (Reuters) - Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) has begun cutting jobs as part of its promise to investors to cut annual costs by $1 billion, the chipmaker said on Wednesday. "Qualcomm is conducting a reduction of our full-time and temporary workforce," a company spokesperson who declined to be identifies said, without disclosing the exact numbers of job cuts. Though the company first evaluated non-headcount expense reductions, it concluded that a workforce reduction is needed to support long-term growth and success, the spokesperson said. Qualcom...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Microchips have macro problems - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d0b537ce-455d-11e8-8ee8-cae73aab7ccb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEnze82tI5-uMBoGrW4tkfIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 12:24:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d0b537ce-455d-11e8-8ee8-cae73aab7ccb" target="_blank"&gt;Microchips have macro problems&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Semiconductor makers, already finding themselves being used as chips in the high-stakes trade game between the US and China, are now suffering the effects of another macro event - the sliding appeal of smartphones. There was a widespread sell-off on Friday after an update from one of Apple’s biggest suppliers, Taiwan Semiconductor, raised expectations of a sharper slowdown in smartphone sales this year. It said in an earnings update that second-quarter revenues would be hit by “weak demand from the mobile sector”. Analog Devices, Cirrus Logic, Dialog Semiconductor, Qualcomm and Qorvo fell b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm is laying off more than 1,500 people - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2018/04/19/technology/qualcomm-layoffs/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOzJfc4ECNkGnxnTXOiR3C0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 02:34:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2018/04/19/technology/qualcomm-layoffs/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm is laying off more than 1,500 people&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualcomm is axing more than 1,500 jobs across California and an undisclosed number in other parts of the United States and around the world. The San Diego-based chipmaker says the cuts are part of a $1 billion cost-reduction plan that it announced in January. A company spokesperson said the layoffs include full- and part-time employees. Documents filed with California's Employment Development Department identify 289 layoffs in San Jose and 1,231 in San Diego. "We concluded that a workforce reduction is needed to support long-term growth and success, which will ultimately benefit all our sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>China demands Qualcomm concessions over NXP deal - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/f69ce1a0-43a8-11e8-803a-295c97e6fd0b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKXJPg6hVSGs-rqobpBALYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 09:42:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f69ce1a0-43a8-11e8-803a-295c97e6fd0b" target="_blank"&gt;China demands Qualcomm concessions over NXP deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US chipmaker Qualcomm must make further concessions over market competition to win Beijing’s approval for its proposed $44bn purchase of Dutch company NXP Semiconductors, China's commerce ministry said on Thursday. The ministry said Qualcomm had resubmitted its application to Chinese authorities on Monday, amid fears that Beijing may use its crucial approval of the deal as a bargaining chip in trade disputes with Washington. “This deal has a wide influence, and may have a negative impact on market competition,” ministry spokesman Gao Feng told reporters. Mr Gao added that Qualcomm had submi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Opinion: U.S. tech dominance is under threat from this one Chinese company - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-tech-dominance-is-under-threat-from-this-one-chinese-company-2018-04-16</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdhO4URwiaupcWO2ezX4P8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-tech-dominance-is-under-threat-from-this-one-chinese-company-2018-04-16" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion: U.S. tech dominance is under threat from this one Chinese company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Ryan Shrout Huawei is challenging Apple and Qualcomm in markets including smartphones and chips Reuters In the hyper-competitive world of smartphones, a company that’s mostly unknown to the average American is challenging the two behemoths of Apple and Samsung. It’s also put Qualcomm on notice in chips. That company is Huawei. Though founded more than three decades ago and having risen to as high as No. 83 on the Fortune 500 list, Huawei remains an enigma to many investors and consumers in the U.S. It has grown to become the world’s third-largest smartphone vendor behind only South Korea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm to cut 1,500 jobs across California - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/79c163fa-441f-11e8-93cf-67ac3a6482fd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIaQHzK8oUJrWwOdPdXNJMwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 22:51:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/79c163fa-441f-11e8-93cf-67ac3a6482fd" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm to cut 1,500 jobs across California&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualcomm on Thursday disclosed that it was cutting 1,500 jobs across its California offices as part of a plan to reduce annual costs by $1bn. 1,231 of the cuts will come from San Diego, where Qualcomm is headquartered, the company said in a Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification (WARN) filing. Meanwhile another 269 jobs will be cut from offices in San Jose and Santa Clara, another WARN notice showed. The job cuts are expected to begin in June. The WARN filings only cover California, meaning overall job losses could be greater as the company reduces its staff around the world. The chi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm to refile China antitrust application for $44 billion NXP takeover: sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-antitrust/qualcomm-to-refile-china-antitrust-application-for-44-billion-nxp-takeover-sources-idUSKBN1HN0RM</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMnAlMvPsEGEZaw8QFK7o1YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 07:26:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-qualcomm-antitrust/qualcomm-to-refile-china-antitrust-application-for-44-billion-nxp-takeover-sources-idUSKBN1HN0RM" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm to refile China antitrust application for $44 billion NXP takeover: sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Matthew Miller BEIJING (Reuters) - U.S. chipmaker Qualcomm (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) will refile as early as Monday an application with the Chinese government to clear its $44 billion takeover of NXP Semiconductors (NXPI.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), sources said, giving regulators more time to decide on the deal and averting a collapse. The San Diego-based firm withdrew its earlier antitrust application on Saturday at the request of China's commerce ministry, just days before the regulator's April 17 deadline to decide on the transaction expires, the sou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China slows review of chip company mergers amid trade tensions: WSJ - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-m-a-china/china-slows-review-of-chip-company-mergers-amid-trade-tensions-wsj-idUSKBN1HL0YU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEX5mehfEnRD4RJNARsIJo4qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 14:23:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-m-a-china/china-slows-review-of-chip-company-mergers-amid-trade-tensions-wsj-idUSKBN1HL0YU" target="_blank"&gt;China slows review of chip company mergers amid trade tensions: WSJ&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Reuters) - Two multi-billion dollar takeovers of semiconductor makers are being stalled by Chinese regulatory reviews amid rising U.S.-China trade tensions, the Wall Street Journal reported on Saturday, citing people familiar with the matter. Qualcomm Inc's (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) proposed $44 billion purchase of Dutch chip maker NXP Semiconductors NV (NXPI.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) could be at risk due to the delayed review. China is the only country that has not yet signed off on the deal, or on Toshiba Corp's (6502.T: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China is holding up a $44 billion US tech deal - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2018/04/19/technology/qualcomm-nxp-deal-china-us-trade/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHN_TrXgIliRipZCuvFnofAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 15:02:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2018/04/19/technology/qualcomm-nxp-deal-china-us-trade/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;China is holding up a $44 billion US tech deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China is standing in the way of an American computer chip maker completing the second-biggest technology deal in history. Qualcomm's proposed $44 billion takeover of NXP Semiconductors is being held up by the Chinese government, whose regulatory approval is needed for the deal to go through. China's Ministry of Commerce said Thursday that Qualcomm needs to do more to ensure its takeover of NXP won't give it an unfair advantage over rivals. It said that measures proposed by the San Diego-based company to tackle antitrust concerns "can hardly solve relevant market competition issues." The dea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Broadcom to buy back up to $12 billion of shares - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-broadcom-buyback/broadcom-to-buy-back-up-to-12-billion-of-shares-idUSKBN1HJ3AZ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIZ0CKXzxjq67WNR3XZtKJIqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 21:50:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-broadcom-buyback/broadcom-to-buy-back-up-to-12-billion-of-shares-idUSKBN1HJ3AZ" target="_blank"&gt;Broadcom to buy back up to $12 billion of shares&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Reuters) - Chipmaker Broadcom Inc (AVGO.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) said on Thursday it would buy back up to $12 billion of its common stock, sending its shares up 4.5 percent to $250 in extended trading. The company, which last month ended its efforts to acquire rival Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), said the repurchase program is effective immediately until the end of Broadcom's fiscal year 2019. Broadcom moved back to the United States from Singapore earlier this month, following U.S. President Donald Trump's decision to block its $117 billion of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Broadcom completes move to U.S. from Singapore - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-broadcom-domicile/broadcom-completes-move-to-u-s-from-singapore-idUSKCN1HB34G</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGo4vWsRqhMpxnZIv6V-gYsqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 22:01:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-broadcom-domicile/broadcom-completes-move-to-u-s-from-singapore-idUSKCN1HB34G" target="_blank"&gt;Broadcom completes move to U.S. from Singapore&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Reuters) - Broadcom Inc (AVGO.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) said on Wednesday it had completed its move back to the United States from Singapore, weeks after President Donald Trump blocked its $117 billion offer to buy Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) on national security grounds. Broadcom, which was a U.S. company until it was bought in 2016 by Singapore's Avago, had announced its plan to redomicile on Nov. 2, days before making its first offer for Qualcomm. The company said it exchanged all shares of Broadcom Ltd to newly issued stock of Broadcom Inc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Undaunted, Broadcom will still look for deals, but smaller ones - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/undaunted-broadcom-will-still-look-for-deals-but-smaller-ones-2018-03-15</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOSYKK-x61RWQ02lsxXXZr4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/undaunted-broadcom-will-still-look-for-deals-but-smaller-ones-2018-03-15" target="_blank"&gt;Undaunted, Broadcom will still look for deals, but smaller ones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARKETWATCH FIRST TAKE By Therese Poletti Opinion: After Qualcomm megadeal falls apart, the guessing games begin Broadcom Ltd.’s campus in Irvine, Calif. Bloomberg News Broadcom Ltd., a few days after President Donald Trump blocked what would have been the biggest deal in tech history, remains undaunted and will look for other companies to acquire, albeit on a smaller scale. On Thursday, the Singapore-based technology conglomerate reported better-than-expected first-quarter earnings, thanks to huge growth in its wireless business, which surged 88%. The company’s conference call was its firs...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item></channel></rss>