<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>The Game Awards - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV5WTNKdGNHWVNBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:50:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>The Game Awards 2018 winners: God of War wins game of the year as Red Dead Redemption 2 rides home with four - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-winners-god-war-wins-game-year-red-dead-redemption/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPDeuR-4L-u41h9dsCE_uYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:22:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-winners-god-war-wins-game-year-red-dead-redemption/" target="_blank"&gt;The Game Awards 2018 winners: God of War wins game of the year as Red Dead Redemption 2 rides home with four&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sony Santa Monica's God of War has won the Game of the Year award at The Game Awards 2018 ceremony. The acclaimed Norse adventure also picked up awards for best direction and best action-adventure. Rockstar's smash hit Western Red Dead Redemption 2 won the most awards, riding home with four. The sprawling adventure won best narrative, best performance for Roger Clarke as Arthur Morgan, best music for Woody Jackson and Daniel Lanois' score and best audio. Indie gem Celeste won two for best independent game and the Game for Impact award. And battle royale phenomenon Fortnite also took two wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Here's The Full List Of Winners From The Game Awards 2018, Including GOTY - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/07/heres-the-full-list-of-winners-from-the-game-awards-2018-including-goty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBmc6X8fby7_V2umw4SOfAAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/07/heres-the-full-list-of-winners-from-the-game-awards-2018-including-goty/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's The Full List Of Winners From The Game Awards 2018, Including GOTY&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;God of War Last night’s Game Awards were…actually quite enjoyable, and Geoff Keighley’s show continues to be improving year after year, now a truly meaningful event in the industry full of world premieres, yes, but also awards that actually matter. The Game of the Year award here really now does feel like the Oscar’s Best Picture, and I love that. So, who won? You can probably guess by my lead image there but yes, God of War took home Game of the Year, somewhat upsetting Red Dead Redemption 2, which early on looked like it could sweep its categories, but God of War ended up winning both Gam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Far Cry: New Dawn first-look preview | Gorgeous mayhem - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/far-cry-new-dawn-first-look-preview-gorgeous-mayhem/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFHNmc37wbVDz1AMUUejWQQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:48:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/far-cry-new-dawn-first-look-preview-gorgeous-mayhem/" target="_blank"&gt;Far Cry: New Dawn first-look preview | Gorgeous mayhem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Far Cry: New Dawn is a rare thing for Ubisoft’s open-world shooter: a direct sequel. Throughout its near 15 year history, the series has been a traveller, jumping from the tropics to Africa and the Himalayas. From modern-day to the prehistoric and an 80s VHS dystopia. Rarely though, does Far Cry pick up its narrative threads, preferring to share its themes and systems than storylines. New Dawn, though, picks up where previous game Far Cry 5 left off. Well, sort of. Without getting too far into the spoilery specifics, one of the finales of Far Cry 5 sees the outbreak of global nuclear war. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Game Awards 2018 announcements: Dragon Age 4 and Far Cry: New Dawn headline new game reveals - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-announcements-dragon-age-4-far-cry-new-dawn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOe9WHf9XKnjO0C_nfPE33MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:54:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-announcements-dragon-age-4-far-cry-new-dawn/" target="_blank"&gt;The Game Awards 2018 announcements: Dragon Age 4 and Far Cry: New Dawn headline new game reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BioWare has announced that RPG Dragon Age 4 is coming at The Game Awards ceremony. The long-awaited fantasy RPG is reportedly still early in development, but BioWare has teased its fans with a short video and the phrase The Dread Wolf Rises; a reference to elven apostate Solas. Far Cry: New Dawn, a direct post-apocalyptic sequel to Ubisoft's open-world shooter Far Cry 5, was unveiled for 15 February 2019. The game is set 17 years after Far Cry 5, with a 'super-bloom' transforming the setting of Hope County into a vivid, colourful post-nuclear land. And staying with pink post-apocalyptia, Ra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Watch The 2018 'Game Awards' Livestream Right Here - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/watch-the-2018-game-awards-livestream-right-here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMmQrGyZ87H1TabcOIFwPEYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/watch-the-2018-game-awards-livestream-right-here/" target="_blank"&gt;Watch The 2018 'Game Awards' Livestream Right Here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the 2018 Game Awards right here. The Game Awards return tonight with a whole bunch of nominees for everything from Game of the Year to best eSports player, and everything in-between. Many strong contenders will vie for top honors, from Sony’s excellent single-player exclusives God of War and Marvel’s Spider-Man, to Rockstar’s sprawling Western, Red Dead Redemption 2. Other titles, like Monster Hunter: World and Dragon Quest XI face off against Pillars of Eternity II: Deadfire and Octopath Traveler for best RPG of the year. Perhaps more exciting than the awards themselves, The Game Awa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Ubisoft Just Teased A Post-Apocalyptic 'Far Cry' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/05/ubisoft-just-teased-a-post-apocalyptic-far-cry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKpjuCWH_aD3SUzxf2IrrvoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/05/ubisoft-just-teased-a-post-apocalyptic-far-cry/" target="_blank"&gt;Ubisoft Just Teased A Post-Apocalyptic 'Far Cry'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mysterious new Far Cry game. Out of the blue, Ubisoft dropped a brand new Far Cry teaser trailer Wednesday afternoon. The trailer appears to pick off after the end of Far Cry 5 when (spoilers) a nuclear bomb was dropped on the Montana valley where the cult was operating. This doesn’t look like new DLC for Far Cry 5, however. I expect it’s more along the lines of one of the “junior” Far Cry entries like Far Cry 3: Blood Dragon, Far Cry Primal and so forth. These are smaller games that build off what the larger numbered entries are doing but are more contained and don’t release any expansi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Game Awards 2018: What Time Is It, How To Stream And All Nominees - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/the-game-awards-2018-what-time-is-it-how-to-stream-and-all-nominees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJox_rcxC3_3KQ5B224Sk4AqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/the-game-awards-2018-what-time-is-it-how-to-stream-and-all-nominees/" target="_blank"&gt;The Game Awards 2018: What Time Is It, How To Stream And All Nominees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Game Awards Slowly but surely, the long-awaited “Oscars of video games” is taking shape. No, it doesn’t look anything like the actual Oscars, but we can sort of count our blessings on that score. Geoff Keighley’s Game Awards are now in their fifth year, and in that time they’ve become firmly ensconced as the highest profile of a wide spate of award shows in the industry, known as much for their judgement on the best games of the year as they are for a typically impressive suite of announcements and trailers. It’s also a complete digital native, streaming across the whole Internet at onc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>There's A Big 'Fortnite' Announcement At The Game Awards Tonight, But It's Not What You Think - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/theres-a-big-fortnite-announcement-at-the-game-awards-tonight-but-its-not-what-you-think/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFx_4hkGV0WvjHfenD2tDskqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/theres-a-big-fortnite-announcement-at-the-game-awards-tonight-but-its-not-what-you-think/" target="_blank"&gt;There's A Big 'Fortnite' Announcement At The Game Awards Tonight, But It's Not What You Think&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite It’s a big day for battle royale fans. For one thing, Fortnite Season 7 just launched as Epic Games continues to top itself when it comes to totally transforming its map to match the current season: right now we’ve got a wide-ranging winter wonderland, airplanes, and a ton of other stuff. It’s also The Game Awards tonight, the annual celebration that’s gradually emerging as the most important awards show in the world of video games. The Game Awards are known not only for the awards themselves but also for the announcements, surprises and trailers that have a way of worming their wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Is Likely Dropping Big Season 7 News At The Game Awards - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/03/fortnite-is-likely-dropping-big-season-7-news-at-the-game-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKDh0Twe17EMAWJOAd7mNtIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/03/fortnite-is-likely-dropping-big-season-7-news-at-the-game-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Is Likely Dropping Big Season 7 News At The Game Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite The Game Awards has not only secured itself as the closest thing we’re going to get to video game Oscars, but also, essentially, as Winter E3, where game companies drop news and trailers for their upcoming 2019 releases and beyond. We’re getting a bunch of world premieres, but also something else. Both host Geoff Keighley and Epic have confirmed that there will be Fortnite news at the December 5 event. Fortnite is nominated for a few Game Awards, and seems likely to win best ongoing game and possibly best multiplayer, given the year it’s had. But the timing of the Game Awards just ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Game Awards 2018: What will we see at annual celebration turned game announcement hotbed? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-new-games-will-see-announcement-hotbed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAH3LYht9cY2krWZ_0pEMTQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 09:33:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-new-games-will-see-announcement-hotbed/" target="_blank"&gt;The Game Awards 2018: What will we see at annual celebration turned game announcement hotbed?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite its overly corporate sheen, the annual Game Awards show has slowly become one of the key dates on the gaming calendar. Taking over from Spike TV’s long-running Video Game Awards show in 2014, The Game Awards began life as a celebration of the year’s best games, but is now more anticipated as a glimpse into the next. With most of the year’s games on shelves by the time the December show rolls around, The Game Awards has become the venue of choice for publishers to announce new titles and shed more light on upcoming ones. Away from the throng and pressure of E3, The Game Awards has se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Bafta games awards 2017: Inside and Uncharted 4 lead the way - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/mar/09/bafta-games-awards-2017-inside-and-uncharted-4-lead-the-way</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF__u9V8tPihRRA3ZftTTvUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 10:58:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/mar/09/bafta-games-awards-2017-inside-and-uncharted-4-lead-the-way" target="_blank"&gt;Bafta games awards 2017: Inside and Uncharted 4 lead the way&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bafta has announced the nominations for the 2017 British Academy Game Awards with indie title Inside and blockbuster Uncharted 4 leading the way. Fifty games received nominations across 15 categories, but many appear more than once. Inside has the most potential wins since it is nominated in seven separate categories – every category for which it qualifies. Big-budget blockbuster Uncharted 4, on the other hand, has eight nominations in total, but across fewer categories, so it could take home a maximum of six trophies. In the Performer category, Uncharted 4 represents half the total nominat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'The Witcher 3' And 'World Of Warcraft' Shouldn't Be Nominees At The 2016 Game Awards - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/12/01/the-witcher-3-and-world-of-warcarft-shouldnt-be-nominees-at-the-2016-game-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJDqv_y1vBDCA4UfqjOA3CsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 21:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/12/01/the-witcher-3-and-world-of-warcarft-shouldnt-be-nominees-at-the-2016-game-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;'The Witcher 3' And 'World Of Warcraft' Shouldn't Be Nominees At The 2016 Game Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Witcher 3 doesn’t really belong in a 2016 video game award ceremony. (Credit: CDPR) I’m excited to watch the 2016 Game Awards this evening. We’re in for a few big game reveals and some gameplay footage for highly anticipated titles launching next year. That’s all well and good, but I have a quibble with two of the nominees for Best RPG in this year’s awards. Here are the five games nominated for best roleplaying game of 2016: - Dark Souls 3 (FromSoftware/Bandai Namco Entertainment) - Deus Ex: Mankind Divided (Eidos Montreal/Square Enix) - The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt – Blood and Wine (CD Pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Everything You Need To Know About The 2016 Game Awards - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/12/01/heres-everything-you-need-to-know-about-tonights-2016-game-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKkp2Od0RIozQJ502WVgYFkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 20:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/12/01/heres-everything-you-need-to-know-about-tonights-2016-game-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;Everything You Need To Know About The 2016 Game Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Credit: Erik Kain/Game Awards Tonight marks the 3rd annual Game Awards hosted by Geoff Keighley, the premiere event for honoring the best, or at least most acclaimed, video games of the year. The Game Awards were previously known as the Video Game Awards, which have been around since 2009. The Game Awards have taken on a distinctly different tone than before, however, under the stewardship of host Geoff Keighley. Here’s everything you need to know about the 2016 Game Awards, including where to watch, when the awards are airing, and what to expect from the show, as well as a list of nominees...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Liveblogging The Game Awards 2016 As 'Overwatch,' 'Titanfall 2' And 'DOOM' Battle For GOTY - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/12/01/liveblogging-the-game-awards-2016-as-overwatch-titanfall-2-and-doom-battle-for-goty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARmQTY8rzu3GMjYZa0B2L4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 01:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/12/01/liveblogging-the-game-awards-2016-as-overwatch-titanfall-2-and-doom-battle-for-goty/" target="_blank"&gt;Liveblogging The Game Awards 2016 As 'Overwatch,' 'Titanfall 2' And 'DOOM' Battle For GOTY&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: The Game Awards The Game Awards is back, and I’m having fond flashbacks to a few years ago when I was attending The VGAs back when they were still on Spike. Despite the best efforts of host/organizer Geoff Keighley, the event never quite clicked in any of its TV iterations. But now? Rebranded as simply “The Game Awards,” it’s the closest thing the industry has to a serious awards show, and it’s evolved into something quite nice, actually. The odd part of The Game Awards is that it also wants to be a bit of a micro-E3 in addition to being an awards show. More viewers are tuning into i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Watch The Game Awards Right Here - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2016/12/01/stream-youtube-facebook-twitter-how-to-watch-the-game-awards-tonight/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL-jpZHAcz2vlpOijTClCD4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 16:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2016/12/01/stream-youtube-facebook-twitter-how-to-watch-the-game-awards-tonight/" target="_blank"&gt;Watch The Game Awards Right Here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;image: The Game Awards 2016 is almost coming to a close, for better and for worse. This year has been many things, but today we’re mostly concerned with the fact that it’s seen a positively gigantic number of video games, from AAA to indie and everywhere in between. Tonight, Geoff Keighly and the broader gaming public celebrate that fact with the third annual Game Awards. Expect awards for the best the industry has to offer, as well as a look at some of the biggest games of next year: names like Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild, Mass Effect Andromeda and Red Dead Redemption 2. Streams ki...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Gearing Up For The Third Annual Game Awards - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2016/11/30/gearing-up-for-the-third-annual-game-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGh6ajj10lU2RPv85_y5K50qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2016/11/30/gearing-up-for-the-third-annual-game-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;Gearing Up For The Third Annual Game Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Game Awards in 2015. Image: The Game Awards. The gaming industry does love a show. We’re through most of the major releases of 2016 (The Last Guardian notwithstanding), cold weather is settling in, and we get a second now to look back at the year that was, and to see what’s around the corner. And wouldn’t you know it, we’ve got the Game Awards coming up on Thursday, a chance to argue about the best games that came out in 2016 and get excited for their followups in 2017 and beyond. The show is in its third year: an interesting transition for any institution looking to make it for the lon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>BAFTA Games Awards 2017: Uncharted 4 takes best game as Inside wins big - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/bafta-games-awards-2017-uncharted-4-takes-best-game-inside-wins/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAoIqy-ZnRxHb2GGDdCDXjYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 10:34:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/what-to-play/bafta-games-awards-2017-uncharted-4-takes-best-game-inside-wins/" target="_blank"&gt;BAFTA Games Awards 2017: Uncharted 4 takes best game as Inside wins big&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A trend of the biggest blockbusters walking away with the best game award as indie hits clean up in the other categories continued last night at the latest Bafta Games Awards. Uncharted 4 took home the biggest prize of the night, with Nathan Drake's fabulous final adventure recovering from missing out on its other seven nominations to land Best Game. Uncharted follows in the footsteps of 2016's Fallout 4 and Destiny in 2015. The game's producer Arne Meyer took to the stage to accept the award, calling it 'unexpected' as he paid tribute to the game's cast Nolan North, Troy Baker and Emily Ro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Good, The Bad And The Cringeworthy Of The 2016 Game Awards - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/12/02/the-good-the-bad-and-the-cringeworthy-of-the-2016-game-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKlU4NH-gTTk-ydNa9pMilQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 17:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/12/02/the-good-the-bad-and-the-cringeworthy-of-the-2016-game-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;The Good, The Bad And The Cringeworthy Of The 2016 Game Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2016 Game Awards have come and gone, and it’s time to give the ceremony its postmortem. What worked? What didn’t work? And is this the video game award show we need, or the one we deserve? Let’s go over the good, the bad and the cringeworthy of last night’s show. The Schick Hydrobot says a lot about this year’s Game Awards. (Credit: Schick/Erik Kain) The Good Because we should be positive as often as we can, let’s start with the good… 1. Geoff Keighley Long-time video game commentator and entertainer, Geoff Keighley was the big winner of last night’s show. It’s because of Keighley’s eff...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>The Game Awards 2018: Red Dead Redemption 2 and God of War lead the nominations - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-red-dead-redemption-2-god-war-lead-nominations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFYrK-cwflN5VnDL2KJsHGIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 14:39:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-red-dead-redemption-2-god-war-lead-nominations/" target="_blank"&gt;The Game Awards 2018: Red Dead Redemption 2 and God of War lead the nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rockstar's Wild West epic Red Dead Redemption 2 and Sony's sprawling Norse adventure God of War are leading the way at The Game Awards 2018 with eight nominations each. The two blockbusters will vie for Game of the Year with Assassin's Creed Odyssey, Marvel's Spider-Man and Monster Hunter: World. And delightfully among these goliaths, the small independent platformer Celeste is also up for the main prize of the night. Battle royale phenomenon Fortnite is up for four awards, while Call of Duty: Black Ops 4, Destiny 2: Forsaken and Detroit: Become Human have three each. The nominations were d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Red Dead 2' And 'God Of War' Lead The 2018 Game Awards Nominations: Here's The Full List - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/13/red-dead-2-and-god-of-war-lead-the-2018-game-awards-nominations-heres-the-full-list/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB9ReTMcVGxzPQMw9PL0QW4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 18:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/13/red-dead-2-and-god-of-war-lead-the-2018-game-awards-nominations-heres-the-full-list/" target="_blank"&gt;'Red Dead 2' And 'God Of War' Lead The 2018 Game Awards Nominations: Here's The Full List&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red Dead Redemption 2 The Game Awards is the closest thing our industry has to the Oscars, and while the kinks are still being worked out, it’s evolved into a pretty solid show over the last few years, a combination between an awards show and E3 where a lot of new games and footage make their debut. As for the awards themselves, Geoff Keighley has just released the full, massive list of nominees, and it should surprise no one that Red Dead Redemption 2 and God of War are both leading the pack, each with eight nominations. Spider-Man has seven, so that’s 15 for PS4’s two high profile exclusi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Golden Joystick Awards 2018 | How to watch and all the nominees - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/golden-joystick-awards-2018-watch-nominees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3KA0fVaF1wB9q8sax9LyAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 14:56:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/golden-joystick-awards-2018-watch-nominees/" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Joystick Awards 2018 | How to watch and all the nominees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 36th Golden Joystick Awards 2018 are imminent, with the world's longest-running and most prominent game award ceremonies taking place this Friday. The Golden Joysticks will be at the Bloomsbury Big Top on 16 November and will be hosted by comedian Danny Wallace, the awards will celebrate the last year of the gaming industry across multiple categories. The categories cover a wide range across the industry including storytelling and esports alongside the more traditional disciplines of audio and visual. There is also a new category this year recognising the best co-operative games. Sony's...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Golden Joysticks 2018 nominees announced, voting open now - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/golden-joysticks-2018-nominees-announced-voting-open-now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMjVTAGI_TgM4bBH3IHRwEkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 11:12:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/golden-joysticks-2018-nominees-announced-voting-open-now/" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Joysticks 2018 nominees announced, voting open now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nominees for the Golden Joystick Awards 2018 have been announced and public voting is now open for the 36th edition of the famous UK gaming awards. The Golden Joysticks will take place at the Bloomsbury Big Top on 16 November and will be hosted by comedian Danny Wallace, the awards will celebrate the last year of the gaming industry across multiple categories. The categories cover a wide range across the industry including storytelling and esports alongside the more traditional disciplines of audio and visual. There is also a new category this year recognising the best co-operative gam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Bafta Game Awards 2018 nominations | Hellblade and Horizon Zero Dawn lead the way - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/bafta-game-awards-2018-nominations-hellblade-horizon-zero-dawn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEe33xp_l06UulCJKYkpiQAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 14:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/bafta-game-awards-2018-nominations-hellblade-horizon-zero-dawn/" target="_blank"&gt;Bafta Game Awards 2018 nominations | Hellblade and Horizon Zero Dawn lead the way&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Norse fantasy adventure Hellblade: Senua’s Sacrifice is leading the way at this year’s Bafta Game Awards 2018 as the shortlists for the coveted gaming prize was revealed, picking up nine nominations across a plethora of categories including Best Game. Hellblade, which is developed by the independent UK studio Ninja Theory, follows the trials of young Pict warrior Senua through a hellish Celtic landscape as she deals with the ravaging of her village and her own fragile psychosis. It has received plaudits for its depiction of mental illness within its fantasy setting. The Telegraph's review f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Twitch Comments On The Record-Breaking Drake-Ninja 'Fortnite' Stream - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/03/15/twitch-comments-on-the-record-breaking-drake-ninja-fortnite-stream/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBfva9oTfdsoqhZTkWfldpgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 17:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/03/15/twitch-comments-on-the-record-breaking-drake-ninja-fortnite-stream/" target="_blank"&gt;Twitch Comments On The Record-Breaking Drake-Ninja 'Fortnite' Stream&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Stream “Video games ARE popular culture. Last night was proof of that.” That’s a quote from The Game Awards’ Geoff Keighley on last night’s historic Ninja/Drake Fortnite stream, Ninja, the most popular streamer in Twitch’s history, Drake, you know….Drake. Yes, that one. The unlikely pair played Fortnite together for several hours, shattering Twitch viewership records for an individual stream, and boosting Ninja’s fortunes to absurd new heights. I asked Twitch what exactly the final tally was for the all-time record, and what they made of what happened last night: “Ninja and Drake’s Fort...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'The Game Awards' Finally Hit Its Stride Last Night, Except For One Thing - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/08/the-game-awards-finally-hit-its-stride-last-night-except-for-one-thing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJgKQJ3gbzkuzolykvluBRkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 17:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/08/the-game-awards-finally-hit-its-stride-last-night-except-for-one-thing/" target="_blank"&gt;'The Game Awards' Finally Hit Its Stride Last Night, Except For One Thing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES, CA – DECEMBER 07: (L-R) Hideo Kojima and Norman Reedus on stage at The Game Awards 2017 at Microsoft Theater on December 7, 2017 in Los Angeles, California. (Photo by Greg Doherty/Getty Images) I thought the Game Awards were really good this year. Geoff Keighley obviously learned a great deal over the past few years. For one thing, there was no Hydrobot and really no other meme-worthy (and cringe-worthy) marketing moment during the show (unless I missed something, which is possible.) I thought the Game Awards struck a really good balance between giving out awards and showing of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Here Are All The Winners Of The 2017 Game Awards - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/08/here-are-all-the-winners-of-the-2017-game-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGJSV1nrd9_jd1s_jO-NsF8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 16:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/08/here-are-all-the-winners-of-the-2017-game-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are All The Winners Of The 2017 Game Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the winner is… Well, the fourth annual Game Awards have come and gone. Without question, last night’s awards were the best so far (more thoughts on that in a separate post) and all the winners were well-deserving. It was a tough year, with tons of amazing games to choose from. Below are all the winners, as well as a look at how well I did in my predictions (not terrible, it so happens.) I didn’t predict in categories I don’t really follow such as eSports. We’ll start with GOTY, which went to Zelda, surprising no one…. Game of the Year Horizon Zero Dawn Persona 5 PlayerUnknown’s Battlegr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Watch The 2017 'Game Awards' Livestream Right Here - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/07/watch-the-2017-game-awards-livestream-right-here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKWUy_PgVCnrbT_k54wsZ4gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/07/watch-the-2017-game-awards-livestream-right-here/" target="_blank"&gt;Watch The 2017 'Game Awards' Livestream Right Here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Game Awards livestream begins at 5:30 pm PST. Tonight marks the fourth annual Game Awards. 2017 was an incredible year for video games, even with a few big misses, and it’ll be really interesting to see which games go home with honors and which come up empty-handed. Not only will we get to see who wins in a bevy of different video game categories, with a number of big name announcers like Guillermo Del Toro, Norman Reedus and Hideo Kojima, we’ll also see a bunch of game announcements and trailers. So even if you’re not thrilled by awards shows, at least there will be some tasty new game...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Here Are All The 2017 'Game Awards' Nominees And Predictions For Winners - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/07/here-are-all-the-2017-game-awards-nominees-and-predictions-for-winners/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPf0cGkYQzrcuWrs7v-aGb8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/07/here-are-all-the-2017-game-awards-nominees-and-predictions-for-winners/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are All The 2017 'Game Awards' Nominees And Predictions For Winners&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who will the winners for this year’s ‘Game Awards’ be? The fourth annual Game Awards air this Thursday night. Geoff Keighley, along with a number of announcers including The Walking Dead’s Norman Reedus, acclaimed game director Hideo Kojima, and film director Guillermo Del Toro will take the stage alongside a full orchestra and the band Phoenix. The awards show is as much about announcements for upcoming games as it is for the actual awards, but I always have fun predicting the winners. These aren’t always my own pick, but I like to at least see how close I am to the current of public opini...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Here's What The '2017 Game Awards' Tell Us About The Death Of Single-Player - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/05/heres-what-the-2017-game-awards-tell-us-about-the-death-of-single-player/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAxN_v1GBzc0St762p49FGkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 19:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/12/05/heres-what-the-2017-game-awards-tell-us-about-the-death-of-single-player/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's What The '2017 Game Awards' Tell Us About The Death Of Single-Player&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Geoff Keighley, the man behind the annual Game Awards which are back for the fourth year in a row this Thursday, doesn’t think single-player games are dead. Not by a long shot. Geoff Keighley says the death of single-player games is greatly exaggerated. “There’s been a lot of talk about the death of the single-player game,” Keighley tells me. “But when you look at our nominees [for GOTY] four of them are really impressive single-player only games.” The four games he’s referring to are The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild, Super Mario Odyssey, Horizon Zero Dawn and Persona 5. “I think tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Death Stranding | Trailers, release date, everything we know about Hideo Kojima's next game - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/death-stranding-trailers-release-date-everything-know-hideo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM1oCmr8D0-T5fyS0g7c30QqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 11:13:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/death-stranding-trailers-release-date-everything-know-hideo/" target="_blank"&gt;Death Stranding | Trailers, release date, everything we know about Hideo Kojima's next game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that Hideo Kojima has left Konami and is working at his own studio, Kojima Productions, he's able to work on his own project. That means he's no longer working on Metal Gear, and his next project is, instead, Death Stranding. There's no release date for it yet, and, in a very Kojima fashion, nobody really knows what it's going to be. That said, slowly we're being drip fed tiny bits of information about the game, and so we've collected everything we know so far about Hideo Kojima's next title. When is Death Stranding coming out? We don't know. It was announced in 2016, but since then, we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item></channel></rss>