<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Manchester United F.C. - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFV3Wm1nU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:13:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Jose Mourinho pleads for FFP to help Manchester United catch Manchester City if they are to win the league again - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/jose-mourinho-manchester-united-pep-guardiola-manchester-city-financial-fair-play-a8672906.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGEoaabZLc6OCyHulTnZNQQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 08:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/jose-mourinho-manchester-united-pep-guardiola-manchester-city-financial-fair-play-a8672906.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jose Mourinho pleads for FFP to help Manchester United catch Manchester City if they are to win the league again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jose Mourinho has claimed that Manchester United may need authorities to crack down on Manchester City’s spending before they can hope to challenge their rivals for the Premier League title again. Uefa last month opened an investigation into allegations, published in the German magazine Der Spiegel, that City illegitimately circumvented Financial Fair Play (FFP) regulations. Mourinho has regularly complained that United cannot match City’s clout in the transfer market since his arrival in Manchester and pointed to City’s spending power as a reason why United struggle to compete with their n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Claude Puel hatches plan to keep Leicester’s best players at the club by matching their ambitions - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/leicester-vs-tottenham-premier-league-epl-claude-puel-transfer-news-players-plan-europe-a8673571.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDTjjKGJr8kpFII-C44cxFsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/leicester-vs-tottenham-premier-league-epl-claude-puel-transfer-news-players-plan-europe-a8673571.html" target="_blank"&gt;Claude Puel hatches plan to keep Leicester’s best players at the club by matching their ambitions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leicester City boss Claude Puel admits the Foxes need European football to match his stars’ ambitions. The club are ninth in the Premier League and poised to battle for a Europa League spot this season. Arsenal have been linked with England international Ben Chilwell while Manchester United wanted Harry Maguire in the summer before the defender signed a five-year deal in September. But Puel conceded, before Saturday’s visit of Tottenham Hotspur, Leicester need to play in Europe to have a better chance of keeping the squad together. “I think it would be better, of course,” said the manager, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The United squad have been meeting fans as part of the club Foundation's Dream Day. Read more. - Manchester United</title><link>https://posts.google.com/share/5H189BKH/wJUbjA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiLmh0dHBzOi8vcG9zdHMuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS9zaGFyZS81SDE4OUJLSC93SlViakHSAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:01:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://posts.google.com/share/5H189BKH/wJUbjA" target="_blank"&gt;The United squad have been meeting fans as part of the club Foundation's Dream Day. Read more.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Manchester United&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://posts.google.com">Manchester United</source></item><item><title>Marcus Rashford has a steely mindset in this extract from his United Review Q&amp;A. Read more. - Manchester United</title><link>https://posts.google.com/share/5H189BKH/XkiMfe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiLmh0dHBzOi8vcG9zdHMuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS9zaGFyZS81SDE4OUJLSC9Ya2lNZmXSAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:36:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://posts.google.com/share/5H189BKH/XkiMfe" target="_blank"&gt;Marcus Rashford has a steely mindset in this extract from his United Review Q&amp;A. Read more.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Manchester United&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://posts.google.com">Manchester United</source></item><item><title>Jose Mourinho has given the latest injury news ahead of United's match against Fulham. Read more. - Manchester United</title><link>https://posts.google.com/share/5H189BKH/5NtzNR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiLmh0dHBzOi8vcG9zdHMuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS9zaGFyZS81SDE4OUJLSC81TnR6TlLSAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:01:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://posts.google.com/share/5H189BKH/5NtzNR" target="_blank"&gt;Jose Mourinho has given the latest injury news ahead of United's match against Fulham. Read more.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Manchester United&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://posts.google.com">Manchester United</source></item><item><title>Jose Mourinho has explained why Fred hasn't featured much recently for the Reds. Read more. - Manchester United</title><link>https://posts.google.com/share/5H189BKH/cSS-mv</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiLmh0dHBzOi8vcG9zdHMuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS9zaGFyZS81SDE4OUJLSC9jU1MtbXbSAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:00:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://posts.google.com/share/5H189BKH/cSS-mv" target="_blank"&gt;Jose Mourinho has explained why Fred hasn't featured much recently for the Reds. Read more.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Manchester United&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://posts.google.com">Manchester United</source></item><item><title>Premier League LIVE - Latest scores and goal updates from Arsenal vs Huddersfield, Manchester United vs Fulham - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/premier-league-live-latest-scores-goal-updates-odds-predictions-arsenal-manchester-united-epl-news-a8673676.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-HkyqR2yFPC7penWzEkrcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/premier-league-live-latest-scores-goal-updates-odds-predictions-arsenal-manchester-united-epl-news-a8673676.html" target="_blank"&gt;Premier League LIVE - Latest scores and goal updates from Arsenal vs Huddersfield, Manchester United vs Fulham&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow all the latest from today’s Premier League action on a bumper day of eight games, with all the goals and updates as they happen. Once Bournemouth vs Liverpool wraps up in the day’s early kick-off, Arsenal host Huddersfield at the Emirates looking to record a 21st consecutive unbeaten result. Manchester United are also in action at 3pm as they welcome Claudio Ranieri's Fulham to Old Trafford, with Jose Mourinho's side in desperate need of a win after four league games without victory. Burnley will look to try and climb out of the relegation zone as they face Brighton at Turf Moor, whi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Premier League bets: Manchester City will inflict more pain on Chelsea - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/premier-league-bets-manchester-city-will-inflict-pain-chelsea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB0PTLn4JS4eJCZeb0nlWtwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/premier-league-bets-manchester-city-will-inflict-pain-chelsea/" target="_blank"&gt;Premier League bets: Manchester City will inflict more pain on Chelsea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After you have lost your unbeaten record with a disappointing performance against one of your huge rivals and suffered another defeat on the road against Wolves after letting a lead slip, the last team you want rolling into town is Manchester City. Maurizio Sarri’s decision to rest Jorginho, Mateo Kovacic, David Luiz and Pedro failed to pay off against Wolves but his side were still unlucky to lose 2-1, given their opponents scored with their only two shots on target. Chelsea are unbeaten at home this season but have drawn three of their eight matches at Stamford Bridge against Liverpool, M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Bournemouth vs Liverpool, Premier League: live score and latest updates - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/bournemouth-vs-liverpool-premier-league-live-score-latest-updates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAHXYMwE0Sz8VX-aTDWHUL8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:45:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/bournemouth-vs-liverpool-premier-league-live-score-latest-updates/" target="_blank"&gt;Bournemouth vs Liverpool, Premier League: live score and latest updates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Kick-off at the Vitality Stadium is at 12.30pm - Live coverage on Sky Sports Main Event or Sky Sports Premier League - Get the best betting odds and offers for today's games​11:45AMThe 500 club James Milner starts, and that means he becomes the 13th player to reach 500 Premier League appearances. At 32 years and 338 days old, Milner is the second-youngest to reach the landmark, after Gareth Barry. James Milner plays his 500th Premier League game todayCredit: Getty images Milner also has the Premier League record for scoring in the most games without ever losing one of those games. The win...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Rob Holding reveals get-well message from Marcus Rashford after Arsenal defender’s knee injury - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/arsenal-manchester-united-news-rob-holding-injury-marcus-rashford-message-latest-team-news-a8673641.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPaN3FbNwkSy3iVz_hTk6bkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/arsenal-manchester-united-news-rob-holding-injury-marcus-rashford-message-latest-team-news-a8673641.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rob Holding reveals get-well message from Marcus Rashford after Arsenal defender’s knee injury&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rob Holding has revealed that Manchester United striker Marcus Rashford has messaged him in the wake of receiving news that his season is over, having suffered a ruptured anterior cruciate ligament in a challenge by the England international. Holding collapsed midway through the first half of Arsenal’s 2-2 draw at Old Trafford on Wednesday and had to be carried off on a stretcher with his left leg in a brace, with scans revealing the worst on Friday. The 23-year-old is set to be out of action for up to nine months, ruling him out of the rest of the season and potentially that start of the 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Leicester vs Tottenham, Premier League 2018-19: What time is kick-off today, what TV channel is it on and what is our prediction? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/leicester-vs-tottenham-premier-league-2018-19-time-kick-off1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDvLEBi1IZ0Dv_PNPLb1-8IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:14:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/leicester-vs-tottenham-premier-league-2018-19-time-kick-off1/" target="_blank"&gt;Leicester vs Tottenham, Premier League 2018-19: What time is kick-off today, what TV channel is it on and what is our prediction?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is it? A Premier League game pitting Leicester City against Tottenham Hotspur. When is it? It's today, so Saturday 8 December. What time is kick-off? This is the (very) late game on Saturday - kick-off is at 7.45pm. What TV channel is it on? You can watch this one on BT Sport 1. Or follow the game with us on this page. What is the team news?Leicester Leicester have been dealt a blow with the news that Jamie Vardy is out of Saturday's game with the groin injury that meant he missed the draw at Fulham in midweek. In better news Jonny Evans should be back in the squad. Harry Maguire will ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Liverpool and Manchester City are bringing rhythmic tension to the Premier League - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/liverpool-manchester-city-chelsea-title-race-jurgen-klopp-latest-updates-a8671331.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIdigccQ4AdKvTRlh1xEQOoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 08:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/liverpool-manchester-city-chelsea-title-race-jurgen-klopp-latest-updates-a8671331.html" target="_blank"&gt;Liverpool and Manchester City are bringing rhythmic tension to the Premier League&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Already this weekend there is something of a twist to the Premier League. For the first time since early November, Liverpool will play before Manchester City, changing the dynamics that have governed the top of the table for the last month. The fact that Jurgen Klopp’s side have always been under such pressure to follow the champions with a win, to keep the gap at just two points, has been one big reason why it has felt they have been just about “hanging on” – despite having already been responsible for the seventh best record after 15 games in English history. It has just added that extra ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Man City may gamble on Sterling for Agüero but ‘won’t be banned in Europe’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/manchester-city-raheem-sterling-sergio-aguero-chelsea-pep-guardiiola</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA9BXnLbPjQFfYuirSn7Oq8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:30:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/manchester-city-raheem-sterling-sergio-aguero-chelsea-pep-guardiiola" target="_blank"&gt;Man City may gamble on Sterling for Agüero but ‘won’t be banned in Europe’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manchester City travel to Chelsea not yet ready to risk Sergio Agüero as he recovers from an abductor muscle strain and with Pep Guardiola weighing up the pros and cons of using Raheem Sterling in a more central role. Related: Chelsea v Manchester City: match preview The City manager would not reveal his intended lineup but has three in-form wingers in Sterling, Riyad Mahrez and Leroy Sané, while Gabriel Jesus has so far failed to make the most of Agüero’s absence. “Raheem can play in many positions,” Guardiola said. “I prefer him on the wing but he did not always play there for Liverpool.”...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Manchester United vs Fulham, Premier League: Prediction, what time, what channel, how to stream online, team news, odds and more - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/manchester-united-vs-fulham-live-stream-info-online-latest-score-updates-goals-tv-watch-a8673121.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJWGWYTmUnTWogE4U4tXSdEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/manchester-united-vs-fulham-live-stream-info-online-latest-score-updates-goals-tv-watch-a8673121.html" target="_blank"&gt;Manchester United vs Fulham, Premier League: Prediction, what time, what channel, how to stream online, team news, odds and more&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manchester United will be looking for their first league win in four games when they entertain bottom club Fulham. Jose Mourinho’s team have drawn their past three Premier League games, including 2-2 draws against both Southampton and Arsenal in the past week. Claudio Ranieri’s side meanwhile remain rooted to the bottom of the table but are just one point off Huddersfield Town in 17th and they will therefore hope to snatch something from Old Trafford. What time does it start? Manchester United vs Fulham kicks off at 3pm (GMT) Fantasy Premier League Dream Team 2018-19 - 11 show all Fantasy P...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pep Guardiola: Beating Chelsea last season was catalyst for Manchester City title win - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/pep-guardiola-beating-chelsea-last-season-catalyst-manchester/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGNci-dRfu18UmwH6gU5HzgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDKzbcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/pep-guardiola-beating-chelsea-last-season-catalyst-manchester/" target="_blank"&gt;Pep Guardiola: Beating Chelsea last season was catalyst for Manchester City title win&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pep Guardiola returns to Chelsea on Saturday convinced that Manchester City’s victory at Stamford Bridge last season was the moment his masterplan began to crystallise. City’s 1-0 win against the defending champions in September last year, secured by a stunning second-half goal from midfielder Kevin De Bruyne, won widespread plaudits and was one of the highlights of a remarkable 18-match winning run in the Premier League. Guardiola believes it set the tone for City’s march to the title with an unprecedented 100 points and marked a level they have since continued to reach with regularity. “L...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Premier League clubs' Rainbow Laces posts draw homophobic responses - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/premier-league-clubs-rainbow-laces-posts-draw-homophobic-responses</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMTeMUkYR62byh1aIJ7vNX0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:54:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/premier-league-clubs-rainbow-laces-posts-draw-homophobic-responses" target="_blank"&gt;Premier League clubs' Rainbow Laces posts draw homophobic responses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Premier League football teams including Manchester United, Arsenal and Chelsea have received thousands of homophobic responses on social media for showing solidarity with Stonewall’s pro-LGBT Rainbow Laces campaign. Over the past two weeks the clubs have been posting pictures on social media of rainbow-striped logos and messages to back the annual campaign, which was launched by Stonewall in 2013 to kick out homophobia in football. A post on Manchester United’s Facebook page in support of the campaign received more than 43,000 “angry” responses. Fans’ comments including “Say No to LGBT”, “G...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Arsenal’s Unai Emery tells Mattéo Guendouzi: get your hair cut - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/06/arsenal-unai-emery-matteo-guendouzi-hair-cut-marouane-fellaini-manchester-united</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC5blpmHDeSkfayrBkGn5VYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:56:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/06/arsenal-unai-emery-matteo-guendouzi-hair-cut-marouane-fellaini-manchester-united" target="_blank"&gt;Arsenal’s Unai Emery tells Mattéo Guendouzi: get your hair cut&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unai Emery has brushed aside controversy over Mattéo Guendouzi’s hair by telling his youngster to get it cut. The French midfielder had his frizzy hair pulled straight by Marouane Fellaini during Arsenal’s 2-2 draw with Manchester United on Wednesday. The Belgian, who recently got rid of his own trademark afro, escaped punishment from the referee, Andre Marriner, and Emery believes the incident is now cut and dried. Related: Stalemate at Old Trafford and Wolves at Chelsea's door – Football Weekly Extra “I think the best thing is that he cuts his hair before the next match, then the problem ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'The club is very happy with him': Jose Mourinho given public backing via agent's statement - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/jorge-mendes-rumours-jose-mourinho-leaving-manchester-united/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHUul7HdAlzyA3GxCT03uBUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:17:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/jorge-mendes-rumours-jose-mourinho-leaving-manchester-united/" target="_blank"&gt;'The club is very happy with him': Jose Mourinho given public backing via agent's statement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jose Mourinho has been granted his wish of a formal assurance from Manchester United that his job is safe, with the club giving their blessing to a rare public statement from his all-powerful agent Jorge Mendes that there is no current prospect of a change at Old Trafford. The United manager goes into Saturday’s game at Fulham with just three points from his last four league games and the club eighth in the table, 18 behind leaders Manchester City. Once again he has experienced frustrations with gaining the public support of his club, as was the case three years ago at Chelsea. United have ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Arsenal vs Huddersfield: Unai Emery must decide when to rest senior players as fixtures come thick and fast - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/arsenal-news-vs-huddersfield-fc-unai-emery-team-latest-watch-video-prediction-preview-a8673196.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDAde8xtn8b5DrNc8yoL7dUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/arsenal-news-vs-huddersfield-fc-unai-emery-team-latest-watch-video-prediction-preview-a8673196.html" target="_blank"&gt;Arsenal vs Huddersfield: Unai Emery must decide when to rest senior players as fixtures come thick and fast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week last year, with an important Champions League match against Bayern Munich looming large on the horizon, Paris Saint-Germain manager Unai Emery decided to shuffle his pack. For the long journey to struggling Strasbourg’s Stade de la Meinau, Emery boldly dropped Edinson Cavani to the bench. Marco Verratti, too. Club captain Thiago Silva did not even make the squad. Strasbourg gratefully snatched at their chance. Goals from Nuno da Costa and Stephane Bahoken saw them run out unlikely 2-1 winners, rising to fourteenth in the Ligue 1 table. It was PSG’s first defeat of the season – and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Jurgen Klopp explains why it can be difficult when Liverpool and Manchester City play at different times - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/liverpool-vs-bournemouth-manchester-city-jurgen-klopp-team-news-latest-fixtures-a8673321.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN35lki2QpRXmugI6MazQDMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/liverpool-vs-bournemouth-manchester-city-jurgen-klopp-team-news-latest-fixtures-a8673321.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jurgen Klopp explains why it can be difficult when Liverpool and Manchester City play at different times&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This time it is Liverpool who will get the chance to strike first. Jurgen Klopp's side travelled to Burnley in midweek knowing that Manchester City had stretched their lead at the top of the Premier League table to five points 24 hours earlier. Klopp's men managed to respond, a come from behind victory at Turf Moor confirming this as Liverpool's best ever start to a league season. A trip to Bournemouth for Saturday's lunchtime kick-off means it is the Reds who can apply the pressure this time, possibly taking top spot in the Premier League, with Pep Guardiola's men facing a potentially diff...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Manchester United vs Fulham, Premier League 2018-19: What time is kick-off, what TV channel is it on and what is our prediction? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/manchester-united-vs-fulham-premier-league-2018-19-time-kick/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4QIeN5Y6LpHlENPz0AXyAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:14:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/manchester-united-vs-fulham-premier-league-2018-19-time-kick/" target="_blank"&gt;Manchester United vs Fulham, Premier League 2018-19: What time is kick-off, what TV channel is it on and what is our prediction?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is it? It's Manchester United against Fulham in the Premier League. Jose Mourinho was the first manager to welcome Claudio Ranieri back to England's top flight when he was appointed Fulham boss. Fulham, this weekend, visit Old Trafford, where Mourinho's United will hope to secure their first Premier League victory in five games, reuniting the pair for the first time since Ranieri's departure from Leicester. When is it? Saturday, December 8. What time is kick-off? 3pm. Newsletter Promotion - James Ducker's Man United briefingWhat TV channel is it on? Because it's a 3pm game, it's not on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>No laughing matter: Arsenal to speak to players after ‘hippy crack’ video emerges - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/sport/445843-arsenal-players-hippy-crack-video/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDn6aPlpL7V82dNRlgVom8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwlujfAw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:00:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/sport/445843-arsenal-players-hippy-crack-video/" target="_blank"&gt;No laughing matter: Arsenal to speak to players after ‘hippy crack’ video emerges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arsenal football club has said it will speak to several star players after footage emerged apparently showing them taking nitrous oxide – also known as ‘hippy crack’ – at a lavish party in London earlier this year. The Sun newspaper released CCTV footage on Friday which allegedly shows a group of Arsenal stars – including midfielder Mesut Ozil and striker Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang – inhaling nitrous oxide from balloons at a £30,000 “champagne and vodka party” attended by around 70 women at the exclusive Tape club in London’s West End. According to the newspaper, the group of Gunners players...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Jose Mourinho claims he can't play £52m Fred while Manchester United look so fragile in defence - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/jose-mourinho-claims-cant-play-52m-fred-manchester-united-look/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI_1PyUyiPOErhRHwpaRM8UqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDKzbcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:06:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/jose-mourinho-claims-cant-play-52m-fred-manchester-united-look/" target="_blank"&gt;Jose Mourinho claims he can't play £52m Fred while Manchester United look so fragile in defence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jose Mourinho has claimed it is difficult for him to play Fred while Manchester United remain so susceptible defensively. Fred was United’s headline summer signing in a £52 million deal from Shakhtar Donetsk, but he has been a peripheral figure this season. The Brazil midfielder, 25, was omitted from United’s squad for Wednesday’s 2-2 draw against Arsenal at Old Trafford and has been an unused substitute in five of the past seven matches. United have conceded 25 goals in Premier League 15 matches - more than anyone bar the bottom five - and Mourinho believes that fragility is behind Fred’s ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fantasy football picks and scout tips gameweek 16: Alexandre Lacazette, Trent Alexander-Arnold and more - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/fantasy-football-scout-tips-gameweek-16-fpl-a8671231.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEa-1YJ5ZdbcqUHJHZGv9ssqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/fantasy-football-scout-tips-gameweek-16-fpl-a8671231.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fantasy football picks and scout tips gameweek 16: Alexandre Lacazette, Trent Alexander-Arnold and more&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandre Lacazette Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang was very much the flavour of the week, seeing more price rises than points, and remains an excellent choice ahead of this weekend's meeting with Huddersfield Town. At £1.6m cheaper, however, Alexandre Lacazette should not be ignored, especially if he is restored to the starting line-up for Arsenal's forthcoming run of favourable fixtures. Lacazette scored in the north London derby and was a shade unlucky not to be awarded Marcos Rojo's goal at Old Trafford on Wednesday night. Lukasz Fabianski Even with just one clean sheet in his last nine outin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Jürgen Klopp admits Ben Mee tackle was ‘clean’ but bemoans rash sliding in - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/klopp-liverpool-sturridge-cheat-dyche</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIwx_aSWrWcrS-5nADaZgcUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:42:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/klopp-liverpool-sturridge-cheat-dyche" target="_blank"&gt;Jürgen Klopp admits Ben Mee tackle was ‘clean’ but bemoans rash sliding in&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jürgen Klopp has said Ben Mee did not intentionally injure Joe Gomez and the challenge that fractured the Liverpool defender’s leg was “the cleanest” committed by Burnley at Turf Moor. Related: Liverpool’s Joe Gomez suffers leg fracture but Sean Dyche defends tackles Klopp and Sean Dyche were embroiled in an angry exchange following Liverpool’s 3-1 win on Wednesday, with the Burnley manager annoyed by criticism of his players’ tackling. The Liverpool manager asked referee Stuart Attwell to take action over challenges that he believes were rash, but accepted were not fouls. That prompted Dyc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Home turf: Tyson Fury calls for Deontay Wilder rematch at Old Trafford - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/sport/445759-tyson-fury-deontay-wilder-rematch-old-trafford-manchester/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDI8SNJ4EpI8XlcoSCTSJGAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwlujfAw</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:03:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/sport/445759-tyson-fury-deontay-wilder-rematch-old-trafford-manchester/" target="_blank"&gt;Home turf: Tyson Fury calls for Deontay Wilder rematch at Old Trafford&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tyson Fury wants to bring Deontay Wilder over to England for their WBC world heavyweight title rematch, with the home of the British fighter's beloved Manchester United, the famous Old Trafford stadium, his preferred venue. Fury went the distance with reigning WBC heavyweight champion Wilder in a thrilling title clash at the Staples Center in Los Angeles last weekend, but was left angry and frustrated when the judges at ringside rendered a split draw verdict. READ MORE: All square! Champ Wilder and plucky Fury scored a draw in heavyweight title fight (PHOTOS) Immediately after the scores we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Unai Emery: ‘Arsenal are conceding more goals than we want’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/unai-emery-we-are-conceding-more-goals-than-we-want-but-we-are-improving</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEElhgL0Zevh3V8_E4Ct_1x0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:30:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/unai-emery-we-are-conceding-more-goals-than-we-want-but-we-are-improving" target="_blank"&gt;Unai Emery: ‘Arsenal are conceding more goals than we want’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This time last year Unai Emery came to the end of a 25-match unbeaten run with Paris Saint-Germain but the manager says he cannot remember a thing about it as he seeks to extend Arsenal’s 20-game streak against Huddersfield. Related: Lucas Torreira caps Arsenal’s comeback in 4-2 derby win over 10-man Spurs After a thrilling triumph against Tottenham and a solid point at Old Trafford, Arsenal came down to earth with news the defender Rob Holding will be out for the season through injury and a tabloid exposé that showed several players apparently taking nitrous oxide. Emery’s focus, however, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Bournemouth vs Liverpool LIVE - What time does it start, TV channel, team news, odds and predictions - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/bournemouth-vs-liverpool-live-stream-info-online-latest-score-updates-goals-tv-watch-a8673156.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEORp-XuzFBkrsSGxas_foXoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/bournemouth-vs-liverpool-live-stream-info-online-latest-score-updates-goals-tv-watch-a8673156.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bournemouth vs Liverpool LIVE - What time does it start, TV channel, team news, odds and predictions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liverpool have the opportunity to leapfrog Manchester City and go top of the table for a few hours at least when they meet seventh-placed Bournemouth. The Reds are yet to taste league defeat this season and will be confident of a win which could would them to the summit of the Premier League before Pep Guardiola’s side face a difficult task at Chelsea. Bournemouth however ended a run of four straight defeats in a 2-1 win over Huddersfield in midweek, with in-form Callum Wilson notching his eighth of the season. Follow the live action below. What time does it start? Bournemouth vs Liverpool ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Paul Scholes doubts Zinedine Zidane is right man to replace Jose Mourinho if Manchester United boss is sacked - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/manchester-united-news-jose-mourinho-next-manager-sacked-zinedine-zidane-paul-scholes-a8671876.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEATSEJ22Ekb31GB3FmkjzC4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/manchester-united-news-jose-mourinho-next-manager-sacked-zinedine-zidane-paul-scholes-a8671876.html" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Scholes doubts Zinedine Zidane is right man to replace Jose Mourinho if Manchester United boss is sacked&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Scholes has doubts over Zinedine Zidane’s suitability to be the next Manchester United manager when Jose Mourinho eventually leaves, with the former England midfielder unsure on the Frenchman’s ability to rebuild a club desperately short on confidence. Zidane is strongly considered by bookmakers to be the next United manager if the Premier League club decides to sack Mourinho, or he chooses to leave of his own accord. With last Wednesday’s 2-2 draw with Arsenal dropping United to eighth in the Premier League table and an alarming 18 points of rivals Manchester City, Mourinho is under g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Arsenal news: Rob Holding out for up to nine months with ruptured ACL, club confirm - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/arsenal-news-rob-holding-injury-team-knee-how-long-injured-defender-watch-video-latest-a8672141.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgMoD8qP42frU4SOUFEKY0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/arsenal-news-rob-holding-injury-team-knee-how-long-injured-defender-watch-video-latest-a8672141.html" target="_blank"&gt;Arsenal news: Rob Holding out for up to nine months with ruptured ACL, club confirm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arsenal defender Rob Holding has ruptured the anterior cruciate ligament of his left knee and will miss the remainder of the 2018/19 season, the club confirmed on Friday. Holding was taken off on a stretcher during the first-half of Arsenal’s 2-2 draw with Manchester United at Old Trafford on Wednesday, having broken into the first-team under Unai Emery this season. The 23-year-old was taken back to London for tests following the collision with Marcus Rashford, with scans revealing he had ruptured the anterior cruciate ligament of his left knee. “Rob will undergo surgery to repair this in t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Big Match Decoded: Why Chelsea must compete to win the midfield battle - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/big-match-decoded-chelsea-must-compete-win-midfield-battle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOJVS8Apdk3s_jSo0t9PvUEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 08:19:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/big-match-decoded-chelsea-must-compete-win-midfield-battle/" target="_blank"&gt;Big Match Decoded: Why Chelsea must compete to win the midfield battle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big game on Saturday in the Premier League is at Stamford Bridge as Maurizio Sarri's side hosts title favourites Man City. Chelsea have fallen out of form in recent weeks and Sarri-ball isn't having quite the effect it was earlier in the season. Pep Guardiola is a master at figuring out how to stop his opponents playing their game and with City flying high in the league, could do some damage, if not end Sarris' ambitious title ambitions. Some key tactical decisions have to be made - where will the game be won and lost? How Man City are dominating games It's essential that Sarri figures ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Defensive injuries mount up as Liverpool prepare for 'crazy' week - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/defensive-injuries-mount-liverpool-prepare-crazy-week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECjTsdG2ctRlwGlhrDLbr3sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/defensive-injuries-mount-liverpool-prepare-crazy-week/" target="_blank"&gt;Defensive injuries mount up as Liverpool prepare for 'crazy' week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liverpool start what Jurgen Klopp, their manager, believes is a “crazy” week of games with a minor defensive crisis ahead of Saturday’s lunchtime trip to Bournemouth. Victory would take Klopp’s side to the top of the Premier League, for a few hours at least, but they will have to do it with just two recognised centre-backs available – Virgil van Dijk and Joel Matip. Joe Gomez will miss around six weeks after suffering a break in his lower left leg in the victory at Burnley in midweek. Klopp revealed that his natural replacement, Dejan Lovren, was unavailable due to concussion. Klopp is hopi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Bournemouth vs Liverpool, Premier League 2018-19: What time is kick-off today, what TV channel is it on and what is our prediction? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/bournemouth-vs-liverpool-premier-league-2018-19-time-kick-off1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9laMKyVXG6xqYZ1CGrDaEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:50:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/bournemouth-vs-liverpool-premier-league-2018-19-time-kick-off1/" target="_blank"&gt;Bournemouth vs Liverpool, Premier League 2018-19: What time is kick-off today, what TV channel is it on and what is our prediction?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is it? It's the opening match of the 16th round of Premier League fixtures - seventh-placed AFC Bournemouth host unbeaten Liverpool in second. Liverpool have won five of these sides' six league meetings but two years ago Eddie Howe's side fought back from 3-1 down with 14 minutes to play to win a thriller 4-3 at the Vitality Stadium, which will always be known as Dean Court to people of a certain age and sensible disposititions. When is it? It's today, so Saturday, December 8. What time is kick-off? 12.30pm. Newsletter Promotion - Chris Bascombe's Liverpool briefingWhat TV channel is i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Arsenal to talk to players seen apparently inhaling nitrous oxide - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/arsenal-nitrous-oxide-ozil-aubameyang-spoken-to-responsibilities</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPmvlMTLZtZrt1mpebUNyUUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:39:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/arsenal-nitrous-oxide-ozil-aubameyang-spoken-to-responsibilities" target="_blank"&gt;Arsenal to talk to players seen apparently inhaling nitrous oxide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arsenal have responded to footage showing some of their players apparently inhaling nitrous oxide in a London nightclub by saying those involved will be spoken to and reminded of their responsibilities. A number of players, including Mesut Özil, Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang, Alexandre Lacazette and Mattéo Guendouzi, appear to inhale nitrous oxide – also referred to as laughing gas or hippy crack – in footage published by the Sun. Related: Arsenal’s Unai Emery tells Mattéo Guendouzi: get your hair cut The incident is reported to have taken place in August, before the start of the season. A club...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Manchester United 'very happy' with José Mourinho, says Jorge Mendes - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/jose-mourinho-manchester-united-fred-premier-league</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFFDVlItVckkMcPr7y6giPkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:56:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/jose-mourinho-manchester-united-fred-premier-league" target="_blank"&gt;Manchester United 'very happy' with José Mourinho, says Jorge Mendes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;José Mourinho’s agent, Jorge Mendes, has issued a rare statement in which he insists Manchester United’s manager is content at the club and the board are “very happy” with his client. Mourinho has cut an embattled figure for most of the campaign because of issues related to United’s summer transfer policy, his relationship with Paul Pogba and poor league form that has left his team 18 points behind the leaders, Manchester City, after 15 matches. Mendes’s move, then, will be viewed with interest. Related: Premier League: 10 things to look out for this weekend “There have been more rumours of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Chelsea vs Manchester City, Premier League 2018-19: What time is kick-off today, what TV channel is it on and what is our prediction? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/chelsea-vs-manchester-city-premier-league-2018-19-time-kick1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH28b2BMjikbgPgPKu28kMcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:05:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/chelsea-vs-manchester-city-premier-league-2018-19-time-kick1/" target="_blank"&gt;Chelsea vs Manchester City, Premier League 2018-19: What time is kick-off today, what TV channel is it on and what is our prediction?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is it? This is the Premier League match between table-toppers Manchester City and third-placed Chelsea. Can Chelsea inflict a first defeat of the season on the reigning champions? When is it? It's today, so Saturday, December 8. What time is kick-off? 5.30pm. What TV channel is it on? The match will be shown live on BT Sport 1. Should you not have access to that channel you can follow all the action right here when this page turns into our live blog. What is the team news? Chelsea Jorginho and David Luiz are expected to return to Chelsea's starting line-up. Chelsea manager Maurizio Sar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Liverpool’s Joe Gomez suffers leg fracture but Sean Dyche defends tackles - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/06/liverpool-joe-gomez-fracture-sean-dyche-defends-burnley</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDSiNX3PhDugvcjmHusw8ZsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:41:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/06/liverpool-joe-gomez-fracture-sean-dyche-defends-burnley" target="_blank"&gt;Liverpool’s Joe Gomez suffers leg fracture but Sean Dyche defends tackles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liverpool’s Joe Gomez will be out until the new year with a fracture of the lower left leg after crashing into the perimeter wall at Turf Moor on Wednesday. Related: Liverpool hot on City’s heels after James Milner sparks fightback at Burnley Playing at right-back, Gomez was racing down the touchline in an attacking position when a sliding tackle from Ben Mee took the ball cleanly but followed through to bring down the Liverpool player, who skidded over the dead ball line and into an advertising hoarding. Gomez was treated pitchside but was in obvious pain and ended up being carried off on ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Jesse Lingard: Playing at the World Cup has taken its toll on my body - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/06/jesse-lingard-playing-world-cup-has-taken-toll-body/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0A8WAVwRXTeUsEHcXCIncqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/06/jesse-lingard-playing-world-cup-has-taken-toll-body/" target="_blank"&gt;Jesse Lingard: Playing at the World Cup has taken its toll on my body&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jesse Lingard has admitted that his exertions at the World Cup with England have taken their toll. The Manchester United forward has been suffering from a groin problem and, although he attempted to manage the inflammation, he had to eventually take a rest, missing games in October. “Coming off the World Cup, I played a lot of games over the course of last season and it kind of paid a toll,” the 25-year-old said. “We didn’t get much rest in the summer after the World Cup, so, coming back, there’s always going to be little niggles here and there. I wasn’t really 100 per cent fit, but I feel ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Chelsea vs Manchester City LIVE - What time does it start, TV channel, team news, prediction and odds - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/chelsea-vs-manchester-city-live-stream-info-online-latest-score-updates-goals-tv-watch-a8673036.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPpTiZWYke0T4v_W7iMo6DAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/chelsea-vs-manchester-city-live-stream-info-online-latest-score-updates-goals-tv-watch-a8673036.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chelsea vs Manchester City LIVE - What time does it start, TV channel, team news, prediction and odds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maurizio Sarri will have his work cut out in his attempts to restart Chelsea’s season when they welcome unbeaten Manchester City in the late kick-off. Chelsea looked to have bounced back from their first defeat of the season against Tottenham with victory over Fulham last weekend, but a second loss quickly followed in the Midlands at Wolves in midweek. Pep Guardiola's side however have dropped just two points all season and have won their last seven top-flight games, and so will be hoping to inflict another defeat on the hosts. What time does it start? Chelsea vs Manchester City kicks off a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Arsenal vs Huddersfield, Premier League 2018-19: What time is kick-off today, what TV channel is it on and what is our prediction? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/arsenal-vs-huddersfield-premier-league-2018-19-time-kick-off1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDvQ-JOybL0ZlebuoBdxKdwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:12:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/08/arsenal-vs-huddersfield-premier-league-2018-19-time-kick-off1/" target="_blank"&gt;Arsenal vs Huddersfield, Premier League 2018-19: What time is kick-off today, what TV channel is it on and what is our prediction?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is it? It is Arsenal vs Huddersfield in the Premier League - the 16th league match for each side this season. When is it? It's today, so Saturday December 8. What time is kick-off? It is a 3pm GMT start at the Emirates. What TV channel is it on? Unfortunately in the UK, it is not, because of the 3pm TV blackout. Highlights will be on Match of the Day at 10.20pm on BBC One. Alternatively, you can follow the game live here. Rob Holding is out for nine months with injuryCredit: Reuters What is the team news? Arsenal: Defender Rob Holding is out of Arsenal's Premier League clash with Hudde...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Pep Guardiola confident Manchester City will not face Uefa ban after speaking to club chairman - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/pep-guardiola-manchester-city-press-conference-ban-financial-fair-play-uefa-a8672991.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGKnw6-xc7KY08gItzVTtXIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/pep-guardiola-manchester-city-press-conference-ban-financial-fair-play-uefa-a8672991.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pep Guardiola confident Manchester City will not face Uefa ban after speaking to club chairman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pep Guardiola is confident that Manchester City will not be banned from the Champions League despite Uefa’s investigation into the club’s Financial Fair Play (FFP) compliance. Uefa will consider taking strong action against City if allegations published by Der Spiegel, the German magazine, are found to be proven by the investigation launched last month. Aleksander Ceferin, the president of Uefa, this week said City had “a concrete case” to answer and pledged an outcome “very soon”. Across Manchester on Friday, Jose Mourinho suggested that authorities must clamp down on City’s spending in or...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Manchester United team news: Anthony Martial and Eric Bailly face late injury tests of Fulham clash - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/manchester-united-vs-fulham-team-news-injury-updates-anthony-martial-paul-pogba-jose-mourinho-luke-a8672431.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaN_d3rouqCeanCAO2aczwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/manchester-united-vs-fulham-team-news-injury-updates-anthony-martial-paul-pogba-jose-mourinho-luke-a8672431.html" target="_blank"&gt;Manchester United team news: Anthony Martial and Eric Bailly face late injury tests of Fulham clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anthony Martial, Chris Smalling and Phil Jones are among the players that could be absent for Manchester United against Fulham. The trio will be assessed on Friday, as will centre-back Eric Bailly after Wednesday’s 2-2 draw against Arsenal. Luke Shaw is hoping to return after missing that match with a knock and Ashley Young is back from suspension. Paul Pogba and Romelu Lukaku will be hoping to return to the starting line-up after being dropped to the bench against the Gunners, but Victor Lindelof (groin) and Alexis Sanchez (hamstring) are out. There is unlikely to be any place in the side ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Jay Rodriguez admits scoring late equaliser for West Brom against Aston Villa with hand - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/late-jay-rodriguez-handball-goal-rescues-point-west-brom/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-7wJXP-GOPPfRfC3L6ACsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDKzbcF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 08:33:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/late-jay-rodriguez-handball-goal-rescues-point-west-brom/" target="_blank"&gt;Jay Rodriguez admits scoring late equaliser for West Brom against Aston Villa with hand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;West Brom 2 Aston Villa 2 Aston Villa were controversially denied maximum points as Darren England, the referee, allowed a Jay Rodriguez stoppage-time equaliser to stand after the West Bromwich Albion striker had clearly bundled the ball into the net with his hands. The South Yorkshire official consulted his assistant on the line in response to vehement protests by goalkeeper Orjan Nyland and his team-mates but did not reverse his decision, leaving Villa with a sense of injustice that replays showed was understandable. Diving in to meet a Matt Phillips cross, with Albion throwing everything...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Matteo Guendouzi should cut his hair like Marouane Fellaini, says Unai Emery - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/06/matteo-guendouzi-should-cut-hair-like-marouane-fellaini-says/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPIXs2FCBf-QljxpO7dfd7wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:24:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/06/matteo-guendouzi-should-cut-hair-like-marouane-fellaini-says/" target="_blank"&gt;Matteo Guendouzi should cut his hair like Marouane Fellaini, says Unai Emery&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unai Emery has joked that Matteo Guendouzi should cut his extravagant hair if he wants to avoid a repeat of Wednesday’s night hair-pulling incident with Marouane Fellaini. The Arsenal midfielder was tugged back by his hair by Fellaini in the second half of the 2-2 draw at Old Trafford. Fellaini will not face any retrospective action for the foul because it was seen by Andre Marriner, who decided not to book the Manchester United midfielder. Fellaini has in fact been on the receiving end of similar treatment in the past. The Belgian, who only recently shaved his own sizeable hairdo, had his ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tottenham’s Danny Rose: playing at Wembley no longer feels like an honour - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/06/tottenham-danny-rose-playing-wembley-no-longer-honour</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPVWnh8vKRZGNSuOV5n9WugqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:00:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/06/tottenham-danny-rose-playing-wembley-no-longer-honour" target="_blank"&gt;Tottenham’s Danny Rose: playing at Wembley no longer feels like an honour&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Danny Rose says it is no longer an honour to play at Wembley as he laid bare the frustration of Tottenham players with the club’s delayed new stadium and their unsatisfactory stop-gap accommodation. Spurs will continue to play their home matches at Wembley until at least the end of the month – with the suggestion being it could be February before they get into the rebuilt White Hart Lane – and there was a low point on Wednesday when only 33,012 turned up to see them beat Southampton 3-1. Related: UK betting firms back live sports advertising ban The club’s previous lowest league attendance ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Exclusive interview: Fabian Delph on day he told Man City stars to get basics right and how his hard work mantra has paid off - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/fabian-delph-day-told-man-city-stars-get-basics-right-hard-work/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDE8yG8vZgeoNvULzB83XFUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2018/12/07/fabian-delph-day-told-man-city-stars-get-basics-right-hard-work/" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive interview: Fabian Delph on day he told Man City stars to get basics right and how his hard work mantra has paid off&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;He can laugh about it now and, in reality, he is teased about it so often by his Manchester City team-mates that he does not have much choice but to see the funny side. Indeed, there were few more unintentionally amusing moments in the recent Amazon documentary, All Or Nothing, than the sight of Fabian Delph lecturing City’s dressing room on “the basics of football” in that thick Yorkshire accent of his after their shock 3-2 derby defeat to Manchester United in April. “The guys always come up to me now and say, ‘Oh, the basics!’” Delph says, chuckling at the recollection of a moment that ca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Chelsea vs Manchester City: Maurizio Sarri would do well to follow Pep Guardiola’s example - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/chelsea-vs-manchester-city-maurizio-sarri-pep-guardiola-latest-kick-off-a8672996.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED0IBAkieZpLg5ecca8Z2Q0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/football/premier-league/chelsea-vs-manchester-city-maurizio-sarri-pep-guardiola-latest-kick-off-a8672996.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chelsea vs Manchester City: Maurizio Sarri would do well to follow Pep Guardiola’s example&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pep Guardiola is a long-time admirer of Maurizio Sarri, and before he took over as Chelsea manager in July, Guardiola gave him some advice. The pair went for lunch with their shared hero Arrigo Sacchi, and Guardiola told Sarri how difficult it is to come to the Premier League and try to impose a new style of football on a playing squad. So difficult, in fact, that it is only worth trying to improve a small group – “14 players” – because trying to work with a large squad is almost impossible. In that first City season Guardiola soon realised he could not improve every player City had, so had...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Mauricio Pochettino: ‘If you look at our budgets Spurs are the same as Leicester’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/mauricio-pochettino-spurs-on-same-level-as-leicester-budget</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEkVKjIgQxWrrFUqyBn8T3sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:29:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/dec/07/mauricio-pochettino-spurs-on-same-level-as-leicester-budget" target="_blank"&gt;Mauricio Pochettino: ‘If you look at our budgets Spurs are the same as Leicester’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mauricio Pochettino has admitted Leicester are on Tottenham’s level when it comes to investment but insists money is not everything when it comes to competing at the top end of the Premier League. Related: Leicester City v Tottenham: match preview After bouncing back from a derby defeat against Arsenal with a midweek win over Southampton, Spurs travel to the King Power stadium on Saturday night. They could be 11 points behind the leaders Manchester City by the time they kick off but Tottenham are also eight points better off than they were this time last season and their manager believes ti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item></channel></rss>