<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>5G - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR00wTVdvNGVSSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:55:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>German 5G auction at risk if government demands roaming: FAZ - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-telecoms/german-5g-auction-at-risk-as-berlin-mulls-compulsory-roaming-faz-idUSKBN1O526U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFgzbBqrK56YjdgwcRGeHc4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:13:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-telecoms/german-5g-auction-at-risk-as-berlin-mulls-compulsory-roaming-faz-idUSKBN1O526U" target="_blank"&gt;German 5G auction at risk if government demands roaming: FAZ&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A German regulator has said the government's auction of fifth-generation (5G) mobile licenses could be delayed if operators had to offer roaming in rural areas, the Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung (FAZ) reported on Thursday. But the Transport Ministry said national roaming was not possible based on a European provision and so not planned. It said details in a letter cited by FAZ were taken out of context. FAZ had said the government was mulling changes to the auction requirements envisaging compulsory roaming in rural areas with patchy mobile phone coverage. FAZ said it was citing a letter f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECs8OiMwxPuwcZzcG4cRAdMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes no notch in the Galaxy S10, the 5G S10 confirmed for America, the OnePlus 5G heading to the UK, three new Nokia handsets, a review of the Pocophone F1, Huawei’s ongoing security issues, and an innovation award for the Pixel 3 and 3XL. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). No Notch, But There Will Be A Hole, In The New Galaxy S10 Samsung appe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why are countries banning Huawei? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/countries-banning-huawei-181206130850129.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDteHDrcCES2me443duLxuEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:36:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/countries-banning-huawei-181206130850129.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why are countries banning Huawei?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, Canadian authorities arrested Meng Wanzhou, the chief financial officer (CFO) of Chinese tech company Huawei. The details of the arrest are still unclear but Meng faces extradition to the United States, according to the Canadian Department of Justice. Following the arrest, both the Chinese embassy, as well as Huawei called for the release of Meng, who is the daughter of the company's founder Ren Zhengfei. Under Ren's leadership, Huawei has become one of the biggest telecommunications companies in the world and has established itself as a leading smartphone manufacturer. But Hua...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Huawei Executive's Arrest Threatens To Derail Company's Global Ambitions - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ywang/2018/12/07/huawei-executives-arrest-threatens-to-derail-companys-global-ambitions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDe_Ws6cjyED0o2f_WyZ7fIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ywang/2018/12/07/huawei-executives-arrest-threatens-to-derail-companys-global-ambitions/" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei Executive's Arrest Threatens To Derail Company's Global Ambitions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attendees stand at the Huawei Technologies booth at the Mobile World Congress Shanghai on June 28, 2018. (Photo: Qilai Shen/Bloomberg) The arrest of a senior executive at telecom equipment supplier Huawei Technologies will likely give rise to more security concerns in other countries closely allied with the U.S. and jeopardize the company’s future revenue streams. Huawei’s Chief Financial Officer Meng Wanzhou, who is also the daughter of the company’s founder Ren Zhengfei, was detained in Vancouver and faces possible extradition to the U.S. While the charges against Meng haven’t been specif...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What is Huawei, and why the arrest of its CFO matters - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/tech/what-is-huawei/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGqZk536Mn4unUzP6IRjJJIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:35:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/tech/what-is-huawei/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;What is Huawei, and why the arrest of its CFO matters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The arrest of a top Huawei executive has roiled the business world and threatens to derail the tenuous trade truce between the United States and China. Meng Wanzhou, the Chinese tech company's chief financial officer, was detained in Vancouver on Saturday at the request of US authorities. She's accused by the United States of helping Huawei cover up violations of sanctions on Iran, according to Canadian prosecutors. US lawmakers are condemning Huawei, which they say poses a national security threat to the United States. Chinese officials have called for Meng's release. An op-ed in the Chine...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Japan government to halt buying Huawei, ZTE equipment: sources - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-china-huawei/japan-government-to-halt-buying-huawei-zte-equipment-sources-idUSKBN1O600X</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDg2o64e5N4PEWa1sdvSWsqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:35:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-china-huawei/japan-government-to-halt-buying-huawei-zte-equipment-sources-idUSKBN1O600X" target="_blank"&gt;Japan government to halt buying Huawei, ZTE equipment: sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan plans to ban government purchases of equipment from China's Huawei Technologies Co Ltd and ZTE Corp to beef up its defenses against intelligence leaks and cyber attacks, sources told Reuters. Chinese tech companies are under intense scrutiny from Washington and some prominent allies over ties to the Chinese government, driven by concerns they could be used by Beijing for spying. A government ban in Japan will come after Huawei has already been locked out of the U.S. market and after Australia and New Zealand have blocked it from building 5G networks. Huawei has repeatedly insisted Bei...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>O2 tries to get to grips with fallout from network failure - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1a6b11be-fa3e-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECo6lCK5aDeiRZKyibfSdwkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:17:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1a6b11be-fa3e-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;O2 tries to get to grips with fallout from network failure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;O2 has offered millions of angry customers credits and discounts after one of Britain’s longest mobile network failures caused chaos on Thursday. It took almost 24 hours for the mobile phone operator to restore data services to its 3G and 4G networks. Brands including Tesco Mobile and GiffGaff, whose networks piggy-back on O2’s, were also hit. Text and voice services were unaffected, but the sheer number of people forced to use them overloaded that network. The chaos went far beyond smartphones and tablets, however. In an illustration of how dependent modern systems are on connectivity, pas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Explainer: What is China's Huawei Technologies and why is it controversial? - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei-explainer/what-is-chinas-huawei-technologies-and-why-is-it-controversial-idUSKBN1O5172</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2JkNqkTxoNaJ_C8GNBku8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:40:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei-explainer/what-is-chinas-huawei-technologies-and-why-is-it-controversial-idUSKBN1O5172" target="_blank"&gt;Explainer: What is China's Huawei Technologies and why is it controversial?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The arrest in Canada of Meng Wanzhou, a top executive at China's Huawei Technologies Co Ltd and daughter of the founder and CEO, jolted the global business community on Thursday and raised fears that a truce in the U.S.-China trade war could come to a swift end. Meng's arrest came at the behest of U.S. authorities and is connected to an investigation into alleged violations of U.S. trade sanctions, a person familiar with the matter told Reuters. China's foreign ministry said neither the United States nor Canada have explained reasons for the arrest. What is Huawei? Huawei is the world's lar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Apple Loop: Poor iPhone Sales Frighten Apple, Frustrating iPhone 5G Delay, Huge iPhone XR Price Cut - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/apple-news-headlines-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-iphone-xr-discount-5g-airpods/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJnlWej_IG0szwozRXTPvhQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/apple-news-headlines-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-iphone-xr-discount-5g-airpods/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Loop: Poor iPhone Sales Frighten Apple, Frustrating iPhone 5G Delay, Huge iPhone XR Price Cut&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at another week of news from Cupertino, this week’s Apple Loop includes Apple’s response to falling iPhone sales, no 5G for next year’s iPhone, the return of TouchID, no new AirPods for Christmas, the first official iPhone XR cover, and the legend of the Apple Store. Apple Loop is here to remind you of a few of the very many discussions that have happened around Apple over the last seven days (and you can read my weekly digest of Android news here on Forbes). iPhone XR’s $300 Discount Apple continues to react to the low sales of the iPhone with decisions that feel more pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>US and China Fight for Supremacy in 5G Technology - VOA News</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xnZt1Xd8Vpg</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBh-AMUYtZS0JRHW_mt03eAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw78Uq</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:33:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xnZt1Xd8Vpg" target="_blank"&gt;US and China Fight for Supremacy in 5G Technology&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many experts predict that the emerging 5G wireless technology will revolutionize the world's economy. They say it holds the key to a smarter, more efficient, more connected and much wealthier world. But a recent congressional report outlines how China plans to use the transition to 5G and its access to billions of networked electronic devices for intelligence-gathering, sabotage and business deals. As VOA's Jela de Franceschi reports, China's aim is to put an end to US high-tech pre-eminence. Originally published at - https://www.voanews.com/a/us-and-china-fight-for-supremacy-in-5g-technolo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>China's Huawei, a Big Tech Seller Globally, Runs Afoul of US - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/china-huawei-runs-afoul-of-us/4690514.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG_gWu8lDtA9a5CQNmEHescqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:59:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/china-huawei-runs-afoul-of-us/4690514.html" target="_blank"&gt;China's Huawei, a Big Tech Seller Globally, Runs Afoul of US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent arrest of a top Huawei executive in Canada has put a spotlight — again — on the Chinese telecommunications giant. Huawei (pronounced Wah Way) is little known inside the U.S. except as a target of U.S. security agencies. Yet the Chinese telecommunications firm recently passed Apple as the No. 2 seller of smartphones worldwide after Samsung and is in a race with other telecom firms to build out the next generation wireless network, known as 5G. What is Huawei? Huawei, based in Shenzhen, is a Chinese telecommunications equipment and hardware firm, the largest supplier of networking ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The Guardian view on Huawei: the bigger story - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/the-guardian-view-on-huawei-the-bigger-story</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDX0jr4Wp3bhE94Yzpikr_YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:54:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/06/the-guardian-view-on-huawei-the-bigger-story" target="_blank"&gt;The Guardian view on Huawei: the bigger story&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets can be erratic beasts, as indicative of collective neuroses as collective wisdom. But it is not surprising that they reacted to Wednesday’s thunderbolt. Much remains unclear about Canada’s arrest of a powerful executive from Chinese telecoms behemoth Huawei at the request of the US. Whatever precisely happened, and however this plays out, it is a dramatic course of action against a company at the heart of Chinese technology ambitions – and the pushback against them. It comes in the midst of a trade war with the US and broader security fears about Chinese firms. Huawei is the world’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Ericsson sorry for software glitch that hits mobile services in Britain and Japan - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-o2telefonica-outages/ericsson-software-glitch-hits-mobile-services-in-britain-and-japan-idUSKBN1O51I2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8tuGmv-BO7LlFiaeDWYgAqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:57:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-o2telefonica-outages/ericsson-software-glitch-hits-mobile-services-in-britain-and-japan-idUSKBN1O51I2" target="_blank"&gt;Ericsson sorry for software glitch that hits mobile services in Britain and Japan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sweden's Ericsson (ERICb.ST: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) apologized and said it was working hard to fix a software glitch that was responsible for millions of smartphone users in Britain, Japan and other countries losing internet access on Thursday. O2 (TEF.MC: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), Britain's second biggest network, and Japan's Softbank (9984.T: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), both Ericsson customers, reported outages on their 4G networks earlier on Thursday. The mobile network equipment maker confirmed that a problem with its software was to blame for the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Why is Huawei so controversial and being targeted by foreign governments? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/why-is-chinese-tech-company-huawei-being-targeted/10593156</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEItErome4rnibBMo5F_JXu8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:00:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/why-is-chinese-tech-company-huawei-being-targeted/10593156" target="_blank"&gt;Why is Huawei so controversial and being targeted by foreign governments?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The dramatic arrest in Canada of a top Chinese technology executive for possible extradition to the United States has sent stock markets plummeting and cast doubt on a recent US-China trade truce. Key points: - Meng Wanzhou has been with Huawei for 25 years and is seen as a future chief - Huawei operates in 170 countries, servicing more than a third of the world's population - US intelligence agencies have warned people not to buy Huawei products due to concerns about spying Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said his Government had no involvement in the arrest of Meng Wanzhou and he ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>AT&amp;T To Verizon: 6 Experts Talk Up 8 Favorite Telecoms - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/moneyshow/2018/12/06/att-to-verizon-6-experts-talk-up-8-favorite-telecoms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJh6e7YJiNLpq1rFu3mXJQ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/moneyshow/2018/12/06/att-to-verizon-6-experts-talk-up-8-favorite-telecoms/" target="_blank"&gt;AT&amp;T To Verizon: 6 Experts Talk Up 8 Favorite Telecoms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verizon, the largest mobile carrier, covers 98% of the U.S. Here, Consumer Electronics Association president Gary Shapiro, left, greets Verizon Communications Inc., chairman and CEO Ivan Seidenberg, right, and president and COO Lowell McAdam during the CES, in Las Vegas. Jan. 6, 2011. (AP file photo/Julie Jacobson) Telecom stocks have pulled back with the overall market. But with the continued global growth of smartphones, increased data usage, new trends in digital media and upcoming advances such as 5G, several contributors to MoneyShow.com continue to see long-term opportunities in the t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Huawei/Ericsson: signal failure - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/085eafb0-f964-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMTalhvwpLXwEaXz4HiMGQMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:10:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/085eafb0-f964-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei/Ericsson: signal failure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Security experts worry about back doors. That is stopping Huawei getting through the front ones. Nordic rivals of the Chinese telecoms equipment group will benefit. On Thursday morning Ericsson was the sole gainer among Europe’s tech stocks as markets reeled following Canada’s arrest of the daughter of Huawei’s founder. Meng Wanzhou, the group’s chief financial officer, is facing extradition to the US on suspicions of violating US trade sanctions. While not directly linked to security worries, it adds to the thickening fog of distrust about Huawei. A day earlier, it emerged the UK’s BT Grou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>EE signs deal with Chinese smartphone firm in bid for UK's first 5G coverage - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/05/ee-signs-deal-chinese-smartphone-firm-bid-uks-first-5g-coverage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDMIxDKppIVkE5D7CLkeaEAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/05/ee-signs-deal-chinese-smartphone-firm-bid-uks-first-5g-coverage/" target="_blank"&gt;EE signs deal with Chinese smartphone firm in bid for UK's first 5G coverage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BT's mobile network arm EE will launch what is expected to be the first 5G smartphone on UK networks early next year, signing a deal with Chinese smartphone minnow OnePlus for its upcoming 5G phone. The network operator is planning to launch the latest generation of wireless technology from 2019 in 16 cities in the UK. The deal with OnePlus will mean the smartphone maker will be among the first to secure network coverage for its new phone on the fifth-generation network. While countries like Japan, South Korea and China have been making advances on 5G technology, EE is the first network so ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>OnePlus to make first 5G phone in Europe with EE, company claims - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/oneplus-5g-phone-ee-bt-qualcomm-faster-internet-connection-network-a8669226.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPiYCwu5P2Fo3VR-FvNzilMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/oneplus-5g-phone-ee-bt-qualcomm-faster-internet-connection-network-a8669226.html" target="_blank"&gt;OnePlus to make first 5G phone in Europe with EE, company claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OnePlus is going to make the first 5G phone available in Europe, the company has said. The decision could entirely change the way that phones work and will introduce a transformative technology to the UK, Andy Lau, OnePlus’s chief executive and founder, told The Independent. The phone maker has teamed up with EE to make the handset available, aiming to have it ready for users in 2019. The two companies have signed a research and development partnership that will help deliver much faster and more reliable internet connections across the UK, they said. 5G technology has become one of the most...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>BT to remove Huawei hardware from 4G network amid fears of Chinese spying - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/05/bt-remove-huawei-hardware-4g-network-amid-fears-chinese-spying/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFh_vDNtc6vTrEHv_vAVWbcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:28:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/05/bt-remove-huawei-hardware-4g-network-amid-fears-chinese-spying/" target="_blank"&gt;BT to remove Huawei hardware from 4G network amid fears of Chinese spying&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BT will remove Huawei hardware from its core 4G network within the next two years amid concerns over China's influence on national telecoms infrastructure. The decision comes as governments increase their scrutiny of Huawei equipment ahead of rolling out 5G, the next generation mobile communication technology that promise faster download speeds and better connections. A spokesman said that Huawei devices will be removed “from the core of our 3G and 4G networks as part of our network architecture principles in place since 2006”. “We’re applying these same principles to our current request fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm Launches 5G With The Snapdragon 855 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/05/qualcomm-launches-5g-with-the-snapdragon-855/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEE9eii9TsBtzbZk2FeOQjMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/05/qualcomm-launches-5g-with-the-snapdragon-855/" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm Launches 5G With The Snapdragon 855&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Qualcomm Snapdragon 855 platform supports 5G applications and connectivity We have all become accustomed to new, faster, and more efficient mobile processors, or more appropriately called System-on-Chips or SoCs, every year as the mobile industry continues to push performance and functionality to new levels. With the slowing of Moore’s Law, one would expect the performance enhancements to mobile SoCs to slow, but as Qualcomm demonstrated with the new Snapdragon 855, that is not the case. Dubbed the first 5G chipset by Qualcomm, the Snapdragon 855 is a significant increase in performance...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Huawei phone equipment in UK to be dismantled amid fears they could be used by China to spy on people - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/huawei-5g-phone-masts-equipment-bt-ee-internet-data-chinese-government-a8669076.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGBukS-0PGxvwWvEKdU5tDwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/huawei-5g-phone-masts-equipment-bt-ee-internet-data-chinese-government-a8669076.html" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei phone equipment in UK to be dismantled amid fears they could be used by China to spy on people&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BT is removing Huawei technology from the phone networks amid fears that the Chinese government could be using its infrastructure to spy on citizens. The company says it will no longer use Huawei's equipment in its existing 3G and 4G networks, and that it would not use it to build the 5G ones that it is building at the moment. It is just the latest operator to announce that it would not use the Chinese companies equipment amid fears that phone messages they are relaying could be intercepted. New Zealand and Australia have stopped telecom operators using Huawei's equipment in new 5G networks...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>BT to strip China's Huawei from core networks, limit 5G access - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-bt-group-huawei-tech/bt-to-strip-chinas-huawei-from-core-networks-limit-5g-access-idUSKBN1O41C1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjIignXS5kRu00lNyKRnZMqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:16:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-bt-group-huawei-tech/bt-to-strip-chinas-huawei-from-core-networks-limit-5g-access-idUSKBN1O41C1" target="_blank"&gt;BT to strip China's Huawei from core networks, limit 5G access&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain's BT Group said on Wednesday it was removing Huawei Technologies' equipment from the core of its existing 3G and 4G mobile operations and would not use the Chinese company in central parts of the next network. New Zealand and Australia have stopped telecom operators using Huawei's equipment in new 5G networks because they are concerned about possible Chinese government involvement in their communications infrastructure. Huawei, the world's biggest network equipment maker ahead of Ericsson and Nokia, has said Beijing has no influence over its operations. BT said Huawei's equipment ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Huawei's no good, very bad year just got even worse - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/tech/china-us-huawei/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF89-J4q2gHfwaQfR0d-VzEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:56:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/tech/china-us-huawei/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei's no good, very bad year just got even worse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The arrest of Huawei's chief financial officer caps a terrible year for the Chinese tech company. Canadian authorities said late Wednesday they had detained Meng Wanzhou at the request of the US government, which wants her extradited on unspecified charges. A spokesperson for Huawei said the company was "not aware of any wrongdoing" by Meng, the daughter of company founder Ren Zhengfei. Huawei, which makes smartphones and equipment for telecommunications networks, has already found itself on the defensive this year after a number of countries blocked wireless carriers from using some of its...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Samsung Suddenly 'Confirms' Radical 5G Galaxy S10 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-5g-release-date-price-cost-verizon-att-upgrade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzHJ9vIrddPWJnbbQDtf0oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/samsung-galaxy-s10-5g-release-date-price-cost-verizon-att-upgrade/" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Suddenly 'Confirms' Radical 5G Galaxy S10&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We already know Samsung’s 10th-anniversary Galaxy S10 is the biggest shake-up of the Galaxy range in years. There will be four models (including a new, more affordable version), up to six cameras, massive displays and ‘gradient’ colour schemes. And now Samsung isn’t even trying to hide its biggest upgrade of all… In a pair of official announcements which are about as subtle as a brick, both Verizon and AT&amp;T have announced a partnership with Samsung to deliver a ‘5G Galaxy smartphone’ in the first half of 2019. And yes, we know exactly what this is. Galaxy S10 Plus Concept “5G is going to b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Galaxy S10 Details Confirm Powerful Features - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-5g-qualcomm-snapdragon-855-confirmed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBfJb5891KEyjYbQeeJek7wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/samsung-galaxy-s10-plus-5g-qualcomm-snapdragon-855-confirmed/" target="_blank"&gt;New Galaxy S10 Details Confirm Powerful Features&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samsung has confirmed its continuing partnership with Qualcomm will see the South Korean company use the new SnapDragon 855 system on chip inside 2019′s Galaxy smartphones, starting with its first 5G device for US market. Both Verizon and AT&amp;T have confirmed a 5G Galaxy smartphone will arrive in the first half of next year. While the connection was not explicitly made, Samsung’s VP of Product Marketing and Strategy, Justin Denison, confirmed that the upcoming US 5G smartphone from the South Korean company would be powered by Qualcomm’s SnapDragon 855 system on chip. The only handset we’re a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Huawei arrest imperils a fragile US-China truce - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/505a7be6-f955-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGV8MYxUWfpON1dV987rgmEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:47:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/505a7be6-f955-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei arrest imperils a fragile US-China truce&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The arrest in Canada of a top executive of Huawei, the Chinese telecoms group, marks an alarming escalation in the trade and technology transfer dispute between China and the US even if ostensibly its cause is unrelated. The detention of Meng Wanzhou is certain to complicate efforts to repair relations between the world’s two largest economies. Concern over the implications for the global economy were reflected in market jitters on Thursday, when stocks worldwide extended their recent decline. Ms Meng, Huawei’s chief financial officer, was picked up during a layover in Canada following an e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>BT removing Huawei equipment from parts of 4G network - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/05/bt-removing-huawei-equipment-from-parts-of-4g-network</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM6nO5EJbtuuyU3HaFneFecqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:25:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/05/bt-removing-huawei-equipment-from-parts-of-4g-network" target="_blank"&gt;BT removing Huawei equipment from parts of 4G network&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BT has confirmed it is removing Huawei equipment from key areas of its 4G network after concerns were raised about the Chinese firm’s presence in critical telecoms infrastructure. The company said the removals were merely the continuation of a policy which began when it purchased the mobile phone carrier EE in 2015, to ensure that both parts of the combined network ran on the same technology. Many peripheral parts of BT and EE’s systems still run on Huawei equipment, and there were no plans to alter that. Governments in the US, New Zealand and Australia have already moved to block the use o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Huawei Q&amp;A: what you need to know about the Chinese phone maker - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/06/huawei-qa-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-chinese-phone-maker</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI4Y85Vbj-j2SbMh_od1u5oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:55:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/06/huawei-qa-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-chinese-phone-maker" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei Q&amp;A: what you need to know about the Chinese phone maker&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is Huawei? Huawei (pronounced “Wah-Way”) is a telecommunications and electronics company based in Shenzhen in the south of China. It is also the world’s largest telecoms equipment firm – in August it overtook Apple to become the world’s second-largest smartphone seller behind Samsung. In the second quarter of 2017 the Chinese company sold 54.2m phones, making up 15% of the share of the market. Though its phones are popular all over the world, Huawei has been blocked by several countries from being involved in supplying equipment for the rollout of 5G networks, with governments citing n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Canada arrests Huawei CFO after US extradition request - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/10065056-f8e2-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENtPizh_V3-Kfudi155OHUoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 06:22:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/10065056-f8e2-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Canada arrests Huawei CFO after US extradition request&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canada has arrested Huawei’s chief financial officer following a US extradition request, reigniting tensions between Washington and Beijing just days after Donald Trump and Xi Jinping tried to resolve their trade conflict at the G20 summit. Canadian officials on Wednesday said that they had detained Meng Wanzhou, the daughter of Ren Zhengfei, founder and chief executive of the Chinese telecoms group, on Saturday in Vancouver. Ms Meng, who became one of Huawei’s four deputy chairpersons this year, will face a bail hearing on Friday. Her arrest comes against a backdrop of heightened tensions ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Qualcomm unveils new chip to power 5G smartphones - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-samsung-elec/qualcomm-unveils-new-chip-to-power-5g-smartphones-idUSKBN1O32P1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMecw1wB_A6sq8OQSIV_45wqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:51:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-qualcomm-samsung-elec/qualcomm-unveils-new-chip-to-power-5g-smartphones-idUSKBN1O32P1" target="_blank"&gt;Qualcomm unveils new chip to power 5G smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chip supplier Qualcomm Inc (QCOM.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) on Tuesday unveiled a new generation of mobile phone processor chips that will power 5G smartphones in the United States as soon as next year. The key feature of the Snapdragon 855 chip, launched at an event in Hawaii, is a so-called modem for phones to connect to 5G wireless data networks with mobile data speeds of up to 50 or 100 times faster than current 4G networks. Mobile carriers are investing in 5G networks and are eager to sell 5G phones and data plans to recoup investment costs. Qualcomm, the largest supplier...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Huawei's 5G ambitions suffer another big setback - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/tech/huawei-5g-bt-technology/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAYcRmGQWMgVlapWItqVb2MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:46:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/tech/huawei-5g-bt-technology/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei's 5G ambitions suffer another big setback&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei's dream of becoming a global leader in 5G mobile networks has suffered another blow. UK telecoms group BT (BT) confirmed on Wednesday that it would not buy equipment from the Chinese tech company for the core of its next generation wireless network. The company also said it would remove existing Huawei technology from the heart of its 4G network within two years. A spokesperson for BT said the decision was taken to align its mobile phone business, which it acquired from EE in 2016, with long-standing company policies that have excluded Huawei from its core networks. The Chinese compa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>'Far too early to write the obituary for fixed broadband' as Telstra unveils 5G mobile plans - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/is-telstra-5g-evolution-or-revolution/10576342</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEPDa43Fp7m9w5koRAdAp7QqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 22:32:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/is-telstra-5g-evolution-or-revolution/10576342" target="_blank"&gt;'Far too early to write the obituary for fixed broadband' as Telstra unveils 5G mobile plans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;by business reporter Stephen Letts It is said 5G, or the next generation in mobile communications, is a brilliant technology in search of a business plan. Even without a revolutionary 5G application to unleash a flood of new revenues, or cover the cost of building the new networks, the big telcos are ploughing on with the roll out. Business plan or not, it's the way mobile telecommunications have evolved. Every decade or so a new generation, or G, is unveiled. The jump from 4G to 5G may prove to be profound in the history of telecommunications, but for the average phone user the change will...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Huawei finance chief arrested in Canada, faces extradition to US over Iran sanctions – report - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445687-huawei-executive-arrest-extradition/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELhmedhfNOyF0-5-Iv8zvkgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445687-huawei-executive-arrest-extradition/" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei finance chief arrested in Canada, faces extradition to US over Iran sanctions – report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canadian law enforcers have arrested a top executive at Chinese telecommunications equipment maker Huawei, heeding a request from the US. She is reportedly sought by the US for breaking trade embargo with Iran. The arrest of Wanzhou Meng, Huawei’s chief financial officer and board deputy chair, has been confirmed by the Canadian authorities. The woman was apprehended on Saturday and is awaiting the bail hearing scheduled for Friday, Canada’s Department of Justice spokesman Ian McLeod told The Globe and Mail. READ MORE: ‘National security risks’: New Zealand blocks use of Huawei equipment fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>New iPhone Leak Exposes Apple's Nasty Surprise - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-xs-max-xr-upgrade-problem-5g-price-cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKXV3t_Srlgj2YNZgtxojBAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-xs-max-xr-upgrade-problem-5g-price-cost/" target="_blank"&gt;New iPhone Leak Exposes Apple's Nasty Surprise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mounting evidence suggests Apple’s iPhone XS (details), iPhone XS Max (details) and iPhone XR (details) are not selling well even despite price cuts. We already know the crowd-pleasing innovation Apple has planned to win users back, but it might not be enough after a major source confirmed the most serious problem with the company’s new iPhones… Bloomberg reports Apple has fallen substantially behind its rivals and will not be able to equip iPhones with 5G until late 2020 at the earliest. And 5G is about to become a game-changer. Apple’s iPhone XS, iPhone XS Max and iPhone XR Bloomberg’s ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENR6R3fi9qwUs_y2cSw6FUgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:42:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2" target="_blank"&gt;Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verizon Communications Inc and Samsung Electronics Co Ltd on Monday confirmed long-held industry expectations they would seek to steal a march on Apple Inc by launching U.S. 5G smartphones in the first half of 2019. The two companies said in a statement they would unveil a prototype, using Qualcomm Inc's modem chips, at the chipmaker's annual Snapdragon Technology Summit in Maui, Hawaii this week. While Verizon is leading the charge to trial 5G in some cities next year, industry analysts say the higher-speed networks are unlikely to be widely available until the middle of the next decade. A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>BT to remove Huawei equipment from its core 4G network: FT - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-bt-group-huawei-tech/bt-to-remove-huawei-equipment-from-its-core-4g-network-ft-idUSKBN1O40ED</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENg34mqJsRgq45yUcL5fTqIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:51:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-bt-group-huawei-tech/bt-to-remove-huawei-equipment-from-its-core-4g-network-ft-idUSKBN1O40ED" target="_blank"&gt;BT to remove Huawei equipment from its core 4G network: FT&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain's BT Group Plc will remove Huawei Technologies Co's equipment from its core 4G network within two years, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday. The move by BT will bring its mobile phone business in line with an internal policy to keep the Chinese company's equipment at the edge of telecoms infrastructure, the paper said here BT has also excluded Huawei from bidding for contracts to supply equipment for use in its core 5G network, it said. However, BT will continue to use Huawei's kit in what it considers to be benign parts of the network, such as equipment on masts, FT said. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>5G smartphones are coming in 2019. What does that mean? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/samsung-verizon-5g/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBg7H2jCZlAeINu5jVJYwXUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:58:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/samsung-verizon-5g/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;5G smartphones are coming in 2019. What does that mean?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;5G is already here, but you can't do much to access those super-fast speeds unless you live in a specific place with a particular piece of technology. That's about to change. Samsung and Verizon (VZ) jointly announced Monday the companies would sell a 5G smartphone in the first half of 2019. Although they didn't say which phone would support 5G, Samsung usually announces its latest Galaxy S smartphone in the spring. The mystery phone may not be the first 5G smartphone to hit the market. Unsure of other companies' plans, Verizon and Samsung hedged by saying it would be "one of the first." Bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>iPhone: New Apple handset with faster 5G internet will not arrive until 2020, report claims - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/iphone-5g-release-date-apple-new-faster-internet-update-a8667116.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG33uTE2kblKqnMBP8jnl84qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/iphone-5g-release-date-apple-new-faster-internet-update-a8667116.html" target="_blank"&gt;iPhone: New Apple handset with faster 5G internet will not arrive until 2020, report claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple might not make a 5G iPhone until 2020, leaving its customers without the latest, fastest internet technology. The new report from Bloomberg comes despite the fact that networks – and most other major manufacturers – are preparing to update for the technology over the next year. It will mean that Apple will be far from the first to the market with the fast new internet technology. Rivals like Samsung are expected to launch their own 5G phones soon, which will theoretically benefit from vastly improved connectivity. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>BT to strip Huawei equipment from its core 4G network - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c639aaf4-f7c9-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHl1sQnLR4vcU0nY39PCoPkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c639aaf4-f7c9-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;BT to strip Huawei equipment from its core 4G network&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BT will strip Huawei equipment out of its core 4G network within two years to bring its mobile phone business in line with an internal policy to keep the Chinese company’s equipment at the periphery of telecoms infrastructure. Governments around the world have become increasingly wary of Huawei’s presence in critical national telecoms infrastructure, especially as they prepare for auctions for 5G, a superfast service that will enable a new generation of digital products and services. The US, Australia and New Zealand have moved to block the use of the Chinese company’s 5G equipment on secur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>British and German concerns mount over China's Huawei - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/29/british-german-concerns-mount-chinas-huawei/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB7rl_dDFg0auEmOHImLCLUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:57:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/29/british-german-concerns-mount-chinas-huawei/" target="_blank"&gt;British and German concerns mount over China's Huawei&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain's cyber-security agency has warned that it still has “technical concerns” over Huawei following growing US calls for its allies to block the controversial Chinese telecoms giant from rolling out its network technology, amid espionage fears. The National Cyber Security Centre, the UK’s cyber defence agency and part of GCHQ, responded after New Zealand became the latest country to block Huawei from bidding for its next generation 5G telecom network. An NCSC spokesman said it “has concerns around a range of technical issues and has set out improvements the company must make”. The UK ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Apple will wait until at least 2020 to release a 5G iPhone - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/03/apple-will-wait-least-2020-release-5g-iphone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA4VQPPcjFON2AfYdkPBXgEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:47:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/03/apple-will-wait-least-2020-release-5g-iphone/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple will wait until at least 2020 to release a 5G iPhone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple is said to be holding off releasing an iPhone which can connect to 5G until at least 2020, giving its rivals the chance to steal a lead on the tech giant for speedier service. According to Bloomberg, the next iPhone being released by Apple will not connect to 5G networks, and the company is expected to wait at least a year after the initial deployment of 5G technology. Rivals Huawei and Samsung are readying to launch their own 5G phones next year, offering customers data speeds up to 100 times faster than those available through current 4G networks. Earlier today, Samsung announced i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Huawei UK revenues and profits slide as security challenges pile up - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/02/huawei-uk-revenues-profits-slide-security-challenges-pile/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGIRTVaWFLGUsxouMJwCYwwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 13:06:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/02/huawei-uk-revenues-profits-slide-security-challenges-pile/" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei UK revenues and profits slide as security challenges pile up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese telecoms company Huawei has suffered slipping revenues in the UK as security concerns mount for the tech giant ahead of global deployment of faster mobile network technology. Huawei's UK revenues fell 14pc, down from £908m to £781m for the year ending in December 2017. Profits also slipped, down 9.6pc to £36.6m. Huawei blamed a "challenging and competitive" environment. "The UK telecommunication market had experienced downturns in the past year, in which operators substantially reduced their capital spending on new equipment," Huawei said in its accounts. Global telecoms providers h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>President Trump's National Spectrum Framework Is Smart Policy - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/fredcampbell/2018/11/29/president-trumps-national-spectrum-framework-is-smart-policy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIWanUWX2EzlvIA1C-9gNgwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 20:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/fredcampbell/2018/11/29/president-trumps-national-spectrum-framework-is-smart-policy/" target="_blank"&gt;President Trump's National Spectrum Framework Is Smart Policy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fifth generation of wireless technology, or “5G,” offers new possibilities in transportation, health care, manufacturing, and mobile entertainment. The revolutionary potential of this technology is limited only by the ability of the federal government to allocate enough spectrum to support robust 5G networks. Allocating spectrum for new uses is a complex task that’s becoming even more difficult as the demand for additional frequencies expands. President Donald Trump’s framework for developing a national spectrum strategy presents a new approach to coordinating federal and non-federal wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What To Expect From Nokia In 2019 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/12/04/what-to-expect-from-nokia-in-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOc3ou8wNioukRxsXsh8JI4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 16:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/12/04/what-to-expect-from-nokia-in-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;What To Expect From Nokia In 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attendees try out Nokia phones on display at a launch event for the Nokia X6 smartphone, produced by HMD Global Oy, in Beijing, China, on Wednesday, May 16, 2018. Photographer: Giulia Marchi/Bloomberg Nokia, one of the largest mobile network equipment providers, has had a mixed 2018. While revenues declined modestly over the first nine months of the year, the company has been benefiting from traction in its technology licensing business, a gradually stabilizing network equipment market and solid cost reductions. Nokia’s stock price has risen by close to 20% year-to-date to levels of around ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Watch man and robot merge Avatar-style thanks to 5G - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90274703/watch-man-and-robot-merge-avatar-style-thanks-to-5g</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGqGFL44BBRebB3gSIDp8-EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 06:38:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90274703/watch-man-and-robot-merge-avatar-style-thanks-to-5g" target="_blank"&gt;Watch man and robot merge Avatar-style thanks to 5G&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The future is getting closer every day, and it’s starting to look like James Cameron’s Avatar (okay, without the 10-foot blue aliens). Toyota has revealed that it has successfully linked an off-site human with its T-HR31 humanoid robot thanks to 5G wireless technology from Japanese telecom NTT Docomo. What’s especially amazing about this is that the human controlling the robot was 10 kilometers (6.2 miles) away. The T-HR31 humanoid robot works by having a human host strapped into a control harness with hand, arm, and foot controls. As the human controller moves her body, the T-HR31 humanoid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>The Coming U.S.-China Showdown On The Future of Wireless - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/arthurherman/2018/11/28/the-coming-u-s-china-showdown-on-the-future-of-wireless/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN58Lmoj6QFTQ6AxpIezEE4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/arthurherman/2018/11/28/the-coming-u-s-china-showdown-on-the-future-of-wireless/" target="_blank"&gt;The Coming U.S.-China Showdown On The Future of Wireless&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alphabet, Cloud Computing, Computer, Computer Monitor, Computer Network An epic battle is brewing over the future of wireless technology, and the future of 5G technology. On one side is China, which is stopping at nothing to make sure it dominates global telecommunications in the 21st century, by any means fair or foul. On the other is the United States, which is beginning to wake up to the fact that losing the 5G future to China will be a major catastrophe, not only for the U.S. but for freedom and democracy around the globe. On November 13 the Hudson Institute hosted an event describing h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>iPhones Could Get Hit By Tariffs...And Other Small Business Tech News This Week - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/quickerbettertech/2018/12/02/iphones-could-get-hit-by-tariffs-and-other-small-business-tech-news-this-week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAOoAn4wuqHf-_GqsInLLlkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/quickerbettertech/2018/12/02/iphones-could-get-hit-by-tariffs-and-other-small-business-tech-news-this-week/" target="_blank"&gt;iPhones Could Get Hit By Tariffs...And Other Small Business Tech News This Week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are five things in technology that happened this past week and how they affect your business. Did you miss them? 1 — Apple falls after Trump suggests iPhones could get hit by tariffs. After President Trump suggested that 10% tariffs could be placed on mobile phones and laptops made in China, Apple Inc. shares lost about a fifth of their value. Earlier in the same week, Apple briefly moved to Number 2 as the world’s most valuable publicly traded company when overtaken by Microsoft Corp. (Source: Bloomberg) Why this is important for your business: Don’t worry, Apple will be fine. But th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Len Blavatnik’s Norwegian telecoms group Ice set to float - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9b4e961e-eda7-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJB7HyN_WOeIWsLL6LP1NhsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 04:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9b4e961e-eda7-11e8-8180-9cf212677a57" target="_blank"&gt;Len Blavatnik’s Norwegian telecoms group Ice set to float&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Norwegian telecoms company owned by billionaire Len Blavatnik’s Access Industries believes it can buck the negative sentiment in European telecoms with a successful float of the business by the end of the year. Ice Group, Norway’s third-largest telecoms company, plans to raise NKr3bn (£275m) by floating the company in Oslo. It intends to expand its 4G network to 95 per cent of Norway and prepare for the launch of 5G services. It would be the first initial public offering in European telecoms since Play Communications in Poland in 2017 and DNA in Finland in 2016. Other substantial planne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Huawei under fire as politicians fret over 5G security - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8bb75604-f4a6-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIr7qLsAM9QSAHOXYJg8XM4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 09:04:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8bb75604-f4a6-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei under fire as politicians fret over 5G security&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For nearly 15 years, the Chinese group Huawei has seen the UK as a key market and a springboard to the other deals that helped it become the world’s largest telecoms equipment maker. Huawei’s partnerships with the likes of BT and Vodafone have weathered bouts of unease over its rumoured links to the Chinese government and the People’s Liberation Army, which the company denies. But as politicians from the UK and other countries start to consider the rollout of their 5G communications network, Huawei is suddenly facing a grave threat to its international business. In recent weeks, US official...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>5G IP leadership -- It's Too Early To Determine - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/01/5g-ip-leadership-its-too-early-to-determine/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDJ3VF7oyJ4onHI850GIyoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 07:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2018/12/01/5g-ip-leadership-its-too-early-to-determine/" target="_blank"&gt;5G IP leadership -- It's Too Early To Determine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;5G represents the 5th generation of cellular communications technology as defined by 3GPP Release 15 The patent sharing model of the cellular wireless industry has always made Intellectual Property (IP) licensing the driving force behind each new generation of cellular technology. This model has been critical to incentivizing innovators to make rather risky investments in future technology and for funding the development of each new standard. The 5th generation of the wireless standard, known as 5G, extends the model even further by connecting everything through a wireless interface in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Technology Predictions For 2019: 5G, Edge Computing, Hybrid Cloud, SDDC And More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/11/27/technology-predictions-for-2019-5g-edge-computing-hybrid-cloud-sddc-and-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEErH4AMdksyqv9nJVRnrBWoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/11/27/technology-predictions-for-2019-5g-edge-computing-hybrid-cloud-sddc-and-more/" target="_blank"&gt;Technology Predictions For 2019: 5G, Edge Computing, Hybrid Cloud, SDDC And More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty As cloud technology continued to be adopted throughout the industry in 2018, we started to see the early stages of serverless computing and initial 5G discussions. There’s also an ongoing revolution of analytics, network virtualization and user experience digitization. This is the time of year to look into 2019 and consider what impact the latest technology will have in a few short months. IT: Organizations Will Have To Master Their Hybrid Cloud Strategies While some expect that Kubernetes and Docker will eventually become part of the daily practice in IT, our existing networks and to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Huawei seeks clarification after New Zealand intelligence agency rejects 5G bid - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spark-nz-huawei-tech/huawei-seeks-clarification-after-new-zealand-intelligence-agency-rejects-5g-bid-idUSKCN1NY09X</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF5QcXSpihJDiAqXwLp7xDwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 05:13:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spark-nz-huawei-tech/huawei-seeks-clarification-after-new-zealand-intelligence-agency-rejects-5g-bid-idUSKCN1NY09X" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei seeks clarification after New Zealand intelligence agency rejects 5G bid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei Technologies Co Ltd said it was seeking clarification from New Zealand after the country's intelligence agency rejected the telecommunication industry's first request to use the Chinese firm's equipment in its planned 5G mobile network. Huawei said it had not had formal contact with the Government Communication Security Bureau (GCSB), which has cited national security concerns in declining a proposal from telecoms operator Spark New Zealand to build its 5G network using Huawei equipment. "Huawei is seeking an urgent meeting with the relevant ministers and officials to understand the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Zealand blocks 5G bid by China's Huawei due to spy fears - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/28/new-zealand-blocks-5g-bid-chinas-huawei-due-spy-fears/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHKN4R4cssjYACXUsDQZxqgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 11:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/28/new-zealand-blocks-5g-bid-chinas-huawei-due-spy-fears/" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand blocks 5G bid by China's Huawei due to spy fears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand has blocked telecoms firm Huawei from supplying components for its 5G phone network amid growing concerns of Chinese espionage. Spark Telecom, which plans to build the new network, was warned by New Zealand's Government Security Bureau to avoid the Chinese firm's hardware or face "significant national security risks". Huawei is one of the world's biggest manufacturers of telecom equipment, including the network kit required for 5G mobile networks, which promise faster download speeds and better connections. The company said in a statement that it will "actively address any conce...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Nokia reshuffles management with focus on 5G market - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-5g/nokia-reshuffles-management-with-focus-on-5g-market-idUSKCN1NR0M3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDUiMTZDmI9QMZlrg7UxWooqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 09:20:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-5g/nokia-reshuffles-management-with-focus-on-5g-market-idUSKCN1NR0M3" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia reshuffles management with focus on 5G market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The head of Nokia's (NOKIA.HE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) mobile networks arm, its largest business unit, is leaving the Finnish company as part of changes designed to position the company for the 5G telecoms era, Nokia said on Thursday. Marc Rouanne, Nokia's head of mobile networks will be replaced by Tommi Uitto, a Finn described by the company as an "expert in radio technologies". Frenchman Rouanne is the second senior executive to leave Nokia within the past few weeks after the head of its patent business, Ilkka Rahnasto, resigned at the beginning of last month. Nokia plans t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Oracle BrandVoice: Communications Providers Offer Lesson In How To Embrace Digital Disruption - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/oracle/2018/11/30/communications-providers-offer-lesson-in-how-to-embrace-digital-disruption/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENa5BX5mharIHvRKwO2BP2cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/oracle/2018/11/30/communications-providers-offer-lesson-in-how-to-embrace-digital-disruption/" target="_blank"&gt;Oracle BrandVoice: Communications Providers Offer Lesson In How To Embrace Digital Disruption&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Elmar Rode What do you do when your main revenue sources start to become commoditized? Ask a telco. Communications service providers have watched their business model change over the years as digital interlopers turned consistent revenue streams, such as voice and messaging, into essentially free services. [id=0] For CSPs, the past decade has been one full of hard lessons. First, consumer and business customers not only demand, but often times dictate, innovation. Second, a positive customer experience is paramount in this digital world. Here, CSPs still have some work to do to overcome ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>AT&amp;T CFO cautions on how quickly 5G revenue will come - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tmt-conference-at-t/att-cfo-cautions-on-how-quickly-5g-revenue-will-come-idUSKCN1NJ18F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELpgzUqo224pYWSSlhJ94jMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 09:58:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tmt-conference-at-t/att-cfo-cautions-on-how-quickly-5g-revenue-will-come-idUSKCN1NJ18F" target="_blank"&gt;AT&amp;T CFO cautions on how quickly 5G revenue will come&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT&amp;T is upbeat on long-term revenue prospects for 5G services but expects it to take years before 5G-enabled devices predominate, CFO John Stephens said on Wednesday. AT&amp;T, the second-largest U.S. wireless carrier, has developed some use cases for the next-generation mobile technology, such as connected factories, but does not expect 5G-enabled handsets to hit the market until late 2019 or 2020. "It's an exciting spot. We're ready. But I'm not here to make any predictions on revenue opportunities in '19," Stephens told the Morgan Stanley TMT Conference in Barcelona. Stephens said only aroun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Zealand prevents mobile carrier from buying Huawei 5G tech over security fears - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/tech/huawei-spark-nz/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJSM4UosY8ayiTI7Quv9VW8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 09:06:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/tech/huawei-spark-nz/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand prevents mobile carrier from buying Huawei 5G tech over security fears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand blocked its top telecom firm from using Huawei equipment for its 5G mobile network, dealing another blow to the Chinese tech company's ambitions to become a leader in the next generation wireless technology. Spark, the country's largest telecommunications company, said government officials told the company Wednesday that using Huawei's 5G equipment "would, if implemented, raise significant national security risks." New Zealand's spy agency, the Government Communications Security Bureau (GCSB), confirmed the assessment in a statement to CNN. "I have informed Spark that a signific...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Zealand Halts Huawei from 5G Upgrade Over Security Fears - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/new-zealand-halts-huawei-from-5g-upgrade-over-security-fears/4679242.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKhZ7ZyFjtAQ-1vi1mZoVz4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 02:54:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/new-zealand-halts-huawei-from-5g-upgrade-over-security-fears/4679242.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand Halts Huawei from 5G Upgrade Over Security Fears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand's international spy agency on Wednesday halted mobile company Spark from using Huawei equipment in its planned 5G upgrade, saying it posed a "significant network security risk.'' The action follows a ban in Australia, where the Chinese telecommunications giant was blocked in August from rolling out Australia's 5G network due to security concerns. In New Zealand, Huawei has previously helped build mobile networks. In March, Spark and Huawei showcased a 5G test site across the street from the Parliament, in a publicity move that was attended by then Broadcasting Minister Clare Cur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>T-Mobile says Sprint deal may close as early as first-quarter next year - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sprint-corp-m-a-t-mobile-us-idUSKCN1NL0Z9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEClndc5bKCoQj07U0o359LgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:32:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sprint-corp-m-a-t-mobile-us-idUSKCN1NL0Z9" target="_blank"&gt;T-Mobile says Sprint deal may close as early as first-quarter next year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;T-Mobile US Inc's TMUS.N Chief Financial Officer said there is a possibility that its $26 billion acquisition deal of Sprint Corp (S.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) will close as early as the first quarter of 2019. T-Mobile, majority owned by Deutsche Telekom AG (DTEGn.DE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), agreed in April to buy wireless carrier Sprint and the deal was initially expected to close in the first half of 2019. The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) and the Department of Justice are currently scrutinizing the deal. "The only remaining thing that is happening i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Zealand blocks Huawei 5G bid on national security concerns - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/7387411a-f2bd-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAEVSMj8-hS6ySvK6Z6f7f0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 07:25:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/7387411a-f2bd-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand blocks Huawei 5G bid on national security concerns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand has blocked one of its biggest telecoms operators from using 5G telecoms equipment from Huawei because of national security concerns, in the latest sign of growing unease over the company’s alleged links to the Chinese government. The decision is a blow to the world’s biggest telecoms equipment maker, which is a leader in the next generation of mobile technology but has already been blocked from supplying such equipment in Australia and the US on similar grounds. Spark New Zealand’s proposal to use Huawei’s 5G technology was denied after the country’s intelligence agency said i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>How Photorealistic VR And 5G May Change The Future Of Media - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescommunicationscouncil/2018/11/20/how-photorealistic-vr-and-5g-may-change-the-future-of-media/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB-99_N0CfbWe72Wm_cC3nEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbescommunicationscouncil/2018/11/20/how-photorealistic-vr-and-5g-may-change-the-future-of-media/" target="_blank"&gt;How Photorealistic VR And 5G May Change The Future Of Media&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty I witnessed an impressive 5G-based artificial reality/virtual reality (AR/VR) demo at this year’s Qualcomm 4G/5G Summit in Hong Kong. Indeed, AR and VR together, referred to as extended reality (XR), is possible today, and 5G’s higher speeds, greater capacity and lower latency will naturally improve the experience. But this demo, referred to as “boundless XR,” clearly showed how transformational 5G could be and gave further credence to the “wireless edge” concept that I discussed in my previous article. (Full disclosure: Qualcomm is a client of my company, Tantra Analyst.) Today’s XR,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>UK and Germany grow wary of Huawei as US turns up pressure - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/6719b6b2-f33d-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOHMbzSyiGjwxzG_F3Q4lvAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 19:15:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6719b6b2-f33d-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;UK and Germany grow wary of Huawei as US turns up pressure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK and Germany are growing wary of allowing Huawei, the Chinese telecoms company, to install 5G equipment in their countries after a US delegation visited Europe to urge heightened vigilance against national security threats. UK security officials on Thursday issued a new public warning to Huawei, saying the Chinese company must fix problems in the equipment it provides to British networks or risk a further deterioration in what is an increasingly strained relationship. The clear message delivered by the US delegation this month and in online communications is that Germany and the UK as...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>US reportedly urges allies to block use of Huawei equipment - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/tech/huawei-us-government/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDo2u1O0QlhiB347bhGktXgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 23:56:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/tech/huawei-us-government/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;US reportedly urges allies to block use of Huawei equipment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States is urging its allies to stop using Huawei telecommunications equipment because the Chinesecompany poses a securitythreat, according to a published report. The Wall Street Journal, citing sources familiar with the discussions, reports that US officials are pushing countries that host American military bases to ban the use of Huawei equipment from their wireless and internet networks. The US military uses secure networks for its most sensitive communications, but it is concerned that much of its traffic still moves over commercial networks in countries such as Germany, Italy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>German regulator sets ball rolling for 5G auctions - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-telecoms-idUSKCN1NV1KJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO8omqhnHOVYl4ad6S_lxv8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 14:14:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-telecoms-idUSKCN1NV1KJ" target="_blank"&gt;German regulator sets ball rolling for 5G auctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Germany's network regulator set the ball rolling on Monday to auction fifth-generation mobile licenses, winning a nod from lawmakers after months of controversy over whether the plan would help to close a connectivity deficit with the country's rivals. The BNetzA agency said it was immediately opening applications for the 5G spectrum, setting a deadline of Jan. 25 for submissions and saying the auction would begin in early 2019. The process of determining the ground rules for 5G services that could power connected factories and wireless broadband has been fraught, reflecting concerns that E...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>FCC launches first U.S. high-band 5G spectrum auction - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-wireless-spectrum-idUSKCN1NJ2ZF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELZ4bux5QiHCI22aoroRyWwqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 21:17:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-wireless-spectrum-idUSKCN1NJ2ZF" target="_blank"&gt;FCC launches first U.S. high-band 5G spectrum auction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Federal Communications Commission on Wednesday launched the agency's first high-band 5G spectrum auction as it works to clear space for next-generation faster networks. Bidding is beginning on Wednesday on spectrum in the 28 GHz band and will be followed by bidding for spectrum in the 24 GHz band. The FCC is making 1.55 gigahertz of spectrum available and the auctions will be followed by a 2019 auction of three more millimeter-wave spectrum bands — 37 GHz, 39 GHz, and 47 GHz. "These airwaves will be critical in deploying 5G services and applications," FCC Chairman Ajit Pai said on Wedne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>O2 Partners With Nokia To Launch Massive MiMo Pilot To Boost UK 5G - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/annatobin/2018/11/25/o2-partners-with-nokia-to-launch-massive-mimo-pilot-to-boost-uk-5g/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECxjjzMgxWh-of7CgQCq5bUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 19:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/annatobin/2018/11/25/o2-partners-with-nokia-to-launch-massive-mimo-pilot-to-boost-uk-5g/" target="_blank"&gt;O2 Partners With Nokia To Launch Massive MiMo Pilot To Boost UK 5G&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Krisztian Bocsi/Bloomberg © 2015 Bloomberg Finance Telefonica-owned UK mobile operator O2 is partnering with Finnish telco Nokia to create two Massive multiple-input, multiple-output, or Massive MiMo, as it’s known, trials in central London . The trials, taking place in Kings Cross and Marble Arch, are designed to improve connectivity for O2′s mobile customers and lay the groundwork for the deployment of fifth generation mobile, or 5G. The Nokia developed Massive MIMO technology will transmit multiple beams of data from one antenna to multiple devices, and in doing so hopefull...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>BMW, Vodafone, Ericsson urge EU to consider 5G car standard - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eu-autos-technology/bmw-vodafone-ericsson-urge-eu-to-consider-5g-car-standard-idUSKCN1NJ2MT?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=businessNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOCLR_44SbGLG300xiF8EcwqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 18:17:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eu-autos-technology/bmw-vodafone-ericsson-urge-eu-to-consider-5g-car-standard-idUSKCN1NJ2MT?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=businessNews" target="_blank"&gt;BMW, Vodafone, Ericsson urge EU to consider 5G car standard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BMW, Vodafone and Ericsson made a last-ditch effort on Wednesday to persuade the European Commission to open the way for the use of 5G technology in cars, concerned about the EU executive's preference for a wifi-based technology being pursued by their rivals. The companies said it was crucial for the industry to have the freedom to adopt a range of technologies for internet-connected cars in a sector estimated to be worth billions of euros a year. "It's concerning that just two years later the principle of technological neutrality appears to be no longer adhered to by the European Commissio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>U.S. asks allies to shun Huawei equipment, WSJ reports; sector stocks fall - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei/u-s-asks-allies-to-shun-huawei-equipment-wsj-reports-sector-stocks-fall-idUSKCN1NR2E6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMZa9Oz-YGcfP2MB4dkWWc4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:57:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-huawei/u-s-asks-allies-to-shun-huawei-equipment-wsj-reports-sector-stocks-fall-idUSKCN1NR2E6" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. asks allies to shun Huawei equipment, WSJ reports; sector stocks fall&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. government is trying to persuade wireless and internet providers in allied countries to avoid telecommunications equipment from China's Huawei Technologies [HWT.UL], the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday. The move would further pile pressure on the world's biggest telecom gear maker, which is under scrutiny from Western intelligence agencies for its perceived ties to China's government and the possibility its equipment could be used for espionage. U.S. officials have reached out to their government counterparts and telecom executives in friendly countries where Huawei equipm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S10 will have six cameras and 5G support, latest rumours hint - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s10-cameras-5g-latest-features-rumours-a8644691.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFYRUhvi19p0FJpH75h6nh8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s10-cameras-5g-latest-features-rumours-a8644691.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S10 will have six cameras and 5G support, latest rumours hint&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next flagship Samsung, presumably called the Galaxy S10, will feature twice as many cameras as Apple's latest iPhone, according to reports. Set to launch on the 10th anniversary of its first flagship smartphone, the Galaxy S10 will pack four cameras on the rear of the device and two on the front, according to The Wall Street Journal. The Galaxy S10 will also reportedly feature a 6.7-inch screen and will come with 5G support, though this may only be available in South Korea and the US. Its expected release date is February 2019. The latest rumours come just a month after Samsung unveiled...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>New OnePlus 7 Details Reveal OnePlus' Big Gamble - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/18/oneplus-7-oneplus-5g-qualcomm-tmobile-leak-new-rumor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM3pTVn71DO-7mAkl1SI_jAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 20:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/18/oneplus-7-oneplus-5g-qualcomm-tmobile-leak-new-rumor/" target="_blank"&gt;New OnePlus 7 Details Reveal OnePlus' Big Gamble&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As OnePlus builds on the successful launch of the OnePlus 6T and prepares for 2019, should we expect to see a second super-fast handset alongside the OnePlus 7? What could be happening? Let’s apply a dash of Taniyama–Shimura… OnePlus 6T (image: Ewan Spence) First up is the specific hardware. At this year’s Mobile World Congress Shanghai, OnePlus CEO Pete Lau noted that the Shenzhen-based manufacturer is aiming to launch a 5G handset in 2019. He also confirmed that the relationship with Qualcomm would be the basis of the 5G circuitry. Sasch Segan for PC Mag: The announcements came as part of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>