<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Apple Watch - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV4YzIxaU5ESVNBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:32:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Apple Watch heart features finally arrive, allowing people to take ECGs on their wrist - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/apple-watch-series-4-heart-features-release-ecg-wrist-a8673061.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGMIqyDedGr2ID-ZFedgrzsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/apple-watch-series-4-heart-features-release-ecg-wrist-a8673061.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Watch heart features finally arrive, allowing people to take ECGs on their wrist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Apple Watch's long promised heart features have finally arrived on people's watches. When the Series 4 was announced in September, the company said that it would let people take ECGs and see if their heartbeat is irregular. But it would not be available straight away because it had to be approved by regulators, it said at the time. Now the features have been given clearance by the US Food and Drug Administration and so will finally be available, arriving through a software update. The ECG and atrial fibrillation features are not yet available outside the US, including in the UK. A numbe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Apple Watch Series 4 ECG Heart Rate Feature Now Live: Here's All You Need To Know - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/06/apple-watch-series-4-ecg-heart-rate-feature-now-live-heres-all-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAlRVOTHtRoY0CHY8C7bdzMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/06/apple-watch-series-4-ecg-heart-rate-feature-now-live-heres-all-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Watch Series 4 ECG Heart Rate Feature Now Live: Here's All You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Apple launched the latest Apple Watch Series 4 on September 12, one of the most exciting features is the capability to take ECG (electrocardiogram, also known as EKG) readings from your wrist. Apple Watch Series 4 now boasts the ECG feature But it had only just been cleared by the FDA, so the software needed more work before it could go live. The company said that it would happen this year but no date was given. It was the subject of much debate. It’s just gone live. It is currently limited to Apple Watches that have been bought and are being used in the U.S., and further locations wil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Dr. Sanjay Gupta tests the Apple Watch's new ECG heart monitor - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/health/apple-watch-ecg-app-review/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJTbWVIx4IPkdeGn1nlhA5UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:12:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/health/apple-watch-ecg-app-review/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Sanjay Gupta tests the Apple Watch's new ECG heart monitor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the Apple Watch Series 4 was announced in September, one of its most anticipated functions has been the promise to perform a mobile electrocardiogram (ECG or EKG) whenever a consumer wants. The feature becomes available in the United States on Thursday via a software update. This new ECG app represents a big venture into health for Apple. The company's ambition is for Apple and health to become as closely linked as Apple and music. It even produced a commercial featuring people who say the Apple Watch has helped them lead healthier lives. Apple says its new ECG application and the abi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Here's how the Apple Watch's heart monitor works - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/05/apple-watch-ecg-app-health-review.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENgBvHpaTyOqY49JFQXWsbMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:37:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/05/apple-watch-ecg-app-health-review.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;Here's how the Apple Watch's heart monitor works&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN's Dr. Sanjay Gupta explains how to use Apple Watch's built-in ECG monitor. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Snip, snip: Morgan Stanley latest to cut Apple target on China woes - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cc64bbcc-fa2f-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHvfyuM0NnrZQOunEFYOEcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:20:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cc64bbcc-fa2f-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Snip, snip: Morgan Stanley latest to cut Apple target on China woes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Apple price cut club welcomed a new member on Friday after Morgan Stanley blamed the Chinese smartphone market for weakening the outlook for iPhone sales. Flattening iPhone sales have stoked concerns on Wall Street that consumer demand has peaked for Apple’s most important device. In September, the tech giant offered a weaker than expected forecast for the holiday quarter and said it would no longer offer a quarterly breakdown of sales for each of its devices. Meanwhile, key iPhone suppliers have lowered financial guidance, and the Wall Street Journal reported last month that Apple redu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>AirPods 2: New Patent Reveals Noise-Canceling, Biometrics And Profound Design Change - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/05/airpods-2-new-patent-reveals-noise-canceling-biometrics-and-profound-design-change/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8eej5jAIDN0lFR3Ri5qi4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/05/airpods-2-new-patent-reveals-noise-canceling-biometrics-and-profound-design-change/" target="_blank"&gt;AirPods 2: New Patent Reveals Noise-Canceling, Biometrics And Profound Design Change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple AirPods 2 are not yet with us, though they may be coming early next year. The current AirPods are “Apple’s most popular accessory ever”, according to reliable analyst Ming-Chi Kuo. Apple’s opening video at its recent keynote features AirPods. There have already been hints that new features, such as hands-free “Hey, Siri” will be coming very soon. And now, it’s come to light that a patent that has just been granted, which has been spotted by 9to5Mac. It refers to “Earbuds with compliant member” and deals with “earbuds configured with one or more biometric sensors”. A compliant member, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>China's Xiaomi takes lead over Apple as top seller of wearable technology globally - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/04/chinas-xiaomi-takes-lead-apple-top-seller-wearable-technology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPbjZfrDpoAf3KsArbOjGUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:46:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/04/chinas-xiaomi-takes-lead-apple-top-seller-wearable-technology/" target="_blank"&gt;China's Xiaomi takes lead over Apple as top seller of wearable technology globally&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese smartphone specialist Xiaomi has taken a lead over Apple as the world’s largest manufacturer of wearables, according to new figures from an industry analyst. A report from the International Data Corporation found that Xiaomi took top position in the third quarter of 2018 following positive sales of its Mi Band 3, a fitness tracker. Xiaomi’s push into markets such as India, Europe and the Middle East has been attributed to its overtaking of Apple. The share of the company’s deliveries within its home market has dropped from 80pc to 61pc as its international expansion plans pick up pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Apple patents interchangeable AirPods with health tracking features - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/05/apple-patents-interchangeable-airpods-health-tracking-features/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9eSCEj2JA9ZwnbKrRBPbIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:11:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/05/apple-patents-interchangeable-airpods-health-tracking-features/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple patents interchangeable AirPods with health tracking features&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple is working on interchangeable AirPod headphones that come with health tracking features to measure heart rate and stress levels. That's according to a new patent filed by the firm which reveals how a new version of its wireless in-ear headphones would be able to fit in either ear. The filing shows the device slipping into the ear canal and being held in place with a bendable band. Apple's current wireless AirPods were first launched in 2016, although some users have complained they can easily fall out or become uncomfortable. Apple removed the headphone jack from its iPhone models fro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Apple iPhone Sales Off To A Slow Start This Holiday Season - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyswan/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-sales-off-to-a-slow-start-this-holiday-season/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECX_QcHVflT5gTr9TGOgd2MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyswan/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-sales-off-to-a-slow-start-this-holiday-season/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple iPhone Sales Off To A Slow Start This Holiday Season&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The iPhone XS, left, and XS Max are displayed side to side during an event to announce new products at Apple headquarters Wednesday, Sept. 12, 2018, in Cupertino, Calif. (AP Photo/Marcio Jose Sanchez) photo credit: ASSOCIATED PRESS The day after the keynote address, Consumer Purchase Intent Data was already telling us that Apple was going to have a very rough road ahead of it. Since then, the stock has fallen big. More importantly, the holiday shopping season has begun. This gives us fresh consumer insights to tap into from the first week of the season. 2018 Holiday Slowdown? Black Friday...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How Incentives -- And a Free Apple Watch -- Make People Healthier - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tobyshapshak/2018/11/29/how-incentives-and-a-free-apple-watch-make-people-healthier/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGJij0BBKdNNm7m2yDuoSRAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tobyshapshak/2018/11/29/how-incentives-and-a-free-apple-watch-make-people-healthier/" target="_blank"&gt;How Incentives -- And a Free Apple Watch -- Make People Healthier&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vitaly Apple Watch offer. When Discovery Health began offering Apple Watches as part of its Vitality wellness program it gave South Africa’s largest medical insurer the opportunity to prove one of its fundamental tenants: people will be healthier if they have an incentive. Or at least exercise more. Discovery announced that a two-year study of 400,000 people using an Apple Watch in conjunction with its Vitality Active Rewards program that offers incentives for meeting exercise goals delivered “dramatic and sustained improvements in physical activity levels”. These were on average 34% mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>AirPods 2 New Rumor: Coming Early 2019, All-New Design In 2020 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/02/airpods-2-new-rumor-coming-early-2019-all-new-design-in-2020/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFIR2KUViO3toKB5Tr-NfuMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/02/airpods-2-new-rumor-coming-early-2019-all-new-design-in-2020/" target="_blank"&gt;AirPods 2 New Rumor: Coming Early 2019, All-New Design In 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple’s AirPods and an updated version which may be called AirPods 2, are the subject of a research note from top analyst Ming-Chi Kuo, just revealed. Apple AirPods… are the updated earbuds almost here? In it, Kuo says that the latest version of something he calls “Apple’s most popular accessory ever” will not be with us in time for Christmas. Still, previously hinted improvements such as hands-free “Hey, Siri” may not be off the table, let’s hope. In the research note, seen by 9to5Mac and also by MacRumors, there are indications of how the new AirPods will differ from the current model and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Essential Travel Tech For An Active Getaway - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/leebelltech/2018/11/29/the-essential-travel-tech-for-an-active-getaway/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAQSc68KtN331IZTqET7TF8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 16:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/leebelltech/2018/11/29/the-essential-travel-tech-for-an-active-getaway/" target="_blank"&gt;The Essential Travel Tech For An Active Getaway&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that the cold winter months are upon us, and it’s still dark outside when the morning alarm goes off, it’s hard not to dream of those summer months. It’s hardly surprising, then, that it’s becoming increasingly popular to pack up and escape the cold of the west in favour of much more exotic climes when the going gets nippy. But while it’s now the perfect time of the year to drop everything and travel as far as you can from any sign of civilisation, it doesn’t mean to say you won’t be taking any essential bits of tech away with you. Well, this is what I discovered when I found myself in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Cyber Monday 2018 Best Apple Watch, Samsung Galaxy Watch, Fitbit Versa Deals. Update: B&amp;H Bargains - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/25/cyber-monday-2018-hottest-apple-watch-samsung-galaxy-watch-fitbit-versa-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKFOjOrZzaxfQzZUluLpt8wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 23:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/25/cyber-monday-2018-hottest-apple-watch-samsung-galaxy-watch-fitbit-versa-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyber Monday 2018 Best Apple Watch, Samsung Galaxy Watch, Fitbit Versa Deals. Update: B&amp;H Bargains&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Apple Watch and Fitbit gadgets are the most desirable wearable tech around. So, Cyber Monday, and Black Friday before it, are the time to try and snag a bargain with one of them. Apple Watch models which attract gift cards at the company’s four-day shopping event. I’ve been rounding up offers over the last few days but here, as a useful, I hope, guide to what to buy, are all the best bargains. Update: B&amp;H Video has now announced a series of deals which are very tempting. See below. The deals highlighted in this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. I’ve al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Watch study could have benefits for preventive medicine - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/6b658e6a-f15f-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOBFhior4B716VEm5yghUfUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 00:39:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/6b658e6a-f15f-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Watch study could have benefits for preventive medicine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A global study conducted for a large insurance company with tech giant Apple has concluded that people are prepared to dramatically increase their exercise levels if they are offered tangible rewards. The insight, gleaned from data generated from 400,000 people, has implications for public policy at a time when cash-strapped health systems are struggling to curb demand for healthcare. Adrian Gore, founder of Vitality Insurance, which commissioned the survey, suggested the findings also made the case for financial services companies adjusting their business models to incentivise clients. “Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Black Friday Extended: Must-See Apple Watch Deal Before Cyber Monday 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/24/black-friday-extended-must-see-apple-watch-deal-before-cyber-monday-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELG6TfS-z_Epi5r9SP-3GA0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 19:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/24/black-friday-extended-must-see-apple-watch-deal-before-cyber-monday-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Friday Extended: Must-See Apple Watch Deal Before Cyber Monday 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple Watch Series 3 (GPS) 38mm Aluminum Case Today, the Apple Watch is $80 off its original price at Target. The deal is for all Apple Watch models that the store carries, including those with and without cellular capabilities. The deal also applies to 38 and 42 mm watches in the multiple varieties of colors offered. These sales won’t last long– Target says the sale ends today, so snap up the perfect watch to gift (or self-gift) for every health fanatic and workout junkie. Shop Now&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Yoga and Wearables: The Role Of Technology In An Ancient Discipline - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/leebelltech/2018/11/29/yoga-and-wearables-the-role-of-technology-in-an-ancient-discipline/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEUi2wfcr_iFe0qWsaZcH1UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/leebelltech/2018/11/29/yoga-and-wearables-the-role-of-technology-in-an-ancient-discipline/" target="_blank"&gt;Yoga and Wearables: The Role Of Technology In An Ancient Discipline&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Apple launched the fourth edition of its highly-anticipated Watch wearable in September, a new update was the ability to track a yoga workout within its native fitness-recording app. While yoga has been around for literally thousands of years, it’s only fairly recently that the practice has become ubiquitous among the masses. You’d have to be a real hermit to have never heard of yoga, whether you’re into health and wellness, or not. So considering how popular yoga is these days, it’s quite surprising that it took Apple three years to add it as a dedicated, trackable option on what has ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best Apple 'Cyber Monday' 2018 iPad, iPhone, MacBook Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/25/best-apple-cyber-monday-2018-ipad-iphone-macbook-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGVGYCXaKiisP0xkij1II90qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 01:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/25/best-apple-cyber-monday-2018-ipad-iphone-macbook-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Apple 'Cyber Monday' 2018 iPad, iPhone, MacBook Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. Do you want a new iPhone, iPad, MacBook or Apple Watch? Cyber Monday 2018 is the biggest sale left for Apple products before Christmas. There are some great savings available (tip: ignore Apple’s rubbish deals), including extensions of some of the best Black Friday discounts, like the red-hot B&amp;H MacBook sale (ad scan link) and T-Mobile’s f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Black Friday 2018 Hottest Apple Watch Deals: Target, Best Buy, Macy's - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/22/black-friday-2018-hottest-apple-watch-deals-target-best-buy-macys-walmart/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhe0yrkC340fsZ_72c0WSgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/22/black-friday-2018-hottest-apple-watch-deals-target-best-buy-macys-walmart/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Friday 2018 Hottest Apple Watch Deals: Target, Best Buy, Macy's&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black Friday is upon us and going strong. Wearables are among the many good deals out there and here I’ve put together Black Friday 2018 wearable gadgets offers available from Best Buy, Walmart, Target and more. This post supersedes my earlier post on Apple Watch, and is your one-stop, updated shop for Black Friday wearable bargains from Apple. Apple Watch Series 4 with a Series 4-only Watch face. The deals highlighted in this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. If Fitbit smart trackers are of interest, check out my round-up of Black Friday Fitbit deals here...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Trump threatens a 25% tariff on the iPhone and Apple laptops - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90272668/trump-threatens-a-25-tariff-on-the-iphone-and-apple-laptops</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAE6J4nsvBscbnkyahag1WUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 19:05:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90272668/trump-threatens-a-25-tariff-on-the-iphone-and-apple-laptops" target="_blank"&gt;Trump threatens a 25% tariff on the iPhone and Apple laptops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever wondered why Apple’s Tim Cook has tried to remain on good terms with Donald Trump, it’s for times like these. Trump told the Wall Street Journal Monday that it’s possible the U.S. will apply new tariffs to Chinese-made consumer tech products like the iPhone. The new tariff could be either 10% or 25%, the president said. His comments come four days before he will meet Chinese leader Xi Jinping for trade talks. Trump had promised Cook that he would not place tariffs on Apple products, the New York Times reported in June, and Apple devices missed the first round of tariffs appli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Apple Black Friday 2018 UK Event Revealed: Big-Value Gift Cards With iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple Watch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/22/apple-black-friday-2018-uk-event-revealed-big-value-gift-cards-with-iphone-ipad-mac-apple-watch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMBHAHmWHwIE-FdzLlHr5u8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/22/apple-black-friday-2018-uk-event-revealed-big-value-gift-cards-with-iphone-ipad-mac-apple-watch/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Black Friday 2018 UK Event Revealed: Big-Value Gift Cards With iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Apple Shopping Event is this year a four-day affair, that’s three days more than usual. And while it’s often on Thanksgiving itself, this time it’ll run from Black Friday through Cyber Monday. It offers gift cards with some purchases, all at least the same value as last year’s event, sometimes more. Apple Watch Nike+ and its strap colours So, what’s available and should you buy? After all, my colleague Gordon Kelly has pointed out that Apple often limits its offers and looking elsewhere often yields better prices. Check out his rundown of it and alternative offers. So, here are all the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>iPhone X could come back after weak sales of new Apple phones, report claims - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/iphone-x-apple-xs-max-xr-buy-latest-store-oled-display-screen-a8647256.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP3QSZ-M1cSv8tWr8T1g8Z4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/iphone-x-apple-xs-max-xr-buy-latest-store-oled-display-screen-a8647256.html" target="_blank"&gt;iPhone X could come back after weak sales of new Apple phones, report claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple could be bringing back the iPhone X after the updates have failed to sell in high enough numbers, according to a new report. The iPhone X was killed off when the iPhone XS, XS Max and XR arrived in September this year. It is no longer available to buy through Apple stores and has been entirely replaced. But Apple is looking to resume production after those new phones didn't sell in the numbers expected, according to the Wall Street Journal. Numerous reports have suggested that the new and expensive new models have underperformed and the decision follows that, the report suggested. iPh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Apple Black Friday 2018: The Best iPad, iPhone, MacBook Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/19/apple-black-friday-2018-sales-ipad-pro-iphone-xs-xr-macbook-pro-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDO38HCHQC4ngVktv_yze4EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/19/apple-black-friday-2018-sales-ipad-pro-iphone-xs-xr-macbook-pro-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Black Friday 2018: The Best iPad, iPhone, MacBook Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. Black Friday is the best time to get discounts on Apple products. The ad scans from Best Buy (52-pages), Target (47-pages), Walmart (32-pages) and T-Mobile (6-pages) have predictably good savings, but they are just the tip of the iceberg. Here are the best Apple iPad, iPhone, MacBook and AirPod deals you will find on Black Friday 2018. Work...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best Buy Black Friday 2018: iPad Mini 4 Gets A Steep Price Cut - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/22/best-buy-black-friday-2018-ipad-mini-4-gets-a-steep-price-cut/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOZqtUnLZ9jm4HqK0EuCVTcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 02:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/22/best-buy-black-friday-2018-ipad-mini-4-gets-a-steep-price-cut/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy Black Friday 2018: iPad Mini 4 Gets A Steep Price Cut&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple iPad Mini 4 The iPad Mini 4 is the perfect gift for the busy, go-getter in your life. Its size makes this iPad an easy tool to carry in a purse or small bag without the weight or size of a laptop. But don’t be fooled, this iPad could give any computer a run for its money. You’ll be editing power points, FaceTiming friends and checking e-mails in a breeze on this incredibly quick tablet. Best Buy is currently selling the iPad Mini 4 at $150 or 38 percent off its original price, so it will only cost you $250. Don’t wait to buy this, we’ve been eyeing this deal since it was announced ear...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Putting The Apple Watch To An Extreme Running Test - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyrobertson/2018/11/15/putting-the-apple-watch-to-an-extreme-running-test/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECct93wYzFkoj66Ben3quG0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 12:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyrobertson/2018/11/15/putting-the-apple-watch-to-an-extreme-running-test/" target="_blank"&gt;Putting The Apple Watch To An Extreme Running Test&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve had the Series 4 Apple Watch for a little while now and decided to put it to the test for running. As an ultra runner this took the form of a super long run over seven hours. When I run it’s important to stay in touch with the family, so I need a device that will last the distance. I expected the Apple Watch to struggle to last long enough to record the run, and had previously switched to Garmin watches for these kinds of distances. To my surprise, and the Apple Watch’s credit, it lasted impressively well. After the seven hours of running I still had over 50% of charge left in the devi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Cyber Monday 2018 Deals Preview: iPad, iPhone, MacBook Sales - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/23/apple-cyber-monday-2018-deals-preview-ipad-iphone-macbook-sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMkeerjcphZNxsAvFM-z-JsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 03:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/23/apple-cyber-monday-2018-deals-preview-ipad-iphone-macbook-sales/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Cyber Monday 2018 Deals Preview: iPad, iPhone, MacBook Sales&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. Still looking for a new iPhone, iPad, MacBook or Apple Watch? Apple has officially confirmed its Cyber Monday 2018 sales. There’s a lot to say about these deals, both good and bad, but there are certainly some solid discounts and you’re buying straight from the source. That said, for big iPhone XS and iPhone XR discounts you’re going to nee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Black Friday 2018 Hottest Tablet Deals: Amazon Fire, iPad, iPad Mini 4 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/23/black-friday-2018-hottest-tablet-deals-amazon-fire-ipad-ipad-mini-4/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2O7oPbwT-AO7lT7_QcXBkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/23/black-friday-2018-hottest-tablet-deals-amazon-fire-ipad-ipad-mini-4/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Friday 2018 Hottest Tablet Deals: Amazon Fire, iPad, iPad Mini 4&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;How is Black Friday 2018 for you? Good, I hope. Apple, Amazon and other brands are doing their best to tempt you with their products. I’ve taken a look at tablets. The deals on offer have changed noticeably since I did the same a week ago, so I figure it’s worth a whole new post. Apple iPad Pro. The deals highlighted in this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. If Fitbit smart trackers are also of interest, check out my round-up of Black Friday Fitbit deals here which has already been updated. I’ve also rounded up the best Apple Watch deals so far and the bes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Watch Could Boast Smart Cameras For FaceTime, Patent Hints - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/15/apple-watch-to-boast-cameras-for-facetime-calls-patent-suggests/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENHzsE3JK-0LdAVW-SggHesqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 01:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/15/apple-watch-to-boast-cameras-for-facetime-calls-patent-suggests/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Watch Could Boast Smart Cameras For FaceTime, Patent Hints&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s only a few weeks since the hugely redesigned and improved Apple Watch Series 4 was released. You can read my review here. Apple Watch Series 4 with Infographic face. Could a future Watch come with cameras? But now, a new patent granted to Apple and picked up by Apple Insider, shows an intriguing future version with a camera on board. So what, you say? Other wearables have had cameras on them and they haven’t proved that popular, have they? True, but the details of the patent show that Apple has decided, to coin a phrase, to think different. The patent, filed two years ago but granted e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Gift This, Not That: Garmin Fenix 5 Plus vs. Apple Watch Nike+ Series 4 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/anthonykarcz/2018/11/14/gift-this-not-that-garmin-fenix-5-plus-vs-apple-watch-nike-series-4/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPfj1Z7aqUQFTu_rynBWnZYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/anthonykarcz/2018/11/14/gift-this-not-that-garmin-fenix-5-plus-vs-apple-watch-nike-series-4/" target="_blank"&gt;Gift This, Not That: Garmin Fenix 5 Plus vs. Apple Watch Nike+ Series 4&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are going to get *so* sweaty One year later, which running smartwatch do you want on your wrist? It’s complicated. Garmin Fenix 5 Plus Smart guts and run tracking? Tell me more. If you’ve spent any time at a race of any sort, you’ve seen hordes of runners, cyclists, and swimmers with Garmin devices on their wrists. And for good reason. Garmins are reliable, durable, and have batteries that last through multiple training sessions and races. Their chunky aesthetic belies a focused mission: helping you wring every last bit of data out of your workout so that you can get better. The fenix...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Target 'Cyber Monday' 2018 Sales: What We Know So Far - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/18/target-cyber-monday-2018-sales-apple-watch-samsung-nintendo-switch-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKiKLPRkWeIyOLtx6t6_6z4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 01:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/18/target-cyber-monday-2018-sales-apple-watch-samsung-nintendo-switch-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Target 'Cyber Monday' 2018 Sales: What We Know So Far&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. Will Cyber Monday deals be better than Black Friday? That’s the big question now Black Friday 2018 is only days away. The good news, if you plan to shop at Target, is the store’s massive 47-page Black Friday ad scan drops a lot of hints. Here’s what you need to know. This is the third in my Cyber Monday 2018 preview series, following my Walmart Cyber Monday and Best ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Watch Series 4, iPad, Sony And Huawei Win Big At Pocket-lint Gadget Awards - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/14/apple-watch-series-4-ipad-sony-and-huawei-win-big-at-pocket-lint-gadget-awards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAxrvX-Z4F_lcl4kZ7H4GcoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/14/apple-watch-series-4-ipad-sony-and-huawei-win-big-at-pocket-lint-gadget-awards/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Watch Series 4, iPad, Sony And Huawei Win Big At Pocket-lint Gadget Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last night, the internationally respected Pocket-lint Awards took place in central London. Pocket-lint is a global website based in the UK. But the reason the site’s awards are so well thought-of is that the calibre of the judges is remarkable. The Pocket-lint Awards taking place in London last night. Where other awards rely on the staff of the company who present them, here, the judges – and there are 45 of them – are drawn from multiple publications, cities and countries. There are many Forbes contributors among the judges, too, including Senior Contributor Gordon Kelly, TV expert John Ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Black Friday 2018 Hottest Tablet Deals: iPad, Amazon Fire, Barnes &amp; Noble Nook - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/17/black-friday-2018-hottest-tablet-deals-ipad-amazon-fire-barnes-noble-nook/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKr9dnIClUxavP_J2nIvtPYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/17/black-friday-2018-hottest-tablet-deals-ipad-amazon-fire-barnes-noble-nook/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Friday 2018 Hottest Tablet Deals: iPad, Amazon Fire, Barnes &amp; Noble Nook&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black Friday is less than a week away so the big sales are achingly close. If you are looking for a tablet or ebook reader, then read on… Apple iPad 2018 and Apple Pencil. The deals highlighted in this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. If Fitbit smart trackers are also of interest, check out my round-up of Black Friday Fitbit deals here which has already been updated. I’ve also rounded up the best Apple Watch deals so far and the best smart home deals from Target. I’ll update this post so do check back or please click the Follow button on my contributor’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Week In Wearables: AirPods 2 Incoming? Black Friday Wearables, Xiaomi Mi Band 3 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/08/week-in-wearables-airpods-2-incoming-black-friday-wearable-deals-xiaomi-mi-band-3-price/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFvqXvOpiv4dTx8n_PxBfB4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/08/week-in-wearables-airpods-2-incoming-black-friday-wearable-deals-xiaomi-mi-band-3-price/" target="_blank"&gt;Week In Wearables: AirPods 2 Incoming? Black Friday Wearables, Xiaomi Mi Band 3&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week in wearable news is dominated by the possible arrival of Apple AirPods 2, the first wearable tech deals for Black Friday and why women might like the Michael Kors Access Runway smart watch. Apple’s iPhone X with the Apple Watch, Airpods and upcoming wireless charging pad. The Week in Wearables is a news digest, out each week, focused on some of the things that have happened in the world of tech you can wear on your wrist, perch on your head, stick in your ear, sling around your waist, tuck into the small of your back or, well, you get the idea. The world-conquering Apple AirPods. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Apple Smart Headphones Leak - While We Wait For AirPods 2 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/10/apple-smart-headphones-leak-while-we-wait-for-airpods-2-reversible-beam-forming/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPR4wtoiYp05iA1maMTcF4EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/10/apple-smart-headphones-leak-while-we-wait-for-airpods-2-reversible-beam-forming/" target="_blank"&gt;New Apple Smart Headphones Leak - While We Wait For AirPods 2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If, like me, you’re waiting for Apple AirPods 2 – and it might not be that long to wait now – then news about over-ear headphones from Apple will be of interest. Part of a patent for new headphones from Apple. As 9to5Mac has reported, a new patent has surfaced which suggests that new headphones could be on their way which are every bit as smart as the Apple HomePod. The world-conquering Apple AirPods. Features The new headphones will include features you may never have realized you’ve been waiting for… Another page from the new Apple patent. Five microphones on each earcup! Since Apple neve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple 'Black Friday' 2018: Early iPad, iPhone, Watch Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/07/apple-black-friday-2018-sales-early-ipad-iphone-xs-apple-watch-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMGZHUGkcboveGVm3bvljfEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 02:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/07/apple-black-friday-2018-sales-early-ipad-iphone-xs-apple-watch-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple 'Black Friday' 2018: Early iPad, iPhone, Watch Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. Many of Black Friday 2018’s best deals have leaked and that includes arguably the year’s hottest products: Apple’s iPad, new iPhones and Watch. Working with my holiday sales partner BestBlackFriday.com, I have dug out the top Apple deals from Target’s massive 47-page Black Friday ad scan as well as leaked ad scans from Costco, Macy’s, Meijer, Sam’s Club, Shopko and S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple 'Black Friday' 2018: AirPods, iPad, iPhone, MacBook Live Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/09/apple-black-friday-2018-airpods-ipad-iphone-macbook-live-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECqsmxhmgCGJfzjJHT6gV-UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/09/apple-black-friday-2018-airpods-ipad-iphone-macbook-live-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple 'Black Friday' 2018: AirPods, iPad, iPhone, MacBook Live Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. Black Friday 2018 is officially only two weeks away and while everyone focuses on Best Buy, Target and Walmart Black Friday Deals perhaps the best Apple discounts you will see this year start this weekend with the Sam’s Club Special One-Day sale and Adorama’s live deals. The latest iPads, iPhones, MacBooks, Watches and Apple’s insanely popu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Amazon strikes deal with Apple to sell iPhones, iPads - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-amazon-com-apple/amazon-strikes-deal-with-apple-to-sell-iphones-ipads-idUSKCN1NE2HV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECeRV0fHhT8DSpPn57nijywqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 23:40:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-amazon-com-apple/amazon-strikes-deal-with-apple-to-sell-iphones-ipads-idUSKCN1NE2HV" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon strikes deal with Apple to sell iPhones, iPads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon.com Inc (AMZN.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) on Friday said it would carry more Apple Inc (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) products globally in time for the holiday shopping season, as the technology rivals put aside past differences to boost sales. In coming weeks, the world's biggest online retailer will sell the latest editions of Apple's iPhone, iPad and other devices in the United States, Europe, Japan and India. Amazon sold a limited assortment from Apple previously that included Mac computers and Beats headphones. The deal underscores how top brands suc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Can wearables transform medical research? - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1a87f69e-e6f2-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHUZnPQojQrqInCy8RagvJkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 05:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1a87f69e-e6f2-11e8-8a85-04b8afea6ea3" target="_blank"&gt;Can wearables transform medical research?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am not a big fan of wearable devices: I’ve always felt they simply quantify what I already know. If I run up a steep hill, my laboured breathing tells me just as much as a wristband that counts the number of floors I’ve climbed. But as wearables get smarter, they are beginning to attract the attention of medical researchers. The Apple Watch Series 4 was recently given clearance by the US Food and Drug Administration for its three heart-monitoring capabilities: heart rate alert, heart rhythm detection and personal electrocardiogram (ECG) monitor. Clearance is a step down from full approval...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Black Friday 2018 Best Wearable Tech Deals: Fitbit - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/08/black-friday-2018-best-wearable-tech-deals-fitbit-release-date-prices/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPfyoN07o_mbY3eS6RO4sfYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 17:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/08/black-friday-2018-best-wearable-tech-deals-fitbit-release-date-prices/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Friday 2018 Best Wearable Tech Deals: Fitbit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fitbit is a real go-to brand for wearable tech, with the Fitbit Charge 3 and Fitbit Versa only the latest of key fitness products. The Fitbit Versa smartwatch, Fitbit’s latest model. If you’ve been wanting to snag a fitness tracker but have been holding back for some reason, Black Friday could be the moment to jump. After all, the food and drink that makes Thanksgiving so special can leave you thinking it’s time to get fit, and a tracker can be the gadget that makes the difference. Black Friday is November 23, but some of the best Fitbit deals are becoming visible now and, surprisingly, the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>iPad Pro (2018) Review: The Computer Of Tomorrow, With Compromises From Today - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/12/ipad-pro-2018-review-the-computer-of-tomorrow-with-compromises-from-today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJpVdU4Gk1xsYTu1zbIfcc4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bensin/2018/11/12/ipad-pro-2018-review-the-computer-of-tomorrow-with-compromises-from-today/" target="_blank"&gt;iPad Pro (2018) Review: The Computer Of Tomorrow, With Compromises From Today&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When people think of Apple, the first thing that comes to mind is either the iPhone or a computer. Which is fair — the iPhone is Apple’s biggest moneymaker and most ubiquitous product, and the Cupertin0-based company began, of course, as a computer brand. But something ironic happened in recent years: Apple’s smartphones and computers (both desktops and laptops) lost its status as the undisputed best and most pioneering products in its respective categories. The iPhone XS may still be the most solid all-around phone (I think so), but if I were to rank every phone by important categories — d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Loop: New iPhone Power Problems, Expensive MacBook Air Launched, Apple Confirms Beauty Filter - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/02/apple-news-headlines-ipad-pro-macbook-air-iphone-8-iphone-x-battery-problems-apple-watch-bricking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPCyMgPYu2feaJu-q8I41TEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/02/apple-news-headlines-ipad-pro-macbook-air-iphone-8-iphone-x-battery-problems-apple-watch-bricking/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Loop: New iPhone Power Problems, Expensive MacBook Air Launched, Apple Confirms Beauty Filter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at another week of news from Cupertino, this week’s Apple Loop includes the launch of the iPad Pro and MacBook Air, secrets of the iPhone XR, Apple’s latest battery throttle, confirmation of its new selfie mode, updates to macOS and iOS, watchOS update bricking the Apple Watch, and the curious case of your iPhone’s helium errors. Apple Loop is here to remind you of a few of the very many discussions that have happened around Apple over the last seven days (and you can read my weekly digest of Android news here on Forbes). The iPad Pro… Is… A… Computer! Apple’s October lau...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Pulls Latest WatchOS Update After Multiple Reports Of Bricked Watches - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/marcochiappetta/2018/10/31/apple-pulls-latest-watchos-update-after-multiple-reports-of-bricked-watches/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMCT_8h0tlwYB6fhFrRuIsoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 20:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/marcochiappetta/2018/10/31/apple-pulls-latest-watchos-update-after-multiple-reports-of-bricked-watches/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Pulls Latest WatchOS Update After Multiple Reports Of Bricked Watches&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the many announcements to come out of Apple’s event this week was the release of watchOS 5.1. Although the update is a simple point release, there were some new feature additions over and above some bug fixes that were supposed to come with it. With the watchOS 5.1 update, Apple Watch Series 4 devices would gain the ability to automatically contacts emergency services if the wearer was immobile for about a minute, should the device detect a hard fall. This feature would play a message to inform first responders that the Watch had detected a fall and would share the wearer’s location ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Week In Wearables: Apple Watch Record Sales, Samsung Galaxy Watch, Bose Sleepbuds - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/01/week-in-wearables-apple-watch-record-sales-samsung-galaxy-watch-bose-sleepbuds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH_cZXlMuRiyjZ5HiJqgCH4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/11/01/week-in-wearables-apple-watch-record-sales-samsung-galaxy-watch-bose-sleepbuds/" target="_blank"&gt;Week In Wearables: Apple Watch Record Sales, Samsung Galaxy Watch, Bose Sleepbuds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week in wearable news saw Apple claiming strong wearables sales as one analyst predicted soaring growth, Samsung’s 4G version of the Galaxy Watch to go on sale and Bose Sleepbuds being tested. The Week in Wearables is a news digest, out each week, focused on some of the things that have happened in the world of tech you can wear on your wrist, perch on your head, stick in your ear, sling around your waist, tuck into the small of your back or, well, you get the idea. Apple Watch Series 4 with the Infographic Watch face. Apple Watch record sales and predicted to grow 40% Analyst firm UBS...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Releases Second Version Of iOS 12.1, Specifically For The iPhone XR - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/11/06/ios-12-1-update-16b94/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPInOrd6TpWfd5giaEpMGBYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 21:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/11/06/ios-12-1-update-16b94/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Releases Second Version Of iOS 12.1, Specifically For The iPhone XR&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;iOS 12 screenshot Apple has released a second version of iOS 12.1, which comes a week after the original version was released. The second version of iOS 12.1 was designed specifically for the iPhone XR. The updated version of iOS 12.1 was sent over-the-air to iPhone XR devices that have not been updated to the original version yet. According to AppleInsider, the build number for this version of iOS 12.1 is known as 16B94. This indicates that some changes were made from the 16B93 build number that was used for the previous version of iOS 12.1. It is unknown what changes Apple made in this ve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple reports profits rise but iPhone sales stall - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/apple-profits-revenue-rise-iphone-sales-stall-apple-watch-ipad-mac-a8613651.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEISVWu-_M0ht4J0wW_V4zBEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 22:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/apple-profits-revenue-rise-iphone-sales-stall-apple-watch-ipad-mac-a8613651.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apple reports profits rise but iPhone sales stall&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple has reported an increase in revenue and profit in its latest financial results despite iPhone sales stalling. The technology giant's revenue for the last three months was 62.9 billion dollars (£48.4 billion) - up 20 per cent on the same period last year - with a profit of $14.1bn (£10.8 billion). Sales of the company's flagship product, the iPhone, stalled at the same level as a year ago. Read more - Everything you need to know about Apple's brand new tablet - Apple product still missing after users wait more than a year - Live updates as Apple reveals whole suite of new products - Ap...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Coach's New Apple Watch Straps Are Fitting Fashion For Fall - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/paullamkin/2018/10/31/coachs-new-apple-watch-straps-are-fitting-fashion-for-fall/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMJzGp7Vp2K_JEC8aaR_lYEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/paullamkin/2018/10/31/coachs-new-apple-watch-straps-are-fitting-fashion-for-fall/" target="_blank"&gt;Coach's New Apple Watch Straps Are Fitting Fashion For Fall&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coach Apple Watch bands Luxury leather company Coach has revealed its latest seasonal Apple Watch straps – with the new Fall collection arriving to give your tech-timepiece a bump up in the style stakes. To add to the Coach summer Apple Watch strap collection launched back in August, the New York based fashion company is adding new ‘Strap with Prints’ editions in two colors: Rose Print and the brilliantly-named Pigtini Party. Rose Print is described as ‘dark red glove-tanned leather with pink roses’, while the Pigtini Party variant is a glove-tanned leather strap with a pig holding balloons...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why Apple's Stock Traded Down Post-Q4 Earnings - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/02/why-apples-stock-traded-down-post-q4-earnings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIJpCX8r9XB0CeO7icF_GX8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/02/why-apples-stock-traded-down-post-q4-earnings/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Apple's Stock Traded Down Post-Q4 Earnings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signage is displayed after an Apple Inc. event in the Brooklyn borough of New York, U.S., on Tuesday, Oct. 30, 2018. Photographer: Jeenah Moon/Bloomberg Apple published its fiscal Q4 results on Thursday, beating market expectations on earnings and revenues, driven by strong iPhone and Services revenue growth. However, the stock declined following the earnings release, as iPhone shipments and holiday guidance fell short of market expectations. Below we provide some of the key takeaways from the company’s earnings. Our interactive dashboard analysis on What’s Driving Our $230 Price Estimate F...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple event: Everything Apple is expected to announce at its latest launch – and everything it won't - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/apple-event-latest-iphone-ipad-pro-mac-predictions-roundup-new-a8607581.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBGUSLxzsfMV2Z_MkOGJJp8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 16:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/apple-event-latest-iphone-ipad-pro-mac-predictions-roundup-new-a8607581.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apple event: Everything Apple is expected to announce at its latest launch – and everything it won't&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple is about to hold its next big event – and is rumoured to be updating a huge number of its products. The October event comes just weeks after the launch of its new iPhone and Apple Watch. Those two products will probably not be mentioned during the event, but everything else is rumoured to be getting at least a little change. The location of the event is a strange one: it is being held in New York, at the Brooklyn Academy of Music, far from Apple's home in California. Most likely, that's intended to emphasise the creative aspect of the event and the products being shown, just like when...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Apple has a problem it doesn't want to talk about - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/02/tech/apple-iphone-metrics-problem/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIIK5aYN3-6fDaC42t0gCM8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 18:15:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/02/tech/apple-iphone-metrics-problem/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apple has a problem it doesn't want to talk about&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The era of rapid iPhone growth ended years ago. Now Apple is making a change to ensure it doesn't have to talk as much about that problem. On a conference call Thursday, top Apple executives laid out their plans to stop disclosing the number of iPhones, iPads and Macs it sells each quarter. It's a move that shocked analysts and only added to jitters around a mixed earnings report. Daniel Ives, an analyst with Wedbush, called the announcement a "jaw dropper" in an investor note Friday morning, particularly because Apple is at a "critical juncture." He said Apple is trying to make up for slow...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Why Apple Is Finally Ditching Its Proprietary Lightning Connector For USB-C On All iPhones, iPads - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/10/31/why-apple-is-finally-ditching-its-proprietary-lightning-connector-for-usb-c-on-all-iphones-ipads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgxWId_HforooPj_SNLsQ8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 16:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/10/31/why-apple-is-finally-ditching-its-proprietary-lightning-connector-for-usb-c-on-all-iphones-ipads/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Apple Is Finally Ditching Its Proprietary Lightning Connector For USB-C On All iPhones, iPads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting with its latest iPad Pro, Apple is moving away from its proprietary 6-years old Lightning connector and Atherton Research expects all iOS devices in 2019 to have a USB-C port instead. At the company’s “More in the Making” event on Tuesday, Apple’s vice-president of hardware engineering John Ternus revealed that the new iPad Pro will have a USB-C port – already present on the latest MacBooks – instead of the company’s proprietary Lightning connector. “Because a high performance computer deserves a high performance connector. And so in these new iPad Pros, we’re moving to USB-C,” sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New 2018 MacBook Air Hands-On Review: Here's All You Need To Know - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/31/new-2018-macbook-air-hands-on-heres-all-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgrBNdkASFapQdPCMhxShsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/31/new-2018-macbook-air-hands-on-heres-all-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;New 2018 MacBook Air Hands-On Review: Here's All You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;From its first appearance 10 years ago, the Macbook Air has been a hit. Apple never removed it from its range, even when other of its laptops changed and morphed, because it was continuously successful. It was the entry-level MacBook, available at a lower price because it had a lower-resolution display, something which owners consistently told Apple they wanted to change. Now, it has. Here are all the updates about which you should know. Apple launched a new MacBook Air in Brooklyn, New York, today. 1 It has been upgraded to the display it deserves The new MacBook Air has a Retina display, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple spruces up Macs, iPad Pros and raises prices - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-ipad/apple-spruces-up-macs-ipad-pros-and-raises-prices-idUSKCN1N415Q</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6bS_bouKxjg6scJUNFpuQqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 22:55:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-ipad/apple-spruces-up-macs-ipad-pros-and-raises-prices-idUSKCN1N415Q" target="_blank"&gt;Apple spruces up Macs, iPad Pros and raises prices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple Inc (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) refreshed some of its lesser-known products at a New York event on Tuesday, adding iPhone features like facial recognition to the iPad Pro and faster processors and better displays to some Mac computers that had gone years without a major update. The devices will hit stores on Nov. 7. Counting new iPhones and Apple Watches released last month, Apple will have more than half a dozen new products on shelves for the holiday shopping season, many at higher prices than previous models. The Cupertino, California, company introduced new vers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Apple emojis: iPhone and iPad users get 77 brand new emoji with iOS 12 update - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/new-emojis-apple-ios-12-update-iphone-bagel-ipad-salt-texting-a8566356.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGMCHf4GXXkJY_6sIz5rytsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 16:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/new-emojis-apple-ios-12-update-iphone-bagel-ipad-salt-texting-a8566356.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Apple emojis: iPhone and iPad users get 77 brand new emoji with iOS 12 update&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple has added more than 70 new emojis for iPhone, iPad and Apple Watch users, including a bagel, a broom and a badger. The new emojis come with the release of the iOS 12.1 mobile software. "Emoji are used by people all over the world to communicate," Apple said in a press release. "iOS 12.1 brings even more characters to the keyboard that better represent global users, including new emoji for moon cake, red gift envelope and nazar amulet." iPhone XS launch in September 2018 - + show all iPhone XS launch in September 2018 - 1/11 Tim Cook speaks about the iPhone XS and XS Max Tim Cook, CEO ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>5 Reasons Why You Should Be Excited About Apple Watch 4's ECG Sensor - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/shourjyasanyal/2018/10/28/5-reasons-why-you-should-be-excited-about-apple-watch-4-ecg-sensor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEImxNPhc-qS_gQTwnXNfzOgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/shourjyasanyal/2018/10/28/5-reasons-why-you-should-be-excited-about-apple-watch-4-ecg-sensor/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Reasons Why You Should Be Excited About Apple Watch 4's ECG Sensor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On September 12, 2018, Apple’s COO Jeff William announced that the Apple Watch Series 4 would contain an FDA-cleared ECG sensor. This immediately triggered a mixed-bag reaction in the digital health community, from healthy skepticism to an outcry about its effect on the already overwhelmed cardiac care ecosystem. Apple announced three separate but related features, in the September launch. First, a heart rate monitoring service that will alert patients when their resting heart rate systematically falls below a certain threshold. Second, an FDA approved algorithm that can predict atrial fibr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>AirPods 2 Could Be Revealed In Days Alongside AirPower Release Date, Analyst Says - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/28/airpods-2-could-be-revealed-in-days-alongside-airpower-release-date-analyst-says/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKdIw9CsbBQWkpKAN_o4ymwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 10:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/28/airpods-2-could-be-revealed-in-days-alongside-airpower-release-date-analyst-says/" target="_blank"&gt;AirPods 2 Could Be Revealed In Days Alongside AirPower Release Date, Analyst Says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple’s big announcement in Brooklyn Academy of Music on October 30 is nearly here, and anticipation is reaching fever pitch. Expectations include two new iPad Pro tablets with all-screen, radically different designs and some new version of a MacBook, perhaps a MacBook Air update or replacement. Oh, and there’s likely to be an updated Apple Pencil. Apple’s iPhone X with the Apple Watch, Airpods and upcoming wireless charging pad. But now, top analyst Ming-Chi Kuo has added more suggestions to what might be on its way in the next few days, as revealed to MacRumors. These include the much-des...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple investigates report that Chinese students were forced to make its watches - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/29/tech/apple-supply-chain-china/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGWaqWIOMDjtgNKdnHdfJhkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 11:45:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/29/tech/apple-supply-chain-china/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apple investigates report that Chinese students were forced to make its watches&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple is investigating allegations that one of its suppliers illegally used high school students to assemble its watches at a factory in China. Hong Kong-based labor rights group Students and Scholars Against Corporate Misbehavior (SACOM) said in a report last week that it found students being made to work on Apple Watch production lines at a plant run by Quanta Computer in the city of Chongqing. The groupalleges that students aged 16 to 19 were forced by their schools to work at the factory through compulsory internships, placed in jobs unrelated to their field of study, often made to work...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Apple event live: New MacBook Air, iPad Pro and Mac Mini revealed - latest news - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/30/apple-event-live-new-ipad-pro-macbook-air-mac-mini-expected/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA1eEZX70Cgd_GBLUpBTpbcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 17:49:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/30/apple-event-live-new-ipad-pro-macbook-air-mac-mini-expected/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple event live: New MacBook Air, iPad Pro and Mac Mini revealed - latest news&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Apple reveals new MacBook Air starting at £1,199 - The updated MacBook Air comes with Retina display and Thunderbolt 3 ports - Apple launches a new iPad Pro with Face ID and no home button starting at £769 - Apple updates its Mac Mini starting at £799 - New MacBook Air available to pre-order from today and in stores November 7 Apple has unveiled new versions of its iPad and Mac computers as it seeks to revive growth in the two divisions amid stalling sales. The US tech company unveiled a redesigned MacBook Air laptop and an overhauled iPad Pro at an event in New York on Tuesday, the secon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Apple to launch new iPad Pro two days before fourth-quarter results - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/fb91889c-d97a-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENfVt_8cIDfau7pKlzbeT1wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/fb91889c-d97a-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8" target="_blank"&gt;Apple to launch new iPad Pro two days before fourth-quarter results&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week was one of the worst in years for tech stocks, as investors were spooked by slower growth at Amazon and Alphabet. But there were also pockets of resilience, with Microsoft and Intel both bucking the trend after posting robust results. With investors so jittery, there could be tens of billions of dollars of market value at stake for Apple this week as it prepares for two big events: Tuesday’s product launch in New York, followed by its fourth-quarter earnings report on Thursday. Here is what to expect from the iPhone maker’s last big push before the holidays. New York, new iPads Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>iPhone XR: Cheaper, colourful version of latest Apple handset finally goes on sale - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/iphone-xr-apple-price-latest-order-buy-store-cost-sale-cheap-colour-a8603396.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDkwqXqkLmxKpEvTfLbsCJ0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 13:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/iphone-xr-apple-price-latest-order-buy-store-cost-sale-cheap-colour-a8603396.html" target="_blank"&gt;iPhone XR: Cheaper, colourful version of latest Apple handset finally goes on sale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple's brand new, cheaper version of the iPhone XR is finally available. The handset has gone on sale weeks after it was launched alongside the more expensive iPhone XS. The XR offers many of the same features but at a reduced price. It includes the same processor and many other technologies, but packs them into a cheaper body that allows Apple to sell the phone at a more affordable price. It also comes in a range of – sometimes very bright – colour finishes. iPhone XS launch in September 2018 - + show all iPhone XS launch in September 2018 - 1/11 Tim Cook speaks about the iPhone XS and XS...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Smart Wearables Market To Double By 2022: $27 Billion Industry Forecast - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/paullamkin/2018/10/23/smart-wearables-market-to-double-by-2022-27-billion-industry-forecast/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGPCyC_bRoKLazcSROY5LtEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/paullamkin/2018/10/23/smart-wearables-market-to-double-by-2022-27-billion-industry-forecast/" target="_blank"&gt;Smart Wearables Market To Double By 2022: $27 Billion Industry Forecast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fossil Q Explorist HR Worldwide smart wearable device sales will double by 2022, becoming a $27 billion+ market with 233 million unit sales. That’s the word according to industry analyst CCS Insight, who state that the growth is being powered by smartwatches, with fitness trackers on the slide in the next four years. CCS’ report states that 85 million smartwatches will be sold in 2019, increasing to 137 million in 2022, but that sales of fitness trackers will drop by 43 million this year to 39 million within those four years. Of the 117 million smart wearable devices the analyst expects to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>iPhone XR review: Cheaper and very cheerful indeed - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/iphone-xr-review-apple-xs-buy-should-i-get-it-order-store-a8597461.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJTlMytkD_wLJ9_uYqT5jK8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 11:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/iphone-xr-review-apple-xs-buy-should-i-get-it-order-store-a8597461.html" target="_blank"&gt;iPhone XR review: Cheaper and very cheerful indeed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month, Apple launched two handsets, the iPhone XS and iPhone XS Max. These were the sequels to last year’s groundbreaking iPhone X and were in the same, (very high), price range as the X. X, you’ll remember, is pronounced ten in this context. So, what if you can’t afford £999 or more for a smartphone? Well, first, you’re not alone. Secondly, the usual iPhone route is to buy the last-generation iPhone at a lower price. iPhone XS launch in September 2018 - + show all iPhone XS launch in September 2018 - 1/11 Tim Cook speaks about the iPhone XS and XS Max Tim Cook, CEO of Apple, speaks ab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Heartfelt Watch 4 Ushers In New Time For Apple - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonmarkman/2018/10/20/heartfelt-watch-4-ushers-in-new-time-for-apple/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG8L6iv6cT6cABqW_UcPFesqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonmarkman/2018/10/20/heartfelt-watch-4-ushers-in-new-time-for-apple/" target="_blank"&gt;Heartfelt Watch 4 Ushers In New Time For Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to beat up on Apple. Management seems smug. Its lack of real product innovation in its yearly releases can get depressing. But every five years or so, the company does something really special. 2018 has become one of those years. Loyalists and tech writers gathered in Cupertino in September. There were slick commercials and new iPhones. And then there was the fourth incarnation of the Apple Watch. Apple CEO Tim Cook, left and soccer player Alex Morgan discuss the new Apple Watch 4 at the Steve Jobs Theater during an event to announce new products Wednesday, Sept. 12, 2018, in Cupe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Rumor: iPad Pro To Ditch Lightning Connector. Will 2019 iPhone Follow? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/20/rumor-ipad-pro-to-ditch-lightning-connector-will-2019-iphone-follow-release-date/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOzTWPxtiGGzXUNy5p84xsMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/20/rumor-ipad-pro-to-ditch-lightning-connector-will-2019-iphone-follow-release-date/" target="_blank"&gt;Rumor: iPad Pro To Ditch Lightning Connector. Will 2019 iPhone Follow?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the date of the latest Apple event revealed as October 30, at the Brooklyn Academy of Music in New York, there is much anticipation about what the new iPad Pro, near-certain to be announced there, will be like. The next Apple iPad Pro may be thinner than ever. There is talk that the new tablet will have an all-screen front and feature Face ID. Rumor has it there will be no headphone jack. And repeatedly there have been leaks suggesting the Lightning connector will be replaced by USB-C. Rumors include a report from the ever-reliable Ming-Chi Kuo, who said in September that USB-C would b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here’s what we know so far about Jamal Khashoggi’s Apple Watch - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90251562/heres-what-we-know-so-far-about-jamal-khashoggis-apple-watch</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFAtW4oZbajbb4xjnyZanaAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 16:38:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90251562/heres-what-we-know-so-far-about-jamal-khashoggis-apple-watch" target="_blank"&gt;Here’s what we know so far about Jamal Khashoggi’s Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mystery surrounding the disappearance of Jamal Khashoggi on October 2 became a tech story with revelations that the journalist regularly wore an Apple Watch, which could have been used to record and transmit what really happened. The Turkish government claims it has recordings of Khashoggi’s murder inside then Saudi consulate October 12 and the Saudis say the journalist left the consulate unharmed. Here’s what we know and don’t know so far about the possible role of the Watch in the story. Could Khashoggi have recorded the events that occurred after he entered the consulate using just h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Apple Loop: iPhone XS Max Fails Battery Test, App Store Scams, iPhone XR Fights iPhone XS - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/10/19/apple-news-headlines-iphone-xs-max-battery-fail-iphone-xr-preorders-scam-apps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECCtOGQ2ycE0EGwGmYGBdOIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 22:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/10/19/apple-news-headlines-iphone-xs-max-battery-fail-iphone-xr-preorders-scam-apps/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Loop: iPhone XS Max Fails Battery Test, App Store Scams, iPhone XR Fights iPhone XS&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at another week of news from Cupertino, this week’s Apple Loop includes major battery problems for the iPhone XS, thoughts on the iPhone XR, a hidden price rise for the iPhone 8, sneaky subscriptions in the App Store, MacBook Pro discounts, and custom watch faces for the Apple Watch. Apple Loop is here to remind you of a few of the very many discussions that have happened around Apple over the last seven days (and you can read my weekly digest of Android news here on Forbes). iPhone XS Max Has A Major Battery Problems There’s been a lot of discussion around iPhone battery...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Confirms October Event: Gorgeous New iPad Pro Likely, AirPods 2 Possible - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/18/apple-confirms-october-event-gorgeous-new-ipad-pro-likely-airpods-2-possible/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBavwBRmpDJ_KMtLS-5wjfUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/18/apple-confirms-october-event-gorgeous-new-ipad-pro-likely-airpods-2-possible/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Confirms October Event: Gorgeous New iPad Pro Likely, AirPods 2 Possible&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, after much anticipation, Apple has revealed that it has another big fall event this year and it’ll be on October 30. It’s near-certain this will mainly focus on the next iPad Pro, though it may also reveal an exact date for the release of the AirPower charging pad and confirmation of a new charging case for the AirPods. There may be a new MacBook, perhaps a replacement for the MacBook Air. I’m still hoping Apple to take the opportunity to upgrade the little earbuds to AirPods 2. At last, the date is official: October 30. Here’s everything you need to know about what to expect… Date and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple gives U.S. users tool to see what data it has collected - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-privacy/apple-gives-u-s-users-tool-to-see-what-data-it-has-collected-idUSKCN1MR296</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELT8vaWdGb2LcqWWjIF4LSUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 20:50:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-privacy/apple-gives-u-s-users-tool-to-see-what-data-it-has-collected-idUSKCN1MR296" target="_blank"&gt;Apple gives U.S. users tool to see what data it has collected&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple Inc (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) on Wednesday rolled out an online tool to users in the United States and several other countries to download, change or delete all the data that the iPhone maker has collected on them. Apple updated its privacy website with the tool, which was unveiled earlier this year for users in the European Union in response to the region's General Data Protection Regulation, or GDPR. Apple will now let users in the United States, Canada, Australia and New Zealand see and download all information that Apple has collected on them. It also gives us...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Week In Wearables: Apple Watch Series 4 Bug, AR Glasses In Theaters, Apple Watch Will Save Lives - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/11/week-in-wearables-apple-watch-series-4-bug-ar-glasses-in-theaters-apple-watch-will-save-lives/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMq7uoeyqAIphYLmTzE8cbQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/11/week-in-wearables-apple-watch-series-4-bug-ar-glasses-in-theaters-apple-watch-will-save-lives/" target="_blank"&gt;Week In Wearables: Apple Watch Series 4 Bug, AR Glasses In Theaters, Apple Watch Will Save Lives&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week in wearable tech: there’s a bug which leaves the latest Apple Watch in a reboot loop, the amazing National Theatre in London is embracing AR for audience members and the absence of a Google Pixel Watch is not exactly mourned. Apple Watch Infographic face, including Heart Rate complication. The Week in Wearables is a news digest, out each week, focused on some of the things that have happened in the world of tech you can wear on your wrist, perch on your head, stick in your ear, sling around your waist, tuck into the small of your back or, well, you get the idea. Incidentally, ther...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why claims Khashoggi's Apple Watch recorded alleged murder are unlikely - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/13/middleeast/khashoggi-apple-watch-analysis-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAwA_I11jomxcALGrBybsBsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 11:22:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/13/middleeast/khashoggi-apple-watch-analysis-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why claims Khashoggi's Apple Watch recorded alleged murder are unlikely&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts have dismissed claims that a recording of the alleged killing of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi may have been transmitted using his Apple Watch. The Turkish newspaper Sabah reported Saturday morning that Khashoggi turned on the recording function of his Apple Watch before walking into the Saudi consulate in Istanbul on October 2, and that audio clips of his "interrogation, torture and killing were audio recorded and sent to both his phone and to iCloud." CNN could not independently verify the Sabah report and was seeking comment from both Saudi and Turkish officials. Saudi Arabia ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Apple Watch Series 4 Sees First Discounted Price, Today At Best Buy - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/10/apple-watch-series-4-sees-first-discounted-price-at-best-buy-today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDGcQo8VYY5vbrONEtVJJHcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/10/10/apple-watch-series-4-sees-first-discounted-price-at-best-buy-today/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Watch Series 4 Sees First Discounted Price, Today At Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gorgeous new Apple Watch Series 4 is reportedly doing big sales. So discounts are rare to non-existent. Apple Watch Series 4 with the Infographic Watch face. But today, as reported by 9to5Toys, Best Buy has an Open-Box sale and the newest Watch is available. Open-Box, according to Best Buy, means that these are products returned under the company’s Return and Exchange Promise and the condition is Excellent-Certified, Excellent, Satisfactory or Fair. By definition, these Watches are not old, as the Series 4 only went on sale for the first time on Friday 21 September – that’s less than th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>