<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Mortal Kombat - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRGwzWTI1ZkVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:02:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>'Mortal Kombat 11' Release Date, Trailer And New 21 Savage Song Revealed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/12/07/mortal-kombat-11-release-date-trailer-and-new-21-savage-song-revealed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO4JEcZyrv34ElP-0pEAl-AqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/12/07/mortal-kombat-11-release-date-trailer-and-new-21-savage-song-revealed/" target="_blank"&gt;'Mortal Kombat 11' Release Date, Trailer And New 21 Savage Song Revealed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2018 Game Awards were packed with honors, tributes, entertainment and gaming announcements. One of the biggest came from the legendary creator of the Mortal Kombat series. Yes, it’s true. Mortal Kombat 11 is on its way and it will arrive with a plethora of fanfare. MK11 A trailer for the new game was revealed along with some pre-order details, the date for a community reveal and the official release date (April 23, 2019) for PS4, Xbox One, and PC. Fans can start pre-ordering the game on December 8 and that will get them access to the Beta and the Shao Kahn DLC once the game is released....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Mortal Kombat's Scorpion To Hillary Clinton: 'Finish Him' - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mortal-kombat-scorpion-hillary-clinton_us_5807fb77e4b0180a36e8b3e0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFqDadH8F-skO_SrzcY2oU0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 00:51:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mortal-kombat-scorpion-hillary-clinton_us_5807fb77e4b0180a36e8b3e0" target="_blank"&gt;Mortal Kombat's Scorpion To Hillary Clinton: 'Finish Him'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump is on the brink. After two devastating first rounds, the Republican presidential nominee is reeling ― one blow away from ultimate defeat. Legendary Mortal Kombat ninja Scorpion’s advice for Hillary Clinton: “Finish him.” That unforgiving message came in a cartoon published Wednesday afternoon by The New Yorker. In it, artist Benjamin Schwartz depicts the Democratic nominee speaking with the ninja spectre before the final presidential debate. Given Trump’s dwindling support, mounting sexual assault allegations and repeated whining about the election being rigged, the debate coul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Injustice 2 review -DC's movie makers could learn something from this fantastic fighting game - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/injustice-2-review-dcs-movie-makers-could-learn-something-fantastic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP-Qy1fCWtM3_ppBibMSubMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/injustice-2-review-dcs-movie-makers-could-learn-something-fantastic/" target="_blank"&gt;Injustice 2 review -DC's movie makers could learn something from this fantastic fighting game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If DC Comics' movie-makers want to learn a thing or two about translating Batman and pals to the screen, they could do a lot worse than having a look at Injustice 2. Somehow the latest fighting game from Mortal Kombat developer Netherrealm Studios has better plotting and intrigue than any DC film in the last decade. Faint praise after the garish incoherence of Batman v Superman and Suicide Squad, sure, but Injustice 2's compelling story mode conjures just the right amount of silliness and graphic novel grit from its enormous ensemble cast. It is largely an excuse for superheroes as wide-ran...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Do video games lead to violence? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2016/07/25/health/video-games-and-violence/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSVH0_HFpg3MRNta9soMYgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 19:08:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2016/07/25/health/video-games-and-violence/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Do video games lead to violence?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump said Thursday during a White House meeting on school safety that the nation needs to address what young people are seeing. "I'm hearing more and more people saying the level of violence on video games is really shaping young people's thoughts," he said. "And then you go the further step, and that's the movies. You see these movies -- they're so violent, and yet a kid is able to see the movie if sex isn't involved." Killing, though, is involved, he said. His remarks were dismissed by Chris Grady, a survivor of the February 14 shootings at Stoneman Douglas High School i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Is Binge-Playing Video Games Bad For You? - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2018/02/20/is-binge-playing-video-games-bad-for-you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFLpiHacmH4nohG1lXhlH7MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2018/02/20/is-binge-playing-video-games-bad-for-you/" target="_blank"&gt;Is Binge-Playing Video Games Bad For You?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Nioh’ Listen to the full episode here: Everyone has their own particular gaming habits. Maybe one person spends hours upon hours in a single game while another zips through shorter indie and mobile fare. And maybe someone goes through their endless game library checking how long each game is and calculating the optimal path to work through the mountain in the most efficient way possible — but then just ends up playing two games of Rocket League. Satchell Drakes and I talk about how we typically work through games and how binge-watching television on Netflix impacts our habits in 2018. We a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Injustice 2's 'Ninja Turtles' Look Way Better Than Michael Bay's Hideous Mutants - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/02/14/injustice-2s-ninja-turtles-look-way-better-than-michael-bays-hideous-mutants/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECQ4oF0yHfJSzR56A4MDtUUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/02/14/injustice-2s-ninja-turtles-look-way-better-than-michael-bays-hideous-mutants/" target="_blank"&gt;Injustice 2's 'Ninja Turtles' Look Way Better Than Michael Bay's Hideous Mutants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles have landed in Injustice 2. The Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles have landed in Injustice 2, the excellent DC Comics superhero fighting game from NetherRealm Studios. The DLC has its first trailer and frankly it looks absolutely great. The Turtles—Leonardo, Donatello, Michelangelo and Raphael—have a slick fighting style and, perhaps more importantly, actually look like Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, unlike the muscled monstrosities we got in Michael Bay’s two ridiculous TMNT movies. You can see what the game’s Turtles look like above. Now here’s the Michael Bay v...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'Dragon Ball FighterZ' Review: Goku Said To Knock You Out - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2018/02/01/dragon-ball-fighterz-review-goku-said-to-knock-you-out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAJJElyst2shcVjpeLdWFTcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2018/02/01/dragon-ball-fighterz-review-goku-said-to-knock-you-out/" target="_blank"&gt;'Dragon Ball FighterZ' Review: Goku Said To Knock You Out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dragon Ball FighterZ is really good. There are two types of gamers who play fighting games and these two types of gamers look for two very different things when reading reviews of fighting games. First, there’s the casual crowd. These gamers may play all sorts of video games—they may, indeed, be “hardcore” gamers in a broad sense of the word—but when it comes to fighting games they’re just here for the story mode and some local brawls. They’ve played fighting games before—some Street Fighter, some Mortal Kombat, maybe some Injustice or Tekken—but they aren’t competitive players and they don...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item></channel></rss>