<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>2014 West Africa Ebola outbreak - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV3TUY5Zk9YRVNBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:00:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Uganda Vaccinates Health Workers Against Ebola - New Vision</title><link>https://www.newvision.co.ug/new_vision/news/1490826/uganda-vaccinates-health-workers-ebola</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiWmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5ld3Zpc2lvbi5jby51Zy9uZXdfdmlzaW9uL25ld3MvMTQ5MDgyNi91Z2FuZGEtdmFjY2luYXRlcy1oZWFsdGgtd29ya2Vycy1lYm9sYdIBAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 04:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newvision.co.ug/new_vision/news/1490826/uganda-vaccinates-health-workers-ebola" target="_blank"&gt;Uganda Vaccinates Health Workers Against Ebola&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Vision&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HEALTH Uganda has vaccinated thousands of health workers against Ebola to counter the spread of the deadly virus from its neighbour Democratic Republic of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newvision.co.ug">New Vision</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/qg4VURS_YZlar_24O8tsIkB0JE69aDhOraFCtA8vxj7g3tPDPajeCFStN3gSwaPiCFCveh4F9p9M-NUCWiJJCKSel8lr0UjVzR-7wB1NkS6IvTiViD-Y6E3KctrNTFrdGMI5xDJTOas8vc4dijJr7g=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Death toll tops 200 in DR Congo Ebola outbreak - Daily Monitor</title><link>https://www.monitor.co.ug/News/World/Death-toll-tops-200-DR-Congo-Ebola-outbreak/688340-4846324-dgf1sq/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMicWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm1vbml0b3IuY28udWcvTmV3cy9Xb3JsZC9EZWF0aC10b2xsLXRvcHMtMjAwLURSLUNvbmdvLUVib2xhLW91dGJyZWFrLzY4ODM0MC00ODQ2MzI0LWRnZjFzcS9pbmRleC5odG1s0gHFAWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LW1vbml0b3ItY28tdWcuY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy93d3cubW9uaXRvci5jby51Zy9OZXdzL1dvcmxkL0RlYXRoLXRvbGwtdG9wcy0yMDAtRFItQ29uZ28tRWJvbGEtb3V0YnJlYWsvNjg4MzQwLTQ4NDYzMjQtdmlldy1hc0FNUC12Z2x1ZS9pbmRleC5odG1sP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.monitor.co.ug/News/World/Death-toll-tops-200-DR-Congo-Ebola-outbreak/688340-4846324-dgf1sq/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Death toll tops 200 in DR Congo Ebola outbreak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Daily Monitor&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;About half of the cases were in Beni, a city of 800000 people, in the North Kivu region.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.monitor.co.ug">Daily Monitor</source></item><item><title>Congo Ebola Outbreak Reaches Major City - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/congo-ebola-outbreak-reaches-major-city</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGvn50HEPIrXUw7XM1Mo49kqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:27:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/congo-ebola-outbreak-reaches-major-city" target="_blank"&gt;Congo Ebola Outbreak Reaches Major City&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHN WESSELS, A devastating Ebola outbreak that has been ravaging war-torn regions of central Africa has spread to Butembo, a major city in the east of the Democratic Republic of the Congo, and is now being recognized as the second worst recorded outbreak of the deadly hemorrhagic fever in history. Aid agencies have struggled to manage the epidemic in the face of a brutal insurgency, with rebel attacks making tracking the virus and reaching victims impossible at times. About 41,000 people, mainly health workers and contacts of Ebola victims, have received an experimental vaccine, but there ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Ebola spreads to major Congo city as vaccines a concern - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/86fd89fa73594ed0aa098c6c5a063300</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECcQK_eMENy536lpeE25eqUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6udAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:45:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/86fd89fa73594ed0aa098c6c5a063300" target="_blank"&gt;Ebola spreads to major Congo city as vaccines a concern&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAKAR, Senegal (AP) — The second-largest Ebola outbreak in history has spread to a major city in eastern Congo, as health experts worry whether the stock of an experimental vaccine will stand up to the demands of an epidemic with no end in sight. Butembo, with more than 1 million residents, is now reporting cases of the deadly hemorrhagic fever. That complicates Ebola containment work already challenged by rebel attacks elsewhere that have made tracking the virus almost impossible in some isolated villages. "We are very concerned by the epidemiological situation in the Butembo area," said J...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Fears for Ebola vaccine stockpiles as Congo outbreak spreads - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/fears-for-ebola-vaccine-stockpiles-as-congo-outbreak-spreads/10596352</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJvJbdHDNhOy6XJ2zEv0iL8qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:14:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-07/fears-for-ebola-vaccine-stockpiles-as-congo-outbreak-spreads/10596352" target="_blank"&gt;Fears for Ebola vaccine stockpiles as Congo outbreak spreads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second-largest Ebola outbreak in history has spread to a major city in eastern Congo, as health experts worry whether the stock of an experimental vaccine will stand up to the demands of an epidemic with no end in sight. Butembo, with more than 1 million residents, is now reporting cases of the deadly haemorrhagic fever. That complicates Ebola containment work already challenged by rebel attacks elsewhere that have made tracking the virus almost impossible in some isolated villages. "We are very concerned by the epidemiological situation in the Butembo area," said John Johnson, project ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Refusal to give pregnant women vaccines branded unacceptable - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/refusal-give-pregnant-women-vaccines-branded-unacceptable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELnnUtq1G-e9viUwlB62EtgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:33:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/refusal-give-pregnant-women-vaccines-branded-unacceptable/" target="_blank"&gt;Refusal to give pregnant women vaccines branded unacceptable&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Failure to vaccinate pregnant women during deadly infectious disease outbreaks is putting them and their unborn children at risk, a new report has warned. Pregnant women are usually excluded from vaccination campaigns because vaccines against infectious diseases like Ebola are rarely tested or approved for use in pregnant women. This approach has led to anger among some that women are being put unnecessarily at risk during the current Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC). Studies of previous outbreaks showing that between 80 and 90 per cent of all pregnant women who cont...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ebola cases surge in Congo, with women and children disproportionately sick - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/health/ebola-women-children-africa-bn/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAXxZs67Yq1GQJhCQ28O068qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:25:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/health/ebola-women-children-africa-bn/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ebola cases surge in Congo, with women and children disproportionately sick&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been 18 more cases of illness and five more deaths reported in just two days in the Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo, according to the Ministry of Health. Since the outbreak began, the total number of probable cases is now 471, including 273 deaths, the ministry reported Thursday. Public health authorities are investigating an additional 106 suspected cases, the ministry indicated. Second-largest outbreak in history This is the 10th outbreak since 1976 in Congo, where the virus is endemic, and the second this year. It is also now the second-deadliest Ebola outbr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Congo's Worst Ebola Outbreak Hits Women Especially Hard - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/congo-worst-ebola-outbreak-hits-women-especially-hard/4686041.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECB4Evd0ixgp9X-AOn46nlAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:46:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/congo-worst-ebola-outbreak-hits-women-especially-hard/4686041.html" target="_blank"&gt;Congo's Worst Ebola Outbreak Hits Women Especially Hard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democratic Republic of Congo is in the throes of its worst-ever Ebola outbreak, with more than 420 cases in the country’s volatile east, and a mortality rate of just under 60 percent. But this outbreak — the nation’s tenth known Ebola epidemic — is unusual because more than 60 percent of patients are women. Among them is Baby Benedicte. Her short life has already been unimaginably difficult. At one month old, she is underweight, at 2.9 kilograms. And she is alone. Her mother had Ebola, and died giving birth to her. She’s spent the last three weeks of her life in a plastic isolation cube...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>WHO says it can fight Ebola outbreak despite US withdrawal - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/37248f718aa440adb71114fd4667f42a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAEoZKnvQwspiEFXhK02flkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6udAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 22:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/37248f718aa440adb71114fd4667f42a" target="_blank"&gt;WHO says it can fight Ebola outbreak despite US withdrawal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (AP) — The head of the World Health Organization said Monday it can fight the deadly Ebola outbreak in Congo despite the withdrawal of the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, insisting: "We can cover it." The comments by WHO Director-General Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus came in the wake of commentaries in two medical journals appealing to the CDC to return to the epidemic zone in Congo — saying its expertise is needed. The U.S. experts have been sidelined for weeks, ordered away from the region because of State Department security concerns. Violence by rebel groups has com...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Q&amp;A: Conflict, resistance hampering WHO's Ebola efforts in DRC - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/qa-conflict-resistance-hampering-ebola-efforts-drc-181202091946851.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMw98LJ2TJkr1Mr9IZT1zbkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 11:49:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/qa-conflict-resistance-hampering-ebola-efforts-drc-181202091946851.html" target="_blank"&gt;Q&amp;A: Conflict, resistance hampering WHO's Ebola efforts in DRC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo is now the second largest in history, according to the World Health Organization (WHO), with at least 426 confirmed cases in the country. The outbreak, declared on August 1, has caused at least 198 confirmed deaths, DR Congo's health ministry said. It is the tenth in DR Congo since Ebola was first detected there in 1976 and centres around the restive eastern city of Beni in North Kivu, a region which has been blighted by armed conflict, which has hampered efforts to curb the outbreak. Al Jazeera spoke to Dr Matshidiso Moeti, Reg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>The Ebola Outbreak In Congo Just Became The Second Largest Ever - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ebola-democratic-republic-congo-outbreak-second-largest_us_5bfdf54be4b0d23c21379bd7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMLkWshziT6Xtc0IoCCsBWoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:09:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ebola-democratic-republic-congo-outbreak-second-largest_us_5bfdf54be4b0d23c21379bd7" target="_blank"&gt;The Ebola Outbreak In Congo Just Became The Second Largest Ever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo is now the second largest in history, according to figures from the World Health Organization. Since the outbreak was declared Aug. 1, 426 people are suspected or confirmed to have been infected with the deadly hemorrhagic virus, which has killed at least 242. “It’s a tragedy because it should be completely preventable, but it’s not,” J. Stephen Morrison told HuffPost. The director of the Global Health Policy Center, a program at the Center for Strategic and International Studies think tank, stressed that, although this outbreak still p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ebola outbreak in east Congo now world's second biggest - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/ebola-outbreak-in-east-congo-now-worlds-second-biggest-idUSKCN1NY2LY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK-5JamtONcnMzoYcZFQhS8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:05:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/ebola-outbreak-in-east-congo-now-worlds-second-biggest-idUSKCN1NY2LY" target="_blank"&gt;Ebola outbreak in east Congo now world's second biggest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ebola outbreak in eastern Congo is now the second biggest in history, with 426 confirmed and probable cases, the health ministry said late on Thursday. The epidemic in a volatile part of Democratic Republic of Congo is now only surpassed by the 2013-2016 outbreak in West Africa, where more than 28,000 cases where confirmed, and is bigger than an outbreak in 2000 in Uganda involving 425 cases. Ebola is believed to have killed 245 people in North Kivu and Ituri provinces where attacks by armed groups and community resistance to health officials have hampered the response. Congo has suffer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>DR Congo Ebola outbreak second largest in history: WHO - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/dr-congo-ebola-outbreak-largest-history-181130052759767.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPBF2EhUEen5jJAAwJmxuGUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 07:18:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/dr-congo-ebola-outbreak-largest-history-181130052759767.html" target="_blank"&gt;DR Congo Ebola outbreak second largest in history: WHO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democratic Republic of Congo's deadly Ebola outbreak is now the second largest in history, behind the devastating West Africa outbreak that killed thousands a few years ago, according to the World Health Organization (WHO). Dr Peter Salama, WHO's emergencies chief, called it a "sad toll" as DR Congo's health ministry announced the number of cases has reached 426. That includes 379 confirmed cases and 47 probable ones. So far this outbreak, declared on August 1, has 198 confirmed deaths, DR Congo's health ministry said. The latest outbreak is the tenth in DR Congo since Ebola was first d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>US Urged to Send Ebola Experts in as Congo Outbreak Worsens - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-urged-to-send-ebola-experts-in-as-congo-outbreak-worsens/4681172.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRH7CKunPwYw0Wph6mr0xAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:14:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-urged-to-send-ebola-experts-in-as-congo-outbreak-worsens/4681172.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Urged to Send Ebola Experts in as Congo Outbreak Worsens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global health experts are urging the Trump administration to allow U.S. government disease specialists to return to northeastern Congo to help fight the second-largest Ebola outbreak in history. The U.S. experts have been sidelined for weeks, ordered away from the region due to State Department security concerns. Health workers have compared the area to a war zone. Dozens of rebel groups are active and attacks by them have forced workers to halt Ebola containment for days at a time. New statements in two top medical journals this week are calling on the U.S. to change its mind and send its ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Congo's Ebola outbreak now 2nd largest in history, WHO says - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/29ade03c23574bd5ac7430f05fd0b977</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHGWYKGqNtqbrMbRynJz3CwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6udAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:39:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/29ade03c23574bd5ac7430f05fd0b977" target="_blank"&gt;Congo's Ebola outbreak now 2nd largest in history, WHO says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Congo's deadly Ebola outbreak is now the second largest in history, behind the devastating West Africa outbreak that killed thousands a few years ago, the World Health Organization said Thursday. WHO's emergencies chief, Dr. Peter Salama, called it a "sad toll" as Congo's health ministry announced the number of cases has reached 426. That includes 379 confirmed cases and 47 probable ones. So far this outbreak, declared on Aug. 1, has 198 confirmed deaths, with another 47 probable ones, Congo's health ministry said. Attacks by rebel groups and open hostility by some wary ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Polio cases no longer declining; WHO fears global resurgence - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/health/polio-who-bn/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPYv3AgdIiWMoxZyiIg5FTkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:55:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/health/polio-who-bn/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Polio cases no longer declining; WHO fears global resurgence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medecins Sans Frontieres (Doctors without Borders) workers in Monrovia, Liberia during the Ebola crisis in 2014. The outbreak raised questions about our ability to handle the spread of deadly diseases. Eradicating diseases entirely is a tougher task. Scroll through to discover more about ten diseases you thought were gone. DOMINIQUE FAGET/AFP/Getty Images In the 19th century, scarlet fever was a common killer in Europe. In 2016, nearly 20,000 cases were reported in the United Kingdom -- the biggest increase in 50 years. Scarlet fever is just one disease that many have forgotten but that is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US urged to send Ebola experts in as Congo outbreak worsens - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/88c7e2893ad44c25a7498796a87013cf</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDywL_YtY0LdDjum_kS5TcsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:59:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/88c7e2893ad44c25a7498796a87013cf" target="_blank"&gt;US urged to send Ebola experts in as Congo outbreak worsens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Global health experts are urging the Trump administration to allow U.S. government disease specialists — "some of the world's most experienced" — to return to northeastern Congo to help fight the second-largest Ebola outbreak in history. The U.S. experts have been sidelined for weeks, ordered away from the region because of State Department security concerns. Two top medical journals this week have published commentaries calling on the U.S. to change its mind and send them back where they are sorely needed. This Ebola outbreak is like no other, with some health workers c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The Most Important Tool For Doctors Fighting DRC's Ebola Crisis Isn't Medicine - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-ebola-drc-trust_us_5bf57664e4b0eb6d930a81e5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECWvdZR47F7bJkhzYy3dGn4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 11:00:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-ebola-drc-trust_us_5bf57664e4b0eb6d930a81e5" target="_blank"&gt;The Most Important Tool For Doctors Fighting DRC's Ebola Crisis Isn't Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;My experience as a public health practitioner has convinced me that a lack of trust has become a critical driver of modern epidemics. We are seeing this unfold right now in the Ebola epidemic raging in the Democratic Republic of the Congo ― an epidemic that has been declared the worst in the country’s history. Trust is the most important part of the doctor-patient relationship. I know that if I lose my patients’ trust, it will be impossible for me to effectively treat them. In order to establish a trusting relationship, I must understand my patients as more than just their diseases—I must u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Ebola outbreak in eastern Congo is second worst in history - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/479105a0-f47f-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB8GDjrTFlJxoWH3D8N7d6MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 10:30:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/479105a0-f47f-11e8-9623-d7f9881e729f" target="_blank"&gt;Ebola outbreak in eastern Congo is second worst in history&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An outbreak of Ebola in a volatile region of eastern Democratic Republic of Congo is now the second worst in history. At least 426 people have been infected with the virus and 245 people have died since August, the country’s health ministry said late on Thursday. “The outbreak in North-Kivu has become the second largest Ebola outbreak in the world, after the one in west Africa,” Olly Illunga Kalenga, minister for health, said. Congo has suffered ten outbreaks of the virus, since it was discovered in 1976 near the Ebola river in the centre of the country. Over the decades, Congolese health o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Gunfire, threats and curfews slow Congo's fight against Ebola - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/gunfire-threats-and-curfews-slow-congos-fight-against-ebola-idUSKCN1NY0H0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjWGay0elxb2_LesTzMe3wqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 06:09:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/gunfire-threats-and-curfews-slow-congos-fight-against-ebola-idUSKCN1NY0H0" target="_blank"&gt;Gunfire, threats and curfews slow Congo's fight against Ebola&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When medics tried to reach Ebola patients in a village in eastern Democratic Republic of Congo during a recent surge in violence, they were blocked by men wielding machetes and axes. Worried about being kidnapped, they turned back, the latest in a series of setbacks in their attempts to contain the central African country's worst outbreak of the deadly virus. As fighting has worsened between rival militia seeking control of land and natural resources, vaccinations and vital treatments have increasingly been delayed and Ebola has spread. The situation has become so dangerous in eastern Congo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Congo Ebola outbreak is 2nd largest, 2nd deadliest - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/health/drc-ebola-update-who-bn/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJjfaiRe9__jGOjFhEh0LVQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 22:02:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/health/drc-ebola-update-who-bn/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Congo Ebola outbreak is 2nd largest, 2nd deadliest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current Ebola epidemic in the Democratic Republic of Congo -- with 426 total cases, including 245 deaths -- is now the second largest and second deadliest in history, according to Thursday's report from the nation's Ministry of Health. A 2000-01 outbreak in Uganda included 425 cases and caused 224 deaths, according to the World Health Organization. The deadliest outbreak occurred in West Africa in 2014, when the disease killed more than 11,000 people. "This is a milestone nobody wanted to hit," WHO spokesman Tarik Jasarevic wrote in an email. On average, Ebola -- which causes fever, sev...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Why the Ebola crisis in DRC is unlike anything before - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/ebola-crisis-drc-181125140426233.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgeP44-mWDUpdcXM2J5IyQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:20:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/ebola-crisis-drc-181125140426233.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why the Ebola crisis in DRC is unlike anything before&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is the worst Ebola outbreak to have struck the Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC) - and the most complex one. Since August, authorities in the country, together with a host of partners, have been trying to contain a new outbreak of the deadly virus in the eastern North Kivu and Ituri provinces. As of November 21, there have been 373 suspected cases of Ebola, including 347 confirmed cases. At least 217 people have already died. There have been 10 outbreaks of Ebola since 1976 in the DRC, which is considered among the most experienced in dealing with the virus. The situation this time, tho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Congo Starts First-Ever Trial Testing Ebola Drugs - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/congo-starts-first-ever-trial-testing-ebola-drugs/4673965.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJYaGPhUYezxiU2i8oXZzTgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:24:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/congo-starts-first-ever-trial-testing-ebola-drugs/4673965.html" target="_blank"&gt;Congo Starts First-Ever Trial Testing Ebola Drugs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congo has begun the first-ever trial to test the effectiveness and safety of four experimental Ebola drugs, the first time scientists have directly compared such treatments, the World Health Organization said Monday. The U.N. health agency described the multi-drug trial as "a giant step" that would "bring clarity about what works best." "While our focus remains on bringing this outbreak to an end, the launch of the randomized control trial in DRC [Congo] is an important step toward finally finding an Ebola treatment that will save lives," said WHO Director-General Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Ebola in Congo Now Infecting Newborn Babies, UN Says - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/ebola-in-congo-now-infecting-newborn-babies-un-says/4670958.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM_WJquJALyNAqnFROktwnYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 14:39:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/ebola-in-congo-now-infecting-newborn-babies-un-says/4670958.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ebola in Congo Now Infecting Newborn Babies, UN Says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization says a worrying number of the newest Ebola cases amid Congo’s ongoing outbreak are in patients not usually known to catch the disease: babies. In an update published this week, the U.N. health agency reported 36 new confirmed cases of Ebola, including seven in newborn babies and infants younger than 2 years old. Six cases were reported in children aged between 2 and 17 and one case was in a pregnant woman. While Ebola typically infects adults, as they are most likely to be exposed to the lethal virus, children have been known in some instances to catch the dise...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Experts hope to save lives with first ever trial of Ebola drugs - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/experts-hope-save-lives-first-ever-trial-ebola-drugs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECF5e8Buc-iSpQuvPc8GBW8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 15:13:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/experts-hope-save-lives-first-ever-trial-ebola-drugs/" target="_blank"&gt;Experts hope to save lives with first ever trial of Ebola drugs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A treatment for Ebola is a step closer with the launch of the first ever clinical trial of experimental drugs during an active outbreak of the disease. Some 160 patients in the Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC) have already been treated with the experimental therapies but a clinical trial will enable researchers to work out which drugs are the most effective. This is the first time therapies have been available during an outbreak of the deadly haemorrhagic fever – previously, health care professionals had only been able to treat the symptoms of the disease. The drugs that will be tested ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>First-of-its-kind Ebola treatment trial underway in Congo as outbreak surpasses 400 cases - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/26/health/ebola-treatment-trial-bn-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMdmlVjy0Z0OJTGVKvvOR2sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 17:50:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/26/health/ebola-treatment-trial-bn-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;First-of-its-kind Ebola treatment trial underway in Congo as outbreak surpasses 400 cases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democratic Republic of Congo has kicked off the world's first multidrug randomized control trial to evaluate the effectiveness and safety of experimental drugs used to treat Ebola patients, the World Health Organization announced Monday. There have been 412 Ebola cases, including 236 deaths, in this outbreak in Congo as of Saturday, according to WHO. Concerns remain that the outbreak could spread into neighboring nations. "While our focus remains on bringing this outbreak to an end, the launch of the randomized control trial in DRC is an important step towards finally finding an Ebola t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Congo health workers face violence as Ebola virus spreads - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/18/health/dr-congo-ebola-cases-deaths-rise/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMxorUDD2M9PmVAMWb0RY2MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 06:47:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/18/health/dr-congo-ebola-cases-deaths-rise/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Congo health workers face violence as Ebola virus spreads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The death toll from the Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo continues to rise as violence hampers health workers' efforts to battle the virus. There are now 358 cases of Ebola and 213 deaths since the outbreak began in August, according to the nation's Ministry of Health. Conflict between militant groups and government forces has made it difficult for health workers to access some of the hardest-hit areas. Operations suspended On Friday evening, an armed group tried to attack UN peacekeepers in the city of Beni in North Kivu province -- the epicenter of the outbreak. The atta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Series of War Zone Attacks Puts DRC Ebola Outbreak On 'Edge of Crisis' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ebola-outbreak-congo-war-zone-crisis_us_5bec59c7e4b0598443d39d62</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHdrBjF1l8VCzpTA01OgtLAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 02:30:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ebola-outbreak-congo-war-zone-crisis_us_5bec59c7e4b0598443d39d62" target="_blank"&gt;Series of War Zone Attacks Puts DRC Ebola Outbreak On 'Edge of Crisis'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― Global public health experts are growing increasingly alarmed about the Ebola outbreak in the northeast region of the Democratic Republic of Congo, which has killed 219 people so far. It is now the largest outbreak that the DRC has ever seen ― with 341 probable and confirmed cases ― and the third largest Ebola outbreak in history. And it’s continuing to expand. While the risk of it spreading globally remains low, the threat for the country and its neighbors is very high. Constant incidents of rebel violence in the war-torn region, the resulting community protests and community ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Outbreak: Ebola spreads to Congolese city of 1.2 million sparking containment fears - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/outbreak-ebola-spreads-congolese-city-12-million-sparking-containment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ3IaBw2Tj2Y7stRII_oeNgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:36:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/0/outbreak-ebola-spreads-congolese-city-12-million-sparking-containment/" target="_blank"&gt;Outbreak: Ebola spreads to Congolese city of 1.2 million sparking containment fears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A surge in new Ebola cases has been reported in a densely populated Congolese city, adding a dangerous dimension to the worst outbreak of the virus in the country’s history. Health workers have been forced to open up a new and particularly perilous front after 28 people died of Ebola in and around Butembo, a city of approximately 1.2 million people that is located in the heart of the country’s most volatile regions. The government of the Democratic Republic of the Congo admitted this week that the country’s tenth Ebola outbreak is now officially its worst ever, after the number of confirmed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>WHO: DRC Ebola Response Efforts Resume in Beni After Clashes - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/who-drc-ebola-response-efforts-resume-in-beni-after-clashes/4663924.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjbQRDcQlBjT9csvXWildUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 22:56:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/who-drc-ebola-response-efforts-resume-in-beni-after-clashes/4663924.html" target="_blank"&gt;WHO: DRC Ebola Response Efforts Resume in Beni After Clashes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Efforts to fight a deadly Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo's restive eastern Beni region have resumed after a brief suspension following clashes, the World Health Organization said Sunday. "On Sunday, all activities have re-launched, including vaccination," the U.N. health agency said in a statement. Congo's health ministry had announced a suspension of operations in Beni after deadly clashes erupted Friday just a "few meters" from a local emergency center and the hotels of several response teams. UN peacekeepers from the MONUSCO mission had repelled an offensive by the Al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Congo starts first-ever trial testing Ebola drugs - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/05114314c9be48cf90306e6826cc223e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGweRsLVrRGkH4ZODFrEvMEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 12:23:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/05114314c9be48cf90306e6826cc223e" target="_blank"&gt;Congo starts first-ever trial testing Ebola drugs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAKAR, Senegal (AP) — Congo has begun the first-ever trial to test the effectiveness and safety of four experimental Ebola drugs, the first time scientists have directly compared such treatments, the World Health Organization said Monday. The U.N. health agency described the multi-drug trial as "a giant step" that would "bring clarity about what works best." "While our focus remains on bringing this outbreak to an end, the launch of the randomized control trial in DRC (Congo) is an important step toward finally finding an Ebola treatment that will save lives," said WHO Director-General Tedr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>U.S. Not Deploying Experts to Ebola Outbreak in Congo - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/us-not-deploying-experts-to-ebola-outbreak-in-congo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhzmZOoi_VoEWnI5MwIGeMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:43:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/us-not-deploying-experts-to-ebola-outbreak-in-congo" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. Not Deploying Experts to Ebola Outbreak in Congo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Wessels/Getty The U.S. has not sent experts to the epicenter of the Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo because of militia attacks and is working with neighboring companies to contain the worsening outbreak, government officials said on Wednesday. The outbreak in the DRC has now become the worst in the country’s history, officials said in a briefing. Nearly 175 people have died from confirmed cases of Ebola, but hundreds more may have succumbed to the hemorrhagic fever, which attacks organs and the immune system. While nine previous Ebola outbreaks in the Congo were cont...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>DRC ebola outbreak will last at least another six months, WHO chief warns - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/ebola-congo-drc-outbreak-latest-world-health-organisation-who-peter-salama-a8632501.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMro7H6bfwlLcwgES9ohy7kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 21:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/ebola-congo-drc-outbreak-latest-world-health-organisation-who-peter-salama-a8632501.html" target="_blank"&gt;DRC ebola outbreak will last at least another six months, WHO chief warns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo that has killed almost 200 people since August will last at least another six months, the World Health Organisation has warned. Emergencies chief Dr Peter Salama said the central African nation's makeshift “tradi-modern” health centres, which offer both traditional and modern treatment were “major drivers” in transmitting the disease. He added that the informal clinics were thought to be linked to more than half of cases in Beni, a city of 800,000 people in the North Kivu region where infections have been concentrated. - Read more Medica...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ebola outbreak worst in history of Democratic Republic of Congo - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/health/ebola-congo-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGhMbK8TmlMlEp-KPlWIlIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/health/ebola-congo-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ebola outbreak worst in history of Democratic Republic of Congo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democratic Republic of Congo is facing the worst Ebola outbreak in the country's history, according to officials. More than 200 people have died from the disease since August and almost 330 confirmed or probable cases have been reported. This outbreak -- the second this year -- began in North Kivu province before spreading to Ituri province in the east of the country. It's the 10th time since 1976 that Ebola has struck the DRC. The country's Minister of Public Health, Oly Ilunga Kalenga, said Sunday that violence against health officials and civilians by militant groups battling for con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Current Ebola outbreak is worst in Congo's history: ministry - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/current-ebola-outbreak-is-worst-in-congos-history-ministry-idUSKCN1NF0BW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFR3eukLmKaDPNerxS6LjeEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 10:14:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/current-ebola-outbreak-is-worst-in-congos-history-ministry-idUSKCN1NF0BW" target="_blank"&gt;Current Ebola outbreak is worst in Congo's history: ministry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo is the most severe in the country's history with 319 confirmed and probable cases, the health ministry said late on Friday. The hemorrhagic fever is believed to have killed 198 people in North Kivu and Ituri provinces, where attacks by armed groups and community resistance to health officials have complicated the response. Congo has suffered 10 Ebola outbreaks since the virus was discovered near the eponymous Ebola River in 1976. "The current epidemic is the worst in the history of DRC," Jessica Ilunga, a spokeswoman for the min...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Deadly Ebola Outbreak Erupts in DRC - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/deadly-ebola-outbreak-erupts-in-drc/4653547.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsbbik3he75XIREYPfy7KoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 05:43:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/deadly-ebola-outbreak-erupts-in-drc/4653547.html" target="_blank"&gt;Deadly Ebola Outbreak Erupts in DRC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An outbreak of Ebola in the eastern region of the Democratic Republic of Congo has killed more than 200 people. Almost 300 Ebola cases have been confirmed since the outbreak began in August, authorities say. The health ministry said half of the cases were in Beni, a city of 800,000 people, in the North Kivu province. The outbreak is in a conflict zone where dozens of armed groups operate. Aid agencies have been forced to suspend or slow down their work on several occasions since the outbreak. Health Minister Oly Ilunga said his response teams "have faced threats, physical assaults, repeated...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>WHO official predicts 6 more months battling Ebola in Congo - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/9a0545eb142e45929cc9da5a9bc69495</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP9igaz8H1F68FYyaoOFzfoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 18:27:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/9a0545eb142e45929cc9da5a9bc69495" target="_blank"&gt;WHO official predicts 6 more months battling Ebola in Congo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (AP) — The emergencies chief for the World Health Organization predicted Tuesday that Congo's Ebola outbreak will last at least another six months, saying that informal health facilities have become "major drivers" of the current, deadly transmission. Dr. Peter Salama said that makeshift "tradi-modern" health centers — offering both traditional and modern treatment — were believed to be linked to more than half of cases in Beni, the largest city affected by the current outbreak that has taken more than 200 lives. Salama, who returned from a trip to Ebola-hit eastern Congo last week, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>DRC says Ebola outbreak worst in country's recorded history - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/drc-ebola-outbreak-worst-country-recorded-history-181110141022940.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECy8c0KC1rX1rSWX-Nn0aEEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 18:04:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/drc-ebola-outbreak-worst-country-recorded-history-181110141022940.html" target="_blank"&gt;DRC says Ebola outbreak worst in country's recorded history&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC) is facing its worst Ebola outbreak in the country's recorded history, health officials have said. The announcement late on Friday came amid increasing warnings that the situation could deteriorate because of attacks by armed groups and community resistance in the affected areas in eastern DRC. Oly Ilunga Kalenga, the DRC's health minister, said a total of 319 confirmed and probable cases have been reported in North Kivu and Ituri provinces since the outbreak was declared in August. The figure exceeds the 318 cases documented in 1976, when the deadly Eb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Seven peacekeepers killed in clashes near Ebola-hit part of east Congo - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-congo-security-idUSKCN1NK2JE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJGzuHLOdp5BThchodyYBgUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 20:59:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-congo-security-idUSKCN1NK2JE" target="_blank"&gt;Seven peacekeepers killed in clashes near Ebola-hit part of east Congo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least seven U.N. peacekeepers were killed in clashes with militias in an area that is at the center of the Democratic Republic of Congo's worst Ebola epidemic, United Nations and diplomatic sources said on Thursday. "Our peacekeeping colleagues tell us that six peacekeepers from Malawi and one from Tanzania who are part of the U.N. peacekeeping operation in the DRC ... were killed yesterday, in Beni territory, in North Kivu," U.N. spokesman Stephane Dujarric told reporters in New York. Eastern Congo has been plagued by banditry and armed insurrections for more than two decades since the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Ebola outbreak: Death toll tops 200 in Democratic Republic of the Congo - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/11/ebola-outbreak-death-toll-tops-200-in-democratic-republic-of-the-congo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBF7ShSu-N5r70a3eboXCVcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 07:13:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/11/ebola-outbreak-death-toll-tops-200-in-democratic-republic-of-the-congo" target="_blank"&gt;Ebola outbreak: Death toll tops 200 in Democratic Republic of the Congo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The death toll from an Ebola outbreak in eastern Democratic Republic of Congo has risen to more than 200. The health ministry said it had recorded 201 deaths from the virus and that 291 cases have been confirmed since the outbreak began in August. About half of the cases were in Beni, a city of 800,000 people, in the North Kivu region. map of the congo The United Nation’s Department of Peacekeeping on Friday called on armed groups active in the region not to hinder efforts to fight the disease. Teams responsible for responding to the outbreak “have faced threats, physical assaults, repeated...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Uganda Readies to Stave Off Ebola Along DRC Border - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/uganda-ebola-drc-border/4653039.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENNWixA-zkoddm_Jvi7kOxkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 17:24:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/uganda-ebola-drc-border/4653039.html" target="_blank"&gt;Uganda Readies to Stave Off Ebola Along DRC Border&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Uganda, officials have stepped up measures to prevent an outbreak of the deadly Ebola virus. Ebola has infected 319 people in the neighboring Democratic Republic of Congo since August, killing 198. The border between the countries remains open, and health experts fear the virus will enter Uganda through the cross-border traffic. The Lamia River marks the border between the Democratic Republic of Congo’s Ebola-infected North Kivu Province and Uganda. Despite the deadly viral outbreak, Uganda’s Health Ministry says 20,000 people cross the border every week, putting the country at high ri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Congo ministry says Ebola outbreak worst in nation's history - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/dc7a3f8608c14766afe634d16563bc4c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMEt6mwlo0F1YIA3ZwAETy8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6udAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 12:18:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/dc7a3f8608c14766afe634d16563bc4c" target="_blank"&gt;Congo ministry says Ebola outbreak worst in nation's history&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KINSHASA, Congo (AP) — Congo's health ministry says the latest Ebola outbreak has now become the worst in the country's recorded history with 319 confirmed and probable cases. The ministry said late Friday that the deadly virus has killed about 198 people since the outbreak was declared Aug. 1 in the volatile east. Those dead include 163 confirmed Ebola cases, with 35 probable deaths. This is Congo's 10th outbreak since 1976, when the hemorrhagic fever was first identified in Yambuku. Health Minister Dr. Oly Ilunga Kalenga said the figures now exceed that outbreak. He said no other epidemic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>In Congo, Ebola outbreak and war spread fear to neighboring nations - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/08/health/drc-ebola-war-congo-uganda-africa/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBXvshc7jmo55-StWADdOhsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 07:41:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/08/health/drc-ebola-war-congo-uganda-africa/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;In Congo, Ebola outbreak and war spread fear to neighboring nations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Uganda is vaccinating against the Ebola virus spreading in neighboring Democratic Republic of the Congo, where the outbreak fueled by conflict has left at least 189 people dead. No cases have been reported in Uganda so far, but health care workers in high-risk districts bordering the Congo are getting vaccinated as a precaution, health officials said. "In vaccinating frontline health workers against Ebola, even before Uganda detects a single case, health authorities are being cautious having learned bitter lessons from previous outbreaks," the World Health Organization said. While the vacci...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Uganda, at high risk for Ebola, starts vaccinating medics - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/76078baf0d494f428887299387892d16</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKDNyCNmHTF0Bf3LXXth0uQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 11:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/76078baf0d494f428887299387892d16" target="_blank"&gt;Uganda, at high risk for Ebola, starts vaccinating medics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KAMPALA, Uganda (AP) — Uganda has started vaccinating health workers against Ebola in a border district near the outbreak in Congo, where the highly infectious viral disease has killed 189 people. The inoculations, using an experimental vaccine, began on Wednesday and are part of a wider Ebola prevention plan in a country that has faced multiple Ebola outbreaks since 2000. In recent months Ebola cases have been confirmed near the heavily traveled border between Uganda and Congo, where 270 cases have been reported in the country's northeast since August. The vaccinations are crucial to stemm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>How To Meet Future Healthcare Challenges: BARDA - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stephenbrozak/2018/11/09/how-to-meet-future-healthcare-challenges-barda/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKmQ8dDn-S2P5vqhM-nP3kcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 15:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/stephenbrozak/2018/11/09/how-to-meet-future-healthcare-challenges-barda/" target="_blank"&gt;How To Meet Future Healthcare Challenges: BARDA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the person who successfully upended the broadcast radio industry model with the launch of Sirius XM satellite radio and then successfully challenged the drug development model to create new drugs for rare diseases now tells you to focus on bio-defense, you better pay attention. So when Dr. Martine Rothblatt PhD, JD, the Founder and CEO of United Therapeutics Corp., appeared as the keynote speaker for BARDA’s Industry Day, it signaled this was not going to be business as usual, even for a government agency that must be ready to combat exotic diseases like Ebola, Zika and Pandemic flu. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Uganda begins Ebola vaccinations amid Congo transmission fears - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-uganda/uganda-begins-ebola-vaccinations-amid-congo-transmission-fears-idUSKCN1N71HX</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEwK35NCV49ll0mWUX6R0h8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 13:16:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-uganda/uganda-begins-ebola-vaccinations-amid-congo-transmission-fears-idUSKCN1N71HX" target="_blank"&gt;Uganda begins Ebola vaccinations amid Congo transmission fears&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Uganda says it will start to vaccinate some of its health workers against Ebola on Monday, amid fears that the viral haemorrhagic fever could spread from Democratic Republic of Congo which is battling an outbreak. The East African country has suffered regular outbreaks of Ebola and Marburg over the years, both high-fatality viral haemorrhagic fevers. Parts of Uganda's western border are about 100 km (62 miles)from sites of an Ebola outbreak taking place in Congo. Health Minister Jane Ruth Aceng said authorities would administer about 2,100 vaccinations covering so called frontline health pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump's Caravan Fearmongering Sounds Just Like His Appalling Ebola Comments - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-trump-ebola-caravan_us_5bdc6378e4b01ffb1d01b0b5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP4fy0Vozjkr9jdIAVD6jEoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:02:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-trump-ebola-caravan_us_5bdc6378e4b01ffb1d01b0b5" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's Caravan Fearmongering Sounds Just Like His Appalling Ebola Comments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s déjà vu, except this time, the divisive, false and fear-stoking rhetoric is coming from the president of the United States ― not just a fringe potential candidate. In November 2014, my birth country of Liberia endured a devastating Ebola epidemic. The virus, which is transmitted through touch and contact with those infected, ripped through the population, infecting over 10,600 and killing more than 4,800 people. Donald Trump, then best known as a reality TV host who had relentlessly pushed the birtherism conspiracy about President Barack Obama, jumped on the issue. But he didn’t interv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>DRC Ebola Death Toll Rises to 164 - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/drc-ebola-death-toll-rises-to-164/4631925.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIJzGgqEroZliIOHm_BkMmIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 23:30:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/drc-ebola-death-toll-rises-to-164/4631925.html" target="_blank"&gt;DRC Ebola Death Toll Rises to 164&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ebola outbreak in eastern Democratic Republic of the Congo has led to 164 deaths, health authorities said. In mid-October, Congolese authorities said they were facing a "second wave" of the outbreak centered on Beni, a town in North Kivu near the border with Uganda. The epicenter had earlier been focused on Mangina, a town about 20 kilometers (12 miles) from Beni. In total, 257 cases had been recorded in the region, of which 222 were confirmed and 35 were probable, since the start of the outbreak at the beginning of August, the Congolese Health Ministry said in a bulletin dated Friday. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>WHO: 'Very Serious' Ebola Situation in Eastern DRC - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/who-very-serious-ebola-situation-in-eastern-drc/4627654.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELuFaHBnc06Bf1SpPB9nUi4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 19:07:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/who-very-serious-ebola-situation-in-eastern-drc/4627654.html" target="_blank"&gt;WHO: 'Very Serious' Ebola Situation in Eastern DRC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Violence in the eastern Democratic Republic of Congo is hampering efforts to contain an Ebola outbreak that has already killed more than 150 people, according to the World Health Organization. "It's a very serious situation. This is something that we have been fearing from the beginning; that the security situation will influence the response to the level that we cannot really function fully," says a WHO spokesman, Tarik Jasarevic. The outbreak in Congo's North Kivu province is in a conflict zone where dozens of armed groups operate. Aid agencies have been forced to suspend or slow down th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Wave of rebel attacks leads to surge in DRC Ebola cases - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/25/wave-of-rebel-attacks-leads-to-surge-in-drc-ebola-cases</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMUWVjCbUvLPsgdqVPyeXWQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 04:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/25/wave-of-rebel-attacks-leads-to-surge-in-drc-ebola-cases" target="_blank"&gt;Wave of rebel attacks leads to surge in DRC Ebola cases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wave of attacks by rebels and militia on health officials fighting the latest Ebola outbreak in Democratic Republic of Congo is leading to a surge in reported cases as the response to the lethal disease weakens. There have been 157 deaths, of which 122 have been confirmed as Ebola cases, in the outbreak, which was declared almost three months ago. The total of probable and confirmed cases has now reached 244, with 63 recovering from infection. The outbreak is centred on the North Kivu and Ituri provinces, both wracked by armed rebellion and ethnic killing since two civil wars in the late ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How heroic doctor stopped the spread of Ebola in Nigeria - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2016/09/15/africa/93-days-nigerian-film-ebola-heroes/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENOvOV4gPSUXMmfolmlJid0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 11:24:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2016/09/15/africa/93-days-nigerian-film-ebola-heroes/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;How heroic doctor stopped the spread of Ebola in Nigeria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Real-life headlines are played out in this thriller as courageous health-care workers in Lagos battle the Ebola outbreak of 2014. Akintola plays the part of the late Dr. Ameyo Adadevoh, who put her life on the line to detain an infected man. Courtesy TIFF A lavish wedding nearly turns into a nightmare after the arrival of uninvited guests in this film produced by Mo Abudu, the CEO of Ebony Life. Courtesy TIFF Izu Ojukwu sets his film at the time of the attempted 1976 military coup against the government of General Murtala Mohammed, and places a love story there. Army officer Captain Joseph ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Deadly attack amid Ebola outbreak stalls containment efforts - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/acc6e8f56636441c923d0b1e8b80517b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJNo-pMWCXLlzLWER81KVN0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 20:55:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/acc6e8f56636441c923d0b1e8b80517b" target="_blank"&gt;Deadly attack amid Ebola outbreak stalls containment efforts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Congolese rebels killed 15 civilians and abducted a dozen children in an attack at the epicenter of the latest deadly Ebola outbreak, Congo's military said Sunday, as the violence again forced crucial virus-containment efforts to be suspended. "It will be very hard to stop the outbreak if this violence continues," said the World Health Organization's emergencies chief, Peter Salama. A regional WHO official told The Associated Press that it was difficult to say how long work would be affected. Confirmed Ebola cases have reached 202 in this outbreak, including 118 deaths. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Health workers in Congo's Ebola outbreak attacked weekly - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f9c8aeb14d6b42eb9293c74fbdc11754</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIxDeB4thVbN10bhHlWsZYwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 21:28:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f9c8aeb14d6b42eb9293c74fbdc11754" target="_blank"&gt;Health workers in Congo's Ebola outbreak attacked weekly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Health teams responding to Congo's latest Ebola outbreak are attacked three or four times a week on average, a level of violence unseen in the country's nine previous outbreaks of the deadly virus, the health ministry said Monday. The coordinator of the outbreak response, Dr. Ndjoloko Tambwe Bathe, spoke to reporters after a weekend marked by deadly rebel attacks and violent protests that suspended Ebola containment efforts in the epicenter of the outbreak. In one attack, two health agents with Congo's military were killed by rebels in the first such deaths since the out...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Deadly violence in DRC hampers Ebola control - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/22/health/drc-violence-ebola-control-africa-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEjVH35r2N4DbDe_gs1URyQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 11:42:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/22/health/drc-violence-ebola-control-africa-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Deadly violence in DRC hampers Ebola control&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fresh round of deadly violence in the Democratic Republic of Congo's North Kivu province -- the epicenter of an Ebola outbreak -- continues to hamper efforts to stamp out the disease. The Congolese Ministry of Health says at least 12 people were killed Saturday and a dozen were kidnapped in the city of Beni after an armed incursion by the Allied Democratic Forces (ADF), a rebel group active in the area. "We condemn this attack. Civilians are #NotaTarget. Everyone should work to achieving peace and fight Ebola," said Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus, the World Health Organization Director-Genera...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Congo rebels shoot two health workers fighting Ebola outbreak within DRC army - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/ebola-outbreak-health-workers-rebels-shot-drc-army-democratic-republic-of-congo-butembo-mai-mai-a8594356.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbb01O5V5plt3p4QxTWQmsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 10:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/ebola-outbreak-health-workers-rebels-shot-drc-army-democratic-republic-of-congo-butembo-mai-mai-a8594356.html" target="_blank"&gt;Congo rebels shoot two health workers fighting Ebola outbreak within DRC army&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democratic Republic of Congo's health minister declared it a "dark day" for everyone fighting the deadly Ebola outbreak after rebels shot and killed two medical agents with the Congolese army. It appeared to be the first time health workers have been killed by rebels in this outbreak, which is taking place in what has been compared to a war zone. Multiple rebel groups are active in Congo's far north east. - Read more Ebola outbreak 'kills at least 34 in Democratic Republic of Congo' Mai Mai rebels surged from the forest and opened fire on the unarmed agents with the army's rapid interve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Congo's Ebola outbreak to worsen without stepped-up response - WHO committee - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/congos-ebola-outbreak-to-worsen-without-stepped-up-response-who-committee-idUSKCN1MR2QC</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENiu1AQsAL0OMGyj7_gOl-YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 16:34:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/congos-ebola-outbreak-to-worsen-without-stepped-up-response-who-committee-idUSKCN1MR2QC" target="_blank"&gt;Congo's Ebola outbreak to worsen without stepped-up response - WHO committee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ebola outbreak in Democratic Republic of Congo is likely to worsen significantly unless the response to it is stepped up, an emergency committee of experts convened by the World Health Organization said on Wednesday. However, it does not yet constitute a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC), the emergency committee said. "The government of the Democratic Republic of Congo, WHO, and partners must intensify the current response. Without this, the situation is likely to deteriorate significantly," the committee said in a statement. There have been 139 deaths and 215 pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Congo Ebola outbreak not an 'emergency of international concern,' WHO says - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/17/health/who-ebola-outbreak-not-emergency/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDHSWJBI10qqKU3-B54cXWUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:52:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/17/health/who-ebola-outbreak-not-emergency/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Congo Ebola outbreak not an 'emergency of international concern,' WHO says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ongoing outbreak of Ebola in the Democratic Republic of Congo does not meet the criteria for a public health emergency of international concern, the World Health Organization said Wednesday. Since the outbreak began August 1, there have been 216 cases of Ebola including 139 deaths, according to WHO. Fifty-seven patients have recovered from the illness, the nation's Ministry of Health reported Tuesday. "We do have some optimism that this outbreak, just like the one in May, will be brought under control in reasonable time," Robert Steffen, chairman of the WHO International Health Regulati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>WHO: Ebola in DRC Is Not a Global Health Emergency - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-ebola-outbreak-is-worrying-but-not-a-global-emergency/4617798.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDH9KErL7i1IMUrR69eQca4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:25:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-ebola-outbreak-is-worrying-but-not-a-global-emergency/4617798.html" target="_blank"&gt;WHO: Ebola in DRC Is Not a Global Health Emergency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An emergency committee convened by the World Health Organization has decided that the Ebola outbreak in eastern Democratic Republic of the Congo does not constitute a public health emergency of international concern. The WHO said Wednesday that 216 cases of Ebola and 139 deaths had been reported, and its International Health Regulations Emergency Committee said the outbreak was a matter of serious concern, especially since it is occurring in an area of conflict in eastern DRC. It said this posed problems for health workers who need to move around freely and track people who are infected wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Latest Ebola Outbreak Not An International Emergency, World Health Organization Says - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ebola-public-health-emergency-international-concern-congo-who_us_5bc7540fe4b0d38b58743561</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAurByZsvDb38H2CYcUH06AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 17:44:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/ebola-public-health-emergency-international-concern-congo-who_us_5bc7540fe4b0d38b58743561" target="_blank"&gt;Latest Ebola Outbreak Not An International Emergency, World Health Organization Says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization on Wednesday decided not to declare the ongoing Ebola outbreak in the war-torn northeastern region of the Democratic Republic of Congo an international health emergency. This Ebola outbreak, the seventh largest in history, with 216 cases and 139 dead since July, has seen a sharp uptick in cases in the last few days after response efforts were limited by rebel violence, political instability and community resistance. The WHO’s emergency response chief, Peter Salama, previously told HuffPost that this has been the “most difficult context” for dealing with an Ebol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>DRC rebels kill 13, abduct a dozen children in Ebola epicentre - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/drc-rebels-kill-13-abduct-dozen-children-ebola-epicentre-181021093953689.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELZiINnAbr6WjxcGhCiWdGEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 10:57:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/drc-rebels-kill-13-abduct-dozen-children-ebola-epicentre-181021093953689.html" target="_blank"&gt;DRC rebels kill 13, abduct a dozen children in Ebola epicentre&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congolese rebels have killed 13 civilians and abducted a dozen children in an attack at the centre of the latest deadly Ebola outbreak, the Democratic Republic of the Congo's (DRC) military said. The Allied Democratic Forces rebels attacked Congolese army positions and several neighbourhoods of Beni in the DRC on Saturday and into Sunday, a senior army official told The Associated Press. The rebels have killed hundreds of civilians in recent years and are just one of several rebel groups active in the DRC's far northeast. Child kidnappings for ransom are a relatively new phenomenon the Nort...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>UN: Ebola outbreak is worrying but not a global emergency - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f0f7342b9ea54fdda8dc9e3be313273f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjyqPF_hJPShVqwSYMnAAwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f0f7342b9ea54fdda8dc9e3be313273f" target="_blank"&gt;UN: Ebola outbreak is worrying but not a global emergency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (AP) — The World Health Organization says it is "deeply concerned" by the ongoing Ebola outbreak in Congo but the situation does not yet warrant being declared a global emergency. After convening an expert group to assess the epidemic on Wednesday, the U.N. health agency said "response activities need to be intensified and ongoing vigilance is critical." Aid organizations have expressed alarm as the rate of new Ebola cases more than doubled this month and resistance to efforts to stop the virus has turned violent. WHO has warned the risk of Ebola spreading in the region is "very high...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Congo Rebels Kill 15, Abduct Kids in Ebola Outbreak Region - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/rebels-kill-congolese-army-health-workers-fighting-ebola/4622429.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBK7bvKsu8cQBCN3nq47PmgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 01:48:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/rebels-kill-congolese-army-health-workers-fighting-ebola/4622429.html" target="_blank"&gt;Congo Rebels Kill 15, Abduct Kids in Ebola Outbreak Region&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congolese rebels killed 15 civilians and abducted a dozen children in an attack at the center of the latest deadly Ebola outbreak, Congo’s military said Sunday, as the violence threatened to again force the suspension of crucial virus containment efforts. The Allied Democratic Forces rebels attacked Congolese army positions and several neighborhoods of Beni on Saturday and into Sunday, Capt. Mak Hazukay Mongha told The Associated Press. The U.N. peacekeeping mission said its troops exchanged fire with rebels on Saturday in the Mayangose area of Beni during an attack on civilians. Angry over...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>WHO Convenes Emergency Meeting on Congo's Ebola Outbreak - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/congo-ebola/4615305.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPRqTeKk5HbdoaCx-5-v0Y4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 04:41:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/congo-ebola/4615305.html" target="_blank"&gt;WHO Convenes Emergency Meeting on Congo's Ebola Outbreak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization says it is convening a meeting on Wednesday to determine whether Congo's latest Ebola outbreak constitutes a public health emergency of international concern. Aid organizations have expressed alarm as the rate of new cases has more than doubled this month and community resistance to Ebola containment efforts in some cases has turned violent. This is Congo's tenth Ebola outbreak but this is the first time the deadly virus has appeared in the far northeast, an area of active rebel attacks that health workers have compared to a war zone. WHO recently said the risk...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>WHO to meet on Congo's Ebola outbreak as toll soars - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/who-to-meet-on-congos-ebola-outbreak-as-toll-soars-idUSKCN1MP1TB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDO3vTmiIAx6kOho_A--xMQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 22:49:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo/who-to-meet-on-congos-ebola-outbreak-as-toll-soars-idUSKCN1MP1TB" target="_blank"&gt;WHO to meet on Congo's Ebola outbreak as toll soars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization (WHO) said on Monday it would convene an emergency committee to decide whether Congo's Ebola outbreak is a public health emergency of international concern as confirmed cases and deaths from the virus spiraled. The committee of experts may make recommendations to manage the outbreak, which was declared on Aug. 1 and has worsened, with a risk of the virus spreading from northeastern Democratic Republic of Congo into Uganda and Rwanda. Congo's health ministry said on Monday that in the past week alone 33 people were confirmed with Ebola virus and 24 of them died....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Children in Ebola-Affected DRC Return to School - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/children-in-ebola-affected-dr-congo-return-to-school/4612844.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAtFDzGTjKGS-4qlr2Uk1-oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 13:28:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/children-in-ebola-affected-dr-congo-return-to-school/4612844.html" target="_blank"&gt;Children in Ebola-Affected DRC Return to School&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N. children's fund reports the vast majority of children living in Ebola-affected areas of eastern Democratic Republic of Congo have returned to school where they are taught ways to avoid infection. School began one month ago in Democratic Republic of Congo. The U.N. children's fund says efforts to get children to return to school in Ebola-affected areas in conflict-ridden eastern DRC have been hugely successful. It says 80 percent are attending schools in Beni and Mabalako health zones. They are the epicenters of the current Ebola outbreak, which was declared August 1 in North Kivu ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>DR Congo: Ebola claims 24 lives in one week - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/dr-congo-ebola-claims-24-lives-week-181016061932750.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECXmSWZgySrzrXuQt-QQHkQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 07:24:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/dr-congo-ebola-claims-24-lives-week-181016061932750.html" target="_blank"&gt;DR Congo: Ebola claims 24 lives in one week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 33 people have been infected with the deadly Ebola virus in the past week, 24 of which have since passed away, the health ministry of the Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC) said. According the ministry, the cases were discovered between October 8 and October 14. So far, 211 confirmed and probable cases of Ebola have been reported since early July, when the latest outbreak of the disease started, the World Health Organization (WHO) has said. Of those, 138 people have passed away from the highly deadly hemorrhagic fever. All cases have been found in the northeastern region of the cen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Battles Over Safe Ebola Burials Complicate Work in DRC - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/battles-over-safe-ebola-burials-complicate-work-in-drc/4612691.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP_JTXovckAqYN9xRz4ydfYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 00:41:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/battles-over-safe-ebola-burials-complicate-work-in-drc/4612691.html" target="_blank"&gt;Battles Over Safe Ebola Burials Complicate Work in DRC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A runaway hearse carrying an Ebola victim has become the latest example of sometimes violent community resistance complicating efforts to contain a Congo outbreak — and causing a worrying new rise in cases. The deadly virus' appearance for the first time in the far northeast has sparked fear. Suspected contacts of infected people have tried to slip away. Residents have assaulted health teams. The rate of new Ebola cases has more than doubled since the start of this month, experts say. Safe burials are particularly sensitive as some outraged family members reject the intervention of health w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Corpse of Ebola victim stolen by relatives during funeral procession in Congo - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/441204-ebola-corpse-stolen-congo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIGyH1mdWzLqPF1d3sZsoEEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 08:04:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/441204-ebola-corpse-stolen-congo/" target="_blank"&gt;Corpse of Ebola victim stolen by relatives during funeral procession in Congo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bereaved relatives pulled off a daring plot to hijack a hearse and steal the body of a deceased Ebola victim in the Democratic Republic of the Congo, as an outbreak of the deadly virus ravages the nation. According to the health ministry, the body belonged to a woman who died earlier at the Beni Ebola Treatment Center, located in the northeastern part of the country. The bodies of Ebola victims require proper burials in order to prevent the highly contagious disease from spreading. However, the woman’s relatives managed to convince the response team to relax the protocols and allow the hear...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>AP Explains: Why Congo's latest Ebola outbreak is worrying - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/cfb44014d7e94b458006cc627398050c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOaT14Jge8ODWU7ceHbtOgAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:16:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/cfb44014d7e94b458006cc627398050c" target="_blank"&gt;AP Explains: Why Congo's latest Ebola outbreak is worrying&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — The World Health Organization has announced that Congo's latest outbreak of the deadly Ebola virus is not yet considered a global health emergency. Some aid groups expressed alarm when the rate of new cases more than doubled this month. With the area compared to a war zone, resistance to health workers sometimes turning violent and confirmed cases found near the heavily traveled Ugandan border, the risk of regional spread is "very high." Here's a look at the outbreak that has had 185 confirmed cases, including 107 deaths, since it was declared on Aug. 1. ___ WHAT IS EBOL...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>First US case of rat-sourced virus from the Andes reported - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/18/health/first-andes-virus-case-report/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELoKNoNUKqdc62hT6h8iaSQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 17:43:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/18/health/first-andes-virus-case-report/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;First US case of rat-sourced virus from the Andes reported&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medecins Sans Frontieres (Doctors without Borders) workers in Monrovia, Liberia during the Ebola crisis in 2014. The outbreak raised questions about our ability to handle the spread of deadly diseases. Eradicating diseases entirely is a tougher task. Scroll through to discover more about ten diseases you thought were gone. DOMINIQUE FAGET/AFP/Getty Images In the 19th century, scarlet fever was a common killer in Europe. In 2016, nearly 20,000 cases were reported in the United Kingdom -- the biggest increase in 50 years. Scarlet fever is just one disease that many have forgotten but that is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item></channel></rss>