<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Apple - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIAgKIhpDQkFTRFFvSEwyMHZNR3M0ZWhJQ1pXNG9BQVAB?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:31:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Apple Loop: Poor iPhone Sales Frighten Apple, Frustrating iPhone 5G Delay, Huge iPhone XR Price Cut - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/apple-news-headlines-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-iphone-xr-discount-5g-airpods/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJnlWej_IG0szwozRXTPvhQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/apple-news-headlines-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-iphone-xr-discount-5g-airpods/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Loop: Poor iPhone Sales Frighten Apple, Frustrating iPhone 5G Delay, Huge iPhone XR Price Cut&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at another week of news from Cupertino, this week’s Apple Loop includes Apple’s response to falling iPhone sales, no 5G for next year’s iPhone, the return of TouchID, no new AirPods for Christmas, the first official iPhone XR cover, and the legend of the Apple Store. Apple Loop is here to remind you of a few of the very many discussions that have happened around Apple over the last seven days (and you can read my weekly digest of Android news here on Forbes). iPhone XR’s $300 Discount Apple continues to react to the low sales of the iPhone with decisions that feel more pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Watch heart features finally arrive, allowing people to take ECGs on their wrist - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/apple-watch-series-4-heart-features-release-ecg-wrist-a8673061.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGMIqyDedGr2ID-ZFedgrzsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/apple-watch-series-4-heart-features-release-ecg-wrist-a8673061.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Watch heart features finally arrive, allowing people to take ECGs on their wrist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Apple Watch's long promised heart features have finally arrived on people's watches. When the Series 4 was announced in September, the company said that it would let people take ECGs and see if their heartbeat is irregular. But it would not be available straight away because it had to be approved by regulators, it said at the time. Now the features have been given clearance by the US Food and Drug Administration and so will finally be available, arriving through a software update. The ECG and atrial fibrillation features are not yet available outside the US, including in the UK. A numbe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Australia Passes World’s First Encryption-Busting Law - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/australia-passes-worlds-first-encryption-busting-law/4692133.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP7BnH174EYF5IVYGfVmOB8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwip0i</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:28:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/australia-passes-worlds-first-encryption-busting-law/4692133.html" target="_blank"&gt;Australia Passes World’s First Encryption-Busting Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Security agencies will gain greater access to encrypted messages under new laws in Australia. The legislation will force technology companies such as Apple, Facebook and Google to disable encryption protections to allow investigators to track the communications of terrorists and other criminals. It is, however, a controversial measure. Australian law enforcement officials say the growth of end-to-end encryption in applications such as Signal, Facebook’s WhatsApp and Apple’s iMessage hamper their efforts to track the activities of criminals and extremists. End-to-end encryption is a code tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Google’s Pixel Slate: Great Chromebook, not-so-great iPad/Surface rival - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90272364/googles-pixel-slate-great-chromebook-not-so-great-ipad-surface-rival</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHEukDmmvBBRCMQzQw3xFwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 06:00:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90272364/googles-pixel-slate-great-chromebook-not-so-great-ipad-surface-rival" target="_blank"&gt;Google’s Pixel Slate: Great Chromebook, not-so-great iPad/Surface rival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since their 2011 launch, Chromebooks have been synonymous with low-cost, easily managed laptops that have strong appeal for education. But in 2013, when Google shipped the first Chromebook Pixel–a premium machine with a touchscreen–it became clear that the company was intent on exploring new frontiers for its browser-centric Chrome OS operating system. Google’s new Pixel Slate tablet, which starts at $599, represents the culmination of those efforts. With its minimalist operating system and minimalist form factor, it’s the best pure web tablet ever made. But the Pixel Slate also offers the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Apple buys British music business Platoon - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/07/apple-buys-british-music-business-platoon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARlNRS0QbN6mw7VKsNQ47AqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:18:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/07/apple-buys-british-music-business-platoon/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple buys British music business Platoon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple has acquired Platoon, a British business which provides support for emerging musicians. A source close to Apple confirmed on Friday that the technology giant has purchased the London-headquartered artists and repertoire company set up by technology investor Saul Klein and music industry veteran Denzyl Feigelson in 2016. The deal, first reported by Music Business Worldwide, will see Apple increase the amount of support that it can offer to new musicians using the business’ Apple Music streaming service. Platoon has hired 12 staff to help emerging artists produce videos as well as to re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Snip, snip: Morgan Stanley latest to cut Apple target on China woes - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/cc64bbcc-fa2f-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHvfyuM0NnrZQOunEFYOEcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:20:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/cc64bbcc-fa2f-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Snip, snip: Morgan Stanley latest to cut Apple target on China woes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Apple price cut club welcomed a new member on Friday after Morgan Stanley blamed the Chinese smartphone market for weakening the outlook for iPhone sales. Flattening iPhone sales have stoked concerns on Wall Street that consumer demand has peaked for Apple’s most important device. In September, the tech giant offered a weaker than expected forecast for the holiday quarter and said it would no longer offer a quarterly breakdown of sales for each of its devices. Meanwhile, key iPhone suppliers have lowered financial guidance, and the Wall Street Journal reported last month that Apple redu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>This was the hottest app trend of the year - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-was-the-hottest-app-trend-of-the-year-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKH29I3-FLi2Bb9RtKaV4dUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwuJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-was-the-hottest-app-trend-of-the-year-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;This was the hottest app trend of the year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MONEYISH By Nicole Lyn Pesce Self-care apps topped Apple’s 2018 trends list, as consumers spent $32 million on mindfulness apps like Calm, Headspace and 10% Happier Self-care apps teaching meditation and mindfulness are the year’s top trend. Stígur Már Karlsson /Heimsmyndir/iStock Apps were all about inner peace in 2018. Apple named “self-care” its app trend of the year with its Best of 2018 list released earlier this week, which highlighted what apps, games, movies and music were on everyone’s list — and fingertips — over the past year. “We became mindful of some amazing wellness apps,” th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Apple Watch Series 4 ECG Heart Rate Feature Now Live: Here's All You Need To Know - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/06/apple-watch-series-4-ecg-heart-rate-feature-now-live-heres-all-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAlRVOTHtRoY0CHY8C7bdzMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/06/apple-watch-series-4-ecg-heart-rate-feature-now-live-heres-all-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Watch Series 4 ECG Heart Rate Feature Now Live: Here's All You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Apple launched the latest Apple Watch Series 4 on September 12, one of the most exciting features is the capability to take ECG (electrocardiogram, also known as EKG) readings from your wrist. Apple Watch Series 4 now boasts the ECG feature But it had only just been cleared by the FDA, so the software needed more work before it could go live. The company said that it would happen this year but no date was given. It was the subject of much debate. It’s just gone live. It is currently limited to Apple Watches that have been bought and are being used in the U.S., and further locations wil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here's how the Apple Watch's heart monitor works - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/05/apple-watch-ecg-app-health-review.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENgBvHpaTyOqY49JFQXWsbMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:37:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/05/apple-watch-ecg-app-health-review.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;Here's how the Apple Watch's heart monitor works&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN's Dr. Sanjay Gupta explains how to use Apple Watch's built-in ECG monitor. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Apple iOS 12.1.1 Release: Should You Upgrade? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/apple-ios-12-1-1-release-should-you-upgrade-iphone-ipad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA2IbpHUN-xKiY3NEWnMlBcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/apple-ios-12-1-1-release-should-you-upgrade-iphone-ipad/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple iOS 12.1.1 Release: Should You Upgrade?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While iOS 12.1 left a gaping security hole in the lockscreen, it was otherwise a very solid update which eliminated some pretty fundamental (and also ridiculous) flaws from previous releases. Apple has now released iOS 12.1.1 and it’s an important upgrade, but is it bug-free? Here’s everything you need to know… Apple iOS 12 Who Is It For? iOS 12.1.1 is compatible with all iOS 11 compatible devices. This means the iPhone 5S or later, iPad mini 2 or later and 6th generation iPod touch or later. Compatible devices will be automatically prompted to upgrade but, if that doesn’t happen, you can ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple's New iPhones Have An Expensive Secret - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/apple-iphone-xs-max-xr-price-cut-cost-discount-reduction-upgrade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFfFBgkdrV5Hzgcm_L69zJIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/06/apple-iphone-xs-max-xr-price-cut-cost-discount-reduction-upgrade/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple's New iPhones Have An Expensive Secret&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple may have quietly begun to cut iPhone prices, but it may just be the start. A new report reveals much bigger price cuts appear inevitable if the company hopes to boost interest in the iPhone XS (details), iPhone XS Max (details) and iPhone XR (details)… Picked up by Business Insider, news has broken today that iPhone camera lens maker Largan Precision has reported a jaw-dropping 29% fall in November revenue compared to the same period last year (the new iPhones went on sale in September). And the blowback on Apple may have expensive consequences. Apple’s iPhone XS, iPhone XS Max and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Australia Anti-Encryption Law Rushed to Passage - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/australia-anti-encryption-law-rushed-to-passage-/4691654.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZmojCUjsbJk6GfmdhBwVUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/australia-anti-encryption-law-rushed-to-passage-/4691654.html" target="_blank"&gt;Australia Anti-Encryption Law Rushed to Passage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A newly enacted law rushed through Australia's parliament will compel technology companies such as Apple, Facebook and Google to disable encryption protections so police can better pursue terrorists and other criminals. Cybersecurity experts say the law, the first of its kind globally, will instead be a boon to the criminal underworld by undermining the technical integrity of the internet, hurting digital security and user privacy. "I think it's detrimental to Australian and world security,'' said Bruce Schneier, a tech security expert affiliated with Harvard University and IBM. The law is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Dr. Sanjay Gupta tests the Apple Watch's new ECG heart monitor - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/health/apple-watch-ecg-app-review/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJTbWVIx4IPkdeGn1nlhA5UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:12:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/health/apple-watch-ecg-app-review/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Sanjay Gupta tests the Apple Watch's new ECG heart monitor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the Apple Watch Series 4 was announced in September, one of its most anticipated functions has been the promise to perform a mobile electrocardiogram (ECG or EKG) whenever a consumer wants. The feature becomes available in the United States on Thursday via a software update. This new ECG app represents a big venture into health for Apple. The company's ambition is for Apple and health to become as closely linked as Apple and music. It even produced a commercial featuring people who say the Apple Watch has helped them lead healthier lives. Apple says its new ECG application and the abi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>How Rapidly Declining NAND And DRAM Prices Could Benefit Apple - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/12/06/how-rapidly-declining-nand-and-dram-prices-could-benefit-apple/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM53eTMLe5hyCxdj2LIU_bcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/12/06/how-rapidly-declining-nand-and-dram-prices-could-benefit-apple/" target="_blank"&gt;How Rapidly Declining NAND And DRAM Prices Could Benefit Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pedestrians walk past an Apple Inc. store in Shanghai, China, on Tuesday, Nov. 27, 2018. Photographer: Qilai Shen/Bloomberg Apple is poised to see its growth slow down over 2019, amid a mixed response to its latest iPhone XR and XS models and increasing saturation in the smartphone market. That said, Apple could see tailwinds from fast-declining prices for both DRAM and NAND memory, which form a significant cost component for the company. In this note, we take a look at the potential impact of the declining memory prices on Apple’s margins using the iPhone XS Max (256 GB), likely one of App...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Broadcom earnings beat on strong demand for data center products - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-broadcom-results/broadcom-earnings-beat-on-strong-demand-for-data-center-products-idUSKBN1O52I0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELlyfPcDl_V1K6g8JGOVf0oqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:43:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-broadcom-results/broadcom-earnings-beat-on-strong-demand-for-data-center-products-idUSKBN1O52I0" target="_blank"&gt;Broadcom earnings beat on strong demand for data center products&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Broadcom Inc (AVGO.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) on Thursday reported quarterly revenue and profit above analysts' estimates, driven by strong demand for its enterprise storage and networking products from data centers, sending its shares up 5 percent in extended trading. The chipmaker also forecast better-than-expected full-year revenue and said it would not be giving quarterly guidance going forward. Chief Executive Officer Hock Tan said the first quarter of fiscal 2019 is expected to be "okay", in response to an analyst's question during the company's post-earnings call. Tan s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Tech companies slam new Australian law allowing police to spy on smartphones - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/tech/australia-encryption-law-passes-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAqUOnKbM5GYupjOfVGUYsEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:47:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/tech/australia-encryption-law-passes-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tech companies slam new Australian law allowing police to spy on smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook and other tech companies are warning about the privacy risks from a new Australian law that gives government agencies the power to demand access to encrypted messaging services such as iMessage and WhatsApp. Lawmakers voted in favor of the Telecommunications Access and Assistance Bill late Thursday. The government argues the new measures will help police and security agencies combat serious offenses such as terrorist attacks and child sex crimes. But tech companies and civil liberties groups say it's a dangerous overreach that will affect a wide range of businesses and their custom...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Why 40% iPhone Discount Is Bad For Apple - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/petercohan/2018/12/06/why-40-iphone-discount-is-bad-for-apple/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPGDTNFIdPidc20ik9tLfkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/petercohan/2018/12/06/why-40-iphone-discount-is-bad-for-apple/" target="_blank"&gt;Why 40% iPhone Discount Is Bad For Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KIEV, UKRAINE – 2018/10/06: Apple co-founder Steve Jobs portrait is seen with price list of Apple iPhone mobile phones in his hands, next to a mobile phone shop in down town. (Photo by Pavlo Gonchar/SOPA Images/LightRocket via Getty Images) Apple shares have fallen 26% from their October 2018 high and they’re poised to fall further. You can argue that Apple’s decline is due to factors beyond its control. For example, the White House threatened to endanger Apple by putting it in the cross-hairs of its China trade war. But a Bloomberg report that Apple is offering a 40% discount on the iPhone...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Australia passes bill to force tech firms to hand over encrypted data - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-security-data/australia-passes-bill-to-force-tech-firms-to-hand-over-encrypted-data-idUSKBN1O42SR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZB9TPV2_WSRBvZcxdNZ2QqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:17:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-security-data/australia-passes-bill-to-force-tech-firms-to-hand-over-encrypted-data-idUSKBN1O42SR" target="_blank"&gt;Australia passes bill to force tech firms to hand over encrypted data&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia's parliament on Thursday passed a bill to force tech firms such as Alphabet Inc's Google (GOOGL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), Facebook FB.N and Apple (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) to give police access to encrypted data, the most far-reaching such requirements imposed by a western country. The bill, staunchly opposed by the tech giants which fear Australia could be an example as other nations explore similar rules, is set to become law before the end of the year. "Let's just make Australians safe over Christmas," opposition Labor party leader Bill Shor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>More Bad News From Apple As iPhone XR Price Slashed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/apple-iphone-xr-discount-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-price-sale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEABRDM_nzBTtK33HlXkv86sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/05/apple-iphone-xr-discount-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-price-sale/" target="_blank"&gt;More Bad News From Apple As iPhone XR Price Slashed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding to the signs that the newest iPhones are not meeting Apple’s internal sales targets, let alone the lofty ambitions of significantly increasing the annual sales of the iOS-powered smartphones, details of the actions taken by Tim Cook’s team to boost sales have come to light. Tim Cook, CEO of Apple speaks while unveiling new products during a launch event at the Brooklyn Academy of Music on October 30, 2018 (Photo by Stephanie Keith/Getty Images) Writing for Bloomberg, Mark Gurman notes on an increase in carrier subsidies, an increase in bundled extras, and now an almost unheard of $30...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple MacBook Air review: the new default Mac - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/04/apple-macbook-air-review-the-new-default-mac</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO48qy8Te3PCWFKIIt-Q7UoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 06:00:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/04/apple-macbook-air-review-the-new-default-mac" target="_blank"&gt;Apple MacBook Air review: the new default Mac&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple has finally given the MacBook Air the update fans have been craving for the last three years: new processors and a vastly improved Retina display. But is this the new Mac laptop for most people or has it lost some of the desirability and shine while stagnating since 2015? When closed, the new MacBook Air looks pretty much the same as the old one. The aluminium frame is still wedge-shaped. It still has the cut-out in the deck to lift the screen and still has the Apple logo emblazoned on the lid, even if it is now metallic and shiny rather than being light-up opaque plastic. Like a wedg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>It’s Apple vs. the cloud in race to be the world’s most valuable tech company - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/its-apple-vs-the-cloud-in-race-to-be-the-worlds-most-valuable-tech-company-2018-12-04</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1WfaIBA9HcsxNzxEojShQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 22:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/its-apple-vs-the-cloud-in-race-to-be-the-worlds-most-valuable-tech-company-2018-12-04" target="_blank"&gt;It’s Apple vs. the cloud in race to be the world’s most valuable tech company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERESE POLETTI'S TECH TALES By Therese Poletti Microsoft and Amazon are challenging Apple for top spot, and Google isn’t far behind In Tuesday trading, Microsoft and Apple were trading the market-cap lead back and forth as Amazon remained close and Google brought up the rear. MarketWatch photo illustration/Getty Images, iStockphoto, Bloomberg After nearly a decade of Apple Inc. dominance, there is an evolving four-way race among the top tech giants that is pitting the cash cow against a trio of cloud-computing colossuses. On Friday, Microsoft Corp. (MSFT) (MSFT) (MSFT) ended the week as th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Forget Zuckerberg – the tech giants don’t have to own the future - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/05/zuckerberg-tech-giants-facebook-google-apple</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAgjunQtDiT3ksDF1nlxDb8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 06:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/05/zuckerberg-tech-giants-facebook-google-apple" target="_blank"&gt;Forget Zuckerberg – the tech giants don’t have to own the future&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A quarter of a century ago, the Canadian author Douglas Coupland published his third novel. Microserfs was the tale of a group of young Microsoft employees who decide to exit the realm of Bill Gates in Washington state and chase a dream of their own in California places that, back then, sounded like the epitome of futuristic magic: Palo Alto, Menlo Park. As well as prescient flashes of the world to come – “Beware of the corporate invasion of private memory,” warned one of its protagonists – what always stuck with me was its air of techno-optimism, perfectly crystallised right at the end, wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Apple Releases iOS 12.1.1: Details About The New Features You Should Know About - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/12/05/apple-releases-ios-12-1-1-details-about-the-new-features-you-should-know-about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2uY1syWRfkIyQGWJz-susqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/amitchowdhry/2018/12/05/apple-releases-ios-12-1-1-details-about-the-new-features-you-should-know-about/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Releases iOS 12.1.1: Details About The New Features You Should Know About&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;iOS 12 screenshot Today Apple released the iOS 12.1.1 update for the iPhone and iPad with several new features and bug fixes. Apple had rolled out three betas for developers before releasing it to the public today. What Is Included In The iOS 12.1.1 Update? As iOS 12.1.1 is a minor point update, it contains several new subtle features and bug fixes. Here is a breakdown of what is included in the update: For the iPhone XR, notification preview using Haptic Touch is now supported. Apple integrated Haptic Touch on the iPhone XR instead of 3D Touch. The iPhone XS and XS Max both have 3D Touch s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple's Own iPhone XR Case Revealed At Last: Here's All You Need To Know - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/05/apples-own-iphone-xr-case-revealed-at-last-heres-all-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG3mDSkm5XBmXVuXwd2agPYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/05/apples-own-iphone-xr-case-revealed-at-last-heres-all-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple's Own iPhone XR Case Revealed At Last: Here's All You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Apple iPhone XR is one of the most beautiful phones you can buy. You can read my review of it here. The new clear iPhone XR cases on all six of the colors. It’s also one of the most colorful. So, how can you clad it in a case without disguising its beauty, whether you’ve chosen the especially gorgeous yellow, the deeply attractive coral, the calming blue, the feisty PRODUCT(RED), the snowy-simple white or the enigmatic space gray? You can read my round-up of the best cases here but you’ll see that Apple hasn’t made a single one of them. Well, today Apple finally revealed its own Apple-m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>OnePlus to make first 5G phone in Europe with EE, company claims - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/oneplus-5g-phone-ee-bt-qualcomm-faster-internet-connection-network-a8669226.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPiYCwu5P2Fo3VR-FvNzilMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/oneplus-5g-phone-ee-bt-qualcomm-faster-internet-connection-network-a8669226.html" target="_blank"&gt;OnePlus to make first 5G phone in Europe with EE, company claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OnePlus is going to make the first 5G phone available in Europe, the company has said. The decision could entirely change the way that phones work and will introduce a transformative technology to the UK, Andy Lau, OnePlus’s chief executive and founder, told The Independent. The phone maker has teamed up with EE to make the handset available, aiming to have it ready for users in 2019. The two companies have signed a research and development partnership that will help deliver much faster and more reliable internet connections across the UK, they said. 5G technology has become one of the most...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Russian tech group Yandex launches own smartphone - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/025d31d6-f860-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdaaZqTZ9aRmxHEdfgimm8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:16:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/025d31d6-f860-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Russian tech group Yandex launches own smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian technology group Yandex has launched its first ever smartphone, as the company seeks to leverage its dominant position in apps and services into hardware sales. Yandex, which runs the most popular search engine in Russia, hopes its Yandex.Phone will bind users closer to its suite of products, from food delivery and taxi hailing apps to marketplace and music streaming platforms, as competition rises for online services. The Android-based smartphone’s launch comes amid a fierce race for market share in Russia’s fledgling e-commerce industry, where Yandex and Russian lender Sberbank ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>China's Xiaomi takes lead over Apple as top seller of wearable technology globally - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/04/chinas-xiaomi-takes-lead-apple-top-seller-wearable-technology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPbjZfrDpoAf3KsArbOjGUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:46:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/04/chinas-xiaomi-takes-lead-apple-top-seller-wearable-technology/" target="_blank"&gt;China's Xiaomi takes lead over Apple as top seller of wearable technology globally&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese smartphone specialist Xiaomi has taken a lead over Apple as the world’s largest manufacturer of wearables, according to new figures from an industry analyst. A report from the International Data Corporation found that Xiaomi took top position in the third quarter of 2018 following positive sales of its Mi Band 3, a fitness tracker. Xiaomi’s push into markets such as India, Europe and the Middle East has been attributed to its overtaking of Apple. The share of the company’s deliveries within its home market has dropped from 80pc to 61pc as its international expansion plans pick up pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Australia encrypted data bill passes first hurdle - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/australia-encrypted-data-bill-passes-hurdle-181206025332786.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKrd8lvxbc-kJPsl_Thiq_sqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:36:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/australia-encrypted-data-bill-passes-hurdle-181206025332786.html" target="_blank"&gt;Australia encrypted data bill passes first hurdle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bill to force technology firms including Google, Facebook and Apple to give police access to encrypted data was passed by Australia's lower house of parliament on Thursday, pushing it closer to becoming a precedent-setting law. The proposal, opposed by the tech giants because Australia is seen as a test case for other nations who want to explore similar rules, faces a sterner test in the upper house where there are concerns about privacy and information security. Under the bill, companies that fail to hand over data linked to suspected illegal activities would face a fine of as much as A$...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>AirPods 2: New Patent Reveals Noise-Canceling, Biometrics And Profound Design Change - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/05/airpods-2-new-patent-reveals-noise-canceling-biometrics-and-profound-design-change/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8eej5jAIDN0lFR3Ri5qi4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/05/airpods-2-new-patent-reveals-noise-canceling-biometrics-and-profound-design-change/" target="_blank"&gt;AirPods 2: New Patent Reveals Noise-Canceling, Biometrics And Profound Design Change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple AirPods 2 are not yet with us, though they may be coming early next year. The current AirPods are “Apple’s most popular accessory ever”, according to reliable analyst Ming-Chi Kuo. Apple’s opening video at its recent keynote features AirPods. There have already been hints that new features, such as hands-free “Hey, Siri” will be coming very soon. And now, it’s come to light that a patent that has just been granted, which has been spotted by 9to5Mac. It refers to “Earbuds with compliant member” and deals with “earbuds configured with one or more biometric sensors”. A compliant member, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Australia wants to snoop on WhatsApp and other encrypted apps - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/tech/australia-encryption-law/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHK_jOj5lDH75AOgrGco9GgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:20:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/tech/australia-encryption-law/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Australia wants to snoop on WhatsApp and other encrypted apps&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia is alarming the tech industry by moving ahead with plans to give government agencies the power to demand access to encrypted messages on services such as Apple's iMessage and Facebook's WhatsApp. The plans have faced push-back from tech firms, but the proposed law is expected to be approved by the Australian parliament this week after the two main political parties agreed to support it. The government argues the legislation will help police and security agencies combat serious offenses such as terrorist attacks and child sex crimes. But privacy advocates say it could bring risks f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Apple patents interchangeable AirPods with health tracking features - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/05/apple-patents-interchangeable-airpods-health-tracking-features/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9eSCEj2JA9ZwnbKrRBPbIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:11:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/05/apple-patents-interchangeable-airpods-health-tracking-features/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple patents interchangeable AirPods with health tracking features&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple is working on interchangeable AirPod headphones that come with health tracking features to measure heart rate and stress levels. That's according to a new patent filed by the firm which reveals how a new version of its wireless in-ear headphones would be able to fit in either ear. The filing shows the device slipping into the ear canal and being held in place with a bendable band. Apple's current wireless AirPods were first launched in 2016, although some users have complained they can easily fall out or become uncomfortable. Apple removed the headphone jack from its iPhone models fro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Apple security expert moves to ACLU as 'public interest tech' builds - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-aclu-apple/apple-security-expert-moves-to-aclu-as-public-interest-tech-builds-idUSKBN1O32LY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIENvSZQlNx0E2tHb49iIrAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:11:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-aclu-apple/apple-security-expert-moves-to-aclu-as-public-interest-tech-builds-idUSKBN1O32LY" target="_blank"&gt;Apple security expert moves to ACLU as 'public interest tech' builds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior Apple Inc security expert left for a much lower-paying job at the American Civil Liberties Union this week, the latest sign of increasing activity on policy issues by Silicon Valley privacy specialists and other engineers. Jon Callas, who led a team of hackers breaking into pre-release Apple products to test their security, started Monday in a two-year role as technology fellow at the ACLU. Prior to his latest stint at Apple, Callas designed an encryption system to protect data on Macs and co-founded communications companies Silent Circle, Blackphone and PGP Corp. “Jon has unparall...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>This is how much Steve Jobs’ autograph is now worth - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-how-much-steve-jobs-autograph-is-now-worth-2018-12-05</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENAAqMmvwCgECv5Infm_Fn8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwuJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-how-much-steve-jobs-autograph-is-now-worth-2018-12-05" target="_blank"&gt;This is how much Steve Jobs’ autograph is now worth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jacob Passy Since 2000, this particular John Hancock has increased in value nearly 28% every year Apple’s iconoclastic founder penned one of the most expensive autographs in the world. Getty Images Steve Jobs did a lot of things in his lifetime: He co-founded Apple (AAPL) he helped create one of the first mass-market personal computers and introduced the world to the iPhone and iPad, among his many accomplishments. One thing he rarely did: Sign autographs. As a result, Steve Jobs’ autograph is one of the most expensive in the world, worth 40,000 pounds (nearly $51,000 or 40 iPhone Xs-es)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Tim Cook: Hate speech has no place on our platforms - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/03/tim-cook-apple-hate-speech-no-place-tech.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPEWmVpOOtQcqtPBBh34T_kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 22:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/12/03/tim-cook-apple-hate-speech-no-place-tech.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;Tim Cook: Hate speech has no place on our platforms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple CEO Tim Cook took a hard-line stance against white supremacists and hate speech while accepting an award from the Anti-Defamation League in New York. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENR6R3fi9qwUs_y2cSw6FUgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:42:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-verizon-samsung-5g/verizon-samsung-to-release-5g-smartphones-in-u-s-in-2019-idUSKBN1O21H2" target="_blank"&gt;Verizon, Samsung to release 5G smartphones in U.S. in 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verizon Communications Inc and Samsung Electronics Co Ltd on Monday confirmed long-held industry expectations they would seek to steal a march on Apple Inc by launching U.S. 5G smartphones in the first half of 2019. The two companies said in a statement they would unveil a prototype, using Qualcomm Inc's modem chips, at the chipmaker's annual Snapdragon Technology Summit in Maui, Hawaii this week. While Verizon is leading the charge to trial 5G in some cities next year, industry analysts say the higher-speed networks are unlikely to be widely available until the middle of the next decade. A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Amazon briefly tops Apple and Microsoft to be world’s biggest company - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/3735d8e0-f72f-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGSxL3lhm0J_4rDgXH4NCH4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 20:33:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3735d8e0-f72f-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon briefly tops Apple and Microsoft to be world’s biggest company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The title of the world’s most valuable company seems to be changing hands nowadays about as quickly as Australia chews through prime ministers, with Amazon the latest to have a crack at the top spot. The ecommerce giant’s market capitalisation on Monday briefly surpassed that of Apple, which itself had been dethroned as the world’s most valuable company last week by Microsoft. With shares up 4.7 per cent, Amazon weighed in with a market cap of $865.3bn that crept a few hundred million above Apple, whose shares were up 2.1 per cent at the time. Amazon shares pulled back slightly to trade 4.4...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Trump wants iPhones made in the US. That could be bad news for Americans - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/tech/trump-tariffs-apple-iphones/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOQ6OoVJQ30_PnHSBh1Pre8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:50:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/tech/trump-tariffs-apple-iphones/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump wants iPhones made in the US. That could be bad news for Americans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump is considering new tariffs on China that could make iPhones way more expensive for Americans. Trump said this week that he won't rule out an additional round of tariffs on Chinese exports thatwould hit Apple's signature product as well as laptops. Such a move would hurt US consumers and American companies because the taxes would be levied on the goods when they enter the country. Apple would have to decide whether to raise its prices to compensate. "The direct impact would be in the United States," said Bryan Ma, analyst with research firm IDC. "If push comes to shove...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Microsoft surpasses Apple as most valuable public company - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/80989b347e7848b3a89996c2b4326696</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJwN2xwyj5nhCUO7OLV3DTsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:20:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/80989b347e7848b3a89996c2b4326696" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft surpasses Apple as most valuable public company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft's big bet on cloud computing is paying off as the company has surpassed Apple as the world's most valuable publicly traded company. The software maker's prospects looked bleak just a few years ago, as licenses for the company's Windows system fell with a sharp drop in sales of personal computers. But under CEO Satya Nadella, Microsoft has found stability by focusing on software and services over the internet, or the cloud, with long-term business contracts. That 1990s personal-computing powerhouse is now having a renaissance moment, as it eclipses Facebook, Google, Amazon and the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>New iPhone Leak Exposes Apple's Nasty Surprise - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-xs-max-xr-upgrade-problem-5g-price-cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKXV3t_Srlgj2YNZgtxojBAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-xs-max-xr-upgrade-problem-5g-price-cost/" target="_blank"&gt;New iPhone Leak Exposes Apple's Nasty Surprise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mounting evidence suggests Apple’s iPhone XS (details), iPhone XS Max (details) and iPhone XR (details) are not selling well even despite price cuts. We already know the crowd-pleasing innovation Apple has planned to win users back, but it might not be enough after a major source confirmed the most serious problem with the company’s new iPhones… Bloomberg reports Apple has fallen substantially behind its rivals and will not be able to equip iPhones with 5G until late 2020 at the earliest. And 5G is about to become a game-changer. Apple’s iPhone XS, iPhone XS Max and iPhone XR Bloomberg’s ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Tumblr, a safe haven for adult content since 2007, is finally banning it - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90275792/tumblr-a-safe-haven-for-adult-content-since-2007-is-finally-banning-it</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELqEq6EkhVZYIiXNdhwq5ZMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:25:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90275792/tumblr-a-safe-haven-for-adult-content-since-2007-is-finally-banning-it" target="_blank"&gt;Tumblr, a safe haven for adult content since 2007, is finally banning it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;First Starbucks banned porn, now Tumblr is, too. The company announced today that adult content will not be allowed on Tumblr, “regardless of how old you are,” beginning on December 17. The new policy comes just days after Tumblr was understandably removed from Apple’s iOS App Store after child pornography—which is illegal on Tumblr and all platforms run by humans with souls—slipped through the platform’s filters and was caught by Apple. Now, Tumblr is banning all adult content, which it defines as including “photos, videos, or GIFs that show real-life human genitals or female-presenting ni...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Apple tunes into terrestrial radio to compete with Spotify - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/07206714-f285-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGwJM29sUbpgZ4PDHgP7R3MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:59:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/07206714-f285-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Apple tunes into terrestrial radio to compete with Spotify&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2003, Apple upended the music industry with iTunes, its digital music store that was tightly linked to its iPod devices. Fifteen years later, Apple is taking a much broader approach to boost its music streaming business, from a tie-up with rival Amazon to a potential move into traditional broadcast radio. Investors are watching Apple’s progress closely as it expands its online services to include a new video streaming offering to compete with the likes of Netflix and Amazon Prime Video next year. And after a slow start in streaming, music industry executives say Apple is gaining confiden...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Apple Unveils 2018's Most Popular Apps: Fortnite, YouTube, Minecraft And More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/12/04/apple-unveils-2018s-most-popular-apps-youtube-fortnite-minecraft-and-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAO7MdGnBE_q5uTbuq7rcrUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/12/04/apple-unveils-2018s-most-popular-apps-youtube-fortnite-minecraft-and-more/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Unveils 2018's Most Popular Apps: Fortnite, YouTube, Minecraft And More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite and YouTube were the absolute most popular apps of 2018, for both iPhones and iPads. Selfie-editor FaceTune ($3.99) was the most popular paid app on the iPhone while drawing app Procreate ($9.99) won the top spot on the iPad. (Photo by Hannah Smith / ESPAT Media / Getty Images) Today, Apple unveiled the list of the most popular apps and games (free and paid) for iPhone and iPad in 2018 and you’ll find below the top 10 charts for each category. This year, Battle Royale-style games like Fortnite and PUBG Mobile dominated global gaming culture with exciting, last-player-standing actio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Amazon briefly edges out Apple for most valuable company - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-amazon/amazon-briefly-edges-out-apple-for-most-valuable-company-idUSKBN1O228J</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO_O2aJ--QzMqAJLIw8LmtwqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 23:40:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-amazon/amazon-briefly-edges-out-apple-for-most-valuable-company-idUSKBN1O228J" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon briefly edges out Apple for most valuable company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon.com briefly became the most valuable company on Wall Street in intraday trade on Monday, days after Microsoft Corp dethroned long-time leader Apple Inc. Amazon rose by 4.7 percent at one point, putting its market capitalization at $865.0 billion. At the same time, Apple traded up 2.1 percent, giving it a market capitalization of $864.8 billion. Microsoft, which on Friday closed above Apple's market capitalization for the first time in eight years, was up 0.9 percent, leaving its stock market value at $859.0 billion, third in the group. Amazon's lead lasted only a few seconds. At the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>These Are The Best Technology Gifts You Can Buy This Year - Gift Guide 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/paularmstrongtech/2018/12/03/these-are-the-best-technology-gifts-you-can-buy-this-year-gift-guide-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECMhLce8UbN-Gs7qKjZDtWIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/paularmstrongtech/2018/12/03/these-are-the-best-technology-gifts-you-can-buy-this-year-gift-guide-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;These Are The Best Technology Gifts You Can Buy This Year - Gift Guide 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Best of Technology Gift Guide 2018 2018 has been the year of voice-tech and will see a lot of pebble-sized presents thanks to the aggressive discounting that Google and Amazon have been more than happy offer consumers recently. Beyond voice though, the tech world has been awash with phone upgrades, new tablets and connected technology. Below is the best of the best tech that will change, enhance or otherwise make your life (or a life dear to you) better in some way. A mix of wellness, utility and connectedness all feature. Here is the best tech that money can buy along with some honourable...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple iPhone Sales Off To A Slow Start This Holiday Season - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyswan/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-sales-off-to-a-slow-start-this-holiday-season/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECX_QcHVflT5gTr9TGOgd2MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyswan/2018/12/04/apple-iphone-sales-off-to-a-slow-start-this-holiday-season/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple iPhone Sales Off To A Slow Start This Holiday Season&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The iPhone XS, left, and XS Max are displayed side to side during an event to announce new products at Apple headquarters Wednesday, Sept. 12, 2018, in Cupertino, Calif. (AP Photo/Marcio Jose Sanchez) photo credit: ASSOCIATED PRESS The day after the keynote address, Consumer Purchase Intent Data was already telling us that Apple was going to have a very rough road ahead of it. Since then, the stock has fallen big. More importantly, the holiday shopping season has begun. This gives us fresh consumer insights to tap into from the first week of the season. 2018 Holiday Slowdown? Black Friday...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Amazon briefly overtakes Microsoft and Apple to become world’s most valuable company - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/03/amazon-briefly-overtakes-microsoft-apple-become-worlds-valuable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIg94xTW-GAz1R6xAl2ZLI8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 20:07:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/03/amazon-briefly-overtakes-microsoft-apple-become-worlds-valuable/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon briefly overtakes Microsoft and Apple to become world’s most valuable company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon briefly become the world’s most valuable publicly-listed company for the first time on Monday. The online shopping giant briefly overtook Microsoft, which itself overtook Apple last week, ending the iPhone maker's five-year run at the top. Shares in Amazon rose 4.7pc, giving the company a market capital of $865bn (£680bn). Its share price fell in later trading, leading Apple to regain its crown. The news follows a major downturn in trading across tech shares in recent weeks. Amazon's value surpassed $1 trillion earlier this year before the so-called FAANG stocks - Facebook, Amazon, A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Apple Music’s arrival on Amazon’s Echo is both surprising and logical - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90275969/apple-musics-arrival-on-amazons-echo-is-both-surprising-and-logical</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA9l-BpPlmHoWNqzL3vJSXEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 17:40:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90275969/apple-musics-arrival-on-amazons-echo-is-both-surprising-and-logical" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Music’s arrival on Amazon’s Echo is both surprising and logical&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last Christmas, we had a platform dilemma at my mom’s house. The only thing she loves more than her iPhone 8 is the Amazon Echo in her living room. She likes to call out old jazz tunes from the couch at night. Even so, she let her Amazon music service subscription expire. She refuses to pay for two music services, and she doesn’t like having two digital assistants in her life. Things will be simpler this Christmas. Apple made the surprising move last week of bringing Apple Music to Amazon’s Alexa-powered devices. Now my mom can standardize on Apple Music—which has some pretty great curated ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Europe won't give up on new tech taxes - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/tech/digital-sales-tax-tech-europe/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbKeX4Bifdu8zF2iVsSqqkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:34:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/tech/digital-sales-tax-tech-europe/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Europe won't give up on new tech taxes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EU plans for a new tech tax are on life support. But Facebook and Google could still be on the hook for millions in payments. France and Germany presented a compromise measure on Tuesday that would tax digital advertising sales at 3%, but spare other online services that had been targeted under an earlier proposal. "[The new version] would most likely impact Google and Facebook and other companies that have a large amount of advertising sales online," said Daniel Bunn, director of global projects at Tax Foundation. The proposal is a narrower version of tax plans championed by the European C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Tim Cook: Hate has 'no place' on Apple's platforms - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/apple-tim-cook-adl-summit/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHEQTdsle4advIH6xV6lte0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:18:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/tech/apple-tim-cook-adl-summit/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tim Cook: Hate has 'no place' on Apple's platforms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We only have one message for those who seek to push hate, division and violence: You have no place on our platforms," Apple CEO Tim Cook said Monday, emphasizing, "You have no home here." Cook delivered this message while accepting the Anti-Defamation League's first-ever "Courage Against Hate" award at an event in New York City. He was recognized for his role in championing unity, diversity and social progress. "If we can't be clear on moral questions like these, then we've got big problems," Cook told attendees. in August, Apple pulled five podcasts from far-right conspiracy theorist Alex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>How Bad ApplePay UX Could Cost Apple The Payments Race - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/duenablomstrom1/2018/12/05/how-bad-applepay-ux-could-cost-apple-the-payments-race/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdOI_pqSWWlaOem9THIufcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/duenablomstrom1/2018/12/05/how-bad-applepay-ux-could-cost-apple-the-payments-race/" target="_blank"&gt;How Bad ApplePay UX Could Cost Apple The Payments Race&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contactless – Fast, Easy, Convenient With the new models of the phone, Apple had to take another step towards “paying with one’s mind” and decide on the most secure and effective user experience to adapt ApplePay to screens without a thumbprint. What they came up with is a process that seems minutely different to the untrained eye but is in fact vastly more complicated than the one they had before and as such is the biggest fail l have seen then perform in usability. How it works You can find a tutorial here but in short, to pay with the new devices one has to perform however many clicks th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here's Why Apple Had No Choice But To Bring Its Music Service To Amazon Alexa Smart Speakers - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/12/03/heres-why-apple-had-no-choice-but-to-bring-its-music-service-to-amazon-alexa-smart-speakers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBvW8Jfkms8RnjFwRoOHD9MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/12/03/heres-why-apple-had-no-choice-but-to-bring-its-music-service-to-amazon-alexa-smart-speakers/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's Why Apple Had No Choice But To Bring Its Music Service To Amazon Alexa Smart Speakers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple Music will now play on the 100 million Amazon Echo smart speakers In a surprise announcement on Friday, Amazon and Apple unveiled that Apple Music will start playing on Amazon Alexa speakers. Starting the week of December 17, the 50+ million Apple Music subscribers (including the ones still in the free 1-month trial) will be able to ask Alexa to play their favorite songs, artists, and albums—or any of the playlists made by Apple Music’s editors. Customers will also be able to ask Alexa to stream expert-made radio stations centered on popular genres like Hip-Hop, decades like the 80s, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Music is coming to Amazon Echo - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/tech/apple-music-on-echo-alexa/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN-yHZNThuEZrkK1nEu9z4AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:22:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/tech/apple-music-on-echo-alexa/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Music is coming to Amazon Echo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexa and Apple are playing nice. Amazon's Echo smart speakers will work with Apple Music starting December 17, Amazon announced Friday. If you have an Apple Music account and have connected it to your smart speaker in the Alexa app, the speakers will be able to play music on demand. Just say, for instance, "Alexa, play Baby Shark on Apple Music." Apple's $9.99 a month music subscription service will join Spotify, Pandora, iHeartRadio, Amazon's own music service, and other options on Alexa devices. Apple is careful about access to its services outside of its own ecosystem, especially when i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Correction: Apple-Women In Tech story - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/7314c4daf6c943d694be02c28becfbdc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC3SUXJ43miVJBCTwdHfoB8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvqGdAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 18:24:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/7314c4daf6c943d694be02c28becfbdc" target="_blank"&gt;Correction: Apple-Women In Tech story&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — In a story Nov. 26 about a new training camp that Apple is offering to women pursuing careers in technology, The Associated Press misspelled the first name of the CEO of Catalyst. The correct spelling is Lorraine, not Lorrain. A corrected version of the story is below: Apple to tutor women in tech in bid to diversify industry Apple is opening a new training camp designed to address the technology industry's scarcity of women in executive and computer programming jobs By MICHAEL LIEDTKE AP Technology Writer SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Apple is launching a new program designed t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Apple Reveals The Best Apps And Games Of 2018 For iPhone, iPad, Mac - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/04/apple-reveals-the-best-apps-and-games-of-2018-for-iphone-ipad-mac/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8t_F3fSjwVbhz7rM5PNQ8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2018/12/04/apple-reveals-the-best-apps-and-games-of-2018-for-iphone-ipad-mac/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Reveals The Best Apps And Games Of 2018 For iPhone, iPad, Mac&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple reveals, each December, which apps have been the year’s top sellers, biggest grossers and most popular for the year. Apple’s choicest apps for 2018 The highlights aren’t just made up of what sits at the top of the charts the longest or sells the most copies. More interesting are what the editorial teams at Apple have chosen as their favorites, across iPhone, iPad, Apple TV and Mac. It also includes podcasts and sales of ebooks. There are different lists for various countries, but here I’m going to take a look at the apps and other items on the US and UK lists, and throw in a choice or...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>You probably already own the No. 1 item on teenagers’ holiday wish list - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/for-the-first-time-teens-want-fortnite-v-bucks-and-cryptocurrency-instead-of-cash-2018-11-14</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOjLDARJb8Vc-CjxSjE1JLYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/for-the-first-time-teens-want-fortnite-v-bucks-and-cryptocurrency-instead-of-cash-2018-11-14" target="_blank"&gt;You probably already own the No. 1 item on teenagers’ holiday wish list&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Quentin Fottrell Fortnite ‘V-Bucks’ and Bitcoin are also making an appearance on their holiday wish lists Some American teenagers want cryptocurrency and Fortnite “V-Bucks” virtual currency instead of cash. Getty Images/iStockphoto You might want the same thing as your child this holiday season. Some U.S. holiday wish lists crisscross all generations and some, well, don’t. Analyst firm Piper Jaffray said the No. 1 item on U.S. teenagers’ wish list this holiday season is Apple’s (AAPL) iPhone. In fact, their top four consumer brands — Apple Watch, MacBooks and Airpods — all come in those...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Apple's stock sours, Microsoft's soars. Say what?! - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/86b8b9e7ebc2452aa496cd75fc5c6d61</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHey5Xri0lhTSPUE8TMhg7AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:27:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/86b8b9e7ebc2452aa496cd75fc5c6d61" target="_blank"&gt;Apple's stock sours, Microsoft's soars. Say what?!&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wall Street investors are enamored with a newly emergent tech company. It has nothing to do with posting selfies or finding a soul mate. The company is instead making billions of dollars selling cloud-computing and other technical services to offices around the world. Say hello to Microsoft, the 1990s home-computing powerhouse that is having a renaissance moment - eclipsing Facebook, Google, Amazon and the other tech darlings of the late decade. And now it is close to surpassing Apple as the world's most valuable publicly traded company. Yes, that Microsoft. As other tech giants stumble, it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Fortnite, Drake and driving test practise app come top of Apple's App Store for 2018 - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-drake-driving-test-best-app-apple-app-store-iphone-2018-a8666621.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLxm7iGgoQk5WhbRFwVOckqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 10:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-drake-driving-test-best-app-apple-app-store-iphone-2018-a8666621.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite, Drake and driving test practise app come top of Apple's App Store for 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple has revealed the most popular of all its apps as 2018 comes to a close. Fortnite is, predictably, the most downloaded free game of the year by people eager to play on their iPhones. The game recently said it had been played by more than 200 million people and is entirely free to download on iOS, as it is on every platform. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/42 5G wireless internet is expected to launch in 2019, with the potential to reach speeds of 50mb/s Getty - 2/42 Uber has halted testing of driverless vehicles after a woman was kil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Apple turnover: Microsoft secures spot as world’s most valuable company - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c2005c4e-f4e5-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEKognOpGP2ghcxGL5OFGzMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:24:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c2005c4e-f4e5-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Apple turnover: Microsoft secures spot as world’s most valuable company&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has officially reclaimed the title of world’s most valuable company after its market capitalisation closed above that of Apple at the end of November. Shares in the maker of Windows and Xbox gaming consoles closed 0.6 per cent higher to $110.89 on Friday, giving the company a market capitalisation of $857.06bn, or about $10bn more than that of Apple, whose shares dropped 0.5 per cent to $178.58. In late trade on Tuesday, Microsoft’s market cap briefly surpassed that of Apple, which overtook ExxonMobil in 2011 to become the world’s most valuable company. It has been almost two deca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Microsoft's stock market value pulls ahead of Apple's - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-microsoft-apple/microsofts-stock-market-value-pulls-ahead-of-apples-idUSKCN1NX2G3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECh-C9Tq296_eKhtoZpSOcYqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:03:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-microsoft-apple/microsofts-stock-market-value-pulls-ahead-of-apples-idUSKCN1NX2G3" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft's stock market value pulls ahead of Apple's&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Corp's (MSFT.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) stock market value surpassed Apple Inc's (AAPL.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), pulling ahead by as much as $3 billion on Wednesday as the Windows software maker benefited from optimism about demand for cloud computing services. Shares of Microsoft jumped 3 percent, pushing its market capitalization up to $848 billion. With the broad market rebounding from a recent slump, Apple also rose, but less than Microsoft. Its 2.17 percent increase put Apple's market capitalization at $845 billion, just four months after the iPh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>These are the podcasts you should be listening to, according to Apple - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90276177/these-are-the-podcasts-you-should-be-listening-to-according-to-apple</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECxv3BwJ9ImBL0__5B2PpKgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 06:39:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90276177/these-are-the-podcasts-you-should-be-listening-to-according-to-apple" target="_blank"&gt;These are the podcasts you should be listening to, according to Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company has announced its annual year-end “best of” lists featuring its picks for the best apps and other media of 2018. Included on that list are Apple’s top picks podcasts it thinks everyone should be listening to. The Cupertino company focused on three subjects when choosing their picks for best podcasts: Investigative reporting - American Public Media’s “In the Dark“ - The New York Times’s “Caliphate“ - Slate’s “Slow Burn“ News and Politics - The New York Times’s “The Daily“ - Crooked Media’s “The Wilderness“ Celebrity and Indies - Dax Shepard’s “Armchair Expert“ - Oprah’s “Master C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Poor iPhone Sales Wipe Out Landmark Achievement As Microsoft Beats Apple - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/03/apple-iphone-xs-iphone-xr-sales-valuation-defeat-microsoft-victory/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdhq3sdcGC6cH2NGileSZQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 23:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/03/apple-iphone-xs-iphone-xr-sales-valuation-defeat-microsoft-victory/" target="_blank"&gt;Poor iPhone Sales Wipe Out Landmark Achievement As Microsoft Beats Apple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was all going so well for Apple. It was the world’s first trillion-dollar company; it was expanding into a service based revenue model; and three new iPhone handsets were on their way to lead the charge into the future with facial recognition, a new visual identity, and the latest custom-designed chips. Then it moved out of the fast lane and its long-standing competitor took the lead. CEO of Apple Tim Cook unveils new products during a launch event at the Brooklyn Academy of Music (Photo by VCG/VCG via Getty Images) There’s no doubt that the A12 chips inside the latest iPhone devices are...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Further thaw in Apple-Amazon relations: Alexa will now stream Apple music - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/further-thaw-in-apple-amazon-relations-alexa-will-now-stream-apple-music-2018-12-01</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGwlx-0ld1wpMXt89iPNbecqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 22:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/further-thaw-in-apple-amazon-relations-alexa-will-now-stream-apple-music-2018-12-01" target="_blank"&gt;Further thaw in Apple-Amazon relations: Alexa will now stream Apple music&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE NEW YORK POST By Nicolas Vega Amazon's Echo Dot speaker–cum–electronic personal assistant devices. Getty Images Amazon said Friday that Apple’s music-streaming service will soon be available on its Alexa-powered devices, signaling a further thaw in the relationship between the tech titans. The announcement also ends a nine-month period of exclusivity in which the music-streaming service was only accessible through Apple’s HomePod smart speaker. Beginning on Dec. 17, users will be able to ask their Amazon Echo speakers to play songs from Apple Music much the same way they can request a s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>What The iPod Teaches Us About Workforce Adoption - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/12/04/what-the-ipod-teaches-us-about-workforce-adoption/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEuvYUV7Sr3KjiY9s-5TYLMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/12/04/what-the-ipod-teaches-us-about-workforce-adoption/" target="_blank"&gt;What The iPod Teaches Us About Workforce Adoption&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty As a CTO, the result I see too often is a system that meets the specifications but does nothing to create pervasive change in the organization. As technology leaders, we’ve all probably wondered why, even when we provide the best technical solution, people either won’t use it or worse, they’ll choose to use something inferior. Experience has taught us the answer: Specifications and engineering may define the ruggedness of the solution, but design addresses the human need and defines the level of adoption. Twenty years ago, MP3 manufacturers thought people wanted a device that could pl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple assembler Foxconn considering iPhone factory in Vietnam -state media - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-foxconn-iphone-vietnam/apple-assembler-foxconn-considering-iphone-factory-in-vietnam-state-media-idUSKBN1O3128</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENh53oo0PL73JJldku-Twj4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 03:26:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-foxconn-iphone-vietnam/apple-assembler-foxconn-considering-iphone-factory-in-vietnam-state-media-idUSKBN1O3128" target="_blank"&gt;Apple assembler Foxconn considering iPhone factory in Vietnam -state media&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foxconn, the world's biggest electronics contract manufacturer and a key Apple Inc supplier, is considering setting up a factory in Vietnam to mitigate any impact of an ongoing trade war between the United States and China, Vietnamese state media reported. The move would be one of the first significant steps by a major company with large manufacturing facilities in China to secure an additional production base outside the country because of trade tensions between the world's top two economies. The report also comes as several executives of other corporations interviewed by Reuters singled o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>British AR pioneer Wave Optics signs deal with Google supplier Goertek - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/28/british-ar-pioneer-wave-optics-signs-deal-google-supplier-goertek/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED7wJiUwXYMoJq_t8zHCrPMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:45:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/28/british-ar-pioneer-wave-optics-signs-deal-google-supplier-goertek/" target="_blank"&gt;British AR pioneer Wave Optics signs deal with Google supplier Goertek&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WaveOptics, an Abingdon-based technology start-up, has signed a deal to mass produce components known as waveguides for augmented reality (AR) glasses. Waveguides are lenses that guide light from a tiny projector to the glass of AR devices allowing virtual objects to be overlaid on the real-world. They are currently used in AR headsets sold by companies such as Microsoft and Magic Leap. Partnering with a large business like Goertek, whose customers include Samsung, Sony and Google, will allow WaveOptics to reduce the cost of its components. WaveOptics said that it hopes it can cut costs to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Alibaba, Amazon And Apple, Oh My! Why We Shouldn't Fear The Giants Of E-Commerce And Tech - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/12/03/alibaba-amazon-and-apple-oh-my-why-we-shouldnt-fear-the-giants-of-e-commerce-and-tech/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFkLrHt3-AA0iEQXTufhWKkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/12/03/alibaba-amazon-and-apple-oh-my-why-we-shouldnt-fear-the-giants-of-e-commerce-and-tech/" target="_blank"&gt;Alibaba, Amazon And Apple, Oh My! Why We Shouldn't Fear The Giants Of E-Commerce And Tech&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty Asset values and spending are at record highs, yet customer leakage to the giants of e-commerce and iPhonesis creating challenges for the most profitable industries. Apple’s historic $1 trillion market cap, Jeff Bezos’s position as the first person to top $100 billion on the Forbes list of the world’s billionaires and Alibaba’s market value of $463 billion signal continuing market pressure from Midas Listers, disrupters and unicorns. Why is everyone so enamored with e-commerce? Because of the promise that it makes life easy and eliminates friction. The competitive threat of e-commerce...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Huawei just topped Apple in smartphone shipments for the second quarter in a row - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90275775/huawei-just-topped-apple-in-smartphone-shipments-for-the-second-quarter-in-a-row</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEs7gY017VwdCTS7YnVe5CoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:15:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90275775/huawei-just-topped-apple-in-smartphone-shipments-for-the-second-quarter-in-a-row" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei just topped Apple in smartphone shipments for the second quarter in a row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The global smartphone market grew by just 1.4% last quarter according to Gartner, which estimated 389 total smartphone shipments in Q3 2018. Much of the year-over-year growth came from Huawei, which shipped 52 million phones and edged out Apple (with 45.7 million shipments) for the second quarter in a row. Fellow Chinese firms Xiaomi (33.2 million shipments) and Oppo (30.6 million shipments) also posted strong growth. Samsung, meanwhile, remains the leading smartphone vendor with 73.4 million units shipped last quarter, but that’s down from 85.6 million units in Q3 2017. The company is hopi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Dow Jones sheds 550 points; Apple and oil prices continue to slump - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-21/dow-jones-tumbles-apple-oil-plunge-wall-street-sell-off/10517226</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEBAqDkgwChl7rk8TdkPIdUqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 20:34:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-21/dow-jones-tumbles-apple-oil-plunge-wall-street-sell-off/10517226" target="_blank"&gt;Dow Jones sheds 550 points; Apple and oil prices continue to slump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Panic has taken a hold of investors, as another spike in volatility led to a sell-off across US, European and Asia. Markets at 8:15am (AEDT): - ASX SPI futures -1.1pc at 5,6138, ASX 200 (Tuesday's close) -0.4pc at 5,672 - AUD: 72.18 US cents, 56.43 British pence, 63.49 Euro cents, 81.36 Japanese yen, $NZ1.06 - US: Dow Jones -2.2pc at 24,466, S&amp;P 500 -1.8pc at 2,642, Nasdaq -1.7pc at 6,909 - Europe: FTSE -0.8pc at 6,948, DAX -1.6pc at 11,066, CAC -1.2pc at 4,925, Euro Stoxx 50 -1.4pc at 3,116 - Commodities: Brent crude -6.6pc at $US62.39/barrel, spot gold -0.3pc at $US1,220.36/ounce, iron or...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Sink different? Apple eyes biggest monthly drop since 2008 - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0fb3efd2-f347-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEX6umQ5Vf0z01xg74UkpKIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:13:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0fb3efd2-f347-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Sink different? Apple eyes biggest monthly drop since 2008&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Sir Isaac Newton might have pointed out, stocks that go up, must come down. And in the case of Apple — which is on track for its biggest monthly fall in a decade — its drop from the tree of market milestones has seen it hit numerous branches along the way. Apple shares finished 3.9 per cent higher on Wednesday, handing the stock its best one-day advance since August 1 in a broad rally that saw the S&amp;P 500 jump 2.3 per cent higher. That still leaves the stock down 17.3 per cent this month, which puts it on track for its biggest monthly drop since September 2008 and the bankruptcy of Lehma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>