<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Obsidian Entertainment - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRE53ZVhGeUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:59:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>'The Outer Worlds' Is The 'Fallout' Game We've All Been Waiting For - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/the-outer-worlds-is-the-fallout-game-weve-all-been-waiting-for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGjPrtVHWOtdZJjl-xuPCsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/the-outer-worlds-is-the-fallout-game-weve-all-been-waiting-for/" target="_blank"&gt;'The Outer Worlds' Is The 'Fallout' Game We've All Been Waiting For&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Outer Worlds looks great. I imagine the developers at Obsidian have been watching the Fallout 76 with grim wonder and more than a little schadenfreude. After all, this is a studio who missed out on a bonus from publisher Bethesda because their game, Fallout: New Vegas, didn’t top 85 on Metacritic. Fallout 76 hasn’t even come close to that number. While New Vegas had its problems—Obsidian, like Bethesda, isn’t known for bug-free projects—it was an instant classic and a much-beloved entry into the franchise. Fallout 76 is a disaster. So it must have been rather serendipitous for Obsidian ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Game Awards 2018 announcements: Dragon Age 4 and Far Cry: New Dawn headline new game reveals - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-announcements-dragon-age-4-far-cry-new-dawn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOe9WHf9XKnjO0C_nfPE33MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:54:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-announcements-dragon-age-4-far-cry-new-dawn/" target="_blank"&gt;The Game Awards 2018 announcements: Dragon Age 4 and Far Cry: New Dawn headline new game reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BioWare has announced that RPG Dragon Age 4 is coming at The Game Awards ceremony. The long-awaited fantasy RPG is reportedly still early in development, but BioWare has teased its fans with a short video and the phrase The Dread Wolf Rises; a reference to elven apostate Solas. Far Cry: New Dawn, a direct post-apocalyptic sequel to Ubisoft's open-world shooter Far Cry 5, was unveiled for 15 February 2019. The game is set 17 years after Far Cry 5, with a 'super-bloom' transforming the setting of Hope County into a vivid, colourful post-nuclear land. And staying with pink post-apocalyptia, Ra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Road To Eternity' Is A Compelling Documentary About The Making Of 'Pillars Of Eternity' - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2017/01/26/road-to-eternity-is-a-compelling-documentary-about-the-making-of-pillars-of-eternity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDP314DRpwIvSKfB4AHWywoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 06:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2017/01/26/road-to-eternity-is-a-compelling-documentary-about-the-making-of-pillars-of-eternity/" target="_blank"&gt;'Road To Eternity' Is A Compelling Documentary About The Making Of 'Pillars Of Eternity'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Credit: Obsidian/YouTube In the spring of 2012 Obsidian Entertainment was on the rocks. With games like Neverwinter Nights 2 and Fallout: New Vegas in their portfolio they were well known and respected but the cancellation of Stormlands by Microsoft, the game’s publisher, left them without a project and with too many employees to support. The situation was grim. Staff who had been with Obsidian for a long time had to be let go and the people who remained were demoralized. They took a hard look at their finances and set a date. If they didn’t find a new project with funding by the time that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Why Crowdfunding 'Pillars Of Eternity 2' And 'Banner Saga 3' Was The Right Choice - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/01/27/why-it-was-the-smart-choice-to-crowdfund-pillars-of-eternity-2-and-banner-saga-3/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJowt0Vipzzl_5_wlsOaVYAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/01/27/why-it-was-the-smart-choice-to-crowdfund-pillars-of-eternity-2-and-banner-saga-3/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Crowdfunding 'Pillars Of Eternity 2' And 'Banner Saga 3' Was The Right Choice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pillars of Eternity 2: Deadfire just funded on Fig. (Credit: Obsidian) Obsidian Entertainment is once again using crowdfunding for its Pillars of Eternity sequel. This time they’re opting for Fig instead of Kickstarter. Indie developer Stoic is also using a crowdfunding campaign for its game Banner Saga 3, returning to Kickstarter after forgoing crowdfunding for the trilogy’s second game. Both these developers are smart to use crowdfunding again, but not just because they can raise some extra cash. The real value in a crowdfunding campaign, especially for PC games that find themselves awash...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'Pillars Of Eternity II' Reaches It's Funding Goal In Less Than One Day. - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2017/01/27/pillars-of-eternity-ii-reaches-its-funding-goal-in-less-than-one-day/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGD7PZl1mBA8uHUkoa4AMREqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2017/01/27/pillars-of-eternity-ii-reaches-its-funding-goal-in-less-than-one-day/" target="_blank"&gt;'Pillars Of Eternity II' Reaches It's Funding Goal In Less Than One Day.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Credit: Obsidian Entertainment Obsidian Entertainment’s crowdfunder for Pillars of Eternity II: Deadfire reached its funding goal of $1.1 million in less than one day. Deadfire is the sequel to the original Pillars of Eternity that set Kickstarter funding records by raising $4 million in 2012. Feargus Urquhart, the CEO of Obsidian Entertainment, is a member of the advisory board of Fig, a crowdfunding platform devoted to games. Pillars of Eternity II: Deadfire is being funded through Fig rather than Kickstarter. Fig is significantly different from Kickstarter. For one thing, the only projec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Don't Believe That Unbelievable 'Fallout: New Vegas 2' Rumor - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/01/31/dont-believe-that-unbelievable-fallout-new-vegas-2-rumor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK5GstTu7O_XAgSH6-eGU3MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 15:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/01/31/dont-believe-that-unbelievable-fallout-new-vegas-2-rumor/" target="_blank"&gt;Don't Believe That Unbelievable 'Fallout: New Vegas 2' Rumor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: Obsidian Yesterday, I saw a rumor flying around the internet that looked rather improbable. The idea being floated was that Obsidian was set to make not just another Fallout quasi-sequel, but specifically, New Vegas 2. I cocked my head in, then looked at the source, which is gaming website FragHero. I cocked my head further when I saw that I personally was being called out in their lede. “We’ve had a spectacular track record with this source in the past. As you may recall we were the first to accurately leak Red Dead Redemption 2 details. Other Websites like Forbes even tried to make...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Microsoft add RPG-makers Obsidian and InXile to its growing stable of Xbox studios - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/microsoft-add-rpg-makers-obsidian-inxile-growing-stable-xbox/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECsn93hyz1ZlyYHqFTtmk0wqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 10:42:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/microsoft-add-rpg-makers-obsidian-inxile-growing-stable-xbox/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft add RPG-makers Obsidian and InXile to its growing stable of Xbox studios&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has confirmed the acquisition of Obsidian Entertainment and added a second role-playing-game (RPG) specialist in the form of InXile Entertainment to its growing stable of Xbox-focussed game studios. The confirmation of the acquisitions came at the X018 fan event in New Mexico, where Head of Microsoft Studios Matt Booty said that Microsoft would keep the developers 'unique to preserve the cultures that they have got.' Both studios and its staff have extensive history in the industry. Obsidian has been making behind games such as Fallout: New Vegas, Star Wars: Knights of the Old Rep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Premier RPG Developers inXile And Obsidian Acquired By Xbox - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/12/premier-rpg-developers-inxile-and-obsidian-acquired-by-xbox/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZVXSuwf_6--UvweMDzlZYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 19:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/12/premier-rpg-developers-inxile-and-obsidian-acquired-by-xbox/" target="_blank"&gt;Premier RPG Developers inXile And Obsidian Acquired By Xbox&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Wasteland 3′ Last month it was rumored that Microsoft was set to acquire acclaimed RPG developer Obsidian Entertainment. The rumor was confirmed on Saturday during Xbox’s XO18 event in Mexico City. But Obsidian isn’t the only renowned RPG development studio coming to Xbox. XO18 also brought the announcement that Microsoft has acquired inXile Entertainment. Obsidian and inXile have played a central role in the resurgence of classical RPGs that has taken place over the past few years. Obsidian recently developed Pillars of Eternity and Pillars of Eternity 2: Deadfire, South Park: The Stick o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Rumor Has It That Microsoft Is Set To Acquire Acclaimed RPG Developer Obsidian Entertainment - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/10/rumor-has-it-that-microsoft-is-set-to-acquire-acclaimed-rpg-developer-obsidian-entertainment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECorNSxbWLZuegz-tL6XzqoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 16:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/10/rumor-has-it-that-microsoft-is-set-to-acquire-acclaimed-rpg-developer-obsidian-entertainment/" target="_blank"&gt;Rumor Has It That Microsoft Is Set To Acquire Acclaimed RPG Developer Obsidian Entertainment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft sets it’s eyes on acquiring Oblivion Entertainment. Rumor has it that Microsoft is in the late stages of finalizing a deal to purchase acclaimed RPG development studio Oblivion Entertainment. Kotaku reports that one person with knowledge of the negotiations between the two companies said “It’s a matter of when, not if” while another claimed the deal is “90%” finished. Obsidian has an impressive portfolio of role-playing games that includes Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic (2004), Fallout: New Vegas (2010), Wasteland 2 and South Park: The Stick of Truth (2014), Pillars of Ete...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Bethesda And Xbox Drop The Hammer On Player Who Breaks The 'Fallout 76' NDA - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/16/bethesda-and-xbox-drop-the-hammer-on-player-who-breaks-the-fallout-76-nda/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELobHPvaTW3fhOI_1Qzd4u0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/10/16/bethesda-and-xbox-drop-the-hammer-on-player-who-breaks-the-fallout-76-nda/" target="_blank"&gt;Bethesda And Xbox Drop The Hammer On Player Who Breaks The 'Fallout 76' NDA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guy breaks ”Fallout 76′ NDA. Bethesda and Xbox break guy. Technology and video game companies take NDAs and embargoes seriously. You don’t break them. Apparently, a player who participated in last Saturday’s stress test for Fallout 76 on the Xbox One either didn’t get the message or thought he could get away with it. He didn’t, and both Bethesda and Xbox dropped the hammer on him. Players who signed up for the stress test were required to click-to-agree to an NDA that prohibited taking or sharing photos, videos or audio recordings, describing the game online or offline, allowing people to w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Microsoft set to buy Fallout: New Vegas developer Obsidian Entertainment - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/microsoft-set-buy-fallout-new-vegas-developer-obsidian-entertainment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHT25SNDiYiEuaoSV3bSo6wqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 08:18:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/microsoft-set-buy-fallout-new-vegas-developer-obsidian-entertainment/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft set to buy Fallout: New Vegas developer Obsidian Entertainment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft are reportedly close to finalising a deal to acquire Obsidian Entertainment, with the acclaimed RPG developer set to be the latest studio to join Microsoft’s growing number of Xbox focussed studios. Reports of the acquisition comes from Kotaku, which cites three sources ‘briefed on the negotiations’. One source was quoted as saying the deal was ‘90% done’, while another said it was ‘a matter of when, not if.’ Obsidian are best known for their work on detailed role-playing games. An impressive portfolio includes Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic II, Neverwinter Nights 2, Fallo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Pillars of Eternity II: Deadfire review – swashbuckling retro fun - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/may/08/pillars-of-eternity-ii-deadfire-review-swashbuckling-retro-fun</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgDYPyG_tneR4fmQbYjiL8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 17:00:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/may/08/pillars-of-eternity-ii-deadfire-review-swashbuckling-retro-fun" target="_blank"&gt;Pillars of Eternity II: Deadfire review – swashbuckling retro fun&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pillars of Eternity is an ambitious and successful gamble on role-playing game nostalgia, aimed squarely at people who enjoyed Baldur’s Gate and Planescape: Torment. The first game, released in 2015, brought in $4m in funding on Kickstarter. Its sequel, Deadfire, also raised over $4m in crowdfunding, and has just been released. Unlike its predecessor, Deadfire is arriving into a market with many similar games attempting to leverage 90s RPG nostalgia while adding their own twists to the genre. It doesn’t rock the boat too much, but a fresh theme, clever writing and improvements to the look a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item></channel></rss>