<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Fortnite - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR3M1WW1NNU1CSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:11:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>In 7 Seasons, 'Fortnite' Hasn't Had One Female Tier-100 Skin - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/07/in-7-seasons-fortnite-hasnt-had-one-female-tier-100-skin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGMIavLtgeYncKGLlVUb-MIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/07/in-7-seasons-fortnite-hasnt-had-one-female-tier-100-skin/" target="_blank"&gt;In 7 Seasons, 'Fortnite' Hasn't Had One Female Tier-100 Skin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite We got our first look Fortnite: Battle Royale’s Season 7 battle pass yesterday. The start of a new season is Christmas morning for the ultra-popular battle royale title, with massive map changes, new items, new challenges and a whole new battle pass stacked with skins and other cosmetics ready for players to unlock once they’ve paid out $10. The batttle pass is the primary organizing principle of the game, and that’s why the leadup is so exciting every time: every season Fortnite players race to unlock the ultimate achievement: a Tier-100 battle pass and the elite skin that comes w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite's New Season 7 Gun And Vehicle Wrap Skins May Be Epic's Huge New Moneymaker - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/07/fortnites-new-season-7-gun-and-vehicle-wrap-skins-may-be-epics-huge-new-moneymaker/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDfmSTz2JPox1YFBhlzJ7GMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/07/fortnites-new-season-7-gun-and-vehicle-wrap-skins-may-be-epics-huge-new-moneymaker/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite's New Season 7 Gun And Vehicle Wrap Skins May Be Epic's Huge New Moneymaker&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite While Fortnite earning $300 million a month has allowed Epic to do pretty much whatever they want, including opening up a competitor to Steam, obviously any successful company is going to keep looking for new ways to make money. And it may have just found a significant new path with the launch of season 7. For the first time, Fortnite season 7 has introduced “wraps,” which look like Christmas wrapping paper (an appropriate time to launch), but in practice serve as gun and vehicle skins for the first time. Right now you can apply the pattern to certain guns (shotguns and rifles I be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Video game stocks get crushed as Fortnite reigns - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/investing/video-game-stocks-take-two-activision-blizzard-ea-fortnite/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPj_3caGH93VNKJtvo9AhigqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:09:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/investing/video-game-stocks-take-two-activision-blizzard-ea-fortnite/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Video game stocks get crushed as Fortnite reigns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite and other so-called multiplayer battle royale games are all the rage. And investors in leading video game companies have been stuck doing the "take the L" Fortnite loser dance as a result. Shares of Activision Blizzard (ATVI) have plunged nearly 45% in the past two months. Electronic Arts (EA) is down almost 30%. And Take-Two Interactive (TTWO) has plummeted 25%, despite having a successful new game -- Red Dead Redemption 2. Fortnite may be stealing away some gamers thanks to the fact that it can be downloaded for free on iPhones and iPads, Android phones and tablets as well as pop...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Is 'Fortnite' Teasing Swords And The Infinity Blade For Season 7? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/07/is-fortnite-teasing-swords-and-the-infinity-blade-for-season-7/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOImANARyUqXWIfO732Yo8kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/07/is-fortnite-teasing-swords-and-the-infinity-blade-for-season-7/" target="_blank"&gt;Is 'Fortnite' Teasing Swords And The Infinity Blade For Season 7?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite, as it usually does, kicked Season 7 off with a little movie. Christmas-themed this time, with stop-motion Rankin and Bass-style movie showcasing a pleasant little winter scene before everything goes south. A glacier crashes into the island and Santa leads an invading army of savage snowmen, raining death upon the unsuspecting elf skins from above. It was a pretty good one, as far as Fortnite cinematics go, but there was one little detail that people immediately noticed. Let’s take a look: Fortnite Santa is wielding a pretty slick looking sword there, a weapon class that’s been in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Videogame Star Ninja Drops An Album, And A Peek Into The Future - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dbloom/2018/12/07/fortnite-star-ninja-drops-an-album-and-a-peek-into-the-future/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI_B1F700HG8Qq93kOuXbfAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dbloom/2018/12/07/fortnite-star-ninja-drops-an-album-and-a-peek-into-the-future/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Videogame Star Ninja Drops An Album, And A Peek Into The Future&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justin Caruso (l.) and Ninja (Tyler Blevins) in Capitol Records Studio A Seventy feet from Nat King Cole’s piano, with Frank Sinatra’s microphones nearby, in Capitol Records’ historic Hollywood recording studios, a lanky guy with spiky aqua hair plays the world’s most popular video game alongside a string of musicians. It’s a decided change from the usual reasons people load thousands of dollars worth of expensive gear into Studio A, where countless musical stars have recorded hit records for decades. This Sunday night, it’s about Capitol, a division of Universal Music Group, trying to rema...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Season 7 live with new planes, ziplines, custom weapons and an expanded snowy island - all you need to know - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fortnite-season-7-start-time-downtime-confirmed-patch-notes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGflv_75y1muG4nSxKHraXoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:13:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fortnite-season-7-start-time-downtime-confirmed-patch-notes/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Season 7 live with new planes, ziplines, custom weapons and an expanded snowy island - all you need to know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Season 6 of Fortnite coming to its conclusion, Fortnite Season 7 is now live for the Battle Royale behemoth's 200 million players. The new season brings brand new 'Stormwing', machine-gun equipped biplanes for combatants to fly, ziplines to get around the (now bigger) Fortnite island quicker and a new locations in the form of 'Frosty Flights' and Expedition outposts. The iceberg that was travelling towards the map has shunted into the south-west corner of Fortnite island, growing the map considerably, while that particular quadrant of the map is now covered in snow. Season 7 also bring...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Challenge Guide: Where to Dance In 7 Different Fordidden Locations - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/map-fortnite-challenge-guide-where-to-dance-in-7-different-fordidden-locations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELHxExoHMnn_nPfO-VEStmsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/map-fortnite-challenge-guide-where-to-dance-in-7-different-fordidden-locations/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Challenge Guide: Where to Dance In 7 Different Fordidden Locations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite It’s time for a brand-new Season of weekly Challenges! Season 7 is here in Fortnite:Battle Royale, and with it a chance to start all over again levelling up the battle pass, completing challenges and making your way all the way to the Ice King skin that sits menacingly atop the heap. The best way to do this, as always, is with weekly challenges. Some of these sare straightforward, and some of these are less so. We’re here to help with the straightforward ones, starting with dancing in different forbidden locations. This is actually a repeat from way back in Season 3, and these sign...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here Are All The Leaked Skins And Cosmetics Found In Fortnite's Season 7 Patch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/here-are-all-the-leaked-skins-and-cosmetics-found-in-fortnites-v7-0-patch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-ZgVkRPe8bgWSKjScYB28qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/here-are-all-the-leaked-skins-and-cosmetics-found-in-fortnites-v7-0-patch/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are All The Leaked Skins And Cosmetics Found In Fortnite's Season 7 Patch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are all the new skins and cosmetics found in the Season 7 patch. Today is a big day for Fortnite players. Season 7 kicked off earlier this morning, and with it we now have a bunch of leaked skins, gliders, back bling and other cosmetics slowly trickling out. You can see all the skins included in the Season 7 Battle Pass here. In the meantime, let’s take a look at the various skins/outfits and cosmetics that dataminers have uncovered since this morning’s v7.0 patch went live. Outfits Naturally the first leaked skins are pilot-themed. That makes sense given the inclusion of a new Named A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here Are All The New Season 7 Battle Pass Skins In 'Fortnite: Battle Royale' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/here-are-all-the-new-season-7-battle-pass-skins-in-fortnite-battle-royale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEGmn0Phz7KoVMHUUZry1FAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/here-are-all-the-new-season-7-battle-pass-skins-in-fortnite-battle-royale/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are All The New Season 7 Battle Pass Skins In 'Fortnite: Battle Royale'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out the new skins in Fortnite’s Season 7 Battle Pass. Fortnite: Battle Royale Season 7 is almost upon us, and with it major changes to the game’s huge map including a brand new ice biome. We already have the crazy new patch notes which you can read here, and you can watch the festive new cinematic trailer here. And check out the rest of the Battle Pass for Season 7 here. And now that the servers are back up, we have the full cadre of Season 7 Battle Pass skins—four of which are “progressive” meaning they have special unlocks that add customization options as you progress. So let’s tak...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Challenge: Where To Dance On Top Of A Crown Of RVs (Stage 1) - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/06/fortnite-challenge-where-to-dance-on-top-of-a-crown-of-rvs-stage-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMb_PdiOC-touY8lODdZHcgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/06/fortnite-challenge-where-to-dance-on-top-of-a-crown-of-rvs-stage-1/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Challenge: Where To Dance On Top Of A Crown Of RVs (Stage 1)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite A new season of Fortnite is here, and with it comes a number of new challenges. One of the most significant ones released here in a week 1 is a progressive challenge that tasks players with three objectives. The first of which is to dance on top of a crown of RVs. I genuinely could not think of where this was, as I thought that it might be a new addition to the map which arrived with the iceberg, but that isn’t the case. Rather the crown of RVs is actually on the desert on one of the mesas at the very south the map. Here’s where that is on the map. It’s the mesa right above the lit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Season 7, Week 1 Challenges Revealed And How To Solve Them - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/fortnite-season-7-week-1-challenges-revealed-and-how-to-solve-them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM5a4xw9z4fgsu1go8xFMBsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/fortnite-season-7-week-1-challenges-revealed-and-how-to-solve-them/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Season 7, Week 1 Challenges Revealed And How To Solve Them&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are Fortnite’s Season 7, Week 1 challenges and how to solve them. Season 7 of Fortnite: Battle Royale has arrived and with it a whole bunch of new challenges. These include the new Snowfall weekly challenge as well as challenges for several new characters in the Season 7 Battle Pass. We also have our first batch of Free and Battle Pass challenges as Season 7, Week 1 kicks off. Here they are: Free Challenges - Pick up an item of each rarity (0/5) 5 Battle Stars - Dance in different forbidden locations (0/7) 5 Battle Stars - Play matches with at least one elimination (HARD) (0/5) 10 Batt...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Where To Find Fortnite's Week 1 Hidden 'Snowfall Challenge' Battle Star - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/where-to-find-fortnites-week-1-hidden-snowfall-challenge-battle-star/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPHLy2SqyGvmx25zzFdrBsUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/where-to-find-fortnites-week-1-hidden-snowfall-challenge-battle-star/" target="_blank"&gt;Where To Find Fortnite's Week 1 Hidden 'Snowfall Challenge' Battle Star&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s where to find Fortnite’s first Snowfall challenge Battle Star. Fortnite’s seventh season has begun in earnest. Along with a ton of map changes, we have a new weekly challenge set. Replacing the Hunting Party challenges from Season 6 we have a new Snowfall challenge series. This time some pretty major things have changed, however. Like past seasons, completing every challenge in a week will get you a secret loading screen (week 1 pictured above, which you’ll get when you’ve completed week 1′s challenges) and that loading screen will lead to a hidden Battle Star or, presumably, a secre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Watch The Festive 'Fortnite' Season 7 Cinematic Trailer Right Here - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/watch-the-christmasy-fortnite-season-7-cinematic-trailer-right-here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIBAx5G1ZnlUirib87Mu3R0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/watch-the-christmasy-fortnite-season-7-cinematic-trailer-right-here/" target="_blank"&gt;Watch The Festive 'Fortnite' Season 7 Cinematic Trailer Right Here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch Fortnite’s Season 7 cinematic trailer right here. Fortnite: Battle Royale’s seventh Battle Pass season is upon us, just in time for the holidays. The mysterious iceberg has crashed into the island, and with it comes new snowy areas, planes and much more. (Read the patch notes here.) There’s also a brand new cinematic trailer and it’s very funny. The trailer opens to Crackshot, the Fortnite Nutcracker skin, decorating for Christmas. Check it out: I love the little claymation-looking dog and the cuckoo clock and pretty much the entire opening segment. You can see many of the game’s cla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Creative Mode: What Is Fortnite's Big New Mode, And How Do You Play It? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/access-battle-royale-creative-mode-what-is-fortnites-big-new-mode-and-how-do-you-play-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPud_LyDPsa2l80mTsrjTscqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/access-battle-royale-creative-mode-what-is-fortnites-big-new-mode-and-how-do-you-play-it/" target="_blank"&gt;Creative Mode: What Is Fortnite's Big New Mode, And How Do You Play It?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite You might be zipping around in the new ice biome, testing out a plane or just beginning to level up your battle pass, but none of those things are the biggest changes that developer Epic Games dumped on Fortnite today. Fortnite: Battle Royale got a huge update, as it always does at the start of the season, but the biggest update to the wider Fortnite property is Creative Mode, a third mode for the game to stand alongside Save the World and Battle Royale. That top-level billing should give you a sense of how important this is to the game and its developer. So what is it? Epic detail...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Season 7 start time and downtime confirmed as release hints at new planes - everything we know so far - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fortnite-season-7-teaser-battle-pass-release-date-map-changes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEGiAnt4EZvwgGAeO6zkHuAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:54:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/fortnite-season-7-teaser-battle-pass-release-date-map-changes/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Season 7 start time and downtime confirmed as release hints at new planes - everything we know so far&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Season 6 of Fortnite coming to its conclusion, Epic Games has confirmed the arrival of Fortnite Season 7 today. The developer has confirmed that Fortnite will go down at 9am UK time (4am ET) on 6 December as the new season is implemented. The downtime will likely last a few hour as the new Battle Pass, skins and features are added to the hit game. Patch notes detailing the changes and a new trailer will likely be released as the game updates. Epic first starting teasing the new season at the start of this week, with a tweet from the official Fortnite Twitter account that featured an im...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Season 7 Patch Notes: Airplanes, Vaulted Weapons And A Brand-New Ice Biome - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/fortnite-season-7-patch-notes-airplanes-vaulted-weapons-and-a-brand-new-ice-biome/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED8b-4eGi0t6uN7K58IIT-0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/fortnite-season-7-patch-notes-airplanes-vaulted-weapons-and-a-brand-new-ice-biome/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Season 7 Patch Notes: Airplanes, Vaulted Weapons And A Brand-New Ice Biome&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite It’s time for Season 7 in Fortnite: Battle Royale. We may have gotten an early look at the Season 7 Battle Pass courtesy of Fortnite Korea, but now we’re moving full-steam ahead with the actual release. At the time of this writing servers are down as we wait to get our hands on new weapons and new lands, but in the meantime, we’ve got the patch notes to keep ourselves occupied. There are a ton of changes as you might expect: not just the big new flashy additions, but continuing balance tweaks and big changes to the weapon loadout as well. Here’s what’s in Fortnite’s big v7.00 updat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here's All The Crazy, Frozen New Stuff On The 'Fortnite' Season 7 Map - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/06/heres-all-the-crazy-frozen-new-stuff-on-the-fortnite-season-7-map/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG1NmQAxLQshudvUkA2bHlgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/06/heres-all-the-crazy-frozen-new-stuff-on-the-fortnite-season-7-map/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's All The Crazy, Frozen New Stuff On The 'Fortnite' Season 7 Map&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Fortnite players have woken up this morning to see the entire landscape of the map transformed. Well, at least a significant chunk of it. The polar opposite (no pun intended) of the desert biome before it, a giant iceberg/castle has appeared in the middle a new ice zone and has spread its chilly winds to probably 25-30% of the map. This has transformed many old areas and created some brand new ones as well. Here are the highlights of the new map additions: Polar Peak/Ice Castle The game identifies the giant iceberg as a mountain, but it’s very obvious that it’s a castle, frozen in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Game Awards 2018 winners: God of War wins game of the year as Red Dead Redemption 2 rides home with four - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-winners-god-war-wins-game-year-red-dead-redemption/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPDeuR-4L-u41h9dsCE_uYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:22:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-winners-god-war-wins-game-year-red-dead-redemption/" target="_blank"&gt;The Game Awards 2018 winners: God of War wins game of the year as Red Dead Redemption 2 rides home with four&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sony Santa Monica's God of War has won the Game of the Year award at The Game Awards 2018 ceremony. The acclaimed Norse adventure also picked up awards for best direction and best action-adventure. Rockstar's smash hit Western Red Dead Redemption 2 won the most awards, riding home with four. The sprawling adventure won best narrative, best performance for Roger Clarke as Arthur Morgan, best music for Woody Jackson and Daniel Lanois' score and best audio. Indie gem Celeste won two for best independent game and the Game for Impact award. And battle royale phenomenon Fortnite also took two wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Challenge: Where To Dance On Top Of A Metal Turtle (Stage 2) - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/06/fortnite-challenge-where-to-dance-on-top-of-a-metal-turtle-stage-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDYMZ-3zDhZ14u3Pd0dQUiYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/06/fortnite-challenge-where-to-dance-on-top-of-a-metal-turtle-stage-2/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Challenge: Where To Dance On Top Of A Metal Turtle (Stage 2)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite If you’ve arrived here, that means you have completed at least one task Fortnite season 7 has laid out for you, dancing on top of a crown of RVs. The next step in the multi-tier challenge is to dance on top of a metal turtle, something that again, I didn’t know the location of right away. I may be taking crazy pills, but I genuinely do not remember a giant metal turtle in the game, and I think these objects might be new. But tell me if I’m wrong. Anyway, if you’re like me and don’t know where this is, I’ve found him. The giant metal turtle is to the far east of the map, just above ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Brooklyn rapper sues makers of Fortnite over claims video game stole his moves - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/dec/05/brooklyn-rapper-sues-fortnite-video-game-stole-dance</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELmDK_f2HoPCT0xvtTLuiB0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:43:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/dec/05/brooklyn-rapper-sues-fortnite-video-game-stole-dance" target="_blank"&gt;Brooklyn rapper sues makers of Fortnite over claims video game stole his moves&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rapper 2 Milly filed a lawsuit Wednesday against the makers of Fortnite, saying they were illegally using a dance he created in their wildly popular video game. The Brooklyn-based rapper, whose real name is Terrence Ferguson, alleges that the North Carolina-based Epic Games misappropriated his moves without compensation or credit in the lawsuit, filed in federal court in Los Angeles. The lawsuit states that the dance known on Fortnite as “Swipe It”, one of many that players can buy for their characters, is taken from the “Milly Rock”, a dance he came up with in 2011 that caught on as a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>There's A Big 'Fortnite' Announcement At The Game Awards Tonight, But It's Not What You Think - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/theres-a-big-fortnite-announcement-at-the-game-awards-tonight-but-its-not-what-you-think/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFx_4hkGV0WvjHfenD2tDskqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/theres-a-big-fortnite-announcement-at-the-game-awards-tonight-but-its-not-what-you-think/" target="_blank"&gt;There's A Big 'Fortnite' Announcement At The Game Awards Tonight, But It's Not What You Think&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite It’s a big day for battle royale fans. For one thing, Fortnite Season 7 just launched as Epic Games continues to top itself when it comes to totally transforming its map to match the current season: right now we’ve got a wide-ranging winter wonderland, airplanes, and a ton of other stuff. It’s also The Game Awards tonight, the annual celebration that’s gradually emerging as the most important awards show in the world of video games. The Game Awards are known not only for the awards themselves but also for the announcements, surprises and trailers that have a way of worming their wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Rapper 2 Milly Sues Fortnite Video Game Over Dance Moves - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rapper-2-milly-sues-fortnite-video-game-over-dance-moves</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECt-pV0ixANOvwsDhC9NPr8qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:42:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/rapper-2-milly-sues-fortnite-video-game-over-dance-moves" target="_blank"&gt;Rapper 2 Milly Sues Fortnite Video Game Over Dance Moves&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christian Petersen/Getty, Rapper 2 Milly has sued the makers of Fortnite, claiming they stole a dance he came up with and integrated it into the popular video game without permission, the Associated Press reports. The rapper, whose real name is Terrence Ferguson, reportedly claimed North Carolina-based Epic Games “misappropriated his moves without compensation or credit” in an in-game “emote” called “Swipe It.” Ferguson alleged the dance was taken from “Milly Rock,” a dance he developed in 2011 that gained popularity in the summer of 2015. “They never even asked my permission,” Ferguson was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Rapper 2 Milly files lawsuit against Fortnite creators for 'stolen' dance - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/rapper-2-milly-files-lawsuit-against-fortnite-creators-stolen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2UeDqNwEk6fp4T2ATyVR8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:00:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/rapper-2-milly-files-lawsuit-against-fortnite-creators-stolen/" target="_blank"&gt;Rapper 2 Milly files lawsuit against Fortnite creators for 'stolen' dance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;American rapper 2 Milly has confirmed that he has filed a lawsuit in California against Fortnite creator Epic Games over the apparent use of his 'Milly Rock' dance in the smash video game. The lawsuit, was filed on Wednesday over the alleged 'misappropriation, use and sale' of the dance. The rapper alleges that the Fortnite emote dubbed 'Swipe It', available during Season 5 of the hugely successful game, was an unauthorised recreation of his dance. Epic games sold the 'Swipe It' emote for around $5 (£3.95), which allowed players to perform the dance in-game. The Swipe It emote is no longer ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Season 7: Creative mode confirmed by Epic following leak - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-leak-reveals-major-new-minecraft-style-fortnite-creative/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBOIPKDiMCBtWnzPxMH8rYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:13:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-leak-reveals-major-new-minecraft-style-fortnite-creative/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Season 7: Creative mode confirmed by Epic following leak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gaming sensation Fortnite will be getting a brand new third 'Creative' mode when Season 7 launches this week. In addition to the phenomenally popular Battle Royale mode and co-op survival game Save the World, Fortnite Creative is a Minecraft style building tool that allows players to create their own private islands and minigames with unlimited resources and a slew of rule options. Developer Epic Games confirmed the existence of the mode on its official site, saying that Fortnite Creative will initially be available for buyers of the Season 7 Battle Pass when it releases tomorrow 6 December...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fortnite's Final Season 7 Teaser Shows Off Zip Lines, Airplanes - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/leaked-skin-fortnites-final-season-7-teaser-shows-off-zip-lines-and-brand-new-airplanes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOFAvP_9GapS08nk4WLOqtwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/leaked-skin-fortnites-final-season-7-teaser-shows-off-zip-lines-and-brand-new-airplanes/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite's Final Season 7 Teaser Shows Off Zip Lines, Airplanes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite: Battle Royale season 7 is less than 24 hours away, and Epic just dropped the final teaser for its snow and ice-themed winter offering. In it we can see what yesterday’s teaser had only hinted at: what looks like a new skin ziplining with a SCAR. The skin itself looks sort of like a wookie. The accompanying text is “Ascend to new heights,” which is right in line with yesterday’s snowboarding tease. It looks like new mobility options are going to be a focus in the upcoming season, making this game a little like Ring of Elysium. Fortnite Ziplines would be an exciting way to get aroun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4's Special Orders And Cosmetics Are Hot Garbage - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-special-orders-and-cosmetics-are-hot-garbage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOGgliTUlv6M8ir0-qJ3FsYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/06/call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-special-orders-and-cosmetics-are-hot-garbage/" target="_blank"&gt;Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4's Special Orders And Cosmetics Are Hot Garbage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black Ops 4′s cosmetics are bad, overpriced junk. When Treyarch and Activision announced the new progression system for Call of Duty: Black Ops 4, I felt it was a big step in the right direction—away from loot boxes and toward something more akin to the Fortnite Battle Pass and Item Shop. In Black Ops 4, you can unlock various cosmetic rewards by simply playing the game as you rank up your Black Market Tiers (which reset each season), or you can visit Blackjack’s Shop to by cosmetic items that are regularly rotated. Finally, you can purchase Special Orders which are basically cosmetic bundl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite creative mode launched, offering entirely different experience to battle royale - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/fortnite-creative-mode-update-what-is-it-download-battle-pass-royale-a8668856.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH5un-jYmyOJSKGfnCsD_V4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/fortnite-creative-mode-update-what-is-it-download-battle-pass-royale-a8668856.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite creative mode launched, offering entirely different experience to battle royale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite has launched an entirely new "creative" mode, entirely separate from the battle royale it became famous for. In the latest update, players will be given the ability to stop trying to kill each other and instead work together to create entirely new worlds in which they can do whatever they want. The new features will arrive in the upcoming Season 7, developers Epic said in a blog post that introduced the new mode. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/42 5G wireless internet is expected to launch in 2019, with the potential to reach spe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Fortnite's Big Announcement Leaks Early: Check Out The Brand-New Creative Mode In Action - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/fortnites-big-announcement-leaks-early-check-out-the-brand-new-creative-mode-in-action/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDK4cQP_TL8cTBmFV5zRND8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/fortnites-big-announcement-leaks-early-check-out-the-brand-new-creative-mode-in-action/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite's Big Announcement Leaks Early: Check Out The Brand-New Creative Mode In Action&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Playground in Fortnite. We knew there was a big announcement coming for Fortnite at the Game Awards on Thursday, and it looks like someone just broke embargo on it. Notice that I say Fortnite and not Fortnite: Battle Royale, though I do sometimes use the terms interchangeably. That’s because this new announcement looks to be a complete third mode for the rapidly expanding game, designed to stand beside Battle Royale and Save the World as something entirely different. It’s called Creative Mode, and it looks We first got a look at this thanks to a Youtuber who got an early peek at the game an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite to enter Minecraft territory with new Creative mode - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/dec/05/fortnite-to-launch-creative-mode</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBbM7Jw2PWHMnSMWxixI8qkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:29:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/dec/05/fortnite-to-launch-creative-mode" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite to enter Minecraft territory with new Creative mode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hit video game Fortnite is to get a Creative mode, allowing players to design and play on their own islands. In a major addition to the title, the new mode lets players fly freely around the environment, placing scenic elements, then designing their own mini-games to play with friends. Developer Epic Games is launching the new option, named Fortnite Creative, on 6 December. Best known for its free online multiplayer mode, Battle Royale, in which 100 players land on an island and shoot each other until only one remains, Fortnite has become one of the most successful video games of the la...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Everything You Need To Know About 'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Season 7: Theme, Battle Pass And More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/everything-you-need-to-know-about-fortnite-battle-royale-season-7-theme-battle-pass-and-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFZWj30O-KG1BbN4_A1Ub6wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/05/everything-you-need-to-know-about-fortnite-battle-royale-season-7-theme-battle-pass-and-more/" target="_blank"&gt;Everything You Need To Know About 'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Season 7: Theme, Battle Pass And More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;fortnite It’s time for another season in Fortnite: Battle Royale, that juggernaut of a cultural phenomenon that recently hit 200 million players. You may have been reading a lot about it recent days, but you might be a little bit confused if you’re still new to the game and wondering what exactly this ice king fellow has to do with a multiplayer shooter. Here’s what you need to know about Fortnite: Battle Royale Season 7. What Is It? A season in Fortnite refers to when the developer releases a new battle pass, which is a $10 purchase that unlocks more and more cosmetic items as you play, in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>You probably already own the No. 1 item on teenagers’ holiday wish list - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/for-the-first-time-teens-want-fortnite-v-bucks-and-cryptocurrency-instead-of-cash-2018-11-14</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOjLDARJb8Vc-CjxSjE1JLYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 18:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/for-the-first-time-teens-want-fortnite-v-bucks-and-cryptocurrency-instead-of-cash-2018-11-14" target="_blank"&gt;You probably already own the No. 1 item on teenagers’ holiday wish list&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Quentin Fottrell Fortnite ‘V-Bucks’ and Bitcoin are also making an appearance on their holiday wish lists Some American teenagers want cryptocurrency and Fortnite “V-Bucks” virtual currency instead of cash. Getty Images/iStockphoto You might want the same thing as your child this holiday season. Some U.S. holiday wish lists crisscross all generations and some, well, don’t. Analyst firm Piper Jaffray said the No. 1 item on U.S. teenagers’ wish list this holiday season is Apple’s (AAPL) iPhone. In fact, their top four consumer brands — Apple Watch, MacBooks and Airpods — all come in those...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Developer Epic Is Launching A Huge Steam Competitor With A Better Cut For Devs - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/04/fortnite-developer-epic-is-launching-a-huge-steam-competitor-with-a-better-cut-for-devs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKEOTyDwd4Ae5_BJ3Hl4TCAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 15:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/04/fortnite-developer-epic-is-launching-a-huge-steam-competitor-with-a-better-cut-for-devs/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Developer Epic Is Launching A Huge Steam Competitor With A Better Cut For Devs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Epic Store Split Big, big news in the PC gaming landscape today as all that Fortnite cash has propelled Epic to launch a truly massive project. Epic has announced the Epic Store, a direct competitor to Steam that undercuts the rate Valve’s service gives to developers. That’s the biggest news about this storefront without question. While Steam takes a 30% cut while leaving the developer 70%, the Epic store will take just a 12% cut while leaving 88% for the developer. And if your game is using Epic’s Unreal Engine, that 5% royalty fee will be taken out of Epic’s side, not yours. The timin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Season 7 Is Teasing The Biggest Map Changes Yet - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/04/fortnite-season-7-is-teasing-the-biggest-map-changes-yet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1D0IS-QT6B2TqufIXldDIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/04/fortnite-season-7-is-teasing-the-biggest-map-changes-yet/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Season 7 Is Teasing The Biggest Map Changes Yet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite The launch of a new Fortnite season is typically shrouded in mystery, but this time around we’ve got a little more to work with. Winter is coming to the island: Epic started teasing “a bitter cold” yesterday, and we’ve been slowly watching a snowstorm approach the island for a few weeks now. Also, it’s December: bringing snow and ice to the game is the sort of change we could have guessed at the beginning of last season, even the season before that. There are still some important questions, however, and everything we can see in the game so far is pointing towards the most dramatic ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Mountain Dew's New 'Game Fuel' Drink Has A Seriously Interesting Can - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mitchwallace/2018/12/05/mountain-dews-new-game-fuel-drink-has-a-seriously-interesting-can/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO9li-74Wq6_tP2E8UhvRoQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mitchwallace/2018/12/05/mountain-dews-new-game-fuel-drink-has-a-seriously-interesting-can/" target="_blank"&gt;Mountain Dew's New 'Game Fuel' Drink Has A Seriously Interesting Can&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let the gaming marathon begin. Feeling like your Red Dead Online fishing could use a little tune-up? Maybe that Fortnite Battle Royale dancing is starting to lag? Well, fear not, weary gamers, because Mountain Dew has your back with a brand new beverage, one that’s aiming to increase general gaming aptitude and slated to launch early next year. Planned for broad retail release in January of 2019 is Game Fuel (not to be confused with the powdered G Fuel), a specially concocted refreshment that Mountain Dew is calling ‘the first drink made by gamers, for gamers’. It’s essentially an evolution...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Season 7 Battle Pass Skins Leak Early Thanks To Apple's App Store - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/05/fortnite-season-7-battle-pass-skins-leak-early-thanks-to-apples-app-store/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIAN9JgN_rF0T3DHKF_qi9oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/12/05/fortnite-season-7-battle-pass-skins-leak-early-thanks-to-apples-app-store/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Season 7 Battle Pass Skins Leak Early Thanks To Apple's App Store&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The leak After yesterday when Epic called out Apple’s app store yesterday for being a restrictive, not-open platform for distribution as they launched their own storefront, today the app store has had its revenge, leaking the Fortnite season 7 “cover art” early, showing off three new skins in the process (HD image thanks to @CrossLeaks) Two of the skins appear to be the ones we’ve seen in the first two season 7 previews from Epic itself. We have some sort of evil look ice wizard in the center, then an armored cat on the left. The right with the tattoos and beard could end up being the one w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite developer Epic looking to take on Steam with its own digital games store - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-developer-epic-looking-take-steam-digital-games-store/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJQo0utUppKaY180gNDQa5UqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 16:57:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-developer-epic-looking-take-steam-digital-games-store/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite developer Epic looking to take on Steam with its own digital games store&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Epic Games has announced that it will be opening up its Epic Games Store to other developers as it looks to take on Valve's Steam platform on PC. The Fortnite developer has said that the new digital storefront will offer developers 88% of revenue made on game purchases, with Epic taking just a 12% cut. Epic will also waive the 5% royalty it takes for use of its Unreal Engine if the games are sold on the Epic Store. In comparison, developers selling their games on Steam have a 70/30 split with platform holder Valve. Valve has recently announced that it plans to reduce its cut on games that m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Epic Clears Ninja After An Extremely Stupid 'Fortnite' Witch Hunt - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/18/epic-clears-ninja-after-an-extremely-stupid-fortnite-witch-hunt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENRiWwdNVf30WZRM8UFjn_YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/18/epic-clears-ninja-after-an-extremely-stupid-fortnite-witch-hunt/" target="_blank"&gt;Epic Clears Ninja After An Extremely Stupid 'Fortnite' Witch Hunt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo by Robert Reiners/Getty Images It has been quite a year for Tyler “Ninja” Blevins, whose Fortnite gameplay has attracted millions of followers across Twitch and YouTube, resulting in him landing sponsorship deals and guest spots on The Ellen Show, in addition to a place on our 30 Under 30 list. But with newfound fame comes newfound trolls, and Ninja has been under fire by an angry segment of the Fortnite community in what has turned out to be well, something of a frame job, and he’s been cleared by Epic of what the community had accused him of doing. The way I understand the original ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 7 Video Games I'm Most Thankful For This Thanksgiving - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/11/22/the-7-video-games-im-most-thankful-for-this-thanksgiving/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAwsGCXRjOHqYYT6SmwwQo4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 19:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/11/22/the-7-video-games-im-most-thankful-for-this-thanksgiving/" target="_blank"&gt;The 7 Video Games I'm Most Thankful For This Thanksgiving&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are all the video games I’m most thankful for this Thanksgiving. Thanksgiving is finally here, and everyone is getting ready to sit down with family and stuff their faces with turkey, mashed potatoes and various baked goods. I suspect a fair few are also sitting down to watch football, movies or play video games. It’s gotten me thinking about the video games I’m most thankful for. Not necessarily the best video games ever made, but the ones that had some kind of a big impact on my life. I started gaming when I was young, though I can’t recall the first time I ever played a video game. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 'Fortnite' Monster: 200 Million Players, 8.3 Million Concurrents - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/28/the-fortnite-monster-200-million-players-8-3-million-concurrents/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBPX8lIsAbEqiyHpacdL0ykqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/28/the-fortnite-monster-200-million-players-8-3-million-concurrents/" target="_blank"&gt;The 'Fortnite' Monster: 200 Million Players, 8.3 Million Concurrents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite The era of Fortnite is far from over, as Epic has hit enough new milestones to start talking publicly about them again. Fortnite now has 200 million registered players, a 60% increase from June alone, when it last clocked in at 125 million. It also now has 8.3 million concurrent players on a regular basis, another huge jump from the last time we got these stats, 4.3 million in February. I mean, what else can even be said about Fortnite at this point? It’s a global gaming trend that I’ve rarely seen on this scale, not since Pokémon GO took over the world, but Fortnite has done that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Esports integrity chief concerned about Fortnite gambling - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/dc3ee6764e5142619a38d85bc8e46293</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENmZZjVGujoe7G6pmXy0nCsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwnZidAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 01:45:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/dc3ee6764e5142619a38d85bc8e46293" target="_blank"&gt;Esports integrity chief concerned about Fortnite gambling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The commissioner of the Esports Integrity Coalition says skill-based betting on battle royale games like Fortnite and PlayerUnknown's Battleground could be vulnerable to cheating. Esports gambling website Unikrn announced plans last month to bring legal skill-based betting to the U.S., allowing players to wager on themselves. Users would link their game to the Unikrn platform, and Unikrn will generate odds for the player based on his or her profile within the game. ESIC Commissioner Ian Smith says such wagering is likely to be popular, but he's concerned the industry is not yet prepared to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite: The Story So Far' Is A Must-Watch Video That Took Eight Months To Film - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/27/fortnite-the-story-so-far-is-a-must-watch-video-that-took-eight-months-to-film/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQ_lJWIHmAZDB6JPwg04kIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/27/fortnite-the-story-so-far-is-a-must-watch-video-that-took-eight-months-to-film/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite: The Story So Far' Is A Must-Watch Video That Took Eight Months To Film&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Fortnite remains one of the most strangely fascinating games out there with an engaging story that…is barely a story at all. There are characters, but few have names and literally no one talks. There are big moments that take place in the game that has the community buzzing, yet almost no one truly understands what’s going on. From seasons 3-6, Fortnite has been telling effectively one story, with one event leading into another the seems to have culminated, and possibly ended, midway through season 6. YouTuber LaffenGas has been filming for eight months now, capturing every major e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite Has Bridged the Gap Between E-Sports and Traditional Sports - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/leighsteinberg/2018/11/30/fortnite-has-bridged-the-gap-between-e-sports-and-traditional-sports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBOE41XJpt_uir7-bAM7bbAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 18:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/leighsteinberg/2018/11/30/fortnite-has-bridged-the-gap-between-e-sports-and-traditional-sports/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite Has Bridged the Gap Between E-Sports and Traditional Sports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cross convergence of sports and video games just accelerated with the recent announcement that the NFL and Fortnite are doing a deal to feature jerseys from each of the 32 teams in gameplay. This is the first major deal between a video game company and a major sports league. Fortnite is an action video game which has become a sensation, especially among athletes. Professional athletes in football, soccer, and other sports have broken out in Fortnite celebration dances during real-world sporting events. NFL players like Colts TE Eric Ebron have been mimicking Fortnite dances and other an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Esports: console survivors - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/737001b2-ef2f-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIGqx4q413WvjuGHxt-XmgYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 19:16:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/737001b2-ef2f-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Esports: console survivors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Electronic sports were once seen as an oxymoron. What could be less athletic than sitting in a chair and vaporising enemies on screen? But over the past 10 years, video games have come of age: not just as an activity, but as a spectator sport. Top gamers, such as 26-year old Kuro “KuroKy” Takhasomi of Germany, are famous. Their fans want to watch them play in the flesh, as well as online. Tournaments are multiplying fast. The largest dedicated esports facility in North America opens in Arlington, Texas, on Saturday. Eight teams will play terrorism-themed Counter-Strike at its launch. Winnin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Primary school pupils playing 'strip Fortnite', parents warned - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/primary-school-pupils-playing-strip-fortnite-parents-warned/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA7gjfRVvEZE3V0Zw4jrkV0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:18:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/primary-school-pupils-playing-strip-fortnite-parents-warned/" target="_blank"&gt;Primary school pupils playing 'strip Fortnite', parents warned&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Primary school pupils are playing 'strip Fortnite', parents have been warned. Middleton St Mary’s C of E Primary in Leeds told parents it had learned of a trend of children taking their clothes off in front of a webcam while playing the game. It warned that this was putting them at risk of being exposed to or accidentally sharing indecent images. Head Naomi Wood said: “The School Nursing Team have suggested that we share the following information with you. “Many of you may be aware of the risks and concerns around children playing the online game Fortnite, which has a 12 rating but is playe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>There's a new Fortnite craze overwhelming schools — but a ban would be straight out of Footloose - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-01/fortnite-dance-craze-takes-off/10572058</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECQo3kN2_8PE8evA6oO3N3kqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDc2g4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 18:00:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-01/fortnite-dance-craze-takes-off/10572058" target="_blank"&gt;There's a new Fortnite craze overwhelming schools — but a ban would be straight out of Footloose&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite. By now everyone has heard the name and depending on who you are, it can mean many different things. A fun and exciting free-to-play video game, or a plague on our children? An inspired business model that got its target just right, or a copycat upstart that dumbed down a hardcore game genre? But a dance teacher? That's something that has flown far below the radar for most observers, but I think this is one of the most important aspects of what the game has done to the culture that surrounds not only the game, but playground culture everywhere. The game is about a lot more than sho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Turrets Are Fortnite's Latest Problematic Plague, As Players And Pros Call For Nerfs - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/19/turrets-are-fortnites-latest-problematic-plague-as-players-and-pros-call-for-nerfs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI0jWaThlMH21AgKXFAgOh8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 12:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/19/turrets-are-fortnites-latest-problematic-plague-as-players-and-pros-call-for-nerfs/" target="_blank"&gt;Turrets Are Fortnite's Latest Problematic Plague, As Players And Pros Call For Nerfs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Fortnite recently added stationary turrets to its arsenal, and like many new weapons, there are some…issues. Usually we see new weapons debut as either under or overpowered, but it’s the latter case this time, as players and pros alike are complaining about how dominant turrets have become in the game in many situations. The problems with Fortnite turrets are twofold: First, turrets do an incredible amount of damage to both players and structures alike. They’re supposed to discourage rushing, but they may have gone too far in making that happen. Even Thanos himself seems puny next ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite: More than 200 million people have now played Battle Royale game - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/fortnite-players-how-many-million-download-battle-royale-ps4-xbox-switch-a8656761.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB99WYaGRbjqt_gbKtAk2LAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/fortnite-players-how-many-million-download-battle-royale-ps4-xbox-switch-a8656761.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite: More than 200 million people have now played Battle Royale game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite now has more than 200 million players, marking the latest stage of its intensely fast growth. The battle royale game – which throws 100 players onto an island and has them fight against each other to survive – smashed through the 40 million record in January. But it has kept growing, marking a 60 per cent improvement even since June. Over that time, the game has become a pop cultural phenomenon, as well as one of the biggest games ever to have been released. It has been referenced across popular culture and has raised vast amounts of money through microtransactions. Gadgets and tec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>How To Send A Gift In 'Fortnite: Battle Royale' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/27/how-to-send-a-gift-in-fortnite-battle-royale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL6GqF0f5lZm24ioiWNabtcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/27/how-to-send-a-gift-in-fortnite-battle-royale/" target="_blank"&gt;How To Send A Gift In 'Fortnite: Battle Royale'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite This was first teased when the trees were still young, when there were old songs still not sung and the land was green and new. But gifting is finally here in Fortnite: Battle Royale, albeit it only for a limited time. It’s essentially a streamlined version of the sort of thing people have been doing since the game first launched. It gives you the ability to send a cosmetic item to another player directly from the in-game menu: you get charged, they get the gift. For the past few seasons I’ve been sending my nephews Xbox gift cards with the intention of buying things, and now I can...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Parents losing battle with Fortnite as children forced into rehab for video game addiction - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-addiction-video-games-rehab-children-battle-royale-parents-a8665071.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEMYW9VO417_ehAdlXpc-HYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 16:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-addiction-video-games-rehab-children-battle-royale-parents-a8665071.html" target="_blank"&gt;Parents losing battle with Fortnite as children forced into rehab for video game addiction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Debbie Vitany is fighting a losing battle against Fortnite. Her 17-year-old son, Carson, has been logging 12 hours a day on the video game, searching for weapons and resources in a post-apocalyptic world where the goal is being the last person standing. Teachers complain he falls asleep in class and his grades have plummeted. “We’d made some progress in getting him to cut down his Fortnite hours and get better sleep, but he’s slipped back into his old habits,” Ms Vitany, who lives near Saginaw, Michigan, said in an interview. “I’ve never seen a game that has such control over kids’ minds.” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Is Doing Something Different Than Past Seasons For Season 7 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/26/fortnite-is-doing-something-different-than-past-seasons-for-season-7/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEBmByRtGzj2ZbeVVjz1AGUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/26/fortnite-is-doing-something-different-than-past-seasons-for-season-7/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Is Doing Something Different Than Past Seasons For Season 7&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite We are just a little over one week away from the arrival of Fortnite season 7, and the current state of the game is something I was not expecting to see ahead of a new season. It’s clear that Fortnite is doing something pretty different from what we’ve seen in the past. As in, in this case, it resolved its main “storyline” in the middle of the season, more or less, and we’ve had a time of relatively in-game peace and quiet ever since. This is different than significant transitions in past seasons. We have season 3’s comet that crashed to earth and created Dusty Divot the moment sea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite player count rises 60pc in six months to reach 200 million - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-player-count-rises-60-six-months-reach-200-million/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENH9FOQOqTUZR5-MhsDowq8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:46:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/fortnite-player-count-rises-60-six-months-reach-200-million/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite player count rises 60pc in six months to reach 200 million&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The popularity of Battle Royale phenomenon Fortnite shows no signs of abating. In another arresting milestone, the developer of the smash video game Epic Games has said that Fortnite now has 200 million registered users. This makes for a 60pc jump on the 125 million player-count Epic revealed in June. While many of those 200 million registered users will not be playing the game regularly, Epic also said that Fortnite also recently achieved a record concurrent player count of 8.3 million. This particular figure is one of the clearest indicators of the gaming's extraordinarily successful year...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fortnite facing legal threats over 'stolen' dances, but can you copyright choreography? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/fortnite-facing-legal-threats-stolen-dances-can-copyright-choreography/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPsIwPxxDagDm_l0u8dR3gqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 07:18:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/fortnite-facing-legal-threats-stolen-dances-can-copyright-choreography/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite facing legal threats over 'stolen' dances, but can you copyright choreography?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can you copyright a dance move? What exactly are my legal rights over my uncoordinated Saturday night fever? Do I have a case if, say, a video game creates a dance move called ‘flailing water butt’ and charges its players money to be able to use it in game? Probably not. But more coordinated and famous dance artists just might. Earlier this week, the thorny issue of Epic Games allegedly 'stealing' dances from the real world in its phenomenally popular Fortnite Battle Royale game reared its head again. If you have missed the memo on Fortnite’s ‘emotes’, they are actions, flourishes and dance...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Here's Nvidia's New GeForce 'Fortnite' Counterattack Bundle, And How To Get It - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/29/heres-nvidias-new-geforce-fortnite-counterattack-bundle-and-how-to-get-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDK2y8SDmXu_4bWHob3g9vsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/29/heres-nvidias-new-geforce-fortnite-counterattack-bundle-and-how-to-get-it/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's Nvidia's New GeForce 'Fortnite' Counterattack Bundle, And How To Get It&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Switch has one, PS4 has one, Xbox has one, even Samsung Galaxy. And now PC Players have their own bundle of Fortnite cosmetics, or at least some PC players. Epic Games and Nvidia just announced a new GeForce bundle that comes along with new qualifying graphics cards and laptops. It’s called “Counterattack:” with the purchase of a qualifying card you’ll get the Reflex outfit, the Response Unit back bling, Pivot Glider, Angular Axe harvesting tool and, as always, 2,000 v-bucks. Let’s take a look: fortnite They’re not bad, and like most of the Twitch Prime or hardware bundles, they follow a sl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Apple Unveils 2018's Most Popular Apps: Fortnite, YouTube, Minecraft And More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/12/04/apple-unveils-2018s-most-popular-apps-youtube-fortnite-minecraft-and-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAO7MdGnBE_q5uTbuq7rcrUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/12/04/apple-unveils-2018s-most-popular-apps-youtube-fortnite-minecraft-and-more/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple Unveils 2018's Most Popular Apps: Fortnite, YouTube, Minecraft And More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite and YouTube were the absolute most popular apps of 2018, for both iPhones and iPads. Selfie-editor FaceTune ($3.99) was the most popular paid app on the iPhone while drawing app Procreate ($9.99) won the top spot on the iPad. (Photo by Hannah Smith / ESPAT Media / Getty Images) Today, Apple unveiled the list of the most popular apps and games (free and paid) for iPhone and iPad in 2018 and you’ll find below the top 10 charts for each category. This year, Battle Royale-style games like Fortnite and PUBG Mobile dominated global gaming culture with exciting, last-player-standing actio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 'Fortnite' Season 7 Snowstorm Is Actually A Floating Ice Castle About To Crash Into The Island - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/29/the-fortnite-season-7-snowstorm-is-actually-a-floating-ice-castle-about-to-crash-into-the-island/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA87cf_tV7eGwamxs-kmDngqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/29/the-fortnite-season-7-snowstorm-is-actually-a-floating-ice-castle-about-to-crash-into-the-island/" target="_blank"&gt;The 'Fortnite' Season 7 Snowstorm Is Actually A Floating Ice Castle About To Crash Into The Island&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Players know that winter is coming to Fortnite, and they have been able to see a storm brewing on the horizon for a little while now by looking to the south of the map. But today’s update has made the storm draw closer, and has revealed that actually, it’s not a storm at all. What looks like a storm is actually a cloud concealing an iceberg which appears to be drifting toward the Fortnite map in an inevitable collision course. It’s hard to see with the naked eye, as this was the best shot I could snag of it in the game, but you can see the base of it and the ice around it. Fortnite...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Walmart Is Giving Away Free 'Fortnite' Sprays, Here's How To Get Them - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/02/walmart-is-giving-away-free-fortnite-sprays-heres-how-to-get-them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEWBpZD00NIDfXkx3l2lN1wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 12:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/02/walmart-is-giving-away-free-fortnite-sprays-heres-how-to-get-them/" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart Is Giving Away Free 'Fortnite' Sprays, Here's How To Get Them&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite: Battle Royale. If you want a free Fortnite spray today, you’re going to have to leave the house, unless you live in a Walmart. The mega-retailer is hosting Fortnite parties across the country today featuring, among other things, a code for a free spray for everyone that shows up. Don’t worry! You can still play Fortnite on the way, so long as you get someone else to drive. The event is today, December 2. It runs from 2:00 p.m.– 4:00 p.m. local time at Walmarts across the country. Here’s the description from the press release: “On Sunday, all Supercenters and Walmart Stores will ge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Making millions from 'Fortnite' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2018/11/20/making-millions-from-fortnite-beme.beme</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBUG2XQrIz7_rmz5Cc0WGs4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 19:10:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2018/11/20/making-millions-from-fortnite-beme.beme" target="_blank"&gt;Making millions from 'Fortnite'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fortnite Battle Royale" has sparked a worldwide phenomenon since its release last year, and the game's top streamers are earning millions of dollars. What does it take to reach streaming stardom? ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>A New 'Fortnite' Awaits In Blockchain Gaming - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidpetersson/2018/11/16/a-new-fortnite-awaits-in-blockchain-gaming/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGSanBzD24AmJpvtCu9LpFQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidpetersson/2018/11/16/a-new-fortnite-awaits-in-blockchain-gaming/" target="_blank"&gt;A New 'Fortnite' Awaits In Blockchain Gaming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fortnite Effect The Epic Games Inc. Fortnite: Battle Royale video game is displayed for a photograph on an Apple Inc. iPhone in Washington, D.C., U.S., on Thursday, May 10, 2018. Fortnite, the hit game that’s denting the stock prices of video-game makers after signing up 45 million players, didn’t really take off until it became free and a free-for-all. Photographer: Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg Fortnite is one of the most profitable games in history—and growing. Since launch, the free-to-play game has brought in more than $1.2 billion in revenue. I also holds the record for most revenues in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The US military is using video games and esports to recruit – it's downright immoral - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/army-military-video-game-fortnite-battlegrounds-call-duty-esports-defence-a8648656.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK38SViTbpoEpeHnRYRpdWwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 14:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/army-military-video-game-fortnite-battlegrounds-call-duty-esports-defence-a8648656.html" target="_blank"&gt;The US military is using video games and esports to recruit – it's downright immoral&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the US army’s fiscal year this past September, the independent military news source Army Times reported that it had failed to meet its recruitment target by 7,500 bodies, despite offering up to $40,000 in bonuses, shorter enlistments and student loan repayments. Last week, via a Reddit Ask Me Anything forum, the US military announced its intention to create a military-branded esports team and enter into a video games competition. The military said the team would be populated by active personnel, reservists and veterans, bringing together accomplished players of first-person sh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Season 6, Week 9 Challenges Revealed And How To Solve Them - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/22/fortnite-season-6-week-9-challenges-revealed-and-how-to-solve-them/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK8lDlViu4INGK1yAVSCUckqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 13:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/22/fortnite-season-6-week-9-challenges-revealed-and-how-to-solve-them/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Season 6, Week 9 Challenges Revealed And How To Solve Them&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Fortnite season 6 is winding down, and as we head to season 7, it appears a robot is about to murder some people, a blizzard is coming, or both. But until that happens, we have two more weeks of challenges to get through, especially if you want that robot Hunting Party skin. This week’s batch of Fortnite challenges is…interesting. I’m still trying to puzzle out the difficulty, but there’s definitely a theme, at least with the battle pass challenge. Here they are: Free - Get 30s of airtime in a vehicle (0/30) - Get a score of 10 or more on different Carnival Clown Boards (0/3) - Sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Battlefield 5 review | A great WW2 shooter lies beneath a slim, scrappy and confusing release - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/battlefield-5-review-great-ww2-shooter-lies-beneath-slim-scrappy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHNY_UTX_sAD5OCbTD_b30qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 12:57:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/battlefield-5-review-great-ww2-shooter-lies-beneath-slim-scrappy/" target="_blank"&gt;Battlefield 5 review | A great WW2 shooter lies beneath a slim, scrappy and confusing release&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Battlefield 5 is without doubt one of the most perplexing video game releases of recent years. Not because there isn’t a thunderous, entertaining World War II multiplayer shooter here, because there is. But because it is so resolutely unfinished. Even putting aside the staggered release that publisher EA has begun to put into practice (with EA Access subscribers and Deluxe Edition owners getting to play the game early), Battlefield 5 arrives on its official release date with chunks missing. Faded out menu options with promised December release dates for the Tides of War multiplayer meta-gam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fortnite: Pedophiles Lurk Where Children Gather - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/14/fortnite-pedophiles-lurk-where-children-gather/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHUDARAv8klpFU_8ntkQ-EMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/14/fortnite-pedophiles-lurk-where-children-gather/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite: Pedophiles Lurk Where Children Gather&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Fortnite’ Unless you’ve been living under a rock for the past year, you know that Forniteis a world-wide video game sensation. Millions of people play every day. Who are they? Unfortunately, Epic Games, Fortnite’s developer, hasn’t released information about the game’s demographics. Fornitehas a PEGI rating of 12, but it’s clear that many younger children are playing. It’s also clear that some of those children are at risk from sexual predators. Pedophiles lurk where children gather. Last week the CBC reported that police in the Montreal area are working with local school boards to make pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite's Leaked Season 6, Week 8 Challenges Are All Lies - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/13/fortnites-leaked-season-6-week-8-challenges-are-all-lies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIkdCRL6h8uLgjLBbDrKqUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 14:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/13/fortnites-leaked-season-6-week-8-challenges-are-all-lies/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite's Leaked Season 6, Week 8 Challenges Are All Lies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Every week for the last few seasons now, I’ve been posting the leaked challenges for the upcoming week of Fortnite. Without fail, leakers are able to extract them from the game, but this time, something is…amiss. Here are what are supposed to be the leaked challenges for season 6, week 8 of Fortnite: Free Challenges - Place Traps (0/10) - Search chests in Wailing Woods (0/7) - Shotgun Eliminations (0/4) [HARD] Battle Pass Challenges - Deal damage with a pickaxe to opponents (0/250) - Use a Rift at different spawn locations (0/10) - Search between three Oversized Seats (0/1) [HARD] ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>10 Perfect And Affordable Holiday Gifts For 'Fortnite' Gamers And Fans - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/12/10-perfect-and-affordable-holiday-gifts-for-fortnite-gamers-and-fans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHXD0PW32gTsJ3AkqC_KBt0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 19:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/12/10-perfect-and-affordable-holiday-gifts-for-fortnite-gamers-and-fans/" target="_blank"&gt;10 Perfect And Affordable Holiday Gifts For 'Fortnite' Gamers And Fans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite fans are serious about their passion. In many ways, it’s like they speak their own language–at least when they’re talking about the game. Gift Ideas for Fortnite Fans (Photo by Chesnot/Getty Images) If you know someone who plays a lot of Fortnite, and you’re wondering what to buy them this holiday season, I have some pretty safe game-related gift suggestions for you. V-Bucks The safest gift that you can buy a Fortnite fan is V-Bucks. If you’re unaware, it’s the in-game currency that allows gamers to purchase skins and other digital products. You can get 1,000 V-Bucks for $9.99, 250...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite' Has Let Ghoul Trooper Remain One Of Its Rarest Skins Ever - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/12/fortnite-has-let-ghoul-trooper-remain-one-of-its-rarest-skins-ever/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENf8nhV39Ws8aL4eu5cRDgIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 14:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/12/fortnite-has-let-ghoul-trooper-remain-one-of-its-rarest-skins-ever/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite' Has Let Ghoul Trooper Remain One Of Its Rarest Skins Ever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite We are now moving rapidly toward Thanksgiving and deep into season 6 of Fortnite. The game’s Halloween event, Fortnitemares, has come and gone with the Cube explosion, but one significant aspect of the season remains a mystery. Why did Ghoul Trooper never make a return, in any form, to the store? Ghoul Trooper and Skull Trooper were a pair of Halloween skins that were released a year ago in 2017 before Fortnite: BR was the global phenomenon it is now. As such, they became two of the most sought after skins in the game, because they were not sold again after that point, so only “OG”...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>From Pac-Mania to Fortnite fever: are video games becoming more addictive? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/14/video-games-becoming-more-addictive-fortnite-pac-man-space-invaders</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFMFf0RDCJyBiNBXs4F9nlQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 14:31:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/14/video-games-becoming-more-addictive-fortnite-pac-man-space-invaders" target="_blank"&gt;From Pac-Mania to Fortnite fever: are video games becoming more addictive?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2001, a young graduate named John Hopson wrote a detailed article for the industry website Gamasutra on the topic of behavioural game design. Hopson, an amateur game-designer, decided to pair his hobby and his research, detailing in coolly clinical terms concepts that the industry had previously handled primarily through intuition and artistry. “Under what circumstances do players stop playing, and how can you avoid them?” Hopson asked. “Motivation is relative: the desire to play your game is always being measured against other activities.” Hopson offered a number of suggestions to devel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite': How To Complete The Hunting Party Challenge And Unlock The A.I.M. Robot Skin - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/09/fortnite-how-to-complete-the-hunting-party-challenge-and-unlock-the-a-i-m-robot-skin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-jj_1eYiWaNm4dl53Ys88qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 15:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/09/fortnite-how-to-complete-the-hunting-party-challenge-and-unlock-the-a-i-m-robot-skin/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite': How To Complete The Hunting Party Challenge And Unlock The A.I.M. Robot Skin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite If you want to show off your greatest accomplishments in Fortnite: Battle Royale, the Tier-100 battle pass skin just isn’t going to cut it. Sure, Dire is one cool-looking Werewolf, particularly once you evolve him past his odd human phase and turn him into a ferocious beast of the night. But let’s be real: you could just buy Dire if you wanted it, though shelling out all the cash to fully level the battle pass isn’t cheap. The real achievement for any given Fortnite season is the challenge skin, which just became availabl1e for Season 6 yesterday through the Hunting Party challenge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Official NFL Jersey Skins Are Coming To 'Fortnite' Today: Here's What Time And How Much They'll Cost - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/09/official-nfl-jersey-skins-are-coming-to-fortnite-today-heres-what-time-and-how-much-theyll-cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF1zUbSgldPOzhntb53d-UcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/09/official-nfl-jersey-skins-are-coming-to-fortnite-today-heres-what-time-and-how-much-theyll-cost/" target="_blank"&gt;Official NFL Jersey Skins Are Coming To 'Fortnite' Today: Here's What Time And How Much They'll Cost&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Whenever we talk about character skins in Fortnite: Battle Royale, we remember one thing. Fortnite is a free-to-play game, and so all of this other stuff, whether it’s map updates, new items, gameplay changes or whatever, doesn’t make Epic one cent. It’s important in the process that gets people committed and spending money, of course, but when the rubber hits the road every single dime Epic makes comes from selling cosmetics. And in the case of these NFL skins, I get the feeling they’re going to make a whole lot of dimes. Starting tonight, November 9, players will be able to buy o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>30 Under 30 In Games 2019: The Creators And Players Leveling Up The Games Industry - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2018/11/13/30-under-30-in-games-2019-the-creators-and-players-leveling-up-the-games-industry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHtEyuAeF4Lm-7oMzubnFBUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 11:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2018/11/13/30-under-30-in-games-2019-the-creators-and-players-leveling-up-the-games-industry/" target="_blank"&gt;30 Under 30 In Games 2019: The Creators And Players Leveling Up The Games Industry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gaming is a constantly evolving $135 billion industry, and 2018 brought with it a mix of highlights and challenges. While esports exploded in growth with major investments and permanent league associations, game studios continue to struggle with sustainability and rising budgets. It’s against this backdrop that Forbes presents this year’s 30 Under 30 in Games, a group of individuals striking new paths and riding through a whirlwind of change. Bringing esports to high schools is one such venture. Delane Parnell’s PlayVS greatly simplifies the process of building competitive high school squad...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>