<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Facebook - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREo1TVhaNkVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:10:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Facebook adds $9 billion to share buyback effort - Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.ug/facebook-adds-9-billion-to-share-buyback-effort/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiTmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmluZGVwZW5kZW50LmNvLnVnL2ZhY2Vib29rLWFkZHMtOS1iaWxsaW9uLXRvLXNoYXJlLWJ1eWJhY2stZWZmb3J0L9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 06:00:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.ug/facebook-adds-9-billion-to-share-buyback-effort/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook adds $9 billion to share buyback effort&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;San Francisco, United States | AFP | Facebook said Friday it would add $9 billion to its stock buyback program, which could scoop up shares pummeled over the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.ug">Independent</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/lEgVDYAJ8kG_yz1MzDwXRYUSaetirYSLNJYIrY5TjRlkZBYB7D_MIWZrOWDsBJt2GUlzBfsgIdZx3plGWUOsnxUMjs_ab_er5g6FiBGZ4WEr3xcVeu24Sysq=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Italy fines Facebook for selling users' data - Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.ug/italy-fines-facebook-for-selling-users-data/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiSmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmluZGVwZW5kZW50LmNvLnVnL2l0YWx5LWZpbmVzLWZhY2Vib29rLWZvci1zZWxsaW5nLXVzZXJzLWRhdGEv0gEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:30:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.ug/italy-fines-facebook-for-selling-users-data/" target="_blank"&gt;Italy fines Facebook for selling users' data&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rome, Italy | AFP | Italy's competition authority has fined Facebook 10 million euros ($11.3 million) for selling users' data without informing them and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.ug">Independent</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/lEgVDYAJ8kG_yz1MzDwXRYUSaetirYSLNJYIrY5TjRlkZBYB7D_MIWZrOWDsBJt2GUlzBfsgIdZx3plGWUOsnxUMjs_ab_er5g6FiBGZ4WEr3xcVeu24Sysq=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Iceland pt. XVI - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/285673277/iceland-pt-xvi-by-christian-m%C3%B6hrle</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENxEukMRFwwFdYEX6aEqiSYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:17:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/285673277/iceland-pt-xvi-by-christian-m%C3%B6hrle" target="_blank"&gt;Iceland pt. XVI&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;POST PROCESSING | INSTAGRAM | FACEBOOK Hvítserkur, Iceland&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Facebook faces major repercussions if it continues to resist government scrutiny - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/opinions/facebook-resist-government-scrutiny-urbelis/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBkixpqkfygSOxK4FbtxdkIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 03:02:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/opinions/facebook-resist-government-scrutiny-urbelis/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook faces major repercussions if it continues to resist government scrutiny&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexander J. Urbelis is a lawyer and self-described hacker with more than 20 years' experience with information security. He has worked as a graduate fellow in the Office of General Counsel of the Central Intelligence Agency, as a law clerk at the US Court of Appeals for the Armed Forces and as an associate in the New York and Washington offices of Steptoe &amp; Johnson. He was also information security counsel and chief compliance officer of one of the world's largest luxury conglomerates. He is currently a partner in the Blackstone Law Group and CEO of a separate information security consulta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Facebook adopts bizarre new anti-sex speech code in secret - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445935-facebook-anti-sex-policy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOrTY17XQwi1t_vw56V7OCUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:36:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445935-facebook-anti-sex-policy/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook adopts bizarre new anti-sex speech code in secret&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has opted to purge its platform of all sex-related content with a new policy banning everything from nude pictures to “sexualized slang,” up to and including “vague suggestive statements” – without informing its users. The new “sexual solicitation” rules were adopted in mid-October, according to PCMag, and forbid everything from pornography to “implicit sexual solicitation.” The latter term is purposefully vague, encompassing “vague suggestive statements, such as ‘looking for a good time tonight,’” discussion of “sexual partner preference,” content (including hand-drawn art) that d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>78° North - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/285674815/78-north-by-hermes-s</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECv9bNgHmSE8jOo_oWoilasqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:29:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/285674815/78-north-by-hermes-s" target="_blank"&gt;78° North&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you very much for your visit! If you wish, you could "LIKE" my FB page.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Facebook fears more secret documents have been leaked - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/08/facebook-fears-secret-documents-have-leaked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELJwV5onWUV6NFDlAB8daOkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/08/facebook-fears-secret-documents-have-leaked/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook fears more secret documents have been leaked&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook fears that the confidential internal documents published by Parliament earlier this week may only be a fraction of what has been leaked. Lawyers for the social media giant told a California judge on Friday that they still did not know what other material might now be in circulation and might soon be released. The emails and memos, seized last month by MPs from an American app developer, Ted Kramer, and published on Wednesday, are part of a legal archive thought to include hundreds of thousands of documents. "We literally don't know what information is out there," said Sonal Mehta, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Facebook fined £8.9m by Italy for misleading users over data use - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/facebook-fine-italy-user-data-scandal-privary-settings-cambridge-analytica-social-media-a8673376.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH_pcp8sG34nvIr7W1zqRvcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/facebook-fine-italy-user-data-scandal-privary-settings-cambridge-analytica-social-media-a8673376.html" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook fined £8.9m by Italy for misleading users over data use&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has been fined almost £9m by Italian authorities for misleading users about how it used their data. Italy’s competition watchdog handed the social media giant two fines totalling €10m (£8.9m), the first for “misleadingly” encouraging people to sign up “without informing them in an immediate and adequate way” of how their data would be sold to third parties. The second fine was for “aggressively” discouraging users from trying to limit how the company shared their personal information, by telling them that doing so risked them experiencing “significant limitations”. The fine dwarfs ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Italian regulator fines Facebook £8.9m for misleading users - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/07/italian-regulator-fines-facebook-89m-for-misleading-users</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBeriqdValiwaGna321ObasqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/07/italian-regulator-fines-facebook-89m-for-misleading-users" target="_blank"&gt;Italian regulator fines Facebook £8.9m for misleading users&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has been fined €10m (£8.9m) by Italian authorities for misleading users over its data practices. The two fines issued by Italy’s competition watchdog are some of the largest levied against the social media company for data misuse, dwarfing the £500,000 fine levied by the British Information Commissioner’s Office in September – the maximum that body is able to issue. The Italian regulator found that Facebook had breached articles 21, 22, 24 and 25 of the country’s consumer code by: - Misleading users in the sign-up process about the extent to which the data they provide would be use...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The Dark Days Of Facebook, And The Light Ahead - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidvolodzko/2018/12/07/the-dark-days-of-facebook-and-the-light-ahead/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMe1eKseMiWbbW8TZ_jl0ZEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidvolodzko/2018/12/07/the-dark-days-of-facebook-and-the-light-ahead/" target="_blank"&gt;The Dark Days Of Facebook, And The Light Ahead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Facebook Inc. application on an Apple Inc. iPhone. Photographer: Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg Facebook just suffered the ugliest few weeks in its history, and I’m not talking about its shares plunging over 40% in the last four months. The company allegedly sold user data to businesses in secret deals, according to emails and internal documents released this week by U.K. lawmakers. Facebook has for years been collecting Android phone data — dates, times, call lengths, call recipients, phone numbers and text messages — even when people weren’t using its app, and it sold the personal data of ov...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Instagram best nine 2018: How to find your top photos of the year and share the collage - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/instagram-best-nine-2018-9-how-to-make-top-photos-collage-share-post-a8672786.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILKUQHOUzA1_vXO2wcHdqsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/instagram-best-nine-2018-9-how-to-make-top-photos-collage-share-post-a8672786.html" target="_blank"&gt;Instagram best nine 2018: How to find your top photos of the year and share the collage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the year draws to a close, people are rushing to make their Instagram best nine and find their most popular pictures of the year. The annual collage has become something of a tradition, allowing people to reflect on the posts that were liked most by their friends throughout the year. In 2018, there are a whole range of tools that make it very easy. Instagram doesn't offer the feature, however. Thankfully, you don't have to pick through all your pictures and find out the best ones: there's plenty of websites available to do that for you. The best one appears to be topnine.co, which includ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Facebook is no longer the best place to work in America - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/facebook-is-no-longer-the-best-place-to-work-in-america-2018-12-04</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECM5e1bFgm8430zM-u7ekzsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/facebook-is-no-longer-the-best-place-to-work-in-america-2018-12-04" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook is no longer the best place to work in America&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Quentin Fottrell This week Glassdoor released its annual list of the best companies to work at, as voted by their own employees Facebook fell from No. 1 on Glassdoor’s annual list to No. 7 this year. MarketWatch photo illustration/Getty Images, iStockphoto With unemployment at a 49-year low, are you looking for a job in 2019? These companies may be a good place to start. Global management company Bain &amp; Co. ranked No. 1 in career website Glassdoor’s annual “100 Best Places to Work” in 2019. Facebook (FB) the biggest social-media platform on the planet, which has been plagued by scandal a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Fed up with Facebook, U.S. fund managers look for alternatives - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-funds-facebook/fed-up-with-facebook-u-s-fund-managers-look-for-alternatives-idUSKBN1O519Y</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHoYO05Lh6RQAlWwOLUTVMgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:09:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-funds-facebook/fed-up-with-facebook-u-s-fund-managers-look-for-alternatives-idUSKBN1O519Y" target="_blank"&gt;Fed up with Facebook, U.S. fund managers look for alternatives&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook Inc's (FB.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) losses are becoming other companies' gains. Concerns about the social media giant's declining profit margins and battered reputation have prompted 93 U.S. mutual funds to completely sell out of their positions in the company so far this year, exacerbating a roughly 35 percent decline in Facebook's share price from its highs, according to Refinitiv’s Lipper research service. The selling by fund firms including Fidelity Investments, The Hartford and Putnam Investments combined for a total of nearly 12 million shares, and came amid si...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Online dating is bringing Americans of all religions, race and classes together - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/online-dating-is-bringing-americans-of-all-religions-race-and-classes-together-2018-02-12</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP8FGzNRSSn8NeDnSu8hWIsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwuJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/online-dating-is-bringing-americans-of-all-religions-race-and-classes-together-2018-02-12" target="_blank"&gt;Online dating is bringing Americans of all religions, race and classes together&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOVE &amp;AMP; MONEY By Quentin Fottrell Couples who meet online through any site are more likely to be interracial than those who met off-line Meeting online is associated with greater racial diversity than the ‘real’ world. Picturehouse/Courtesy Everett Collection This is the time of year when people sign up to dating sites in the hope they don’t see in the New Year alone, and they’re looking beyond their own social bubbles for love. Does online dating break down barriers? Research suggests it does. Dating sites bring people from different backgrounds together in a way that other parts of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Facebook DOWN in US Eastern Coast for hundreds of users - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445877-facebook-down-in-us-eastern/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0oAYzHRt6ANIpBzF2pbe8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445877-facebook-down-in-us-eastern/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook DOWN in US Eastern Coast for hundreds of users&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social media behemoth Facebook appears to be suffering from technical difficulties, with hundreds of users reporting the site down across the US Eastern seaboard. Reports flooded into Downdetector.com - a site where users can check up on and report outages - on Friday morning. Almost half of the reports were login issues, while another third reported the social network totally down. The remainder of the reports concerned Facebook’s mobile apps. © Downdetector Late last month, both Facebook and Instagram were hit with major worldwide outages, and Facebook’s Messenger app crashed for hundred...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>We Really Are Just Data For Sale In Facebook's Eyes - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kalevleetaru/2018/12/05/we-really-are-just-data-for-sale-in-facebooks-eyes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDxn9Z_VSJB9yPDJJwuLr-IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kalevleetaru/2018/12/05/we-really-are-just-data-for-sale-in-facebooks-eyes/" target="_blank"&gt;We Really Are Just Data For Sale In Facebook's Eyes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook logo. (JOEL SAGET/AFP/Getty Images) The release today by the British Parliament of the trove of internal Facebook emails from the Six4Three litigation offers an incredibly rich and unvarnished look at Facebook during a period when user growth appeared to outrank any consideration over user privacy or safety. While the company has long outwardly projected an image of a benevolent public works project to connect the world and a careful and trustworthy steward of the intimate information entrusted to it, its internal emails and decisions laid bare in the email trove capture a quite or...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Good for the world'? Facebook emails reveal what really drives the site - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/05/facebook-emails-analysis-user-data-parliament</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDiExVznwM5305ZPG9ZBDxMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 01:13:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/05/facebook-emails-analysis-user-data-parliament" target="_blank"&gt;'Good for the world'? Facebook emails reveal what really drives the site&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The central mythos of Facebook is that what’s good for Facebook is good for the world. More sharing, more friends and more connection will “make the world more open and connected” and “bring the world closer together”, Mark Zuckerberg has argued, even as his company has been engulfed by scandal. But confidential emails, released on Wednesday by the British parliament, reveal the hardheaded business calculations that lurked beneath the feelgood image projected by Zuckerberg and Facebook. “That may be good for the world, but it’s not good for us,” Zuckerberg wrote in a 2012 email about the po...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Facebook Says It's Anti-Conversion Therapy, But It Funded Candidates Who Voted Against Conversion Therapy Bans - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/facebook-says-its-anti-conversion-therapy-but-it-funded-candidates-who-voted-against-conversion-therapy-bans</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPL6QbTZ7eOyep9sOJcU3roqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMIv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:55:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/facebook-says-its-anti-conversion-therapy-but-it-funded-candidates-who-voted-against-conversion-therapy-bans" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook Says It's Anti-Conversion Therapy, But It Funded Candidates Who Voted Against Conversion Therapy Bans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Lyne Lucien/The Daily Beast Facebook prides itself on its support of LGBT rights. The social network has partnered with the Trevor Project—a suicide prevention organization for LGBT youth. The company maintains a perfect 100 score on the Human Rights Campaign’s Corporate Equality Index, which measures the strength of a company’s internal policies for LGBT employees and its public backing of the LGBT community. And earlier this year, Facebook publicly stated that “ads that promote gay conversion therapy” are prohibited. But a Daily Beast analysis of Facebook Inc. PAC—a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Fugitive taunts police appealing for his capture on Facebook: 'You ain't looking good enough!' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/burglar-facebook-post-comment-capture-harry-avis-sussex-police-a8670441.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELglUPocgiykbFBtrRaOgokqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/burglar-facebook-post-comment-capture-harry-avis-sussex-police-a8670441.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fugitive taunts police appealing for his capture on Facebook: 'You ain't looking good enough!'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wanted criminal has taunted police by openly commenting on their Facebook appeals for information leading to his arrest. Officers are seeking Harry Avis after he broke the terms of his early release from prison. So Sussex Police put out a message on their Facebook page last week offering £1,000 for information which led to his arrest. Within 45 minutes of the post going up, the 20-year-old himself commented underneath. He wrote: “I’m not hiding! You just ain’t looking good enough!” The force replied: “Hi Harry. So good to hear from you. Hope you are well. We’re good at hide and seek. We’v...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Salt flat in Tunisia - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/285541711/salt-flat-in-tunisia-by-olga-lipatova</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMEG7NhVlEtnbGKfQ6LH6AIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/285541711/salt-flat-in-tunisia-by-olga-lipatova" target="_blank"&gt;Salt flat in Tunisia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;http://mytravels.ru -- www.facebook.com/Olga.Lipatova.Photography -- www.instagram.com/odikti/&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Tommy Robinson threatened with legal action over 'bully' video - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/dec/06/tommy-robinson-threatened-with-legal-action-over-bully-video</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGkZvHa8Hm40S-JgQgpo7EEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:51:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/dec/06/tommy-robinson-threatened-with-legal-action-over-bully-video" target="_blank"&gt;Tommy Robinson threatened with legal action over 'bully' video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The far-right campaigner Tommy Robinson is being threatened with legal action after he posted a video identifying the alleged bully accused of assaulting a Syrian refugee child at school. Last week, footage was posted online showing the 15-year-old Syrian boy, who can only be identified as Jamal, being allegedly assaulted. The video of the playground incident at a school in Huddersfield, which showed Jamal being pushed to the ground and having water poured on his face, was watched millions of times and attracted widespread condemnation, including from Theresa May. In a video posted on Robin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Facebook spied on Android users’ calls &amp; texts while pretending to care about privacy - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445802-facebook-documents-privacy-android/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENI9VkEPJ5BBx0z149ttBE4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445802-facebook-documents-privacy-android/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook spied on Android users’ calls &amp; texts while pretending to care about privacy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook tried to conceal that it was secretly vacuuming up call and text logs from Android users without their permission, newly-released internal documents have revealed. The hundreds of pages of documents, which were previously sealed as part of an ongoing legal case with a now-defunct app developer called Six4Three, were released yesterday by the British parliament — and they confirm once again that Facebook is more than willing to sacrifice user privacy for company growth. Writing in an email to colleagues, Facebook engineer Micheal LeBeau acknowledged that it was a “pretty high risk t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Facebook's top AI scientist says it's 'dust' without artificial intelligence - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/tech/ai-facebook-lecun/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKtXHLHeVFj838vv7xHcvS0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:59:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/tech/ai-facebook-lecun/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook's top AI scientist says it's 'dust' without artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without artificial intelligence there wouldn't be much left of Facebook as we know it today. That's according to Yann LeCun, who founded Facebook's artificial intelligence research lab five years ago. "If you take the deep learning out of Facebook today, Facebook's dust," LeCun, Facebook's chief AI scientist, recently told CNN Business. "It's entirely built around it now." The technology is included in everything from the posts and translations you see in your news feed to advertisements. When LeCun established the lab, Facebook was already dabbling in deep learning — a type of machine lear...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Facebook emails reveal discussions over call log consent - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/06/facebook-emails-reveal-discussions-over-call-log-consent</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEyS-mtDY8TbXJhfSggWPH0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:36:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/06/facebook-emails-reveal-discussions-over-call-log-consent" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook emails reveal discussions over call log consent&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook employees discussed how to minimise the amount of consent needed to collect user data, according to the latest tranche of emails released by the UK parliament relating to the company’s mass collection of call and text logs. Since 2015, the social network has collected communications metadata from users who install its app on Android phones. In March this year that logging became public when users discovered details of their communications as they downloaded their personal data using new tools created to comply with the EU’s general data protection regulation (GDPR). Facebook has al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Dolomites - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/285491727/dolomites-by-christian-s-</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcSpMQEoSDsPckkQ8c-58cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:08:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/285491727/dolomites-by-christian-s-" target="_blank"&gt;Dolomites&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instagram | Website | Facebook&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Facebook discussed cashing in on user data, emails suggest - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/05/facebook-discussed-cashing-in-on-user-data-emails-suggest</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENCxfQzDKBwPHbi_AlGzNDQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:47:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/05/facebook-discussed-cashing-in-on-user-data-emails-suggest" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook discussed cashing in on user data, emails suggest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook staff in 2012 discussed selling access to user data to major advertisers, before ultimately deciding to restrict such access two years later, according to a tranche of internal emails released by the UK parliament. The internal emails were obtained by the House of Commons digital, culture, media and sport (DCMS) committee last month after they had been disclosed, under seal, by Facebook as part of a lawsuit against it by the American software developer, Six4Three. The emails are a selection, often with little or no context or continuity, showing Facebook staff, including the chief ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Facebook to buy back additional $9 billion of shares - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/facebook-buyback-idUSL4N1YC5AT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPGnorLo1jhhhOzEbCpRpxkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:56:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/facebook-buyback-idUSL4N1YC5AT" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook to buy back additional $9 billion of shares&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook Inc (FB.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) will buy back an additional $9 billion of its shares, as it looks to pacify investors following a slump in its stock. The social media giant's shares, which have tumbled more than 22 percent this year, rose nearly 1 percent in extended trading. The new program is in addition to a share buyback plan of up to $15 billion announced by the company last year. Facebook is being investigated by lawmakers in Britain after consultancy Cambridge Analytica, which worked on Donald Trump's U.S. presidential campaign, obtained personal data of 87 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Facebook testing 'QVC-like' live video streams - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/07/facebook-testing-qvc-like-live-video-streams/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPTzPiEqlCHexnZKmTMVCEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:44:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/07/facebook-testing-qvc-like-live-video-streams/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook testing 'QVC-like' live video streams&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook is setting up a “QVC-like” video streaming service that would allow companies to showcase products like they do on TV shopping channels. The feature, which is being trialed in Thailand, allows businesses to display and model their items through a live stream, as well as take reservations from buyers and request payments through the Messenger app. While watching the live product demos, users can tell the seller what item they want to purchase by sending the merchant a screenshot of the product from the stream. If the trial goes well the US tech giant could introduce the tool to othe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Five years after Lean In, Sheryl Sandberg’s manifesto for women is not working - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/06/five-years-lean-sheryl-sandbergs-manifesto-women-not-working/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELBubEsK-en_3Q4vu2VQNsEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/06/five-years-lean-sheryl-sandbergs-manifesto-women-not-working/" target="_blank"&gt;Five years after Lean In, Sheryl Sandberg’s manifesto for women is not working&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has been a difficult few weeks for Sheryl Sandberg. Facebook’s chief operating officer, long seen as the adult in the room at the social network, has been at the centre of an controversy over its hiring of a controversial communications firm, alleged attempts to suppress research into Russian interference, and attempts to dig up dirt on George Soros, a vocal critic. And now, she has fallen foul of Michelle Obama. The former first lady said earlier this week that Sandberg’s most famous idea, that women should “lean in” at work to challenge inequality, “doesn’t work all the time”. When Sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Forget Zuckerberg – the tech giants don’t have to own the future - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/05/zuckerberg-tech-giants-facebook-google-apple</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAgjunQtDiT3ksDF1nlxDb8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 06:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/05/zuckerberg-tech-giants-facebook-google-apple" target="_blank"&gt;Forget Zuckerberg – the tech giants don’t have to own the future&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A quarter of a century ago, the Canadian author Douglas Coupland published his third novel. Microserfs was the tale of a group of young Microsoft employees who decide to exit the realm of Bill Gates in Washington state and chase a dream of their own in California places that, back then, sounded like the epitome of futuristic magic: Palo Alto, Menlo Park. As well as prescient flashes of the world to come – “Beware of the corporate invasion of private memory,” warned one of its protagonists – what always stuck with me was its air of techno-optimism, perfectly crystallised right at the end, wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>These are some of the most notorious data breaches - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/11/30/notorious-data-breaches-facebook-marriott-yahoo-orig.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHKh6sb0SasETsmcURuBhwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:09:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/11/30/notorious-data-breaches-facebook-marriott-yahoo-orig.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;These are some of the most notorious data breaches&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marriott's data breach has potentially exposed personal information of approximately 500 million Starwood guests. The company joined Yahoo, Myspace, LinkedIn and more on the list of notorious data breaches in history. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Why you should check Twitter before naming your kid - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/millennials-are-using-facebook-and-twitter-to-name-their-children-2018-12-04</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJfTst9bOdqsm69gf05T_roqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/millennials-are-using-facebook-and-twitter-to-name-their-children-2018-12-04" target="_blank"&gt;Why you should check Twitter before naming your kid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MONEYISH By Catey Hill And that’s not a bad idea, some experts say, as using social media to inform a kid’s name could help them in the future Sleeping swaddled infant with a "Hello my name is" sticker iStock Young parents have a handle on naming their kids. “I have two kids — daughters — and social media played a role in both of their names,” Sara Mauskopf, a 33-year-old San Francisco mom and the founder of parenting app Winnie tells Marketwatch. While Mauskopf knew she wanted her now 3-year-old daughter’s first name to be Bryn, her requirements for a middle name were that it started with ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Standing against Soros: Facebook board defends COO Sandberg’s decision to snoop on billionaire - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445757-facebook-board-sandberg-soros/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIzPyqhJn3-PjTF9m7pfq1oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:54:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445757-facebook-board-sandberg-soros/" target="_blank"&gt;Standing against Soros: Facebook board defends COO Sandberg’s decision to snoop on billionaire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook’s board of directors has defended COO Sheryl Sandberg’s decision to conduct opposition research into liberal billionaire George Soros. Facebook was under intense scrutiny for running a PR campaign against the magnate. Sandberg admitted last week that she ordered staff to conduct research into Soros and his trading of Facebook stock, after he called the social media giant a “menace” to society during a speech at the World Economic Forum in Davos in January. In a letter to Patrick Gaspard, president of Soros’ Open Society Foundations NGO, Facebook’s board defended Sandberg’s decision...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Social Media Platforms Are Still Powerless To Stop Data Misuse - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kalevleetaru/2018/12/05/social-media-platforms-are-still-powerless-to-stop-data-misuse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL96u1I7DNf4l2_99EZAYlsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kalevleetaru/2018/12/05/social-media-platforms-are-still-powerless-to-stop-data-misuse/" target="_blank"&gt;Social Media Platforms Are Still Powerless To Stop Data Misuse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook logo. (Aytac Unal/Anadolu Agency/Getty Images) From Geofeedia to Cambridge Analytica, social media companies seem helpless to stop outside companies from repurposing the data of their users for surveillance and profiling against their terms of service, even as they themselves actively exploit their users for their own commercial profit and engage in their own sharing and profiling activities from special data partners to medical research. While the social media platforms continually reassure policymakers and the public that they have things under control, it seems not a month goes ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Make it snow - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/285433753/make-it-snow-by-alex-kuznetsov</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEORQOMFej2FT34u_zyOA7OoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:04:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/285433753/make-it-snow-by-alex-kuznetsov" target="_blank"&gt;Make it snow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instagram | VK | Tg | Facebook&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>WhatsApp hits Indian TVs with ads to tackle fake news after chat rumors turn deadly - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445448-whatsapp-tv-ads-fake-news/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6WraI-5G57ZsOLEPn4V4QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445448-whatsapp-tv-ads-fake-news/" target="_blank"&gt;WhatsApp hits Indian TVs with ads to tackle fake news after chat rumors turn deadly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WhatsApp has branched into Indian TV screens as it launched its first-ever film ads to urge users to spread joy and not rumors, after fake news on the chat app incited a spate of mob lynchings. From Monday, Indians, the world’s biggest users of WhatsApp, will be blasted with ads portraying the grave consequences of false information. The 60-second movies based on the experiences of real users will run on TV, in cinemas, as well as on YouTube and Facebook in nine different languages, including English and Hindi. The protagonists in all three films are ordinary people teaching someone close t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Confidential Facebook documents about data just got dumped. Here's what they say - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-06/facebook-six4three-documents-about-monetising-users-data-dumped/10588668</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK5oB49lMhE5vfXA9uxTHx8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:16:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-06/facebook-six4three-documents-about-monetising-users-data-dumped/10588668" target="_blank"&gt;Confidential Facebook documents about data just got dumped. Here's what they say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has been forced to explain its policies on personal data once again after a British parliamentary committee released more than 200 pages of confidential internal communications at the company. One of the emails shows founder and chief executive Mark Zuckerberg apparently discussing restricting "friends data" access to companies that had paid for it. He also told a colleague in 2012, a year before Cambridge Analytica was founded, "I'm generally sceptical that there is as much data leak strategic risk as you think." As well, the documents show Netflix and Airbnb retained access to us...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>I see you - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/285568739/i-see-you-by-harry-schindler</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL7EY6BkWZYcOAYMATcaj1EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:21:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/285568739/i-see-you-by-harry-schindler" target="_blank"&gt;I see you&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photoshop work - www.fb.com/fotostyleschindler - www.fotograf-straubing.de - www.onlywedding.de - www.instagram.com/fotostyle_schindler&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Facebook’s Sandberg admits to snooping on Soros - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445289-facebook-sandberg-admits-soros/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED8Q2sCPB7QQNfnF_KahNtIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445289-facebook-sandberg-admits-soros/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook’s Sandberg admits to snooping on Soros&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg requested opposition research into liberal billionaire George Soros, internal emails reveal. Sandberg had previously denied going after Soros, as had CEO Mark Zuckerberg. An explosive New York Times report two weeks ago revealed that Facebook had hired a PR firm to smear and discredit its critics as agents of Soros, a billionaire known worldwide for financing liberal causes. Zuckerberg and Sandberg denied any knowledge of Facebook’s work with the company, and Facebook’s outgoing Head of Communications, Elliot Schrage, last week took the fall for hiring the compa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Facebook documents published by UK – the key takeaways - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/05/facebook-documents-uk-parliament-key-facts</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEpsSawzaUiRIgs4f2FaMFsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:05:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/dec/05/facebook-documents-uk-parliament-key-facts" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook documents published by UK – the key takeaways&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK parliament has published a cache of confidential Facebook documents it obtained from a plaintiff in a California lawsuit. The records, which have been under seal in US courts, provided a rare window into internal discussions at the social network about privacy, user data, the company’s handling of competitors and more. Facebook’s director of developer platforms and programs, Konstantinos Papamiltiadis, told the Guardian in an earlier statement that the documents from the lawsuit “are only part of the story and are presented in a way that is very misleading without additional context”...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Sheryl Sandberg Ordered Facebook Staff To Target George Soros, NYT Reports - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sheryl-sandberg-george-soros-research_us_5c00a8fbe4b0d04f48b29a50</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELNkNMTTEsceexhErIAuxA4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 03:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sheryl-sandberg-george-soros-research_us_5c00a8fbe4b0d04f48b29a50" target="_blank"&gt;Sheryl Sandberg Ordered Facebook Staff To Target George Soros, NYT Reports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook executive Sheryl Sandberg reportedly asked communications staff to dig up information on George Soros in response to the billionaire liberal donor’s remarks against the social media giant, according to a New York Times report on Thursday. Citing three people with knowledge of Sandberg’s request, the Times report suggests that the chief operating officer was directly involved in Facebook’s controversial PR campaign against Soros. Sandberg reportedly made the request in January, days after Soros called Facebook a “menace to society” during a speech at the World Economic Forum. Facebo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Facebook and Google are still breaking campaign laws, says Washington State - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90274669/facebook-and-google-are-still-breaking-campaign-laws-says-washington-state</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC4xEmM3PFZ_MUkeWsWzl6YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90274669/facebook-and-google-are-still-breaking-campaign-laws-says-washington-state" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook and Google are still breaking campaign laws, says Washington State&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digital platforms like Facebook and Google must know when they’ve sold political ads aimed at influencing elections and make that information available to the public, regulators in Washington State said on Thursday, effectively rejecting claims by the companies that the requirement was too burdensome. In a unanimous vote, the state’s three-member Public Disclosure Commission reaffirmed a “final rule” on political ad disclosure that requires commercial advertisers to disclose a set of details about each political ad they run. Those details include the name and address of the ad’s purchaser, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Facebook gave data on user's friends to certain companies: documents - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-privacy-britain/facebook-gave-data-on-users-friends-to-certain-companies-documents-idUSKBN1O420Z</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIfQ4NTdpGRcU_zWX7IBN-0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:16:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-privacy-britain/facebook-gave-data-on-users-friends-to-certain-companies-documents-idUSKBN1O420Z" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook gave data on user's friends to certain companies: documents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook Inc (FB.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) let some companies, including Netflix (NFLX.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) and Airbnb, access users' lists of friends after it cut off that data for most other apps around 2015, according to documents released on Wednesday by a British lawmaker investigating fake news and social media. The 223 pages of internal communication from 2012 to 2015 between high-level employees, including founder and Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg, provide new evidence of previously aired contentions that Facebook has picked favorites and engaged...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Alpe di Siusi - Seiser Alm - Dolomites - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/285363703/alpe-di-siusi-seiser-alm-dolomites-by-hannes-heigl-photography</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHFAnrxORJiYMpYrDm_P88MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 17:30:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/285363703/alpe-di-siusi-seiser-alm-dolomites-by-hannes-heigl-photography" target="_blank"&gt;Alpe di Siusi - Seiser Alm - Dolomites&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;facebook Instagram&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>The Fate Of Tech Giants Depends On This Stock -- And It's One Of The Best Investments Today - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stephenmcbride1/2018/12/04/the-fate-of-tech-giants-depends-on-this-stock-and-its-one-of-the-best-investments-today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG0RIYjSCLh83u1o8muY8EgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/stephenmcbride1/2018/12/04/the-fate-of-tech-giants-depends-on-this-stock-and-its-one-of-the-best-investments-today/" target="_blank"&gt;The Fate Of Tech Giants Depends On This Stock -- And It's One Of The Best Investments Today&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2017, The Economist ran a story about how data has surpassed oil as the world’s most valuable resource. Makes sense, right? The 20th century’s most powerful companies got rich selling oil. John D. Rockefeller’s Standard Oil was the first ever $1 billion company. Many of today’s super-firms have gotten rich collecting and selling personal data. Amazon (AMZN), Google (GOOG), and Facebook (FB) all earn a BIG chunk of their profits from leveraging and selling users’ data. These are the third, fourth, and sixth biggest publicly traded companies on earth. This year Google will earn over $100 b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sheryl Sandberg reportedly ordered oppo research on billionaire George Soros - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90274688/sheryl-sandberg-reportedly-ordered-oppo-research-on-billionaire-george-soros</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAAtsSoJNrFsGjoovT92TGUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 05:15:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90274688/sheryl-sandberg-reportedly-ordered-oppo-research-on-billionaire-george-soros" target="_blank"&gt;Sheryl Sandberg reportedly ordered oppo research on billionaire George Soros&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook’s Sheryl Sandberg requested opposition research on billionaire George Soros from a Washington, D.C., opposition research firm, a new report says. Sandberg had previously denied knowledge of the firm. The new information comes from internal Facebook emails described to Ryan Mac of Buzzfeed News. Sandberg’s initial denial came in response to a bombshell New York Times story saying, among many other things, that Facebook had retained the public relations firm Definers to collect information on the company’s opponents and critics, as well as plant news stories containing negative infor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Facebook messenger down: Instant messaging service not working for users across the world - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/facebook-messenger-down-not-working-problems-error-messages-online-contacts-notifications-a8660041.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECnr3ub8X_uTmh-0jUDG5rkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 20:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/facebook-messenger-down-not-working-problems-error-messages-online-contacts-notifications-a8660041.html" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook messenger down: Instant messaging service not working for users across the world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook messenger has reportedly experienced a major outage just days after users across the globe experienced a controversial technical glitch. The issue was first spotted early Thursday afternoon by DownDetector, a site monitoring which brands, platforms and tools are experiencing technical difficulties online. The abrupt interruption in service also follows issues Facebook Messenger experienced earlier this week, in which old chat messages were re-sent to users around the world. The controversy triggered confusion and even distress among many, who reported seeing conversations with folk...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>California judge condemns startup for giving secret Facebook papers to UK - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/30/facebook-lawsuit-six4three-documents-court-uk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKfHYMOx0PUFeQg3AziPYRsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 02:47:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/30/facebook-lawsuit-six4three-documents-court-uk" target="_blank"&gt;California judge condemns startup for giving secret Facebook papers to UK&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A California judge sharply criticized the legal team of the app developer that turned over confidential Facebook documents to the British parliament, accusing the attorneys of behavior that “shocks the conscience” and ordering them to hand over their client’s laptops and other evidence. In a suburban courtroom in Silicon Valley – far from the jurisdiction of Westminster – Judge V Raymond Swope attempted to deal with the legal fallout from an extraordinary maneuver by the UK parliament, which last week seized highly confidential internal Facebook documents from Ted Kramer, founder of Six4Thr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Quora, the site you probably didn't know you had an account for, has been hacked - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/quora-hack-sees-100-million-users-data-stolen/10582126</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE7lRlylNd8DWCvmKxoS0WkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 09:15:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/quora-hack-sees-100-million-users-data-stolen/10582126" target="_blank"&gt;Quora, the site you probably didn't know you had an account for, has been hacked&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Popular Q&amp;A website Quora has announced that the personal information of its 100 million-odd users was affected by "unauthorised access" to one of its systems by a "malicious third party". It other words, it was hacked. Quora first realised it had been compromised on Friday and immediately began investigating. On Monday it began emailing affected users. The thing was, a lot of people who were notified didn't even know they had an account for the site. External Link: @tenderlove: Nothing like a data breach to remind me that I have a Quora account That's because to access a Quora page, you ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Sheryl Sandberg 'asked Facebook staff to research George Soros' after his attack on tech companies - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/sheryl-sandberg-george-soros-facebook-tech-companies-wef-google-a8660436.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED7q_U9ldrado1OQ-DHnLD4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/sheryl-sandberg-george-soros-facebook-tech-companies-wef-google-a8660436.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sheryl Sandberg 'asked Facebook staff to research George Soros' after his attack on tech companies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sheryl Sandberg asked Facebook’s communications staff to research George Soros’ financial interests in the wake of his high-profile attacks on tech companies, according to three people with knowledge of her request, indicating that Facebook’s second in command was directly involved in the social network’s response to the liberal billionaire. Ms Sandberg, Facebook’s chief operating officer, asked for the information in an email to a senior executive in January that was forwarded to other senior communications and policy staff, the people said. The email came within days of a blistering speec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Seven things we learned from the confidential emails that Facebook tried to keep secret - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/06/seven-things-learned-confidential-emails-facebook-tried-keep/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPbSJFC9TAoTDZ1ObCRI9vkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/06/seven-things-learned-confidential-emails-facebook-tried-keep/" target="_blank"&gt;Seven things we learned from the confidential emails that Facebook tried to keep secret&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday Parliament released a trove of confidential documents from inside Facebook that shed light on its business, its dealing with competitors and its attitude to privacy. The company has gone to great lengths to keep the emails secret, convincing a US court to put the documents under seal and then to seize the laptop which was used to transfer them to British MPs. It says the documents do not represent the totality of its internal discussions because they were "cherry-picked" as part of a lawsuit against the social network, and that, "by design", they tell "tell only one side of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Facebook treated user data as competitive weapon, documents reveal - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/facebook-treated-user-data-as-competitive-weapon-documents-reveal-2018-12-05</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECCnJBckwfARbeuyZvVDpK4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 23:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/facebook-treated-user-data-as-competitive-weapon-documents-reveal-2018-12-05" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook treated user data as competitive weapon, documents reveal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ASSOCIATED PRESS By Associated Press U.K. committee releases internal Facebook documents showing how company uses data Facebook called the documents misleading. Bloomberg News Internal Facebook Inc. documents released by a U.K. parliamentary committee offer the clearest evidence yet that the social network has used its enormous trove of user data as a competitive weapon, often in ways designed to keep its users in the dark. Parliament’s media committee accused Facebook (FB) on Wednesday of cutting special deals with some app developers to give them more access to data, while icing out oth...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Google chief prepares to testify before Congress - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4c629e28-f4d3-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFZ7Tum3EmQ9uRqm_LYwSCwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 14:48:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4c629e28-f4d3-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Google chief prepares to testify before Congress&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google is preparing for one of its toughest weeks in recent years, as its chief executive testifies before the US Congress for the first time, a day before he is due to take part in a meeting with other technology bosses at the White House. Sundar Pichai will on Wednesday be questioned by members of the House judiciary committee in a hearing that officials say is likely to be wide-ranging and potentially tempestuous. With the company facing criticism for working on a censored search engine for China and facing allegations that it suppresses certain results for political reasons, officials ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Millennial news site Mic sacks most of its staff in New York - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2018/nov/29/millennial-news-site-mic-sacks-most-of-its-staff-in-new-york</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGr7ZjmMz7xfLtBVPlexrA8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 22:51:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/media/2018/nov/29/millennial-news-site-mic-sacks-most-of-its-staff-in-new-york" target="_blank"&gt;Millennial news site Mic sacks most of its staff in New York&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The millennial news website Mic has sacked most of it staff and is preparing for a fire sale to a rival at a discount price, in a move that raises doubts about the viability of a number of online media startups that have struggled to turn a profit. Related: Facebook to require proof that political ads come from UK Mic, founded in 2011, was one of the many viral websites which boomed when Facebook began prioritising news content in the early part of the decade, swamping newsfeeds and reaching hundreds of millions of viewers around the world with snappy explainers on complicated issues, aggre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Facebook internal emails show Zuckerberg targeting competitor Vine - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/media/facebook-six4three-internal-documents-emails/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN5x8o7KhnN56XSx68gMCVIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/media/facebook-six4three-internal-documents-emails/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook internal emails show Zuckerberg targeting competitor Vine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark Zuckerberg and his colleagues were apparently concerned enough about Vine, a video app from Twitter, that on the day it launched in January 2013, they moved to restrict its access to Facebook user data, a trove of internal Facebook emails released by the U.K. Parliament on Wednesday shows. The decision to restrict Vine's access to data, which would have allowed its users to invite their Facebook friends to join the app, was in line with a company policy at the time, Facebook told CNN on Wednesday. That policy restricted apps' access to Facebook data when the company deemed that the app...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Facebook ‘censors’ Macron pic for violating rules against ‘nudity &amp; sexual acts’ - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445090-macron-facebook-photo-removed-france/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELAW-X_ooGtwSHOrPMp73LAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 20:07:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445090-macron-facebook-photo-removed-france/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook ‘censors’ Macron pic for violating rules against ‘nudity &amp; sexual acts’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A widely mocked photo of the French president posing with a reported cocaine dealer and his middle finger-flipping cousin is purportedly being blocked on Facebook for violating the site’s rules against “nudity and sexual acts.” French netizens are claiming that attempts to share the photograph – which was snapped during Emmanuel Macron’s PR-disastrous visit to the island nation of Saint Martin – are being thwarted by the social media giant. One Frenchman testified on Twitter that he tried to post the photograph along with a snarky caption (“Funny way to celebrate the 60th anniversary of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>‘Entirely appropriate’ for Sandberg to look into George Soros, Facebook’s board says - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/entirely-appropriate-for-sandberg-to-look-into-george-soros-facebooks-board-says-2018-12-05</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL3X91HIdkH5C7EiD6eOP9AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/entirely-appropriate-for-sandberg-to-look-into-george-soros-facebooks-board-says-2018-12-05" target="_blank"&gt;‘Entirely appropriate’ for Sandberg to look into George Soros, Facebook’s board says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WALL STREET JOURNAL By Deepa Seetharaman Facebook COO had been criticized for her handling of the matter Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg speaks in 2015. Getty Images Facebook Inc.’s board of directors said it was “entirely appropriate” for Sheryl Sandberg, the company’s chief operating officer, to ask if George Soros had shorted the company’s stock after the billionaire investor called the social-media giant a “menace.” The board’s letter was sent by Facebook’s general counsel Colin Stretch to Patrick Gaspard, president of Soros’s Open Society Foundations, earlier Wednesday. Previously: Fa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>U.S. rights groups seek secret documents in Facebook encryption case - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-encryption/us-rights-groups-seek-secret-documents-in-facebook-encryption-case-idUSKCN1NX2IV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBLNnTgHJyKUPvgmeYdhBwoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 20:49:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-encryption/us-rights-groups-seek-secret-documents-in-facebook-encryption-case-idUSKCN1NX2IV" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. rights groups seek secret documents in Facebook encryption case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two civil rights groups asked a judge on Wednesday to release documents describing a secret U.S. government effort to force Facebook Inc to decrypt voice conversations between users on its Messenger app. A joint motion by the American Civil Liberties Union and the Electronic Frontier Foundation in U.S. District Court in Fresno, California argued that the public’s right to know the state of the law on encryption outweighs any reason the U.S. Justice Department might have for protecting a criminal probe or law-enforcement method. The issue arose in a joint federal and state investigation into...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Vietnam Jails Rights Activist for Posting Defaced Flag Photo on Facebook - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/vietnam-jails-rights-activist-posting-defaced-flag-photo-facebook/4681248.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOQkVzXY0S_NpZ1gT6XKyaIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:55:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/vietnam-jails-rights-activist-posting-defaced-flag-photo-facebook/4681248.html" target="_blank"&gt;Vietnam Jails Rights Activist for Posting Defaced Flag Photo on Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The founder of a Vietnamese rights group was sentenced Friday to two years and nine months in prison for spraying paint on Vietnamese flags and posting a photo of them on Facebook. Huynh Thuc Vy, 33, was convicted of "desecration of the national flag" at a one-day trial at the People's Court of Buon Ho town in Vietnam's Central Highlands province of Dak Lak, the official Vietnam News Agency reported. Despite sweeping economic reform and increasing openness to social change, Vietnam's ruling Communist Party retains tight media censorship and does not tolerate criticism. Vy's lawyer could not...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The 1996 law that made the web is in the crosshairs - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90273352/maybe-its-time-to-take-away-the-outdated-loophole-that-big-tech-exploits</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELYrYbxvF1zzErwyYP5-bJ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 09:00:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90273352/maybe-its-time-to-take-away-the-outdated-loophole-that-big-tech-exploits" target="_blank"&gt;The 1996 law that made the web is in the crosshairs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was 1995. Bill Clinton was in the White House. Seinfeld and Friends dominated primetime on TV. Radiohead was on the radio. The internet was still an innocent baby (except for porn, of course), but people could anticipate that it was going to be huge. That year, the story goes, California Congressman Chris Cox was on an airplane back to Washington when he read that the early online service provider Prodigy had been sued for defamation over something that a user had posted to one of its bulletin boards. The anonymous person had accused a Long Island securities firm (later immortalized in T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Facebook CEO backed sharing customer data despite second thoughts: documents - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-privacy-zuckerberg/facebook-ceo-backed-sharing-customer-data-despite-second-thoughts-documents-idUSKBN1O50KD</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED8-dRdkR89Sv6baIR7lW-EqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:10:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-privacy-zuckerberg/facebook-ceo-backed-sharing-customer-data-despite-second-thoughts-documents-idUSKBN1O50KD" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook CEO backed sharing customer data despite second thoughts: documents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg questioned the business case for giving millions of outside software developers wide access to customer data before endorsing the practice in 2012, according to internal emails published on Wednesday. The decision made it possible for a quiz app to gather data on about 87 million Facebook users the following year, and later share the information with the now-defunct British political consulting firm Cambridge Analytica, which worked on Donald Trumps' presidential campaign. Zuckerberg lamented his choice in a Facebook post on Wednesday, saying that cr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Is Your Online Identity Vulnerable To Doxing? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/12/03/is-your-online-identity-vulnerable-to-doxing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPxgjwLe2ofj9HDO1kLFd4kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2018/12/03/is-your-online-identity-vulnerable-to-doxing/" target="_blank"&gt;Is Your Online Identity Vulnerable To Doxing?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty Recently, our online reputation and privacy company has heard from an increasing number of individuals that their personal information has been weaponized against them through a malicious practice called doxing, which is the act of publicly distributing personal information online. With a few quick strokes of their keyboard, attackers are accessing and publishing droves of personal information about their targeted victims, including details such as home addresses, names of children and family members, email addresses, phone numbers, social security numbers, driver’s licenses and a bot...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Facebook Gave Data on Users' Friends to Some Firms While Barring Others - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/facebook-gave-data-on-users-friends-to-some-firms-while-barring-others/4688444.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGe8VO4v6lO9Q-QZg2SZaq8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwip0i</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:32:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/facebook-gave-data-on-users-friends-to-some-firms-while-barring-others/4688444.html" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook Gave Data on Users' Friends to Some Firms While Barring Others&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook Inc let some companies, including Netflix and Airbnb, access users' lists of friends after it cut off that data for most other apps around 2015, according to documents released on Wednesday by a British lawmaker investigating fake news and social media. The 223 pages of internal communication from 2012 to 2015 between high-level employees, including founder and Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg, provide new evidence of previously aired contentions that Facebook has picked favorites and engaged in anti-competitive behavior. The documents show that Facebook tracked growth of competitor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>No one can save Facebook – least of all Nick Clegg - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/02/facebook-nick-clegg-pr-liberal-democrats</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFn-XTg-mfrzaJ2PQa6c77kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 11:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/02/facebook-nick-clegg-pr-liberal-democrats" target="_blank"&gt;No one can save Facebook – least of all Nick Clegg&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In October, Facebook named the former UK deputy prime minister Nick Clegg to head its global policy and communications office. In the days since the New York Timesdetailed Facebook’s efforts to use antisemitic language to smear political opponents, one question has been whether Clegg will actually show for work in January, when his job starts. Why would someone with such a sterling résumé want to clean such a disgusting mess? Yet Facebook executives may have chosen the perfect man for the task. That is, if their aim is to shutter their deeply troubled corporation. Clegg, after all, is the m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Facebook gave away $7 million in seconds on Giving Tuesday - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90273801/facebook-gave-away-7-million-in-seconds-on-giving-tuesday</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKLeds7PB150JpiKDPz9Z5MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 17:30:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90273801/facebook-gave-away-7-million-in-seconds-on-giving-tuesday" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook gave away $7 million in seconds on Giving Tuesday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook online fundraisers raked in $125 million for charities on Giving Tuesday. That’s nearly three times more than the $45 million that the social network helped people raise on the same day last year. For donors, part of the lure was a huge matching program provided by both Facebook and PayPal. The companies agreed to mirror up to $7 million in contributions on a dollar-per-dollar, first-come, first served basis. The fine print: It was capped at $250,000 per nonprofit and $20,000 per donor. If the incentive sounds like a Black Friday door buster, it disappeared just as fast. The funds ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Social Networks And Populism: Cause AndEffect? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/enriquedans/2018/12/03/social-networks-and-populism-cause-and-effect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAeodi4Ri1dxcKC3LFjwv5QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 11:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/enriquedans/2018/12/03/social-networks-and-populism-cause-and-effect/" target="_blank"&gt;Social Networks And Populism: Cause AndEffect?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;POPULISM Concept with alphabet blocks on wooden table. There seems to be mounting opinion linking the increase in populism around the world with the popularization of a technology that within a few years has come to monopolize a good part of the time, the thoughts and even how we consume news: the social networks. The relationship between populism and social networks cover more aspects than are usually considered. The awareness of some politicians that social networks, oriented to marketing and hyper-segmented campaigns, offer the perfect way to spread their message is only one facet. Figur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Russian news agency banned by Facebook says it doesn’t peddle fake news - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/russian-news-agency-says-its-being-unfairly-censored-by-facebook-2018-11-26</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIiuvI8DBPC5OKrUuVBjtXAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 20:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/russian-news-agency-says-its-being-unfairly-censored-by-facebook-2018-11-26" target="_blank"&gt;Russian news agency banned by Facebook says it doesn’t peddle fake news&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Andrew Keshner Federal Agency of News insisted in a lawsuit that the news site does not deal in misinformation Federal Agency of News says in a lawsuit that Facebook unfairly blocked and deleted its pages. MLADEN ANTONOV/AFP/Getty Images Facebook is allegedly stifling the free speech rights of a Russian news outlet that’s been banned from the social media platform, a new lawsuit claims — even though the outlet has been linked to Russians accused of election interference. Federal Agency of News and its sole shareholder, Evgeniy Zubarev, insist the news site is the genuine article, not an ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Facebook rolls out tighter rules for British political ads to stop foreign meddling in elections - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/29/facebook-rolls-tighter-rules-british-political-ads-stop-foreign/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEJeL6qGxeQksmhEpkjfVFMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 15:46:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/29/facebook-rolls-tighter-rules-british-political-ads-stop-foreign/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook rolls out tighter rules for British political ads to stop foreign meddling in elections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has introduced new measures that will force political advertisers in the UK to be more transparent about their location and identity in a bid to hold them to account and combat foreign interference in elections. Advertisers will also have to declare who has paid for their politicals ads before they can gain approval to publish them on both Facebook and Instagram. According to the company, ads related to politics will be held in an “Ad Library” for seven years to allow for future analysis of their claims. The system was first introduced in October but a delay in it taking full effec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Facebook Still Doesn't Understand What Privacy Means - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kalevleetaru/2018/12/05/facebook-still-doesnt-understand-what-privacy-means/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIUO2eavXZ3F1gINEJ8pvJ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kalevleetaru/2018/12/05/facebook-still-doesnt-understand-what-privacy-means/" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook Still Doesn't Understand What Privacy Means&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook logo. (JOEL SAGET/AFP/Getty Images) In response to the release earlier today of the Six4Three collection of internal Facebook emails, Mark Zuckerberg issued a statement largely downplaying the significance of the emails that the company had fought so heavily to keep secret. His statement largely acknowledges Facebook’s focus on generating revenue and the fact that as a for-profit company it must be “economically sustainable.” One line in his statement, however, is striking for the way it juxtapositions Facebook’s perceived role in the online ecosystem compared with traditional comm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>