<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Offset - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV4WXpCMmRHUVNBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:10:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Cardi B And Offset Fans Are Excited To 'Finally' See Baby Kulture On Instagram - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-offset-kulture-baby-instagram_us_5c0942a9e4b0844cda50d115</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJm2r3kVNdjRV-93WMOzZIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:49:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-offset-kulture-baby-instagram_us_5c0942a9e4b0844cda50d115" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B And Offset Fans Are Excited To 'Finally' See Baby Kulture On Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B has shared a photo of her daughter Kulture on Instagram, much to the excitement of her fans. The rapper posted the photo of her baby girl, shortly after announcing her split from her husband and Kulture’s dad, Offset, this week. “My heart,” she wrote in the caption for the photo. View this post on Instagram A post shared by CARDIVENOM (@iamcardib) on Dec 5, 2018 at 3:17pm PST Kulture Kiari Cephus, who was born in July 2018, can be seen in the photo sporting a sparkly bow and a bib featuring her name. The picture has garnered more than 7 million likes, with people gushing over the sw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Faces Down Pissed-Off Judge in Strip-Club Brawl Case - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cardi-b-faces-down-pissed-off-judge-in-strip-club-brawl-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsGbKyIYDRVnpgOohOVFAYqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMKv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:33:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/cardi-b-faces-down-pissed-off-judge-in-strip-club-brawl-case" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Faces Down Pissed-Off Judge in Strip-Club Brawl Case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raymond Hall/Getty Cardi B arrived at Queens Criminal Court on Friday with what could best be described as an air of dour glamour. The “Bodak Yellow” rapper, whose given name is Belcalis Almanzar, sported long rainbow hair (a la Tekshi 6ix9ine’s dye job), a black fur-collared jacket, and Louboutin booties. She had crystal-encrusted nails that sparkled with each minuscule hand movement. She donned a wide-brimmed, Fedora-esque hat upon entering court, as well as large sunglasses, almost reminiscent of the old Hollywood vibe of her Marilyn Monroe getup when she surrendered to cops in October f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Judge: Cardi B must not contact strip club melee victims - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/1260d3e0608b40479411dec8a4655e52</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEFIck5Pw5EfgCBRfyVNTb4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:42:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/1260d3e0608b40479411dec8a4655e52" target="_blank"&gt;Judge: Cardi B must not contact strip club melee victims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Cardi B must not contact, in person or through social media, the victims of a melee she was involved in at a New York strip club, a judge ordered Friday. The platinum rapper appeared in court in New York City after a summons was issued Oct. 1 for misdemeanor reckless endangerment and assault. Her lawyer has said she didn't harm anybody. Police said Cardi B and her entourage were at the club around 3 a.m. when she argued with a 23-year-old bartender. They say a fight broke out during which chairs, bottles and hookah pipes were thrown, slightly injuring the woman and another e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Cardi B's chaotic week: Rapper makes court appearance amid breakup and major Grammy nominations - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/cardi-b-court-offset-relationship-grammy-nominations-charges-strip-club-fight-nicki-minaj-a8673041.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFTVWx10HCfhC3nV5lsJ7fEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/cardi-b-court-offset-relationship-grammy-nominations-charges-strip-club-fight-nicki-minaj-a8673041.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B's chaotic week: Rapper makes court appearance amid breakup and major Grammy nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donning Louboutin heels, a black fur coat and a bold new hairstyle, Cardi B arrived at the Queens Criminal Court in New York City to face assault and reckless endangerment charges over a strip club brawl she was allegedly involved in earlier this year. The rapper, whose real name is Belcalis Marlenis Almánzar, smiled to a herd of paparazzi as she entered the court and left shortly after, at one point jokingly asking, "Am I famous?" She was released without bail during a brief hearing. Cardi B initially missed an appearance scheduled five days earlier, receiving a stern warning from the judg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cardi B announces split with Offset - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/12/05/cardi-b-offset-breakup-announcement-epr-orig.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK6wRwaPBVzxm0TSJ-I3fpAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:08:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/12/05/cardi-b-offset-breakup-announcement-epr-orig.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B announces split with Offset&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper Cardi B posted a video on her Instagram account announcing that she and her husband Offset have broken up. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B 'no longer together' with Offset - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/0c32122778a149809659043de1bbac6a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPespQb6UHoaL3pJaQreinwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 14:20:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/0c32122778a149809659043de1bbac6a" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B 'no longer together' with Offset&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Cardi B is no longer feeling the love after little more than a year of marriage to fellow rapper Offset. She posted a video on Instagram saying that "things just haven't been working out between us for a long time." The 26-year-old says "I guess we just grew out of love, but we're not together anymore." Cardi B says "it might take time to get a divorce." Offset responded "Y'all won." The couple got married in September 2017 and welcomed a baby girl in July. Cardi B says she and her baby's father are really good friends and business partners. An email seeking comment was s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Let's give Cardi B a minute - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/entertainment/cardi-b-needs-a-minute/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJmgWJrDiy4Kb2w_QrqSEAQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:05:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/entertainment/cardi-b-needs-a-minute/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Let's give Cardi B a minute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before you tweet me asking, "Why is Cardi B's marital split news?" I will beat you to the punch and say it's not, really. Cardi shot to the top of Twitter trends Wednesday after she announced her split from husband and fellow rapper Offset on Instagram. Celebrity couples who eventual break up is almost a given these days, unless they are in the rarefied air of a few. (You have the power to destroy us Tom Hanks and Rita Wilson, so please keep hanging in there.) Cardi has earned her right to grieve the end of her year-long marriage in private, should she so choose. But given Offset's success ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B announces split from husband Offset: 'I guess we fell out of love' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/cardi-b-offset-relationship-over-split-husband-new-single-a8667791.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFUf5ba-EE-qGlLjYs0wvN8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/cardi-b-offset-relationship-over-split-husband-new-single-a8667791.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B announces split from husband Offset: 'I guess we fell out of love'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B has revealed she has split from her husband Offset, in a video announcement posted on Instagram. I’ve been trying to work things out with my baby father… we’re really good friends, we’re really good business partners and he’s always somebody I run to, to talk to, and we got a lot of love for each other,” the rapper said in the video. “But things just haven’t been working out between us for a long time, and it’s nobody’s fault, I guess we fell out of love," she continued. Read more - Spotify reveals its most streamed albums, artists and tracks of 2018 - The 40 best albums of 2018, fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Snooki pregnant with baby No. 3 - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/entertainment/snooki-pregnant/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIBeiKM-vKTooLhZ-Cf0gBEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 13:22:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/entertainment/snooki-pregnant/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Snooki pregnant with baby No. 3&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The family of Jionni LaValle, Lorenzo Lavalle, Giovanna LaValle and Nicole "Snooki" Polizzi, shown here in September 2015 in Long Valley, New Jersey, will be growing. The "Jersey Shore" star announced on Thanksgiving that she is pregnant with baby number three. Jamie McCarthy/Getty Images Kenya Moore and husband Marc Daly welcomed their first child, a daughter named Brooklyn Doris, in November. Moore, 47, announced during "The Real Housewives of Atlanta" reunion show in April that she and Daly were expecting. She surprised fans when she quietly married Daly in June 2017 during a private, is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B achieves ‘childhood dream’ of buying her mother a house - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/cardi-b-buys-mother-house-childhood-dream-money-a8642676.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ8G7zU0vjnjk1lyO2FN-_4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/cardi-b-buys-mother-house-childhood-dream-money-a8642676.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B achieves ‘childhood dream’ of buying her mother a house&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B has achieved her “childhood dream” of buying her mother a house. The 26-year-old rapper said it was the “happiest day of my life” as she gave fans a video tour of the property in her home state of New York. Cardi B, who was brought up in the Bronx, admitted she was “emotional” and had been crying as she walked fans through the mansion, which features its own gym. - Read more Nicki Minaj addresses Cardi B fight at New York Fashion Week She captioned the post on Instagram: “Stay down till you come up! It’s always been a dream to buy my mother a house. “Last year I was so thirsty to bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Migos Debut Their New Album 'Culture' At No. 1 - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2017/02/05/x-migos-debut-their-new-album-culture-at-no-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJyifilb7DWm3NeQ6pv3rlgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 22:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2017/02/05/x-migos-debut-their-new-album-culture-at-no-1/" target="_blank"&gt;Migos Debut Their New Album 'Culture' At No. 1&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quavo, Offset and Takeoff with Migos performs during the One Hell of a Nite Tour 2015 at Aaron’s Amphitheatre at Lakewood on Saturday, September 5, 2015, in Atlanta. (Photo by Robb D. Cohen/Invision/AP) Hip-hop trio Migos have started their latest album Culture atop the Billboard 200, giving them their first chart-topper. The group’s second full-length begins at No. 1 with 131,000 equivalent copies, 44,000 of which were actual sales. That gives the act an easy lead ahead of the next highest title, which is behind by about 60,000 copies. Culture is Migos’ sophomore album, but they have relea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Beyond The Dab: 8 Reasons Why Migos Has Become Hip-Hop's Trendsetters - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/beyond-the-dab-8-reasons-why-migos-has-become-hip-hops-trendsetters_us_5890d57ae4b0522c7d3d8040</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDiqZ7JGeXf54ZJ5Wkop254qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 00:04:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/beyond-the-dab-8-reasons-why-migos-has-become-hip-hops-trendsetters_us_5890d57ae4b0522c7d3d8040" target="_blank"&gt;Beyond The Dab: 8 Reasons Why Migos Has Become Hip-Hop's Trendsetters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rap group Migos has been soaring to heightened levels of success month after month, banger after banger. The Atlanta-based group, which consists of rappers Quavo, Takeoff and Offset, seem pretty much untouchable at this point. And while many trap music aficionados have long seen the group’s star potential since the release of their 2013 smash “Versace,” their latest hit song “Bad and Boujee” which is featured on their recently released album “Culture,” has only helped to cement their status as superstars. In light of all their success, the group took a trip to New York University last Satur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Migos are making a movie and Quavo's writing the script - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/migos-movie-film-quavo-offset-takeoff-beats-1-a7982026.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE3lN_drsS8f_9oWntGIwKAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 08:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/migos-movie-film-quavo-offset-takeoff-beats-1-a7982026.html" target="_blank"&gt;Migos are making a movie and Quavo's writing the script&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Migos have been a dominant force in hip-hop over the past couple of years, and now they're setting their sights on film. Asked by Zane Lowe on Beats 1 what, if anything, they're concentrating on outside of music, Offset said: "Movies, movies." Directing? Acting? Producing? "All of it, as one," he continued. "My boy Quavo been writing the script, he out here really in the kitchen tryna whip up." 'My boy @QuavoStuntin writing a script, he out here really in the kitchen tryna whip up' @OffsetYRN on working on movies @Migos @Beats1 pic.twitter.com/ESMZObj86L — Zane Lowe (@zanelowe) October 2, 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Madison Beer stars in Music Box episode 38 as she releases 'Hurts Like Hell' video - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/features/madison-beer-hurts-like-hell-music-box-video-session-dead-home-with-you-a8632841.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEASPYcRpM5oqonlCEsZrD64qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 08:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/features/madison-beer-hurts-like-hell-music-box-video-session-dead-home-with-you-a8632841.html" target="_blank"&gt;Madison Beer stars in Music Box episode 38 as she releases 'Hurts Like Hell' video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's hard to believe we're almost at the end of Music Box series four, already! We have three sessions left to go, including this week's episode with the lovely Madison Beer. The US singer shot to fame after receiving praise from fellow pop artist Justin Bieber. Now she's carving out her own career in music, with heartfelt, cool pop that has clearly struck a chord with fans. Madison dropped into the Music Box studio as she was visiting the UK, and gave us two lovely, intimate renditions of her songs "Dead" and "Home With You". We're also excited to share her video for new single "Hurts Like...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Metro Boomin, Migos' Takeoff And Legendary Rockers Queen Take Over The Top 10 This Week - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/14/metro-boomin-migos-takeoff-and-legendary-rockers-queen-take-over-the-top-10-this-week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXMmsK8dEQCunciDkCgit0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/14/metro-boomin-migos-takeoff-and-legendary-rockers-queen-take-over-the-top-10-this-week/" target="_blank"&gt;Metro Boomin, Migos' Takeoff And Legendary Rockers Queen Take Over The Top 10 This Week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON, ENGLAND – JULY 07: Takeoff of Migos perform on the Main Stage during Wireless Festival 2018 at Finsbury Park on July 7, 2018, in London, England. (Photo by Tabatha Fireman/Getty Images) After producing hit singles for some of the biggest names in hip-hop, such as Drake, Future, Migos and Post Malone, this week, Metro Boomin is enjoying his well-deserved moment in the spotlight. The most sought-after producer in the business debuts his solo album Not All Heroes Wear Capes at No. 1 on the Billboard 200 with just under 100,000 equivalent units, giving him his first leader and his third...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Hip-Hop Producer And Songwriter Metro Boomin Debuts His Solo Album At No. 1 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/13/hip-hop-producer-and-songwriter-metro-boomin-debuts-his-solo-album-at-no-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEqQLro0XCoPvbdW4gFUXvAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 14:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/13/hip-hop-producer-and-songwriter-metro-boomin-debuts-his-solo-album-at-no-1/" target="_blank"&gt;Hip-Hop Producer And Songwriter Metro Boomin Debuts His Solo Album At No. 1&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOUISVILLE, KY – SEPTEMBER 16: Metro Boomin (a.k.a. Young Metro) performs at KFC YUM! Center on September 16, 2017, in Louisville, Kentucky. (Photo by Stephen J. Cohen/Getty Images) After spending years as one of the most sought-after producers in the music industry, Metro Boomin has finally reached No. 1 on the most important albums listing, and, somewhat surprisingly, he’s done so all on his own. The producer and songwriter debuts his new collection of tunes Not All Heroes Wear Capes at No. 1 on the Billboard 200 thanks to XXX equivalent units, of which XXX are pure sales. The vast majori...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Carpool Karaoke: James Corden goes shopping with Migos after learning rap trio have $250,000 in cash - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/carpool-karaoke-migos-james-corden-watch-video-cbs-late-show-shopping-a8632726.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENFFd_miJhTGFy_kw8wesoQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 07:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/carpool-karaoke-migos-james-corden-watch-video-cbs-late-show-shopping-a8632726.html" target="_blank"&gt;Carpool Karaoke: James Corden goes shopping with Migos after learning rap trio have $250,000 in cash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;James Corden invited US rap trio Migos for a ride in the latest episode of Carpool Karaoke. The Late Late Show host was filmed with Quavo, Takeoff and Offset – who rose to fame with hits including "Bad and Boujee", "Motorsport" and "Stir Fry". The trio are seen rapping to their own tracks and also to Whitney Houston's 1987 song "I Wanna Dance with Somebody (Who Loves Me)". "Is it true that you were the original creators of the dab?" Corden asks during one moment. Migos oblige with some dabbing during the Houston singalong. Read more - Tyler, the Creator responds to Jaden Smith calling him h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>As 2018 Winds Down, Atlanta Rappers Aim To Finish The Year Strong - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/11/05/lil-baby-21-savage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKsHcCtSBzS2YiL_RHbPLsoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 01:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/11/05/lil-baby-21-savage/" target="_blank"&gt;As 2018 Winds Down, Atlanta Rappers Aim To Finish The Year Strong&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo of 21 Savage by Axelle/Bauer-Griffin/FilmMagic) The holidays may still be some weeks away, but 21 Savage plans to give out his gifts early. The Atlanta rapper behind Billboard hits like “Bank Account” and the chart-topping Post Malone duet “Rockstar” appeared today to announce on Twitter the release date of his new full-length project. If his brief tweet is to be taken at face value, the as-yet untitled solo follow-up to last year’s RIAA gold certified Issa Album would arrive on December 7. After leveling up from the trap mixtape circuit to the Hot 100 in 2016, 21 Savage swiftly beca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Long A Team Player, Migos' Takeoff Lands His First Solo Hot 100 Hit - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/11/06/takeoff-billboard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ2901GMH-QbLRDSus0GdWQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/11/06/takeoff-billboard/" target="_blank"&gt;Long A Team Player, Migos' Takeoff Lands His First Solo Hot 100 Hit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo by Prince Williams/ Getty Images) As part of the trap trio Migos with Offset and Quavo, Takeoff boasts more than two dozen Billboard charting songs. This week, however, the Atlanta rapper reaches a new career milestone with “Last Memory,” his first solo single to chart on the Hot 100. Produced by MonstaBeatz, the track debuts there at No. 54. It also claims No. 18 on On-Demand Streaming Songs, No. 23 on Hot Rap Songs and No. 25 on Hot R&amp;B/Hip-Hop Songs. The lead single off Takeoff’s just-released album debut The Last Rocket, “Last Memory” marks his second solo appearance on the Hot 1...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Halsey And Wes Scheck Land Top 10 Hits Behind Maroon 5 And Cardi B's Massive No. 1 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/05/halsey-and-wes-scheck-land-top-10-hits-behind-maroon-5-and-cardi-bs-massive-no-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARoYLsoxylSXi2_qhkgdZkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 21:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/05/halsey-and-wes-scheck-land-top-10-hits-behind-maroon-5-and-cardi-bs-massive-no-1/" target="_blank"&gt;Halsey And Wes Scheck Land Top 10 Hits Behind Maroon 5 And Cardi B's Massive No. 1&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US singer Halsey performs during the MTV Europe Music Awards at the Bizkaia Arena in the northern Spanish city of Bilbao on November 4, 2018. (Photo by LLUIS GENE / AFP) (Photo credit should read LLUIS GENE/AFP/Getty Images) Despite the fact that it waited in second place for weeks before it finally rose to No. 1 on the Hot 100, Maroon 5 and Cardi B’s “Girls Like You” has now ruled the all-genre singles listing for seven consecutive turns, a lengthier-than-expected stay for a tune that has already enjoyed so many frames so close to the peak. Behind the popular pairing, two newly-released si...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Cardi B reveals death threats to daughter amid feud with Nicki Minaj - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/oct/30/cardi-b-death-threats-nicki-minaj</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENkd1izTeR6tIvAXyiLTmE8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 13:23:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/oct/30/cardi-b-death-threats-nicki-minaj" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B reveals death threats to daughter amid feud with Nicki Minaj&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B has accused Nicki Minaj of leaking her phone number to the public, which led to death threats against her daughter. In one of a series of Instagram videos, Cardi B accuses Minaj of the leak following an altercation at a New York fashion week party that left Cardi B with a bruised forehead after she reportedly threw one of her shoes at Minaj. “How come my phone number got leaked one hour after that altercation at the Harper’s Bazaar party?” Cardi B says. “How come everybody that y’all have issues with, y’all have the numbers in your camp and they numbers got leaked?” She goes on to s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Cardi B vs. Nicki Minaj: An Illustrated Guide to the Greatest Rap Beef of Our Time - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cardi-b-vs-nicki-minaj-an-illustrated-guide-to-the-greatest-rap-beef-of-our-time</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMpJS9QwdkyTnTeAvjfenEkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:11:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/cardi-b-vs-nicki-minaj-an-illustrated-guide-to-the-greatest-rap-beef-of-our-time" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B vs. Nicki Minaj: An Illustrated Guide to the Greatest Rap Beef of Our Time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast In an iconic Love &amp; Hip Hop: New York scene turned legendary .GIF—later immortalized in her debut mixtape Gangsta Bitch Music Vol. 1’s “Foreva”—the artist formerly known as Belcalis Marlenis Almánzar explained, “If a girl have beef with me, she gon’ have beef foreva.” Cardi B might be the hottest hit-maker in hip-hop right now, but at the end of the day she’s still as petty as ever—she’s just graduated her drama from the South Bronx to the Harper’s Bazaar ICONS party. As befitting a chart-topper, Cardi B’s current nemesis is Nicki Minaj, th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Post Malone, Travis Scott, Kodak Black, Offset And Swae Lee Hit The U.K. Top 10 With New Singles - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/10/27/post-malone-travis-scott-kodak-black-offset-and-swae-lee-hit-the-u-k-top-10-with-new-singles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAuJ_HrgyGbBSPzo4yCV9SsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 13:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/10/27/post-malone-travis-scott-kodak-black-offset-and-swae-lee-hit-the-u-k-top-10-with-new-singles/" target="_blank"&gt;Post Malone, Travis Scott, Kodak Black, Offset And Swae Lee Hit The U.K. Top 10 With New Singles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES, CA – OCTOBER 09: Post Malone attends the 2018 American Music Awards at Microsoft Theater on October 9, 2018, in Los Angeles, California. (Photo by Axelle/Bauer-Griffin/FilmMagic) From movies to music, the combination of Bradley Cooper and Lady Gaga has turned out to be a winning one. The duo’s joint single “Shallow” rises all the way to No. 1 in the U.K. this week, giving Cooper his first chart champion and Gaga her fifth. The song serves as the lead single from the A Star Is Born soundtrack, which returns to the summit on that chart this time around. Two new hip-hop tunes bre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Kodak Black, Travis Scott, Offset, Drake And Bad Bunny All Chart New Top 10 Hits This Week - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/10/22/kodak-black-travis-scott-offset-drake-and-bad-bunny-all-chart-new-top-10-hits-this-week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPCOipm8ool20iaEm-OODs4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 18:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/10/22/kodak-black-travis-scott-offset-drake-and-bad-bunny-all-chart-new-top-10-hits-this-week/" target="_blank"&gt;Kodak Black, Travis Scott, Offset, Drake And Bad Bunny All Chart New Top 10 Hits This Week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN BERNARDINO, CA – DECEMBER 16: Rapper Kodak Black performs onstage at the Rolling Loud Festival at NOS Events Center on December 16, 2017, in San Bernardino, California. (Photo by Scott Dudelson/Getty Images) For the fifth consecutive week, Maroon 5 and Cardi B rule the Hot 100 singles chart, blocking a brand new tune from debuting at the top, though its closest competition comes in a relatively close second place and it could compete for the highest slot in the coming frames. New to the Hot 100 is Kodak Black’s just-released single “Zeze,” which enters the listing in the runner-up slot....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Cardi B whispers about her career in ASMR video - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/cardi-b-asmr-video-watch-music-interview-bodak-yellow-offset-a8597211.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPdCxjZn0MvKri8ItEUktrEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/cardi-b-asmr-video-watch-music-interview-bodak-yellow-offset-a8597211.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B whispers about her career in ASMR video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper Cardi B has become the latest celebrity taking part in the ASMR craze. The "Bodak Yellow" star was interviewed by W Magazine and is seen in a video stroking, whispering and purring into the microphones, and playing with a fluffy rug and a children's toy. The 13-minute interview is weirdly hypnotic but also offers some insights into the success of her debut single and her first album Invasion of. Privacy, and returning to work after the birth of her child Kulture, with husband Offset. Read more - The curious phenomenon giving people 'brain orgasms' - Fleetwood Mac are going on tour in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cardi B hands out winter coats in Brooklyn - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/entertainment/cardi-b-winter-coats-brooklyn/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzc1_LupOd7BE_UbTCN1AIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 15:24:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/entertainment/cardi-b-winter-coats-brooklyn/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B hands out winter coats in Brooklyn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B is kicking off the holiday season a bit early with some good will. The rapper handed out free winter coats in Brooklyn, New York on Thursday, where a massive crowd swarmed the "I Like It" performer. Cardi B, a native of the Bronx, was seen at The Marlboro Houses, a housing project in Gravesend, New York. Her good deed comes as New York was hit with unusually cold temperatures this week. "I didn't know it was gonna be so big," Cardi B told WABC about the large crowds who braved the chilly temperatures to see her. "My home boy Chuck, he told me, 'Hey, let's give out coats to our commu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Hands Out Free Winter Coats To Residents In New York - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-free-winter-coats-new-york-brooklyn_us_5bc9fba4e4b0a8f17eebe436</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELz8rKA6BCvBefAup4HjMCkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 18:24:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-free-winter-coats-new-york-brooklyn_us_5bc9fba4e4b0a8f17eebe436" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Hands Out Free Winter Coats To Residents In New York&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B handed out free winter coats to residents in Brooklyn as cooler temperatures hit New York. The Bronx native told New York’s WABC-TV on Thursday that she was excited when she learned about the opportunity from a friend to help give out free coats at a public housing community in Gravesend, Brooklyn. Crowds of fans gathered outside nearby to see the “Invasion of Privacy” rapper during the coat giveaway. Local wholesaler Daniels Leather donated the coats, while NY Tent Sale and TraxNYC provided shoe donations and additional sponsorship, according to Footwork Entertainment, an organizer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Thanks Her Daughter For Inspiring Her To Prove The Haters Wrong - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-2018-ama-speech-mom_us_5bbd5427e4b0876edaa34983</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECy0i3pE3iOQh9A05zxouAwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 02:26:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-2018-ama-speech-mom_us_5bbd5427e4b0876edaa34983" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Thanks Her Daughter For Inspiring Her To Prove The Haters Wrong&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B won the 2018 American Music Award for Favorite Artist in the Rap/Hip-Hop category, but she was an even bigger winner for all the working moms out there. After thanking her fans, her team and “Jeeee-sus,” Cardi gave a special shout out to her daughter Kulture Kiari Cephus. Cardi and her husband Offset gave birth to their first child together in July. “I really wanna thank my daughter, and not just because she’s my daughter,” the rapper from the Bronx said. “When I was pregnant, I was just so influenced to be like, yo I got to do this. I gotta show people wrong. I gotta prove people w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Taylor Swift wins big at AMAs and encourages fans to vote - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/71d4976f018240a88838fdb048835a55</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENLCdLEe2qjYn5ulgO_PNOUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 10:54:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/71d4976f018240a88838fdb048835a55" target="_blank"&gt;Taylor Swift wins big at AMAs and encourages fans to vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taylor Swift kicked off her week with a rare political post on social media, and at the American Music Awards she continued the conversation by encouraging fans to vote in the upcoming midterm elections. Swift won four honors including artist of the year at the fan-voted show on Tuesday in Los Angeles, beating out Drake, Ed Sheeran, Imagine Dragons and Post Malone for the top prize. "This award and every single award given out tonight were voted on by the people, and you know what else is voted on by the people," she said, "the midterm elections on November 6." Swift announced on Sunday tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Cardi B on what sparked that Nicki Minaj fight - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/10/entertainment/cardi-b-interview-minaj/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJaw5WsYmanN5xiEsElCLUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 14:28:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/10/entertainment/cardi-b-interview-minaj/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B on what sparked that Nicki Minaj fight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We now know what exactly sparked Cardi B going after Nicki Minaj at a New York Fashion Week party. In a profile with W, the rapper opened up about everything from her feud with Minaj to her insecurities over husband rapper Offset's potential for infidelity. The rappers were seen leaving New York Fashion Week's annual Harper's Bazaar Icons party last month when some attendees documented Cardi B yelling, throwing a shoe and being restrained while attempting to charge Minaj. After the altercation, Minaj lashed out at Cardi B on her Beats 1's "Queen Radio" show. Nicki Minaj fires back at Cardi ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rapper Cardi B charged in connection with assault in New York - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-cardib/rapper-cardi-b-charged-in-connection-with-assault-in-new-york-idUSKCN1MB3AS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA8VEdry4ydxPtzkiDh6JKkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 21:46:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-cardib/rapper-cardi-b-charged-in-connection-with-assault-in-new-york-idUSKCN1MB3AS" target="_blank"&gt;Rapper Cardi B charged in connection with assault in New York&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper Cardi B surrendered to New York City police on Monday and was charged with assault and reckless endangerment after a complaint claimed she was involved in a fight at a strip club in August. Cardi B, born Belcalis Almánzar, was allegedly involved in an incident at the Angels NYC strip club in the borough of Queens, according to police spokesman Martin Brown, who said the investigation was continuing. Jeff Kern, a representative for the 25-year-old rapper, said she was not arrested and received a court summons charging "misdemeanors only." "We're aware of no evidence that she caused an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Turns Herself In For Alleged Involvement In Strip Club Assault - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-turns-herself-in-alleged-strip-club-assault_us_5bb2249fe4b0343b3dc27158</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENjLBo5YscriKCxdWuRFg8sqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:30:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-turns-herself-in-alleged-strip-club-assault_us_5bb2249fe4b0343b3dc27158" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Turns Herself In For Alleged Involvement In Strip Club Assault&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper Cardi B turned herself in to police Monday after allegedly ordering an assault on two bartenders at a strip club in August. Detective Martin Brown told HuffPost that the New York Police Department received a complaint of an assault that happened on Aug. 29 at 3 a.m. at an address belonging to Angels NYC, a strip club in Queens, New York. The rapper was seen walking into the 109th Precinct on Monday: #breaking cardi B turns herself into police just now on assault charges. @PIX11Newspic.twitter.com/LrfNpDllAS — Anthony DiLorenzo (@ADiLorenzoTV) October 1, 2018 TMZ reported Monday that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Cardi B turns herself into police after apparently 'ordering attack' on strip club workers - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/cardi-b-arrested-jail-offset-fight-strip-club-police-new-york-a8564046.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECs8Z7J5QbiybRAxgva-xPIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 19:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/cardi-b-arrested-jail-offset-fight-strip-club-police-new-york-a8564046.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B turns herself into police after apparently 'ordering attack' on strip club workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B turned herself over to New York City police Monday morning regarding charges stemming from an alleged strip club altercation that occurred on August 29. The rapper, whose real name is Belcalis Marlenis Almánzar, was charged with reckless endangerment and assault, a NYPD spokesperson told The Independent. The fight reportedly occurred at the Angels Strip Club in Flushing, New York - where the singer’s husband Offset was performing. - Read more Nicki Minaj addresses Cardi B fight at New York Fashion Week While the full details of the incident are not clear, TMZ reported the charges ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Will Turn Herself In to Cops For Her Role in Strip-Club Fight - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cardi-b-will-turn-herself-in-to-cops-for-her-role-in-strip-club-fight</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELWGWpFG1pKgdQAjgVYZ_e4qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:02:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/cardi-b-will-turn-herself-in-to-cops-for-her-role-in-strip-club-fight" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Will Turn Herself In to Cops For Her Role in Strip-Club Fight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theo Wargo/Getty, Rap icon Cardi B will reportedly turn herself in to police Monday and admit that she orchestrated an attack on two bartenders at a strip club in Queens, according to a Monday report from TMZ. The drama is said to have begun when Cardi visited the Angels Strip Club in August to watch rap trio Migos perform, and she came face-to-face with bartenders identified only as Jade and Baddie Gi. Cardi is purported to have had a longstanding feud with Jade, who she believes slept with her husband, Offset. TMZ reports Cardi ordered her posse to attack the sisters with bottles, chairs,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Alpha Industries Talks To Migos Rapper Offset And Others About Heroism And Their Heroes - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/raewitte/2018/09/18/alpha-industries-talks-to-migos-rapper-offset-and-others-about-heroism-and-their-heroes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPASN-l8aJ-lXrt4_Rh-ZDAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/raewitte/2018/09/18/alpha-industries-talks-to-migos-rapper-offset-and-others-about-heroism-and-their-heroes/" target="_blank"&gt;Alpha Industries Talks To Migos Rapper Offset And Others About Heroism And Their Heroes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Offset and his daughter. Merriam-Webster dictionary defines a hero as a person who is admired for great or brave acts or fine qualities. Each and every one of us has heroes or people we look up to, think highly, and would openly model aspects of our lives around the philosophies of these individuals. Alpha Industries just released a series to celebrate heroes. The 50-year old heritage military brand turned classic outerwear retailer’s roots are embedded in providing for America’s heroes. They are the first brand to be awarded a U.S. Department of Defense contract and have continued to creat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Where, Oh Where, Can Cardi B Be? Attorney Requests Extension To Serve Assault Lawsuit - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michellefabio/2018/09/14/where-oh-where-can-cardi-b-be-attorney-requests-extension-to-serve-assault-lawsuit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECMahViAsSFinH8seUgmRKIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 15:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/michellefabio/2018/09/14/where-oh-where-can-cardi-b-be-attorney-requests-extension-to-serve-assault-lawsuit/" target="_blank"&gt;Where, Oh Where, Can Cardi B Be? Attorney Requests Extension To Serve Assault Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Offset and Cardi B (Photo by Theo Wargo/Getty Images for NYFW: The Shows) The lawyer for a man who claims he was assaulted by three men employed by rapping couple Cardi B and Offset is asking a New York judge to extend the period of time to serve Cardi B with a lawsuit over the altercation. Giovanni Arnold claims that on May 8, 2018, he was seeking an autograph from Cardi B outside the Mark Hotel after a Met Gala after-party. Arnold alleges the couple ignored two requests for an autograph before Cardi B threatened to “slap the sh*t outta” him and Offset told him to “shut up, bro, before a n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj fires back at Cardi B - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/11/entertainment/nicki-minaj-cardi-b-response/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED0G8kGax8TnesAxZw3FV1YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 05:15:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/11/entertainment/nicki-minaj-cardi-b-response/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nicki Minaj fires back at Cardi B&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicki Minaj said Monday her recent dust-up with fellow rapper Cardi B was "mortifying and humiliating." Minaj addressed the incident during the latest episode of her Beats 1's "Queen Radio" show. "You're angry and you're sad. This is not funny," Minaj said of Cardi B. "Get this woman some f***ing help. This woman's at the highest point in her career and she's throwing shoes?" The pair were leaving New York Fashion Week's annual Harper's Bazaar Icons party late Friday at the Plaza Hotel in New York City when Cardi B appeared to go after Minaj. Video from the exclusive invite-only soiree was ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Reportedly Hurt In Dust-Up With Nicki Minaj At NY Fashion Week Party - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-reportedly-hurt-in-altercation-with-nicki-minaj_us_5b936770e4b0cf7b003fe34d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBgbY_ONX3t-sRjIG4JOA04qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 08:16:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-reportedly-hurt-in-altercation-with-nicki-minaj_us_5b936770e4b0cf7b003fe34d" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Reportedly Hurt In Dust-Up With Nicki Minaj At NY Fashion Week Party&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper Cardi B was reportedly injured when she tried to throw down against Nicki Minaj Friday night at a Manhattan Fashion Week party. Cardi threw a shoe, ripped her long red Dolce &amp; Gabbana gown and left the party venue barefoot escorted out by security with a large lump apparent over her left eye after the altercation, witnesses told TMZ and People magazine. Cardi B Leaving the Harpers Bazaar ICONS Party pic.twitter.com/u45aO5MgML — PowerStarLive (@PowerStarLive) September 8, 2018 The row broke out at the Harper’s Bazaar ICONS party at the Plaza. Cosmopolitan said it started shortly after...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>2018 VMA's: See Some Of The Red Carpet's Standout Looks - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roytelmontero/2018/08/21/2018-vmas-see-some-of-the-red-carpets-standout-looks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIVsIqy6TR2SpRvUEUO4q54qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 16:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/roytelmontero/2018/08/21/2018-vmas-see-some-of-the-red-carpets-standout-looks/" target="_blank"&gt;2018 VMA's: See Some Of The Red Carpet's Standout Looks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, NY – AUGUST 20: Jennifer Lopez attends the 2018 MTV Video Music Awards at Radio City Music Hall on August 20, 2018 in New York City. (Photo by Nicholas Hunt/Getty Images for MTV) MTV’s Video Music Awards have always been the show where you can expect the unexpected. With this year’s show making its return to Radio City Music Hall for its live broadcast, the stars came out in their finest for the spectacle. Leading the pack with ten nominations, Best New Artist and new mother, Cardi B, dazzled in a fuchsia number and an emerald drop earring. A fashion chameleon, Cardi stunned in a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Travis Scott, Tyga And Offset Collect New Top 10 Singles In The U.K. - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/08/10/travis-scott-tyga-and-offset-collect-new-top-10-singles-in-the-u-k/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJz9ApHWNDEf3u1EDK-w8gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 17:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/08/10/travis-scott-tyga-and-offset-collect-new-top-10-singles-in-the-u-k/" target="_blank"&gt;Travis Scott, Tyga And Offset Collect New Top 10 Singles In The U.K.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHICAGO, IL – AUGUST 02: Travis Scott performs during Lollapalooza 2018 at Grant Park on August 2, 2018, in Chicago, Illinois. (Photo by Tim Mosenfelder/Getty Images) Not much changes toward the top of the U.K. singles ranking this week, but closer to the bottom of the top 10, a trio of newly-released tunes become proper hits as they rise into the region. For the fourth week, Drake’s virally-famous “In My Feelings” holds at No. 1, followed immediately by George Ezra’s recent chart-topper “Shotgun,” which was also in the runner-up slot last frame. Up to a new peak of No. 3 is “No Brianer,”...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>New mom Cardi B drops out of Bruno Mars tour - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/8618bcd5068b4ef1a51d5999323e5fe5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB_yVwxF9atqKpUHI7j7TtgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 02:48:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/8618bcd5068b4ef1a51d5999323e5fe5" target="_blank"&gt;New mom Cardi B drops out of Bruno Mars tour&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New mom Cardi B says she's not ready to leave her newborn baby to go on Bruno Mars' tour, so she's dropping out as his opening act. The rapper gave birth to Kulture Kiari Cephus earlier this month and was due to start Mars' tour in Denver in September, when Kulture would be about six weeks. But in an Instagram post Thursday, Cardi B said told she's not physically recovered from childbirth and doctors advised that it wasn't healthy to bring the baby on the road. She told her fans she "underestimated the whole mommy thing" and asked for understanding while thanking Mars for hi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Migos Rapper Offset Arrested In Georgia On Felony Gun Charges - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/migos-rapper-offset-arrested-in-georgia-on-felony-gun-charges_us_5b52530de4b0de86f48d07fb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECqdhJShrtIuxO4SscdzxNoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 12:32:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/migos-rapper-offset-arrested-in-georgia-on-felony-gun-charges_us_5b52530de4b0de86f48d07fb" target="_blank"&gt;Migos Rapper Offset Arrested In Georgia On Felony Gun Charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Migos rapper Offset was arrested in Georgia on Friday after being pulled over outside Atlanta. Multipleoutlets reported that Offset, real name Kiari Cephus, was pulled over for an improper lane change. According to People, citing a police report, officers allegedly detected the smell of marijuana, which prompted them to search the vehicle. Police found three guns and less than an ounce of marijuana in the car. The rapper was taken in four separate charges, including two felony charges: possession of a firearm by a felon and possession of a weapon during a crime. He was also charged with pos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Cardi B won't join Bruno Mars on tour; instead she'll focus on health and her baby - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/26/entertainment/cardi-b-bruno-mars-tour/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPtCYSJBxIrlG38jvLoReBkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 02:10:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/26/entertainment/cardi-b-bruno-mars-tour/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B won't join Bruno Mars on tour; instead she'll focus on health and her baby&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Motherhood calls. Cardi B said Thursday she is pulling out of Bruno Mars' tour this fall to give her more time to recover from giving birth to a daughter earlier this month. She also can't bear to be away from her daughter at this point, the artist said. "I thought that after giving birth to my daughter that 6 weeks would be enough time to recover mentally and physically," she wrote on Twitter. "I also thought that I'd be able to bring her with me on tour, but I think I underestimated this whole mommy thing." The 25-year-old rapper gave birth to Kulture Kiari Cephus on July 10. It is her fi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Gets Real About 'Postpartum S**t' And Struggles As New Mom - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-postpartum-struggles_us_5b5b3c27e4b0b15aba988046</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHmSEP0itthCJJdSiGBgaLoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 18:19:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-postpartum-struggles_us_5b5b3c27e4b0b15aba988046" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Gets Real About 'Postpartum S**t' And Struggles As New Mom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B is being careful with herself. The “I Like It” rapper has passed more milestones in the last few months than most people do in a lifetime. After dropping her smash debut album, “Invasion of Privacy,” which spawned not one but two Billboard No. 1 hits, she got married in secret to Migos rapper Offset and welcomed her first child, a girl named Kulture, on July 10. And yet she still planned to join “Finesse” collaborator Bruno Mars on tour starting in September. Well, plans change, and Cardi, 25, has since pulled out of the tour, announcing on Thursday that she “underestimated the whol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Migos' Offset arrested on felony gun charges in Georgia - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/01c26a32fc0144feaec8ec3f6afc23eb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO_JcuMJz3u_SWj5vTivaYYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 02:09:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/01c26a32fc0144feaec8ec3f6afc23eb" target="_blank"&gt;Migos' Offset arrested on felony gun charges in Georgia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JONESBORO, Ga. (AP) — Offset of the hip-hop group Migos is facing two felony gun charges after he and his bodyguard were pulled over outside of Atlanta. Clayton County Police Sgt. Ashanti Marbury tells WSB-TV that an officer pulled over a Porsche 911 Friday afternoon for failing to maintain its lane. Police say Offset, whose real name is Kiari Kendrell Cephus, was behind the wheel. Police say the vehicle smelled of marijuana, prompting authorities to search the car and find three guns and less than an ounce of marijuana. The 26-year-old is on probation for a 2015 arrest on drugs and weapons...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Report: Rapper Offset Arrested Outside of Atlanta - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/report-rapper-offset-arrested-outside-of-atlanta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKmy3afeFCTK2L-iSlxIpa0qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 22:24:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/report-rapper-offset-arrested-outside-of-atlanta" target="_blank"&gt;Report: Rapper Offset Arrested Outside of Atlanta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frederick M. Brown/Getty, Rapper Offset was arrested on Friday after police pulled his car over and found “at least one weapon” inside his vehicle, according to TMZ. The rapper, part of the group Migos, was originally pulled over while he was driving outside Atlanta for “tinted windows.” Police then found at least one gun in his SUV, which violates his probation. His wife, rapper Cardi B, gave birth to their daughter Kulture earlier this month. A witness told TMZ that Cardi B nor the child were in the vehicle at the time of the arrest. , Read it at TMZ&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Rapper Cardi B Gives Birth to Daughter Kulture Kiari Cephus - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rapper-cardi-b-gives-birth-to-daughter-kulture-kiari-cephus</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBTQLm_8TD_J1G3MX7MC5yMqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 16:16:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/rapper-cardi-b-gives-birth-to-daughter-kulture-kiari-cephus" target="_blank"&gt;Rapper Cardi B Gives Birth to Daughter Kulture Kiari Cephus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mario Anzuoni/Reuters, Cardi B and her husband, fellow rapper Offset, welcomed the birth of their baby girl, Kulture Kiari Cephus, on Tuesday. Cardi B announced the birth on Instagram Wednesday, posting a colorful nude photo of herself surrounded by flowers. The rapper kept her pregnancy mostly under wraps, only revealing her baby bump during a musical performance on Saturday Night Live in April. She also later admitted that she married Offset—whose legal name is Kiari Kendrell Cephus—in a secret ceremony in September 2017 before he publicly proposed to her during a concert a month later. ,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Cardi B and Offset announce birth of baby girl - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/jul/11/cardi-b-and-offset-announce-birth-of-baby-girl</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECItRzVNh5N2S-c6_mS7gK4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 16:15:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/jul/11/cardi-b-and-offset-announce-birth-of-baby-girl" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B and Offset announce birth of baby girl&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B and Offset have announced the arrival of their daughter. Kulture Kiari Cephus was born on 10 July according to a post on the Bronx rapper’s Instagram. She is Cardi B’s first child and the Migos rapper’s fourth. The couple have not commented on the name, though Migos have released albums titled Culture and Culture II. Following months of speculation, Cardi B, 25, revealed her pregnancy in a televised performance on Saturday Night Live in April. As she performed the song Be Careful, the camera panned out to reveal her stomach. After the show she told fans: “I’m free!” Kulture Kiari Ce...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Gives Birth To Baby Girl - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-welcomes-baby-girl-named-kulture-with-offset_us_5b46180ae4b07aea75466ea8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP425DxcsnKTcj9X2uTMI-AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 14:56:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-welcomes-baby-girl-named-kulture-with-offset_us_5b46180ae4b07aea75466ea8" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Gives Birth To Baby Girl&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eeeyoh! Cardi B’s baby is finally here. The “Bodak Yellow” rapper welcomed her first child with husband and Migos rapper Offset on Tuesday in Atlanta, Georgia. Cardi B, whose real name is Belcalis Almanzar, confirmed the arrival with a nude floral-themed photo shoot on Instagram, while also announcing the new baby’s name: Kulture Kiari Cephus. A post shared by Cardi B Official IG (@iamcardib) on Jul 11, 2018 at 7:36am PDT This is Cardi’s first child, while Offset, aka Kiari Cephus, has three children from previous relationships. After months of speculation, the 25-year-old revealed her preg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Cardi B announces birth of her first child, daughter Kulture Kiari - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/11/entertainment/cardi-b-baby/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMddiiJO-DN3shzUkF65FqkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 15:24:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/11/entertainment/cardi-b-baby/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B announces birth of her first child, daughter Kulture Kiari&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B announced on social media that daughter Kulture Kiari Cephus was born on July 10. She's the first child for the rapper and her husband, rapper Offset, whose legal name is Kiari Kendrell Cephus. Craig Barritt/Getty Images North America/Getty Images Actress Eva Longoria and husband José Antonio "Pepe" Bastón welcomed son Santiago Enrique Bastón on June 19, Hola! USA magazine reported. The couple married in 2016. Bastón, president of Latin American media company Televisa, has three children from a previous marriage. Pascal Le Segretain/WireImage/Getty Images Brigitte Nielsen announced ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B countersues former manager Klenord ‘Shaft’ Raphael for $15m - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/jul/06/cardi-b-klenord-shaft-raphael-lawsuit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAkd1nfFcqjEKrHhJ5T8LGIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 10:19:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/jul/06/cardi-b-klenord-shaft-raphael-lawsuit" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B countersues former manager Klenord ‘Shaft’ Raphael for $15m&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rapper Cardi B is countersuing her ex-manager for $15m (£11.3m), following a $10m lawsuit he filed against her in April. In April, Klenord “Shaft” Raphael accused Cardi B (whose real name is Almanzar Belcalis) of breach of contract and defamation after she left his management company for a new deal with the company Solid Foundation. Raphael claimed he played an “integral role in developing her music career and public image … Shaft is disappointed by her actions to freeze him out of her career.” Related: 'I want you to feel that empowerment': how Cardi B went from stripper to star The co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Hip-hop stars Cardi B and Offset wed quietly months ago - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/427a7b03e6944aa087c3ddf57d15f097</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO-82Wpd-WYNwG9_Gro20qEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 23:42:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/427a7b03e6944aa087c3ddf57d15f097" target="_blank"&gt;Hip-hop stars Cardi B and Offset wed quietly months ago&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — A marriage certificate shows hip-hop stars Cardi B and the Migos' Offset were quietly married months ago. Sunday night while accepting best group award at the BET Awards, Offset raised some eyebrows when he said, "I thank my wife, you should thank yours." Cardi B confirmed the marriage in a tweet Monday. A marriage certificate shows that Cardi B and Offset, whose real names are Belcalis Almanzar and Kiari Cephus respectively, were wed Sept. 20 in Atlanta, but only announced their engagement in October. A month after the marriage, Offset proposed to Cardi on stage at Power 99'...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Cardi B And Offset Married In Secret Last Year, Okurr! - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-offset-married-in-secret-last-year_us_5b313a5fe4b0321a01d43300</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPF-s2v8f3h0zDrZHyjmPcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 20:39:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-offset-married-in-secret-last-year_us_5b313a5fe4b0321a01d43300" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B And Offset Married In Secret Last Year, Okurr!&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B wasn’t joking about that whole invasion-of-privacy thing. The “Bodak Yellow” rapper and her supposed fiancé Offset, who are expecting a child together, are actually already husband and wife, according to a marriage certificate obtained by TMZ. The certificate was filed under their legal names, Belcalis Marlenis Almanzar and Kiari Kendrell Cephus, on Sept. 20, 2017, in Fulton County, Georgia, where they both currently reside. Cardi B confirmed that they’d secretly wed in a note released Monday on Instagram that talks about “moments that I want to keep for myself!” She explains that t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Top 5 Songs for Week Ending June 29 - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/top-5-songs-for-week-ending-june-29-2018/4455491.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFm2jV36khSWEb095cipBrwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwmp0i</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 23:30:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/top-5-songs-for-week-ending-june-29-2018/4455491.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top 5 Songs for Week Ending June 29&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re soaring with the five most popular songs in the Billboard Hot 100 Pop Singles chart, for the week ending June 30, 2018. The musical deck gets shuffled this week with the biggest change happening at the top. Number 5: Maroon 5 &amp; Cardi B "Girls Like You" Maroon 5 and Cardi B lose a slot in fifth place with “Girls Like You.” The BET Awards were handed out on June 24 in Los Angeles, and Cardi came away with two: Best Female Hip-Hop Artist, and Viewers’ Choice. Offset of Migos sparked marriage rumors after calling Cardi his “wife” during a speech. Cardi wasn’t present at the ceremony but l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Cardi B and Offset were married when he 'proposed' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/26/entertainment/cardi-b-offset-married/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA7-PgrbPcgUvUegkYcpFgoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 18:31:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/26/entertainment/cardi-b-offset-married/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B and Offset were married when he 'proposed'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rappers Cardi B and Offset came clean about being married after TMZ published a copy of their marriage certificate. Cardi tweeted of their secretly getting married in September 2017 "Our relationship was so new breaking up and making up and we had a lot of growing up to do but we was so in love we didn't want to lose each other, was one morning in September we woke up and decided to get married." Craig Barritt/Getty Images North America/Getty Images Amy Schumer and chef Chris Fischer married in a private ceremony in Malibu, California, on February 13, 2018, according to the star's social me...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>For The First Time In 3 Years, Tyga Cracks The Hot 100's Top 40 - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/06/19/tyga-offset/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDfnw93IPBBrbcbS-CAttmoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 16:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/06/19/tyga-offset/" target="_blank"&gt;For The First Time In 3 Years, Tyga Cracks The Hot 100's Top 40&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo by Stephane Cardinale – Corbis/Corbis via Getty Images) After a 3 year absence from the Hot 100, Tyga appears to have another hit on his hands. The hip-hop artist behind singles like “Faded” and “Hookah” has a lengthy history on Billboard’s all-genre singles chart. Over the past decade, two dozen songs that have Tyga as either a lead or featured artist have charted there, starting with “Coconut Juice” which made a one week showing at No. 94 back in June of 2008. Up until now, however, only 5 of those songs had ever reached the Hot 100′s top 40, with the remainder filling out the lowe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Rap trio Migos to receive ASCAP Vanguard Award - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/26eea1aefbe14c29aa81aa3a1d0c0495</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHfWWddbJFQIl38gk8SKkVAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 16:27:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/26eea1aefbe14c29aa81aa3a1d0c0495" target="_blank"&gt;Rap trio Migos to receive ASCAP Vanguard Award&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The streaming juggernauts Migos will receive the ASCAP Vanguard Award for their successful year in music. The American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers said on Friday the trio of Quavo, Offset and Takeoff will earn the honor on June 21 in Los Angeles at its 31st annual Rhythm &amp; Soul Music Awards. Migos has dominated on the pop and rap charts, as well as streaming platforms like Spotify and Apple Music, with songs like "Bad and Boujee," ''MotorSport," ''Stir Fry" and "Walk It Talk It." Their albums — last year's "Culture" and this year's "Culture II" — have reache...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>What You Need To Know About Tickets To The Drake And Migos Tour - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/05/29/what-you-need-to-know-about-tickets-to-the-drake-and-migos-tour/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM-yZD2gnncYtu0K5UuOY7MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 15:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/05/29/what-you-need-to-know-about-tickets-to-the-drake-and-migos-tour/" target="_blank"&gt;What You Need To Know About Tickets To The Drake And Migos Tour&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drake performs at The SSE Hydro on March 23, 2017 in Glasgow, United Kingdom. The aptly named “Aubrey and the Three Amigos Tour” has been expanded to include more dates in Los Angeles, New York City, and Toronto. The highly anticipated show begins in Salt Lake City, Utah on June 26 and now features more than 40 shows, including multiple nights in Drake’s Toronto hometown. Catch the tour on numerous nights in New York City and Los Angeles before November’s final show in Migos’ Atlanta hometown at the Philips Arena. The quartet will “Walk it like they talk it” as they take the stage of iconic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Rapper from Migos in near-death crash - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2018/05/20/migos-rapper-car-crash.hln</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKfWiB_0ln5AKVJ-JRzXUO8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 02:26:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2018/05/20/migos-rapper-car-crash.hln" target="_blank"&gt;Rapper from Migos in near-death crash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper Offset from Migos shares photos of his mangled Dodge Challenger after being involved in a near-death car crash in Atlanta. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Quavo, Young Thug And Half Of Rae Sremmurd: Meet The Backup Vocalists On 'This Is America' - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/05/21/quavo-young-thug-and-half-of-rae-sremmurd-meet-the-backup-vocalists-on-this-is-america/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKD4UbKTZebSgvjxE-hgpvsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 13:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/05/21/quavo-young-thug-and-half-of-rae-sremmurd-meet-the-backup-vocalists-on-this-is-america/" target="_blank"&gt;Quavo, Young Thug And Half Of Rae Sremmurd: Meet The Backup Vocalists On 'This Is America'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, NY – JUNE 03: Childish Gambino performs live onstage during 2017 Governors Ball Music Festival – Day 2 at Randall’s Island on June 3, 2017, in New York City. (Photo by Taylor Hill/Getty Images for Governors Ball) Between his stellar delivery and the unforgettable, controversial video that accompanies his new single, Donald Glover (known as Childish Gambino when it comes to the multi-talented artist’s musical endeavors) is getting all the credit for “This Is America,” but while no other name is credited on the track, he reached out to some very famous friends to jump on the tune an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Sasha Obama Hanging Out With Cardi B And Offset At A Festival Is A Vibe - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sasha-obama-hanging-out-with-cardi-b-and-offset-at-a-festival-is-a-vibe_us_5ae71966e4b055fd7fce0bc7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECFGijt_SxsRs471cwRcPmoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 14:16:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/sasha-obama-hanging-out-with-cardi-b-and-offset-at-a-festival-is-a-vibe_us_5ae71966e4b055fd7fce0bc7" target="_blank"&gt;Sasha Obama Hanging Out With Cardi B And Offset At A Festival Is A Vibe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second daughter of former President Barack Obama and first lady Michelle Obama spent some time with the rappers Cardi B and Offset over the weekend at Washington’s Broccoli City Festival. The “Bodak Yellow” rapper and Offset, her fiancee and member of the band Migos, headlined the music event ― which, yes, is actually called the Broccoli City Festival ― and they apparently spent some downtime backstage with Sasha Obama. Cardi B, OFFset, and Sasha Obama at #BroccoliCity Photo by @FloNgalapic.twitter.com/SZmuZxoQWF — MEFeaterEIC (@GabrielleAmani) April 29, 2018 How did this trio get toge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Cardi B sued for £10m by former manager and co-writer - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/apr/27/cardi-b-sued-for-10m-by-former-manager-and-co-writer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ8zOQiyMrchdnCT9UbqyKwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 13:14:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/apr/27/cardi-b-sued-for-10m-by-former-manager-and-co-writer" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B sued for £10m by former manager and co-writer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US rapper Cardi B is being sued for $10m (£7.25m) by her former manager, Klenord “Shaft” Raphael, who has accused her of breach of contract and defamation. In a claim filed on 26 April and seen by Variety, the dispute centres on Cardi’s departure from Raphael’s company, World Star Marketing Group, and her new deal with Solid Foundation. The latter is the management arm of Quality Control, the label to whom the rapper’s fiance, Offset, is signed with his group Migos. A statement from a representative for Raphael claims: “Since discovering Cardi B in 2015, Shaft has played an integral role in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Cardi B's Former Manager Sues Her For $10 Million - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-lawsuit_us_5ae2431ae4b055fd7fc9fda9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECZ5nR1AGfQ8epyhexnLO5oqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 23:11:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-lawsuit_us_5ae2431ae4b055fd7fc9fda9" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B's Former Manager Sues Her For $10 Million&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman who gave the world “Bodak Yellow” is now getting sued for a lot of green. The former manager of rapper Cardi B has filed a $10 million lawsuit against the performer. He claims to have turned her into a superstar, but has been left out of her success, according to Page Six. Cardi B dumpedKlenord “Shaft” Raphael last month and signed with Solid Foundation, a management company/label headed by Kevin “Coach K” Lee and Pierre “Pee” Thomas, according to Variety. Raphael said her new contract violates the agreement she had with him, according to Billboard. “While [Raphael] is proud of th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Doesn't Owe You Anything - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-doesnt-owe-you-anything_us_5ac73f55e4b07a3485e33766</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK-weMNrMhFZkYPpOp1mD_sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 14:15:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-doesnt-owe-you-anything_us_5ac73f55e4b07a3485e33766" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Doesn't Owe You Anything&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fresh off the debut of her new record, “Invasion of Privacy,” Cardi B addressed reactions to her revelation on “Saturday Night Live” that she is pregnant. These things were intertwined, the album and the baby, if not in reality then in the hyperreality Cardi B inhabits. Both were treated by certain corners of the public as bits of creative output to be consumed and judged, and last week on the ”Ebro in the Morning” radio show on New York’s Hot 97, Cardi B seemed annoyed with this arrangement. It’s just like, you know what? I’m a grown woman. I’m 25 years old. I’m going to say this in the mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Why Cardi B is a fashion icon for our times - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/fashion/people/cardi-b-fashion-icon-times/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAfIx6WnqIqOwNESxBHJb2kqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCq098D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 11:32:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/fashion/people/cardi-b-fashion-icon-times/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Cardi B is a fashion icon for our times&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a chance, particularly if you're not an avid user of Instagram or SnapChat, that you are among the uninitiated when it comes to Cardi B. Allow us to rectify the situation, and fill you in on a one-of-a-kind fashion personality that, honestly, everyone under the age of 30 is talking about. The Bronx-born rapper recently hit the headlines when her debut album, Invasion Of Privacy, broke records after reaching number one across America in just 24 hours following its much-anticipated release. Cardi B's real name is Belcalis Almanzarher - her stage name came to be because her sister is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tinashe: Joyride review – back with some curveballs - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/apr/15/tinashe-joyride-album-review-kitty-empire</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK2fifnrUr8QIHwJSC0nmisqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 07:00:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/apr/15/tinashe-joyride-album-review-kitty-empire" target="_blank"&gt;Tinashe: Joyride review – back with some curveballs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ululation that opens Joyride, the title track of R&amp;B star Tinashe’s third album, could well be a howl of pain, and the title a sarcastic sneer. The long-awaited return of the child star turned singer (there have been mixtapes) was due in 2016, but repeated delays rapidly made it less of a joyride and more of a breakdown in bank holiday traffic. Moreover, the title track nearly made it on to Rihanna’s 2016 album, Anti, before Tinashe wrested it back. Fortunately, Joyride doesn’t sound too much like trench warfare between star and industry; it has been substantially refreshed over the cou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Tinashe: ‘People are past the point where they think I’m a mindless puppet’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/apr/14/tinashe-people-are-past-point-they-think-im-a-mindless-puppet</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECpvVsA7wpWeeMQ_SjpYOnQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 06:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/apr/14/tinashe-people-are-past-point-they-think-im-a-mindless-puppet" target="_blank"&gt;Tinashe: ‘People are past the point where they think I’m a mindless puppet’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Halfway through school at California’s Crescenta Valley High, budding actor Tinashe Jorgensen Kachingwe made a new best friend. She was delighted to have found this new acquaintance, and sad when she had to leave school for two months to shoot a TV movie, Cora Unashamed. On her return to Crescenta, she discovered her BFF didn’t like her any more. No one did. Her friend turned into a bully and created a We Hate Tinashe group of which she was leader. She would ring Kachingwe at home to describe exactly how she was going to “fuck her up” at school the next day. She, like everyone else, didn’t ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Cardi B has beaten Taylor Swift's Apple Music record - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/cardi-b-taylor-swift-invasion-of-privacy-apple-music-record-a8303356.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbz0-QcvYoRVaJDSAI77g0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/cardi-b-taylor-swift-invasion-of-privacy-apple-music-record-a8303356.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B has beaten Taylor Swift's Apple Music record&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B has broken Apple Music's most--streamed record for a female artist in its first week with her debut album Invasion of Privacy. Before the rapper earned this title, Taylor Swift held the honour for her latest album Reputation. By mid-week, Cardi B had doubled the streams of Swift's Reputation, Variety reports. - Read more Nicki Minaj says she was 'hurt' by Cardi B comments Currently Invasion of Privacy is at the no.5 spot on Apple Music's worldwide chart for most-streamed albums ever. She's even beat out Ed Sheeran's Divide and The Weeknd's Starboy. It's likely that Invasion of Priva...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj vs. Cardi B: When Will We Stop Making Nicki Minaj the Villain? - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nicki-minaj-vs-cardi-b-when-will-we-stop-making-nicki-minaj-the-villain</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM8ViRzJrLhBYhsz0FlGnZsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 22:31:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/nicki-minaj-vs-cardi-b-when-will-we-stop-making-nicki-minaj-the-villain" target="_blank"&gt;Nicki Minaj vs. Cardi B: When Will We Stop Making Nicki Minaj the Villain?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast When you keep up with pop culture long enough, there are headlines you just get tired of reading. In this case, you don’t have to have been keeping up long at all to be exasperated by one particular and, as it turns out, myopic, sexist, and racist trope: “Nicki Minaj vs. [Insert Celebrity Here].” Rounding up Nicki Minaj’s “feuds” and “beefs” has become its own cottage industry in entertainment writing, constantly updating lists of all the women in music she’s apparently been at odds with. There’s a running theme of these aggregations and narratives: Nic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Says She Kept Her Pregnancy A Secret Because People Are 'So Thirsty' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-pregnant-expecting-her-first-child_us_5aba84f6e4b06409775abdbc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGQrfOkEEbvVjMnhhNLKlIUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 13:31:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-pregnant-expecting-her-first-child_us_5aba84f6e4b06409775abdbc" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Says She Kept Her Pregnancy A Secret Because People Are 'So Thirsty'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper Cardi B confirmed she is pregnant with her first child during a performance on “Saturday Night Live” over the weekend. In lieu of an official announcement, the rapper wore a white, custom Christian Siriano gown that showed off her baby bump. Shortly after her performance, she posted photos on Instagram thanking fans and celebrities like Rihanna and 50 Cent for their support. “The love I’m receiving is overwhelming! I can’t thank you enough for always finding the time to share your support!! Thank you a million times @badgalriri,” the rapper wrote, reposting a picture from Rihanna. A ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item></channel></rss>