<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZrZUdKcmVYSnhNeElDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:25:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>There's A Big 'Fortnite' Announcement At The Game Awards Tonight, But It's Not What You Think - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/theres-a-big-fortnite-announcement-at-the-game-awards-tonight-but-its-not-what-you-think/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFx_4hkGV0WvjHfenD2tDskqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/12/06/theres-a-big-fortnite-announcement-at-the-game-awards-tonight-but-its-not-what-you-think/" target="_blank"&gt;There's A Big 'Fortnite' Announcement At The Game Awards Tonight, But It's Not What You Think&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite It’s a big day for battle royale fans. For one thing, Fortnite Season 7 just launched as Epic Games continues to top itself when it comes to totally transforming its map to match the current season: right now we’ve got a wide-ranging winter wonderland, airplanes, and a ton of other stuff. It’s also The Game Awards tonight, the annual celebration that’s gradually emerging as the most important awards show in the world of video games. The Game Awards are known not only for the awards themselves but also for the announcements, surprises and trailers that have a way of worming their wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 'Fortnite' Monster: 200 Million Players, 8.3 Million Concurrents - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/28/the-fortnite-monster-200-million-players-8-3-million-concurrents/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBPX8lIsAbEqiyHpacdL0ykqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/11/28/the-fortnite-monster-200-million-players-8-3-million-concurrents/" target="_blank"&gt;The 'Fortnite' Monster: 200 Million Players, 8.3 Million Concurrents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite The era of Fortnite is far from over, as Epic has hit enough new milestones to start talking publicly about them again. Fortnite now has 200 million registered players, a 60% increase from June alone, when it last clocked in at 125 million. It also now has 8.3 million concurrent players on a regular basis, another huge jump from the last time we got these stats, 4.3 million in February. I mean, what else can even be said about Fortnite at this point? It’s a global gaming trend that I’ve rarely seen on this scale, not since Pokémon GO took over the world, but Fortnite has done that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The US military is using video games and esports to recruit – it's downright immoral - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/army-military-video-game-fortnite-battlegrounds-call-duty-esports-defence-a8648656.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK38SViTbpoEpeHnRYRpdWwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 14:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/army-military-video-game-fortnite-battlegrounds-call-duty-esports-defence-a8648656.html" target="_blank"&gt;The US military is using video games and esports to recruit – it's downright immoral&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the US army’s fiscal year this past September, the independent military news source Army Times reported that it had failed to meet its recruitment target by 7,500 bodies, despite offering up to $40,000 in bonuses, shorter enlistments and student loan repayments. Last week, via a Reddit Ask Me Anything forum, the US military announced its intention to create a military-branded esports team and enter into a video games competition. The military said the team would be populated by active personnel, reservists and veterans, bringing together accomplished players of first-person sh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Esports integrity chief concerned about Fortnite gambling - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/dc3ee6764e5142619a38d85bc8e46293</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENmZZjVGujoe7G6pmXy0nCsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwnZidAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 01:45:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/dc3ee6764e5142619a38d85bc8e46293" target="_blank"&gt;Esports integrity chief concerned about Fortnite gambling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The commissioner of the Esports Integrity Coalition says skill-based betting on battle royale games like Fortnite and PlayerUnknown's Battleground could be vulnerable to cheating. Esports gambling website Unikrn announced plans last month to bring legal skill-based betting to the U.S., allowing players to wager on themselves. Users would link their game to the Unikrn platform, and Unikrn will generate odds for the player based on his or her profile within the game. ESIC Commissioner Ian Smith says such wagering is likely to be popular, but he's concerned the industry is not yet prepared to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Here Are The Best Deals On Xbox One X For Black Friday 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/22/here-are-the-best-deals-on-xbox-one-x-for-black-friday-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEmNVrGiFtUMFRyPsEi7wvEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/22/here-are-the-best-deals-on-xbox-one-x-for-black-friday-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are The Best Deals On Xbox One X For Black Friday 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xbox One X Console and Controller. Xbox One X is the console for the person that wants the best. Not necessarily in terms of exclusive software, mind you, where the PS4 still reigns supreme followed by the Nintendo Switch. But you can’t touch it when it comes to raw power, and that means that this is the machine you want if you’re looking to put that new 4K HDR TV through its paces. It’s the machine you want to get to see Red Dead Redemption 2 at its absolute best, which for some will be worth the price of admission alone. But the Xbox One X isn’t cheap, and so you might have been waiting u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here's Why More Games Need To Copy 'PUBG' For The Battle Royale Genre To Flourish - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/09/25/heres-why-more-games-need-to-copy-pubg-for-the-battle-royale-genre-to-flourish/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC49_hUhMFWlxQV4mbvFZwMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2017/09/25/heres-why-more-games-need-to-copy-pubg-for-the-battle-royale-genre-to-flourish/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's Why More Games Need To Copy 'PUBG' For The Battle Royale Genre To Flourish&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other game developers should take a page from Epic Games and find ways to riff on the Battle Royale genre that PUBG has popularized. Nothing is new under the sun. So the saying goes, and so it is when it comes to video games and many other mediums. When something is popular, and when something is making money, it’s almost certainly bound to be copied. The success of Dark Souls has resulted in many imitators, and to some calling the Souls games now a micro-genre within the larger action-RPG fold, with distinct game mechanics. The formula is tweaked with, but it’s not hard to see when a devel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate' And The 5 Biggest Video Game Releases In December 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/22/super-smash-bros-ultimate-and-the-5-biggest-video-game-releases-in-december-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENzY4FTxF_QtGEGK1so4w6wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/22/super-smash-bros-ultimate-and-the-5-biggest-video-game-releases-in-december-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate' And The 5 Biggest Video Game Releases In December 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;December is never really a huge month for video game releases and 2018 is no exception. WASHINGTON, DC – OCTOBER 8: Super Smash Bros Ultimate by Nintendo is part of The Washington Post via Getty Images annual gift guide October 08, 2018 in Washington, DC. (Photo by Katherine Frey/The Washington Post via Getty Images) That said, there are a handful of games that might be worth a look. In fact, there are at least two that could register as must-haves for hardcore gamers. It starts with Super Smash Bros. Ultimate. The latest edition in the hit Nintendo series arrives in stores on December 7 an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Red Dead Redemption 2' Is Going To Give Us 'Red Dead Royale,' Isn't It? - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/09/29/red-dead-redemption-2-is-going-to-give-us-red-dead-royale-isnt-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIpioZyRdoyOqXVgasYPqdsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/09/29/red-dead-redemption-2-is-going-to-give-us-red-dead-royale-isnt-it/" target="_blank"&gt;'Red Dead Redemption 2' Is Going To Give Us 'Red Dead Royale,' Isn't It?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red Dead Redemption 2 Yesterday was the debut of the story trailer for Red Dead Redemption 2, our first real look at the meat of the game. It shows off a new, less-than-noble hero in the form of Arthur Morgan, a member of John Marston’s old gang presumably before Marston himself left, though he’s not seen in the trailer. But this is a true prequel, meaning we’re staying in the Wild West, and not moving into the modern era like we were at the end of the original Red Dead Redemption. But while it’s nice to get a look at the story, I’m more curious about what Rockstar is doing besides that. Na...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Microsoft Isn't Saying Whether Xbox One Will Keep 'Battlegrounds' Off PS4 For Good - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/08/21/microsoft-isnt-saying-whether-xbox-one-will-keep-battlegrounds-off-ps4-for-good/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFiG3R3uUAo506Hq1xxdoykqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 16:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/08/21/microsoft-isnt-saying-whether-xbox-one-will-keep-battlegrounds-off-ps4-for-good/" target="_blank"&gt;Microsoft Isn't Saying Whether Xbox One Will Keep 'Battlegrounds' Off PS4 For Good&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Battlegrounds There wasn’t too much news made during Microsoft’s Gamescom press event yesterday, some new trailers for old games and a few debuts like what appears to be a Jurassic Park RTS from the creators of Elite: Dangerous. But one game was focused on somewhat significantly, PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds, which has been a massive hit on PC, and a game Microsoft has previously announced is coming to Xbox One for its console debut. What was announced at Gamescom was that Microsoft would in fact be acting as the publisher for the Xbox One release, which is a new level of involvement and i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds' Keeps Almost Giving Me Heart Attacks - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/06/27/playerunknowns-battlegrounds-keeps-almost-giving-me-heart-attacks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECfthxHLxHr2kafixgEUiSgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/06/27/playerunknowns-battlegrounds-keeps-almost-giving-me-heart-attacks/" target="_blank"&gt;'PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds' Keeps Almost Giving Me Heart Attacks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PLAYERUNKNOWN’S BATTLEGROUNDS I am way, way behind the curve on this one, but I finally tore myself away from Marvel’s Contest of Champions to play a game that’s more relevant in the current landscape, PLAYERUNKNOWN’S BATTLEGROUNDS, the all-caps sensation that has been tearing up the Twitch charts for a while now, and subsequently tearing up sales charts as well with 4 million copies of the early access game sold already. I am not a “Battle Royale” player, a patron of Rust or DayZ when those game were also all the rage a while back, but the hype surrounding BATTLEGROUNDS has gotten just too...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'PUBG' Developer Unironically Calls Out 'Fortnite' For Copying Its Battle Royale Format - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/09/22/pubg-developer-calls-out-fortnite-for-copying-its-battle-royale-format/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARuSuFdJzq63Rr27-LLrVoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 14:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/09/22/pubg-developer-calls-out-fortnite-for-copying-its-battle-royale-format/" target="_blank"&gt;'PUBG' Developer Unironically Calls Out 'Fortnite' For Copying Its Battle Royale Format&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite’s Battle Royale PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds developer Bluehole may be new to having enormous success, but it’s already starting to throw its weight around. Today, the developer of PUBG specifically called out Epic Games’ Fortnite in a press release(!), accusing the game of copying PUBG’s signature battle royale format, and the statement ends with a foreboding note about possible “further action” being taken against Epic. “We’ve had an ongoing relationship with Epic Games throughout PUBG’s development as they are the creators of UE4, the engine we licensed for the game,” Bluehole ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'Battlefield 5' Vs. 'Call Of Duty Black Ops 4': 7 Questions To Determine Which Is Best For You - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/19/battlefield-5-vs-call-of-duty-black-ops-4-7-questions-to-determine-which-is-best-for-you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEGUMELft7JNOUsY_A8JJmAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 19:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/19/battlefield-5-vs-call-of-duty-black-ops-4-7-questions-to-determine-which-is-best-for-you/" target="_blank"&gt;'Battlefield 5' Vs. 'Call Of Duty Black Ops 4': 7 Questions To Determine Which Is Best For You&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Battlefield and Call of Duty series will forever be compared. With both series releasing their newest titles within a month of the other and coming just ahead of the holiday season, there are going to be a number of consumers deciding which one is best for them–if they can’t get both. Battlefield V vs. Call of Duty BO4 Battlefield V and COD BO4 have their positives, so owning both is ideal, but it may not be realistic or practical for many. Perhaps you only one have room in the budget for one first-person shooter, or only have time to get acquainted with one or the other. In any case, I...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What is PUBG? A guide to everything you need to know about PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/pubg-guide-everything-need-know-playerunknowns-battlegrounds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIHprl-qN4To149jCWC_GYQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 12:13:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/pubg-guide-everything-need-know-playerunknowns-battlegrounds/" target="_blank"&gt;What is PUBG? A guide to everything you need to know about PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might have seen it being called Battlegrounds, PUBG, or Plunkbat. You might have seen montages and videos of people's chicken dinners. You might have seen it has had 1.5 million concurrent players. You might have even heard about the winner winner, chicken dinners that arise from it. Given an unwieldy name and a speedy rise to fame, we’re here to explain what on earth PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds is. What is PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds? While the full title is PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds, most people call it PUBG, because it’s not quite a title that rolls off the tongue. As of writ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tencent's Profit Surge Will Be Short Lived If Game Approvals Remain Blocked - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ywang/2018/11/16/tencents-profit-surge-will-be-short-lived-if-game-approvals-remain-blocked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMWdsaHCSNKecvkyiuvxeEcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 09:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ywang/2018/11/16/tencents-profit-surge-will-be-short-lived-if-game-approvals-remain-blocked/" target="_blank"&gt;Tencent's Profit Surge Will Be Short Lived If Game Approvals Remain Blocked&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ma Huateng, chairman and CEO of Tencent. (Photo: Anthony Kwan/Bloomberg) Tencent finally delivered some relief to its weary investors by reporting better-than-expected results for the quarter ended September, but the tech giant’s growth prospects still look anything but certain. Although Tencent managed to beat expectations with a 30% jump in quarterly profits that came in at 23.3 billion yuan ($3.4 billion), 8.8 billion of that was from one-time gains. These include a big windfall from the public listing of local services site Meituan Dianping, which counts Tencent as one of its early inve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Golden Joystick Awards 2018 | How to watch and all the nominees - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/golden-joystick-awards-2018-watch-nominees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3KA0fVaF1wB9q8sax9LyAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 14:56:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/golden-joystick-awards-2018-watch-nominees/" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Joystick Awards 2018 | How to watch and all the nominees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 36th Golden Joystick Awards 2018 are imminent, with the world's longest-running and most prominent game award ceremonies taking place this Friday. The Golden Joysticks will be at the Bloomsbury Big Top on 16 November and will be hosted by comedian Danny Wallace, the awards will celebrate the last year of the gaming industry across multiple categories. The categories cover a wide range across the industry including storytelling and esports alongside the more traditional disciplines of audio and visual. There is also a new category this year recognising the best co-operative games. Sony's...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>How To Download 'PUBG' For Free On Xbox, Right Now - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/07/how-to-download-pubg-for-free-on-xbox-right-now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFexwXmeOv3gijLRi3JMKP4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 17:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/07/how-to-download-pubg-for-free-on-xbox-right-now/" target="_blank"&gt;How To Download 'PUBG' For Free On Xbox, Right Now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Player Unknown’s Battlegrounds. Here’s an odd thing that happened today: PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds, the game that kicked off the battle royale phenomenon and dominated the PC gaming conversation in 2017, dropped its price on Xbox One. By how much, you ask? All $30 of it. The game is currently free on the Xbox Store, and it seems like you can keep it if you download it. If you don’t already have it, go ahead and grab it: you can’t afford not to. At first this just sort of showed up out of the blue, but then we got an official announcement from Microsoft’s Larry Hyrb: “Free Play Days For ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Crackdown 3 release date revealed along with first multiplayer trailer - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/crackdown-3-release-date-revealed-along-first-multiplayer-trailer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMth-v5ZECdWzAVCIZipllYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 11:24:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/crackdown-3-release-date-revealed-along-first-multiplayer-trailer/" target="_blank"&gt;Crackdown 3 release date revealed along with first multiplayer trailer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The oft-delayed Crackdown 3 has finally been given a firm release date by Microsoft. The action-adventure will release on 15 February 2019 for Xbox One and PC and will be available on Microsoft's increasingly impressive Xbox Game Pass service. Announced at the X018 showcase, the release date reveal brings an end to Crackdown 3's often tumultuous development. Originally announced at the Xbox E3 showcase in 2015 by the original game creator's David Jones, Crackdown 3 has suffered multiple delays on the road to release. But with the release date seemingly set, Microsoft also revealed an impres...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tencent to expand underage ID check to all games - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tencent-games-id/tencent-to-expand-underage-id-check-to-all-games-idUSKCN1NA18L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOs-snxFvbwm2Z1JOYPtF50qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 12:10:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tencent-games-id/tencent-to-expand-underage-id-check-to-all-games-idUSKCN1NA18L" target="_blank"&gt;Tencent to expand underage ID check to all games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tencent Holdings will expand an addiction-prevention system for underage gamers to all of its games, the company said on Monday, as the industry faces increased government scrutiny. A "healthy gaming" system that includes time limits on daily play and can perform facial recognition-aided ID checks, already in use on Tencent's most popular Honour of Kings smartphone game, will be applied to nine other mobile games this year and expanded to cover all Tencent games next year, the company said in a post on its official WeChat account. The move marks Tencent's latest attempt to meet the Chinese ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Official NFL Jersey Skins Are Coming To 'Fortnite' Today: Here's What Time And How Much They'll Cost - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/09/official-nfl-jersey-skins-are-coming-to-fortnite-today-heres-what-time-and-how-much-theyll-cost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF1zUbSgldPOzhntb53d-UcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/09/official-nfl-jersey-skins-are-coming-to-fortnite-today-heres-what-time-and-how-much-theyll-cost/" target="_blank"&gt;Official NFL Jersey Skins Are Coming To 'Fortnite' Today: Here's What Time And How Much They'll Cost&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite Whenever we talk about character skins in Fortnite: Battle Royale, we remember one thing. Fortnite is a free-to-play game, and so all of this other stuff, whether it’s map updates, new items, gameplay changes or whatever, doesn’t make Epic one cent. It’s important in the process that gets people committed and spending money, of course, but when the rubber hits the road every single dime Epic makes comes from selling cosmetics. And in the case of these NFL skins, I get the feeling they’re going to make a whole lot of dimes. Starting tonight, November 9, players will be able to buy o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here Are Kohl's Black Friday 2018 Gaming Deals, Big Discounts On Xbox One X And Nintendo Switch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/03/here-are-kohls-black-friday-2018-gaming-deals-big-discounts-on-xbox-one-x-and-nintendo-switch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN98CHi1s9sFipeBXNeCWlQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/03/here-are-kohls-black-friday-2018-gaming-deals-big-discounts-on-xbox-one-x-and-nintendo-switch/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are Kohl's Black Friday 2018 Gaming Deals, Big Discounts On Xbox One X And Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kohl’s Black Friday ad. Black Friday leaking season is rolling in earnest, with full ads from places like Target and Costco already in the mix. It’s looking like a good year for console deals, with the Xbox One S, PS4, Xbox One X, and PS4 Pro all mature enough to be pushing for some impressive bundles and discounts as we enter into the golden years of this hardware generation. Today, we’re going to look at the gaming deals from Kohl’s, which are always some of the best on offer. For Kohl’s full ad scan, head to BestBlackFriday.com. For other tech deals, check out Gordon Kelly. As in past y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Review: The Good, The Bad And The Blackout - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2018/10/30/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-review-the-good-the-bad-and-the-blackout/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJfR2kfLIW9P1lCkWajsi0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2018/10/30/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-review-the-good-the-bad-and-the-blackout/" target="_blank"&gt;'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Review: The Good, The Bad And The Blackout&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4 isn’t without its flaws, but overall it’s one of the best shooters in years. This is the first time I’ve written a review of a Call of Duty game where I didn’t have to either avoid spoilers or put in spoiler warnings. After all, this year Black Ops 4 ships with multiplayer, the Blackout battle royale mode, and Zombies. There is no single-player campaign. A part of me wasn’t certain how to even review this game now that the solo campaign is gone. Does one dock points because a staple of the series is no longer present? Or does one review the game based on what’s inc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Battlefield 5's 'Firestorm' Battle Royale Mode Will Not Launch Until March 2019 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/24/battlefield-5s-firestorm-battle-royale-mode-will-not-launch-until-march-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrhW_8CJG3qEtF4FW3TFgkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 16:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/24/battlefield-5s-firestorm-battle-royale-mode-will-not-launch-until-march-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;Battlefield 5's 'Firestorm' Battle Royale Mode Will Not Launch Until March 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Battlefield V In a move that technically may not be a “delay,” but is a surprise all the same, DICE has revealed that Battlefield V’s entry into the battle royale genre, Firestorm, will not arrive in the game until the spring, March 2019 specifically. DICE rolled out a new roadmap for upcoming Battlefield content, which is really taking the games as service model to a new level, as even though technically it was never stated outright that Firestorm would be there at launch, I think nearly everyone planning to pick up the game was assuming that. It’s hard to view this as anything but a blow ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Update Changes Player Counts For Blackout Mode In 'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/17/new-update-changes-player-counts-for-blackout-mode-in-call-of-duty-black-ops-4/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB8wzgmJNUUsrlP0UmmkF08qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/17/new-update-changes-player-counts-for-blackout-mode-in-call-of-duty-black-ops-4/" target="_blank"&gt;New Update Changes Player Counts For Blackout Mode In 'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 hasn’t even been out for a week, but right after launch is sometimes the best time to do some tinkering. This year the venerable shooter came loaded with Blackout mode, Activision’s answer to the battle royale craze spawned by PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds and accelerated by Fortnite. That means large player counts on a map big enough to hold them all, no respawns and last man standing gameplay. It’s good, even if it’s not quite as ridiculous a battle royale as I’ve become accustomed to in Fortnite. Treyarch is already starting to tinker with things, h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Won't Have Loot Boxes: Here's How Customization Works Instead - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/19/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-wont-have-loot-boxes-heres-how-customization-works-instead/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECFNVarpjCKprb0DKe0V7EMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/19/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-wont-have-loot-boxes-heres-how-customization-works-instead/" target="_blank"&gt;'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Won't Have Loot Boxes: Here's How Customization Works Instead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can earn cosmetics just by playing ‘Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4′ or buy items you want directly. I really enjoyed last year’s Call of Duty: WWII, but one thing that drove me crazy about the game was the implementation of loot boxes. For real world money you could purchase “Supply Drops” which included various cosmetic items, from super lame pistol grip designs to really cool and varied uniforms for troops from myriad different countries. The problem with loot boxes, of course, is that you don’t know what you’re going to get and the act of opening one after another is a lot like pulling th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>‘Black Ops 4’: How ‘Call of Duty’s’ New Battle Royale Mode Outshines ‘Fortnite’ - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/black-ops-4-how-call-of-dutys-new-battle-royale-mode-outshines-fortnite</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENHq4PczYvLYz3576ikSlmoqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMKv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 08:47:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/black-ops-4-how-call-of-dutys-new-battle-royale-mode-outshines-fortnite" target="_blank"&gt;‘Black Ops 4’: How ‘Call of Duty’s’ New Battle Royale Mode Outshines ‘Fortnite’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activision Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 is the most significant release in the wildly successful first-person shooter franchise in over a decade. Maybe there’s something about fourths, because it was Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare that changed what the series was and could be in 2007. The critically acclaimed single-player campaign made a splash, but the waves that its multiplayer version left behind are still being felt all these years later. Ever since, the online modes have been many players’ real draw to the games. Now, they’re all that they have. Black Ops 4 may not change gaming, but it ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 review – a battle royale with military precision - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/oct/17/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-review-activision</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJQ0OXQp7vCiFjD4bYpCKYMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 10:54:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/oct/17/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-review-activision" target="_blank"&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 review – a battle royale with military precision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s weird to think of Call of Duty as an underdog. It was once the world’s biggest entertainment franchise, earning billions of dollars every year for its publisher Activision. But in recent times the military shooter has fallen out of favour, usurped by the bright, glossy thrills of Overwatch and Destiny and the more family-friendly multiplayer charms of Minecraft and Fortnite. At first glance, Black Ops 4 looks like a sad anachronism, desperate for relevance. The single-player campaign has been jettisoned, leaving us with just the multiplayer experience. Or, more accurately, three experi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4'--At Least Blackout Is Much Easier Than 'Fortnite' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/16/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-at-least-blackout-is-way-easier-than-fortnite/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFxBqr5xlikl1lmfcT6q9MwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/16/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-at-least-blackout-is-way-easier-than-fortnite/" target="_blank"&gt;'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4'--At Least Blackout Is Much Easier Than 'Fortnite'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty Blackout mode in Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 is a strange beast. As the first true AAA entry into the world of battle royale, it brings a sense of gunplay and mechanics refined over more than a decade to a space that just didn’t have anything like it. It manages to capture the tension of a hearing those menacing footsteps coming up behind you to a T, transposing the chaotic world of Call of Duty to something slower and more considered. In other ways, it shows us that ‘battle royale’ isn’t a genre so much as it is just another game mode, albeit one that’s been able to carry a few ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Good, The Bad And The Silly Of Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4's Blackout Mode - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/13/the-good-the-bad-and-the-silly-of-call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-blackout-mode-review/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIyfQEX_c0SJ-SnwEkNtFHwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 12:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/13/the-good-the-bad-and-the-silly-of-call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-blackout-mode-review/" target="_blank"&gt;The Good, The Bad And The Silly Of Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4's Blackout Mode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty It’s here: Call of Duty is back withBlack Ops 4, and things are pretty different this time around. There’s no single-player campaign for the first time in franchise history, but in its absence, we have Blackout mode: the first true AAA take on the battle royale genre and arguably the biggest departure from classic Call of Duty gameplay since we first got zombies. I played back in the beta and I played fairly nonstop yesterday, and I like what I see so far. This game isn’tFortnite,but it is sort ofPlayer Unknown’s Battlegrounds. Except it works, which is a good thing. Here’s my ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Day 1 With Call of Duty: Black Ops 4's Blackout -- Solid, But Strangely Unrewarding - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/13/day-1-with-call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-blackout-solid-but-strangely-unrewarding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1bHmBmD0VWPD-iJ1TFA24qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 14:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/13/day-1-with-call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-blackout-solid-but-strangely-unrewarding/" target="_blank"&gt;Day 1 With Call of Duty: Black Ops 4's Blackout -- Solid, But Strangely Unrewarding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty The launch of Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 has been strange. Usually, I dive into the campaign, finish that after 5 hours or so, then head to multiplayer in zombies. But with Black Ops 4, an official campaign is gone, reduced to a series of tiny cutscenes embedded in tutorials of multiplayer specialists, which I’ve found too tedious to get through so far, so where do I start? Blackout, of course. Black Ops 4’s campaign has been replaced by a mode that I have to agree is probably a more significant and important addition to the series than five more hours of a new campaign would ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 review | Blackout the star of freshest Call of Duty in years - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/call-duty-black-ops-4-review-blackout-star-freshest-call-duty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-fnQkvJ8SVsKhk2bJQzXoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 13:32:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/call-duty-black-ops-4-review-blackout-star-freshest-call-duty/" target="_blank"&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 review | Blackout the star of freshest Call of Duty in years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a card-carrying member of the single-player society, it was with some trepidation I dived into Call of Duty: Black Ops 4; a three-pronged multiplayer compendium of competitive action, Battle Royale and co-operative zombie slaying. And while there is part of me that still hankers for my yearly fix of the breakneck bombast and ooh-ra melodrama of a Call of Duty campaign, Black Ops 4 won me over with its ebullient variety and extraordinary polish. It is, simply put, the most fun I’ve had with a FPS multiplayer package since Overwatch rewrote the rulebook in 2016. The real reason for a lack ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4's Blackout Feels Like It's Going To Kill The Battle Royale Trend - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/12/call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-blackout-feels-like-its-going-to-kill-the-battle-royale-trend/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-Q98-jXetQLzisfOmZ1asqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 12:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/10/12/call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-blackout-feels-like-its-going-to-kill-the-battle-royale-trend/" target="_blank"&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4's Blackout Feels Like It's Going To Kill The Battle Royale Trend&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blackout It’s a weird feeling to load up a yearly Call of Duty release for the first time and not have a campaign to start. Rather, there’s a series of character “specialist” vignettes with some light story elements attached to them, and instead the centerpiece of Black Ops 4 is Blackout, its sprawling Battle Royale mode. Having played a good amount of Blackout in the beta and then some cursory matches this morning, I’ve already come to a conclusion. This feels like the beginning of the end for the Battle Royale trend. To be clear, this is not because I think Blackout is bad. The opposite, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Call Of Duty's 'Blackout' Doesn't Truly Compete With 'Fortnite' For Two Simple Reasons - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/12/call-of-dutys-blackout-doesnt-really-compete-with-fortnite-for-two-simple-reasons/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJovaDEJZfCz5JhtC2XROdsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 15:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/12/call-of-dutys-blackout-doesnt-really-compete-with-fortnite-for-two-simple-reasons/" target="_blank"&gt;Call Of Duty's 'Blackout' Doesn't Truly Compete With 'Fortnite' For Two Simple Reasons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Here’s a small indication of what publisher Activision thinks about Blackout, the new battle royale mode for Call of Duty: Black Ops 4, out today. As with all games, there’s a minimum amount you need to download before you can start playing Black Ops 4. And if you boot up the game at that minimum viable moment, you’ll notice something on the mode select screen. You won’t be able to play zombies and you won’t be able to play traditional multiplayer, because Blackout is the first thing the game downloaded. And why wouldn’t it be? Blackout has already made a splash in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Rare Weapons And Loot: Every Zombie Spawn Location In Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4's Blackout Mode - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/13/rare-weapons-and-loot-every-zombie-spawn-location-in-call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-blackout-mode/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBCJ5iPW47v6xhTZQ9Oeiv8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 12:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/13/rare-weapons-and-loot-every-zombie-spawn-location-in-call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-blackout-mode/" target="_blank"&gt;Rare Weapons And Loot: Every Zombie Spawn Location In Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4's Blackout Mode&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blackout Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 is here, and with it comes Blackout mode, the AAA shooter’s take on the battle royale genre. For the most part, things are pretty staightforward here: it’s more or less PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds in the world of Call of Duty, though it’s quicker and tighter than PUBG’s standard maps. There is one particularly Treyarch wrinkle, however, and that’s the presence of zombies. Zombies are a sort of curious addition to the game: they don’t really impact gameplay unless you go looking for them, but they add another wrinkle if you do. It’s less about any particu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Player Count And More: Everything You Need To Know About Blackout In 'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/11/player-count-and-more-everything-you-need-to-know-about-blackout-in-call-of-duty-black-ops-4/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED8oguj4ghn2wf-8kJ0MUk4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 15:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/11/player-count-and-more-everything-you-need-to-know-about-blackout-in-call-of-duty-black-ops-4/" target="_blank"&gt;Player Count And More: Everything You Need To Know About Blackout In 'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty: Blackout Call of Duty comes a little earlier this year. Activision’s titanic shooter franchise usually launches in early November, but this year the publisher wisely chose to give Red Dead Redemption 2 some space when it comes to game releases. And so we’re getting Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 tomorrow, October 12 with some other important changes. There’s no single-player campaign, and developer Treyarch has decided to lean into the game’s various multiplayer modes to create an experience it hopes will leave players not noticing its absence. But it’s not just a subtraction game...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Black Ops 4's Blackout Mode Has A Secret Weapon No Other Battle Royale Game Has - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/12/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-mode-has-a-secret-weapon-no-other-battle-royale-has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHhcpQmMJ7wSigL14czYAtcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/12/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-mode-has-a-secret-weapon-no-other-battle-royale-has/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Ops 4's Blackout Mode Has A Secret Weapon No Other Battle Royale Game Has&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blackout mode has split-screen, and it’s the only battle royale game that makes couch co-op possible. Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4 launched worldwide today on PS4, Xbox One and PC. So far it’s off to a great start, with servers up and running and tons of multiplayer content to explore across traditional MP, Blackout battle royale and Zombies. While there are some queues to wait in for Blackout, mostly that mode is off to a killer start. It’s obviously not going to unseat the free-to-play Fortnite, but it is the new gold standard in Battle Royale games, and titles like PUBG have much to fear. B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Enters Open Beta On Android, Now Available To Everyone - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/11/fortnite-battle-royale-enters-open-beta-on-android-now-available-to-everyone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFyhd1-GP2s236R2Eabfj7AqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 15:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/11/fortnite-battle-royale-enters-open-beta-on-android-now-available-to-everyone/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fortnite: Battle Royale' Enters Open Beta On Android, Now Available To Everyone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite is now available to everyone on Android, so long as you have a compatible device. Fortnite: Battle Royale has left closed beta on Android and is now open to everyone with a compatible device. You can see which devices are compatible with the free-to-play battle royale game here. Previously gamers had to sign up for an invitation to play the game on Android devices. Now you can simply go to Epic’s website and download the game. I haven’t played Fortnite on my Galaxy S8+ since it first came out. At the time it was laggy and not great, similar to when I first played the game on my iPa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout tips and tricks | Your guide to conquering CoD's Battle Royale - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/call-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-tips-tricks-guide-conquering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgQneMBm8DD-EJ1NkxpwxsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 10:30:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/call-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-tips-tricks-guide-conquering/" target="_blank"&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout tips and tricks | Your guide to conquering CoD's Battle Royale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4, which is out now on PS4, Xbox One and PC, is diving into the Battle Royale arena with Blackout, a military take on the popular mode made phenomenon by Fortnite. A large group of players will be dropped onto the Blackout map, forced to scavenge for weapons as a circle encloses the combatants and forces them together. Last player standing wins. Many Blackout players will likely be familiar with the Battle Royale format due to Fortnite or PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds, but Call of Duty will bring its own sense of fast-paced combat to the mix. To get an edge on the Ba...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fortnite's Floating Island Is Its Most Impressive Map Change Yet - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/27/fortnites-loot-lake-floating-island-is-its-most-impressive-map-change-yet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKJSKMz-EwR_n6vTc5z8UkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 15:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/27/fortnites-loot-lake-floating-island-is-its-most-impressive-map-change-yet/" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite's Floating Island Is Its Most Impressive Map Change Yet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost exactly a year ago, Player Unknown’s Battlegrounds was on top of the world and Epic Games was testing the waters with a battle royale game of its own, for which it used its zombie survival game Fortnite as a template. At the time, it looked something like a PUBG clone, though it was one of the first of such clones to hit the market. It took place on a largely barren map with some small buildings and the occasional larger subdivision or farm, and we wondered how it would distinguish itself from PUBG. A year later, we’re staring this thing in the face: Fortnite Season 6 has arrived in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How to play Fortnite | Top tips and tricks guide for beginners as Season 6 begins - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/play-fortnite-top-tips-tricks-guide-beginners-season-6-begins/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBMaePvwEWs_Q9VSor3JegoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 10:08:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/play-fortnite-top-tips-tricks-guide-beginners-season-6-begins/" target="_blank"&gt;How to play Fortnite | Top tips and tricks guide for beginners as Season 6 begins&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are just starting out in Fortnite, perhaps intrigued by the hype surrounding today's release of Fortnite Season 6, there is a chance you have dropped onto the game's colourful map and found yourself quickly zapped by another, apparently lightning=speed player before you have even had a chance to find your first gun. We are here to help you with that, with our tips and trick for players just starting out in Fortnite. Only one person in 100 can come out of Fortnite: Battle Royale alive, so the chances of it being you are very slim indeed. Whether it’s a cheeky sniper, surprise shotgun ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Monster Hunter World' Outperformed 'PUBG' In August On PC - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/25/monster-hunter-world-outperformed-pubg-in-august-on-pc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJIEnvBIyJuZV_pG8qRjTFoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 16:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/25/monster-hunter-world-outperformed-pubg-in-august-on-pc/" target="_blank"&gt;'Monster Hunter World' Outperformed 'PUBG' In August On PC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monster Hunter World, World of Warcraft, Madden NFL 19 and Fortnite were the big winners in August. SuperData Research has released its list of top-grossing digital games for August, 2018. The firm analyzes worldwide digital game revenue across PC, consoles and mobile. In August, the top-grossing PC game was Dungeon Fighter Online; the top-grossing console game was Fortnite: Battle Royale; and the top-grossing mobile game was Honour of Kings. The top-grossing premium PC game (as opposed to free-to-play) was Monster Hunter World, unseating PUBG which held the #1 spot before. Monster Hunter W...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The clever UX that made Fortnite a $1.2 billion sensation - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90241691/the-clever-ux-that-made-fortnite-a-1-2-billion-sensation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_dKHB11_NlDC85n-E10Z4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 09:00:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90241691/the-clever-ux-that-made-fortnite-a-1-2-billion-sensation" target="_blank"&gt;The clever UX that made Fortnite a $1.2 billion sensation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The online videogame Fortnite Battle Royale was launched just a year ago in September 2017. Since then the game had amassed 125 million active players by June and made $1.2 billion for its developer Epic Games. It has also been linked to 200 divorces and a case of aggravated harassment where a 45-year-old man threatened to kill an 11-year-old boy after losing to him in the game. Love it or hate it, the question is: How has Epic Games created a game with such enormous social, economic, and psychological impact? Fusing elements from recent hits such as Minecraft, PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Golden Joysticks 2018 nominees announced, voting open now - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/golden-joysticks-2018-nominees-announced-voting-open-now/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMjVTAGI_TgM4bBH3IHRwEkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 11:12:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/golden-joysticks-2018-nominees-announced-voting-open-now/" target="_blank"&gt;Golden Joysticks 2018 nominees announced, voting open now&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nominees for the Golden Joystick Awards 2018 have been announced and public voting is now open for the 36th edition of the famous UK gaming awards. The Golden Joysticks will take place at the Bloomsbury Big Top on 16 November and will be hosted by comedian Danny Wallace, the awards will celebrate the last year of the gaming industry across multiple categories. The categories cover a wide range across the industry including storytelling and esports alongside the more traditional disciplines of audio and visual. There is also a new category this year recognising the best co-operative gam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Yes, 'Fortnite' Should Be Worried About 'Call of Duty: Blackout' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/09/17/yes-fortnite-should-be-worried-about-call-of-duty-blackout/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG3qsDgsoI-0R7zVeqWfzYUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 15:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/09/17/yes-fortnite-should-be-worried-about-call-of-duty-blackout/" target="_blank"&gt;Yes, 'Fortnite' Should Be Worried About 'Call of Duty: Blackout'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blackout The beta reviews are in, and generally, everyone seems pretty impressed with Blackout, Call of Duty’s stab at the battle royale genre, desperate not to be left behind in the shooter landscape, as if it ever could, remaining the most popular game of the year, every year, indefinitely. But all that shooter experience and several hundred million dollars per game have yielded a very polished, very fun version of battle royale that should have its competitors concerned, even market leader and global phenomenon, Fortnite. Obviously the most similar competition to Blackout is going to be ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>‘Fortnite’ frenzy may have peaked as Twitch viewership falls sharply - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fortnite-frenzy-may-have-peaked-as-twitch-viewership-falls-sharply-2018-09-18</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMTfDCb8Wv2yATF4Vv10zHEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw6JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 11:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fortnite-frenzy-may-have-peaked-as-twitch-viewership-falls-sharply-2018-09-18" target="_blank"&gt;‘Fortnite’ frenzy may have peaked as Twitch viewership falls sharply&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RATINGS GAME By Tomi Kilgore Twitch viewership falls 13% for ‘Fortnite’ in August, but jump 48% for Activision games Twitch streamer and professional gamer Tyler "Ninja" Blevins Getty Images Interest in “Fortnite,” which has taken the videogame world by storm since its release last year, may have peaked, as data compiled by Piper Jaffray showed that viewership on streaming video platform Twitch suffered the steepest-ever monthly decline for the game. Amazon.com Inc.’s (AMZN) Twitch is a leading social-gaming platform. “Overall, we believe tracking Twitch viewership can provide insight i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Do Analysts See Tencent's Decline As A Buying Opportunity Or As A Structural Concern? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bonanzachalaban/2018/09/19/do-analysts-see-tencents-decline-as-a-buying-opportunity-or-as-a-structural-concern/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOiZa04Pbl6sxTWWwwoqgl8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 13:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/bonanzachalaban/2018/09/19/do-analysts-see-tencents-decline-as-a-buying-opportunity-or-as-a-structural-concern/" target="_blank"&gt;Do Analysts See Tencent's Decline As A Buying Opportunity Or As A Structural Concern?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teenager playing Minecraft multiplayer online game (MMO). Getty Royalty Free Tencent stock has declined by about 30% over the last six months as government regulation on gaming has hampered the business. However, while some investors are feeling the pain of the decline, others see an opportunity. More investors are now kicking the tires to see if the dip presents a buying opportunity or is reflective of real concerns that could further limit company growth. What happened to the gaming business? The Chinese government temporarily suspended the approval process for new releases earlier in the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Blackout Beta Gets A Suprise Extension And Huge Player Count Increase - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/17/call-of-duty-blackout-beta-gets-a-suprise-extension-and-huge-player-count-increase/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKkp05U1R-fBXeRUdkWnorEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/17/call-of-duty-blackout-beta-gets-a-suprise-extension-and-huge-player-count-increase/" target="_blank"&gt;'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Blackout Beta Gets A Suprise Extension And Huge Player Count Increase&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 One part of this headline I saw coming, another part of this headline I didn’t quite. The first is commonplace among major AAA betas: The Blackout beta for Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 is getting a minor extension, from 10:00 a.m. Pacific to 12:00 p.m. Pacific, which is quite a bit shorter than what we normally see in these situations. On its own, it’s not a huge deal. During that time, however, Treyarch is increasing the player count from 88 to 100: Treyarch has been pushing that from an original 80 players, adding in a whopping 20 by this point. 100 is a sort of a m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout beta impressions | Can new Battle Royale take on Fortnite? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/call-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-beta-hands-on-review-can-battle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQbIoohNDN8REIwttfhA3UqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:51:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/call-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-beta-hands-on-review-can-battle/" target="_blank"&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout beta impressions | Can new Battle Royale take on Fortnite?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout beta has started in earnest, with the Battle Royale mode looking to take on Fortnite as gaming’s premier last-man-standing pursuit. This week’s test-run is the first time we have had a proper look at Blackout, which currently drops 80 combatants into a huge map, each of them vying to be the sole survivor by collecting equipment and eliminating enemies. Developer Treyarch recently revealed some new details about the game, including the presence of zombies across the map, but for the most part the beta has players going in cold to learn how Blackout is h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Call of Duty: Blackout' Is Poised To Challenge 'Fortnite,' Crush 'PUBG' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/09/11/call-of-duty-blackout-is-poised-to-challenge-fortnite-crush-pubg/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDlmA41P7LgMqyknm3vi2ygqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 13:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/09/11/call-of-duty-blackout-is-poised-to-challenge-fortnite-crush-pubg/" target="_blank"&gt;'Call of Duty: Blackout' Is Poised To Challenge 'Fortnite,' Crush 'PUBG'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blackout Like most people, I sort of shrugged at the news that Call of Duty would be attempting a battle royale mode this fall in order to chase the PUBG/Fortnite trend. Of course they were doing that, only this time, it was costing us a single player campaign, which was its own sort of annoyance. And yet, after playing Blackout in the beta going on right now, I’m more impressed than I thought I would be, and this feels like it’s going to be the first real challenger to Fortnite in a good long while. It has more potential than Battlefield V’s similar attempt, and seems like it could place a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Call of Duty Black Ops 4 Blackout beta extends to Xbox One and PC players and adds new playlists - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/call-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-beta-extends-xbox-one-pc-players/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKtgXXE2JYOjfe3jWHNbDKoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:47:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/call-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-beta-extends-xbox-one-pc-players/" target="_blank"&gt;Call of Duty Black Ops 4 Blackout beta extends to Xbox One and PC players and adds new playlists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Call of Duty Black Ops 4 Blackout beta is now available on Xbox One and PC. The test run for Call of Duty's take on the popular Battle Royale mode, which pits a large amount of combatants against each other across an open map in an effort to be the last man standing, had already released on PS4 to a positive reception. And, as promised in an interview with The Telegraph, developer Treyarch has begun to experiment with the gametypes beyond the base Battle Royale mode. Close Quarters is the latest playlist to be added in an update, which limits players to short-range weaponry and fists in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Is This New 'Fortnite' Leak An Xbox Exclusive Skin Bundle At Last? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/09/14/is-this-new-fortnite-leak-an-xbox-exclusive-skin-bundle-at-last/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQJeuT1TVQARCQprvZ8ORwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/09/14/is-this-new-fortnite-leak-an-xbox-exclusive-skin-bundle-at-last/" target="_blank"&gt;Is This New 'Fortnite' Leak An Xbox Exclusive Skin Bundle At Last?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortnite New skins are a big deal in Fortnite, as are new bundles, and one is currently making the rounds that may have a certain subset of players very excited. This was first found by TrueAchievements, an Xbox site, and it seems as if this leaked “Eon Bundle” may be Xbox One exclusive. The Eon Bundle contains the Eon skin, seen above, the Aurora glider, which is essentially a reskin of the Oblivion glider, and the Resonator pickaxe, which is not shown, but might be this one. Why does this appear to be Xbox exclusive? Well, for starters, it’s Xbox colors, silver and a glowing neon green. S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Tencent's New Battle Royale Game 'Ring Of Elysium' Brings Extreme Winter Sports To The Genre - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/12/tencents-new-battle-royale-game-ring-of-elysium-brings-extreme-winter-sports-to-the-genre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELRR_MIj-V9NTds_2ybWSJsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/12/tencents-new-battle-royale-game-ring-of-elysium-brings-extreme-winter-sports-to-the-genre/" target="_blank"&gt;Tencent's New Battle Royale Game 'Ring Of Elysium' Brings Extreme Winter Sports To The Genre&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tencent’s new battle royale game ‘Ring of Elysium’ includes snowboarding, hang-gliding and dynamic weather events like avalanches and it releases for free on Steam next week. I’d heard about Ring of Elysium (RoE) in the past but never really paid close attention to it was pretty much limited to Asia. Now the game is finally making its way to the US, releasing for free on Steam on September 19th as an Early Access title. It also looks way different than what I remember from early footage. Tencent has put a ton of work into the game and it looks like no other battle royale title out there cur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Tencent under pressure to step up its game as regulatory restrictions bite - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tencent-strategy-analysis/tencent-under-pressure-to-step-up-its-game-as-regulatory-restrictions-bite-idUSKCN1LS0MP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK779O1lFrJhAJgWMiDuV_EqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 06:01:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tencent-strategy-analysis/tencent-under-pressure-to-step-up-its-game-as-regulatory-restrictions-bite-idUSKCN1LS0MP" target="_blank"&gt;Tencent under pressure to step up its game as regulatory restrictions bite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tencent Holdings, which has lost some $200 billion in market value this year, is facing fresh criticism from analysts and investors unnerved by regulatory roadblocks, a fuzzy overseas strategy and growing debt. The gaming and social media firm is one of a number of Chinese internet companies whose prospects are suddenly in question after years of spectacular growth. But Tencent's fall, triggered mainly by a government crackdown on online gaming, has been especially dramatic. In the latest setback, Tencent on Monday shut an online Texas Hold'Em poker game in response to government scrutiny. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Blackout Beta Impressions: The Good, The Bad And The Ugly (So Far) - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/11/the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly-of-the-call-of-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-beta-so-far/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG4cSoWP9FEW08WhE_Z115kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/11/the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly-of-the-call-of-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-beta-so-far/" target="_blank"&gt;'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Blackout Beta Impressions: The Good, The Bad And The Ugly (So Far)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4 ‘Blackout’ beta is really good, with a few small problems. Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4 is set to launch in just a few weeks. In the meantime, we have the weeklong Blackout battle royale beta now live on PS4. It goes live for Xbox One and PC this weekend. I spent a good portion of the afternoon yesterday playing Blackout and have come away mostly very pleased. It’s a fun new mode that should really appeal to both fans of Call Of Duty and the emerging battle royale genre. It’s quite a bit different from king-of-the-hill Fortnite, but bears more than a few similarit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Tencent shuts poker platform amid widening gaming crackdown - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-videogames/tencent-shuts-poker-platform-amid-widening-gaming-crackdown-idUSKCN1LQ0UL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ9ENfbwEcLrIFHI412XBZ8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 08:13:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-videogames/tencent-shuts-poker-platform-amid-widening-gaming-crackdown-idUSKCN1LQ0UL" target="_blank"&gt;Tencent shuts poker platform amid widening gaming crackdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tencent Holdings will shut a popular Texas Hold'Em poker video game, the Chinese tech giant said to its users on Monday, in a further step to comply with intensifying government scrutiny hitting the country's gaming industry. Tencent said it would formally begin to shutter "Everyday Texas Hold'Em" from Monday and would closer the game's server from Sept 25. Tencent would compensate users in accordance with regulations of Ministry of Culture. The Shenzhen-based company, which draws a huge amount of its profit from gaming, is facing mounting challenges this year from stringent regulation and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Chinese Gaming Companies Target Overseas Players As Regulators Clamp Down - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ywang/2018/09/06/chinese-gaming-companies-target-overseas-players-as-regulators-clamp-down/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENowBPs8F6BHdCXzemKCDkIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 06:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ywang/2018/09/06/chinese-gaming-companies-target-overseas-players-as-regulators-clamp-down/" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese Gaming Companies Target Overseas Players As Regulators Clamp Down&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ma Huateng, chairman and chief executive officer of Tencent Holdings Ltd. (Photo: Anthony Kwan/Bloomberg) China’s largest gaming companies are accelerating their efforts to expand abroad as Beijing plans new restrictions on the country’s gaming sector. Last week, Tencent and NetEase both saw their stocks tumble more than 5% after regulators announced their intention to limit the release of new games and introduce restrictions on the amount of time minors can spend playing online games. The new curbs follow a longer-than-expected regulatory freeze that delayed the approval of new games, whic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Watch The New 'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Blackout Battle Royale Trailer Right Here - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/06/watch-the-call-of-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-battle-royale-trailer-right-here/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN7boyBfw-1bUo3YxaPa0E8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 18:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/06/watch-the-call-of-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-battle-royale-trailer-right-here/" target="_blank"&gt;Watch The New 'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Blackout Battle Royale Trailer Right Here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s your first glimpse at Call of Duty: Black Ops 4′s new battle royale mode ‘Blackout’. Treyarch has finally released a gameplay trailer for Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4′s new battle royale mode, ‘Blackout.’ It looks pretty sweet. The new mode combines air, land and sea-based combat in the largest map in the franchise’s history. (You can see the full map here.) Blackout 80 players compete to see who the last player (or duo or squad) standing is, and it all takes place across a map filled with familiar Call of Duty locations. Check it out: So that looks pretty sweet, honestly. Then again I’...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout player count and map revealed, zombies confirmed and more - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/call-duty-black-ops-4-beta-battle-royale-mode-blackout-will/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENlfGQGYKy6KenBoV7Ye_nkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 19:02:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/call-duty-black-ops-4-beta-battle-royale-mode-blackout-will/" target="_blank"&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout player count and map revealed, zombies confirmed and more&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 developer Treyarch has revealed that its Fortnite challenging Battle Royale mode, Blackout, will start with a player count of 80 combatants. Speaking to Game Informer, Treyarch revealed that Blackout's private beta will be used to assess and possibly tweak the player count depending on player feedback. "We’re starting with 80 players, but we’ve gone higher than that," said co-studio head Dan Bunting. Bunting said that the beta was 'the beginning of something' and that the team will 'make changes and adapt'. "A lot that can go on that can happen beyond that first im...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4's Blackout Closed Beta: How To Get A Code On PS4, Xbox One Or PC - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/07/call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-blackout-closed-beta-how-to-get-a-ps4-xbox-one-or-pc-code/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEm_i4Uv441BlY73nSKcKgEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 15:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/09/07/call-of-duty-black-ops-4s-blackout-closed-beta-how-to-get-a-ps4-xbox-one-or-pc-code/" target="_blank"&gt;Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4's Blackout Closed Beta: How To Get A Code On PS4, Xbox One Or PC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty: Blackout Sure, we’ve already played regular multiplayer in Call of Duty: Black Ops 4, but there’s something else coming our way. The beta for the new Blackout mode is right around the corner, though it’s a closed beta, so you’ll need a code to participate. Read on to find out how you can get access to the Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Blackout beta on PS4, Xbox One and PC. As is common with this sort of closed beta, participation is limited to people who have pre-ordered the game. If you pre-ordered through a participating retailer, you should get the code either through a printed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Blackout Battle Royale Player-Count Revealed Plus New Details - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/04/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-battle-royale-player-count-revealed-plus-new-details/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrpiSJJCTkrGkvAYL87yCgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 19:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/04/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-battle-royale-player-count-revealed-plus-new-details/" target="_blank"&gt;'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Blackout Battle Royale Player-Count Revealed Plus New Details&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call of Duty: Black Ops 4′s Blackout Battle Royale mode will feature 80 player matches. Treyarch has revealed the player count for the upcoming Blackout battle royale mode in Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4. 80 players will take to the battlefield to see which player, duo or squad (goofily referred to as “quads” in Black Ops 4) can emerge last-gamer-standing. That’s 20 fewer players than you’ll find in PUBG or Fortnite and 16 more than you’ll find in the new Firestormbattle royale mode in Battlefield 5. “What’s really more important to us than a number is that the gameplay experience is as refine...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here's The Massive 'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Blackout Battle Royale Map - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/05/heres-the-massive-call-of-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-battle-royale-map/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKpWFMBL4edbzj9-f7H8sEoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 21:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/09/05/heres-the-massive-call-of-duty-black-ops-4-blackout-battle-royale-map/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's The Massive 'Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4' Blackout Battle Royale Map&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treyarch has finally revealed the Blackout map. The Call Of Duty: Black Ops 4 ‘Blackout’ battle royale beta begins next week, and we’re getting little tidbits and details about the new mode on an almost daily basis at this point. Yesterday we learned the player-count for a Blackout match. Today we get our first glimpse at the mode’s massive map—by far the largest in Call Of Duty history. Treyarch revealed the map today on Twitter. Here it is: The Blackout map is huge. It’s an interesting map. Rather than an island, we have one coastal section, quite a bit of forest, some rivers and, presuma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fortnite app for Android let hackers hijack players' phones, Google warns - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-app-android-hackers-google-epic-games-a8512431.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC6j71GvZYCdgZRIzTapCJ0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 10:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/fortnite-app-android-hackers-google-epic-games-a8512431.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fortnite app for Android let hackers hijack players' phones, Google warns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fortnite app on Android can be hijacked by hackers to instigate "worm" attacks on players, Google has revealed Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney acknowledged the issue, which allows other apps on a user's device to silently install unapproved software in the background, but said Google should have waited longer to reveal the problem. The disagreement is the latest in a long-running dispute between the two companies and comes after Epic refused to make the Android version of its hit game available on the official Google Play store. Yes, telling users that a flaw was found and advising updating ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Tencent games revenue in focus after China blocks "Monster Hunter: World" - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-tencent-videogames/tencents-monster-hunter-world-axed-in-china-days-after-launch-idUSKBN1KY1OU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOcexncoErrCdUMBC_aAdyUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 09:31:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-tencent-videogames/tencents-monster-hunter-world-axed-in-china-days-after-launch-idUSKBN1KY1OU" target="_blank"&gt;Tencent games revenue in focus after China blocks "Monster Hunter: World"&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China's Tencent Holdings Ltd saw its stock tumble on Tuesday, wiping out around $15 billion in its market value, amid concern of a blow to its video game revenue after regulators blocked the sale of one of its blockbuster titles. Analysts had widely expected "Monster Hunter: World" to be one of 2018's biggest hits for Tencent, which licensed the game from Japan's Capcom Co Ltd to sell on its WeGame platform. However the game, where players hunt fearsome creatures, disappeared from the platform on Monday, days after its Aug. 8 release. Tencent in a statement said regulators had received a la...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Regulatory limbo hits Tencent with first profit fall in nearly 13 years - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tencent-results/regulatory-limbo-hits-tencent-with-first-profit-fall-in-nearly-13-years-idUSKBN1L0115</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO175ihJMAlModvWULY7AVMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 16:10:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tencent-results/regulatory-limbo-hits-tencent-with-first-profit-fall-in-nearly-13-years-idUSKBN1L0115" target="_blank"&gt;Regulatory limbo hits Tencent with first profit fall in nearly 13 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese technology giant Tencent Holdings Ltd has "no clarity" on when it may get approval to start charging for its most popular game, it said on Wednesday, after reporting its first quarterly profit fall in nearly 13 years on weak gaming revenue. Company president Martin Lau said "the biggest issue" before Tencent could return to rapid revenue growth was to gain regulatory approval to start charging for its PlayerUnknowns' Battlegrounds (PUBG) video game in China, while confirming a sector-wide freeze for new game approvals in the world's largest gaming market due to a government restruct...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Profit at China's Tencent falls for first time in 13 years - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/08/15/profit-chinas-tencent-falls-first-time-13-years/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBbgRn8FnCt00C8-DZeO57EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 14:51:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/08/15/profit-chinas-tencent-falls-first-time-13-years/" target="_blank"&gt;Profit at China's Tencent falls for first time in 13 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese technology giant Tencent unveiled its first profit fall in 13 years after a sluggish performance from its mobile gaming division. Profits for the most recent quarter fell to 17.87bn yuan (£2bn), below the 19.67bn yuan expectation of analysts. Tencent, the second most valuable firm listed in Asia and one of the largest constituents of the MSCI Emerging Market index, blamed the slowdown in growth on weak sales of some of its popular gaming titles. The poor performance, which triggered a 2 per cent sell-off in Tencent shares, came after the Chinese government blocked the sale of “Mons...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>PUBG developer launches new website called 'Fix PUBG' as it admits that game is broken - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/pubg-fix-latest-update-fortnite-battle-royale-problems-issues-download-a8482901.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMxGORfzNU854vHfr8REes4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/pubg-fix-latest-update-fortnite-battle-royale-problems-issues-download-a8482901.html" target="_blank"&gt;PUBG developer launches new website called 'Fix PUBG' as it admits that game is broken&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The developers of Playerunknown's Battlegrounds have promised to fix the game and launched a special website to force them to do so. The page – called "Fix PUBG" – takes its name from a popular rallying cry of fans who are tired of the games various bugs, issues and problems. The website lists 100 major bugs and crosses them off as developers fix them. Many of them have been removed by the latest update for Xbox and PC, though many more are still remaining. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/43 Designed by Pierpaolo Lazzarini from Italian co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>China’s gaming groups locked in battle for growth - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/96ea0e2e-9ae5-11e8-ab77-f854c65a4465</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENtYhv_L_qVEk34VL8b7zHoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 21:00:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/96ea0e2e-9ae5-11e8-ab77-f854c65a4465" target="_blank"&gt;China’s gaming groups locked in battle for growth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would make a great survival game: player must win over politicians and vault a 3,000-strong line of competitors all clamouring for regulatory approval, while also fighting rivals to grab the spoils in the world’s biggest market. For online and mobile gaming companies that operate in China, where players spent $30bn last year — mostly on mobile games — that virtual scenario is morphing uncomfortably into reality. Growth in the market, like others dependent on online users, is slowing. Regulatory approval for new games has been suspended since March, a byproduct of politics and a bureaucra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Match Fixing Remains A Serious Or Moderate Threat To Esports Community - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2018/07/25/match-fixing-remains-a-serious-or-moderate-threat-to-esports-community/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBWtiqYl_zecjpxO8iaz2UkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 12:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/darrenheitner/2018/07/25/match-fixing-remains-a-serious-or-moderate-threat-to-esports-community/" target="_blank"&gt;Match Fixing Remains A Serious Or Moderate Threat To Esports Community&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Esports players participating in ‘PlayersUnknown’s Battlegrounds’ in the PUBG Pan-Continental tournament on July 14, 2018 in Las Vegas, Nevada. (Photo by David J. Becker/Getty Images) The biggest threat to continued success for the esports industry is match fixing. A total of 78% of respondents to a recently conducted survey view match fixing as a serious or moderate risk to the sustained wellness and growth of an industry that is projected to grow to nearly $1 billion by the end of 2018 and can now brag about investments from individuals such as former HP CEO Meg Whitman as well as Golden ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Why the world loves “Fortnite” and I don’t - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90204342/im-too-old-for-fortnite-but-i-get-its-appeal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBYNDwYgq28vxM53Yj8XekMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90204342/im-too-old-for-fortnite-but-i-get-its-appeal" target="_blank"&gt;Why the world loves “Fortnite” and I don’t&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s no secret that as you get older, you become less attuned to popular music. Your tastes change with your maturing personality, and you become less concerned about keeping up with what’s new. You may even experience something called “taste freeze,” in which you gravitate back to the music of your adolescence because of the strong emotions it stirs. I’ve never had the same feeling about video games until I started playing Fortnite, the free-for-all multiplayer shooter which has transcended mere popularity to become a global phenomenon. Perhaps you’ve heard the stories by now: Kids sneakin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>PUBG drops Fortnite game lawsuit without explanation - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/jun/28/pubg-drops-fortnite-lawsuit-epic-games</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSOm2WyeF8zICmFWij1zc4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 15:22:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/jun/28/pubg-drops-fortnite-lawsuit-epic-games" target="_blank"&gt;PUBG drops Fortnite game lawsuit without explanation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lawsuit against the creator of hit online game Fortnite has been quietly dropped, according to Bloomberg. In May, it was reported that PUBG Corp, the company behind successful PC title PlayerUnknown’s Battleground had filed a lawsuit in South Korea against Epic Games, the developer of Fortnite. The suit alleged that Epic had copied ideas from PUBG Corp’s game, notably its “Battle Royale” structure, in which 100 players descend on an island and then fight until only one remains. On Monday, however, PUBG Corp sent a letter of withdrawal to Epic’s attorneys. At the time of the action, legal ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item></channel></rss>