<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Nokia - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFZpTldNU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-UG&amp;gl=UG&amp;ceid=UG:en</link><language>en-UG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:36:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>10 questions answered about Nokia smartphones - Dignited</title><link>https://www.dignited.com/37011/10-questions-answered-about-nokia-smartphones/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiTWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRpZ25pdGVkLmNvbS8zNzAxMS8xMC1xdWVzdGlvbnMtYW5zd2VyZWQtYWJvdXQtbm9raWEtc21hcnRwaG9uZXMv0gGaAWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LWRpZ25pdGVkLWNvbS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy5kaWduaXRlZC5jb20vMzcwMTEvMTAtcXVlc3Rpb25zLWFuc3dlcmVkLWFib3V0LW5va2lhLXNtYXJ0cGhvbmVzL2FtcC8_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.dignited.com/37011/10-questions-answered-about-nokia-smartphones/" target="_blank"&gt;10 questions answered about Nokia smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Dignited&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nokia, a Finland-based smartphone manufacturer, is one of the oldest makers of mobile phones. Here are 10 questions answered about Nokia smartphones.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.dignited.com">Dignited</source></item><item><title>A Nokia Phone Buying Guide for Absolute Nokia fans - Dignited</title><link>https://www.dignited.com/37013/a-nokia-phone-buying-guide-for-absolute-nokia-fans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiUmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRpZ25pdGVkLmNvbS8zNzAxMy9hLW5va2lhLXBob25lLWJ1eWluZy1ndWlkZS1mb3ItYWJzb2x1dGUtbm9raWEtZmFucy_SAZ8BaHR0cHM6Ly93d3ctZGlnbml0ZWQtY29tLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3Mvd3d3LmRpZ25pdGVkLmNvbS8zNzAxMy9hLW5va2lhLXBob25lLWJ1eWluZy1ndWlkZS1mb3ItYWJzb2x1dGUtbm9raWEtZmFucy9hbXAvP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.dignited.com/37013/a-nokia-phone-buying-guide-for-absolute-nokia-fans/" target="_blank"&gt;A Nokia Phone Buying Guide for Absolute Nokia fans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Dignited&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you a Nokia fan? Or a smartphone user looking to buy Nokia? Read through this Nokia Phone Buying Guide to see the best kind of Nokia phone to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.dignited.com">Dignited</source></item><item><title>HMD Global Confirms Android 9.0 Pie Update For Nokia 3, 5, 6 and 8 Smartphones - Dignited</title><link>https://www.dignited.com/36967/hmd-global-confirms-android-9-0-pie-update-for-nokia-3-5-6-and-8-smartphones/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRpZ25pdGVkLmNvbS8zNjk2Ny9obWQtZ2xvYmFsLWNvbmZpcm1zLWFuZHJvaWQtOS0wLXBpZS11cGRhdGUtZm9yLW5va2lhLTMtNS02LWFuZC04LXNtYXJ0cGhvbmVzL9IBuQFodHRwczovL3d3dy1kaWduaXRlZC1jb20uY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy93d3cuZGlnbml0ZWQuY29tLzM2OTY3L2htZC1nbG9iYWwtY29uZmlybXMtYW5kcm9pZC05LTAtcGllLXVwZGF0ZS1mb3Itbm9raWEtMy01LTYtYW5kLTgtc21hcnRwaG9uZXMvYW1wLz9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.dignited.com/36967/hmd-global-confirms-android-9-0-pie-update-for-nokia-3-5-6-and-8-smartphones/" target="_blank"&gt;HMD Global Confirms Android 9.0 Pie Update For Nokia 3, 5, 6 and 8 Smartphones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Dignited&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HMD Global has announced that Nokia 3, Nokia 5, Nokia 6 and Nokia 8 smartphones will receive the Android 9.0 Pie update.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.dignited.com">Dignited</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECs8OiMwxPuwcZzcG4cRAdMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/07/android-google-headlines-galaxy-s10plus-samsung-nokia-oneplus-5g-pixel-3xl/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: New Galaxy S10 Plus Leaks, Three New Nokia Handsets, OnePlus 5G Confirmed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes no notch in the Galaxy S10, the 5G S10 confirmed for America, the OnePlus 5G heading to the UK, three new Nokia handsets, a review of the Pocophone F1, Huawei’s ongoing security issues, and an innovation award for the Pixel 3 and 3XL. Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). No Notch, But There Will Be A Hole, In The New Galaxy S10 Samsung appe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What To Expect From Nokia In 2019 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/12/04/what-to-expect-from-nokia-in-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOc3ou8wNioukRxsXsh8JI4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 16:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/12/04/what-to-expect-from-nokia-in-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;What To Expect From Nokia In 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attendees try out Nokia phones on display at a launch event for the Nokia X6 smartphone, produced by HMD Global Oy, in Beijing, China, on Wednesday, May 16, 2018. Photographer: Giulia Marchi/Bloomberg Nokia, one of the largest mobile network equipment providers, has had a mixed 2018. While revenues declined modestly over the first nine months of the year, the company has been benefiting from traction in its technology licensing business, a gradually stabilizing network equipment market and solid cost reductions. Nokia’s stock price has risen by close to 20% year-to-date to levels of around ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nokia 7.1 Review: King Of The Middle Of The Road - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/02/nokia-7-1-review-hmdglobal-android-androidone-specifications/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL7ztJsannlHG2kTaAvBE_sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 01:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/12/02/nokia-7-1-review-hmdglobal-android-androidone-specifications/" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia 7.1 Review: King Of The Middle Of The Road&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not everyone wants a high-end flagship smartphone. Not everyone wants to pay the high cost to own one of these computational monsters outright or can budget for two years of contract payments. Even options such as the OnePlus 6T or the Xiaomi Mi8 Pro can be seen as overkill for people who just want ‘a decent smartphone’ to get them through the day. The rise in price of the flagship iPhone and Galaxy handsets have left a number of spaces between the high flyers and the ‘as low a price as you can go’ market. In here you will find the affordable flagships from the aforementioned OnePlus and X...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>HMD Global Rolls Out Latest Android 9 Pie Update To The Nokia 7.1 Midrange Smartphone - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/11/27/hmd-global-rolls-out-latest-android-9-pie-update-to-the-nokia-7-1-midrange-smartphone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG2WIUL9rQ6TRp_RMueTcUEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeanbaptiste/2018/11/27/hmd-global-rolls-out-latest-android-9-pie-update-to-the-nokia-7-1-midrange-smartphone/" target="_blank"&gt;HMD Global Rolls Out Latest Android 9 Pie Update To The Nokia 7.1 Midrange Smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With its hardware capabilities, Android One support and a $350 price tag, the Nokia 7.1 already stood out at launch from the rest of the midrange phones under $400 including the LG G6, LG Q7 or Motorola X4. With the Android 9 update, the Nokia 7.1 is the first midrange device running Google’s latest mobile operating system in the U.S. HMD Global, the Finland-based maker of Nokia branded phones, announced today that Android 9 also commonly referred by the codename “Pie”, is arriving on its midrange smartphone, the Nokia 7.1, launched last month in the U.S. With this upgrade, the Nokia 7.1 jo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nokia reshuffles management with focus on 5G market - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-5g/nokia-reshuffles-management-with-focus-on-5g-market-idUSKCN1NR0M3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDUiMTZDmI9QMZlrg7UxWooqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 09:20:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-5g/nokia-reshuffles-management-with-focus-on-5g-market-idUSKCN1NR0M3" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia reshuffles management with focus on 5G market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The head of Nokia's (NOKIA.HE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) mobile networks arm, its largest business unit, is leaving the Finnish company as part of changes designed to position the company for the 5G telecoms era, Nokia said on Thursday. Marc Rouanne, Nokia's head of mobile networks will be replaced by Tommi Uitto, a Finn described by the company as an "expert in radio technologies". Frenchman Rouanne is the second senior executive to leave Nokia within the past few weeks after the head of its patent business, Ilkka Rahnasto, resigned at the beginning of last month. Nokia plans t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Can Ericsson Make Meaningful Progress In China's 5G Market? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/27/can-ericsson-make-meaningful-progress-in-chinas-5g-market/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI2MH1hDXa8rBLH6KOAFSq0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 17:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/27/can-ericsson-make-meaningful-progress-in-chinas-5g-market/" target="_blank"&gt;Can Ericsson Make Meaningful Progress In China's 5G Market?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ericsson AB logo sits on banners as the Swedish network maker opens their 5G mobile data service and IoT center at the Corda Campus in Hasselt, Belgium. Photographer: Dario Pignatelli/Bloomberg Ericsson, one of the largest network equipment manufacturers, has been turning around its business over the last several quarters, driven by a stabilizing radio access network equipment market and aggressive cost reductions. Now, the company is counting on next-generation 5G technology to drive growth after two years of revenue declines. While 5G deployments have started in earnest in the U.S., w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New Nokia 9 Leak Reveals Powerful Feature - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/20/nokia-9-penta-five-lens-camera-leak-rumor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPFzFTjO_PqsLLYLVwNyJpgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2018/11/20/nokia-9-penta-five-lens-camera-leak-rumor/" target="_blank"&gt;New Nokia 9 Leak Reveals Powerful Feature&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More details have come to light around the presumptively named Nokia 9 from HMD Global. The focus on imaging through the use of Carl Zeiss hardware and software that uses both cameras for live streaming (the ‘bothie’ mode) is set to continue with a mammoth five-lens rear camera. Thanks to images of a Nokia 9 case published by SlashLeaks (below), we can see an orientation of seven holes, the assumption being that there are five lenses, one flash, and one autofocus sensor. The use of five lenses opens up many possibilities depending on the lenses used and how the information would combine. Ex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>O2 Partners With Nokia To Launch Massive MiMo Pilot To Boost UK 5G - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/annatobin/2018/11/25/o2-partners-with-nokia-to-launch-massive-mimo-pilot-to-boost-uk-5g/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECxjjzMgxWh-of7CgQCq5bUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 19:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/annatobin/2018/11/25/o2-partners-with-nokia-to-launch-massive-mimo-pilot-to-boost-uk-5g/" target="_blank"&gt;O2 Partners With Nokia To Launch Massive MiMo Pilot To Boost UK 5G&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Krisztian Bocsi/Bloomberg © 2015 Bloomberg Finance Telefonica-owned UK mobile operator O2 is partnering with Finnish telco Nokia to create two massive multiple-input, multiple-output, or Massive MiMo, as it’s known, trials in central London. The trials, taking place in Kings Cross and Marble Arch, are designed to improve connectivity for O2′s mobile customers and lay the groundwork for the deployment of fifth generation mobile, or 5G. The Nokia developed Massive MiMo technology will transmit multiple beams of data from one antenna to multiple devices. In doing so, it should in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Flow Festival review, Helsinki, Finland: Finds the perfect balance between local stars and international big-hitters - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/reviews/flow-festival-review-helsinki-finland-lineup-lana-del-rey-princess-nokia-skott-a7905796.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPk6_qY16R5ZhJ3sOYWSH_MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 17:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/reviews/flow-festival-review-helsinki-finland-lineup-lana-del-rey-princess-nokia-skott-a7905796.html" target="_blank"&gt;Flow Festival review, Helsinki, Finland: Finds the perfect balance between local stars and international big-hitters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the European festival scene has changed drastically over recent years, it’s instantly noticeable that Helsinki’s Flow Festival has managed to embrace the shift while also holding on to the traditions that have consistently made it stand out from a plethora of similar events. The main sponsor appears to be a Scandinavian oat milk company, for instance, while the crowd itself is distinctly Scandinavian, and at least half of the bill has been saved for emerging artists from Finland and neighbouring countries. Whether that balance, musically-speaking, quite works is somewhat by-the-by, an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: Ericsson scraps push for new clients beyond telecoms - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-ericsson-strategy-idUSKBN19I0HU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED9gmmRF6-t_6HqgCIJkX7MqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 05:32:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-ericsson-strategy-idUSKBN19I0HU" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: Ericsson scraps push for new clients beyond telecoms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Sophie Sassard and Olof Swahnberg LONDON/STOCKHOLM (Reuters) - Ericsson (ERICb.ST: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) has ditched its goal of winning more clients beyond the telecoms industry to refocus on selling networks to mobile phone companies in a move to cut costs and halt a dramatic fall in its share price. The Swedish firm's clients in its core business include Vodafone and Verizon but profits have plunged due to competition from Nokia (NOKIA.HE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) and China's Huawei [HWT.UL] and as telecoms companies make savings. Its shares have fallen 30...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Apple and Nokia see deeper partnership after ending patent dispute - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-apple-patents-idUSKBN18J0RT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHdO9I-9U1Hpl1W0pacCHOoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 17:18:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-apple-patents-idUSKBN18J0RT" target="_blank"&gt;Apple and Nokia see deeper partnership after ending patent dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jussi Rosendahl and Tuomas Forsell HELSINKI (Reuters) - Apple has settled a patent dispute with Finnish telecom equipment maker Nokia and agreed to buy more of its network products and services, sending Nokia shares up 7 percent. The deal means Nokia will get bigger royalties from Apple for using its mobile phone patents, helping offset the impact of waning demand for its mobile network hardware. Such legal battles are common in the industry but can drag on for years and analysts had not been expecting such a quick resolution to the dispute that started in December. Under the deal announ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Earnings growth could spell ‘escape velocity’ for European stocks - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a36708b6-33ce-11e7-99bd-13beb0903fa3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELajGCmGXlPEwR0rNtaOcxoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 10:28:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a36708b6-33ce-11e7-99bd-13beb0903fa3" target="_blank"&gt;Earnings growth could spell ‘escape velocity’ for European stocks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This time the markets and the opinion polls that influenced them proved right. Emmanuel Macron’s comfortable win in the French presidential election was neatly priced in during the two weeks between the first and second round of voting. As the centrist candidate celebrated on Monday, the CAC 40, which had jumped to its highest level since the financial crisis over the last two weeks, fell sharply. So what will be needed to return equities and how much of their recent gains can they hold on to? For much of the rest of the year, the fortunes of the French benchmark and its European peers will...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S8 price leak: 20 times more expensive than relaunched Nokia 3310 - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s8-price-leak-smartphone-launch-date-note-7-20-times-expensive-nokia-3310-a7620601.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENsjhrytJ64UIZESm_j5muQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/samsung-galaxy-s8-price-leak-smartphone-launch-date-note-7-20-times-expensive-nokia-3310-a7620601.html" target="_blank"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S8 price leak: 20 times more expensive than relaunched Nokia 3310&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Samsung Galaxy S8 has been subject to so many leaks over the past few months that we already have a strong idea of its capabilities and features. However, until now we haven’t had any indication of how much it could cost. UK retailer MobileFun has revealed what it believes to be the right figures for the smartphone, and the numbers are unsurprisingly lofty. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 44 show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/44 A humanoid robot gestures during a demo at a stall in the Indian Machine Tools Expo, IMTEX/Tooltech 2017 held in Bangalore Getty Images - 2/44 A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Nokia 3310 on sale today: Nostalgia is not reason enough to buy the rebooted classic - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/nokia-3310-on-sale-today-classic-reboot-mobile-cost-snake-navigation-50-a7753431.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDZZl344hJnlhtV9MUMvncqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/nokia-3310-on-sale-today-classic-reboot-mobile-cost-snake-navigation-50-a7753431.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia 3310 on sale today: Nostalgia is not reason enough to buy the rebooted classic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new Nokia 3310 is now available to buy in the UK, where it will cost you £50. The upgraded version of the 17-year-old phone caused a storm when it was announced in February, and Nokia has been riding a huge wave of nostalgia ever since. However, while it’s certainly appealing, the 3310 might not be the most sensible purchase. Here’s what you should know before buying it. Nokia 3310 - + show all Nokia 3310 - 1/13 Nokia 3310 Originally revealed 17 years ago, Nokia has resurrected the classic mobile phone - 2/13 Nokia 3310 - 3/13 Nokia 3310 - 4/13 Nokia 3310 - 5/13 Nokia 3310 - 6/13 Nokia ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: German carmakers' HERE spent 640 million euros on R&amp;D in 2016 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-here-technologies-results-exclusive/exclusive-german-carmakers-here-spent-640-million-euros-on-rd-in-2016-idUSKCN1BX15R</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOPbVreZaeyEMQfLOKKgWWwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 10:18:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-here-technologies-results-exclusive/exclusive-german-carmakers-here-spent-640-million-euros-on-rd-in-2016-idUSKCN1BX15R" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: German carmakers' HERE spent 640 million euros on R&amp;D in 2016&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Toby Sterling AMSTERDAM (Reuters) - Germany's three biggest carmakers have accelerated R&amp;D spending at HERE after their 2015 acquisition of the digital mapping company as they race to develop the navigation technology needed for self-driving cars. HERE, the biggest provider of digital maps for the automotive industry, spent 640 million euros ($767 million) on R&amp;D in 2016, or around 55 percent of the company's sales of 1.16 billion euros, according to documents reviewed by Reuters. As a subsidiary of Nokia, HERE reported 266 million euros in R&amp;D spending in the first six months of 2015 an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>SAPVoice: Why Platform, Not Pipeline, Will Save Your Business - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2017/03/04/why-platform-not-pipeline-will-save-your-business/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSjHgm52LIMzlfvojNPE44qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2017/03/04/why-platform-not-pipeline-will-save-your-business/" target="_blank"&gt;SAPVoice: Why Platform, Not Pipeline, Will Save Your Business&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapidly pacing the front of the room, voice bellowing, arms gesticulating, you’d think Erich Joachimsthaler, Founder of Vivaldi, was doing his best drill sergeant impersonation from Stanley Kubrick’s Full Metal Jacket. Alas, Mr. Joachimsthaler was nowhere near marine barracks; he kicked off a pretty great “Jam Session” called “Disrupt or Be Disrupted: Embracing Digital in B2B.” Hosted by the Institute for the Study of Business Markets and SAP Hybris, the day-long event served as a stark wake-up call to attendees that digital disruption is here and they need to act now to re-invent their bus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Ericsson: swing time - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/99a0b050-45f0-11e7-8d27-59b4dd6296b8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECuMgssWZgM8vsvRH03eOxIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 12:01:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/99a0b050-45f0-11e7-8d27-59b4dd6296b8" target="_blank"&gt;Ericsson: swing time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fifty years ago a pop band asked if listeners believed in magic. It would seem fans of Ericsson’s newish chief executive Börje Ekholm do. Shares in the Swedish telecom equipment maker have jumped 38 per cent since he was appointed. That is more than Finnish rival Nokia, but it has not stopped a new shareholder demanding more change. Mr Ekholm has promised to remove the rocks from Ericsson’s business, retaining the roll. But Cevian Capital wants to see new members on Ericsson’s board to ensure that his plan is delivered. On Tuesday evening, it revealed that it has taken a stake of over 5 per...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>New Nokia 8 Leaks Suggests Summer Start For Killer Smartphone - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2017/03/09/nokia8-leak-rumor-release-launch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI3f30rRUSNWv9fNkm7cN1cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2017/03/09/nokia8-leak-rumor-release-launch/" target="_blank"&gt;New Nokia 8 Leaks Suggests Summer Start For Killer Smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;No matter how hard Samsung tried, the big winner in the smartphone world from Mobile World Congress was the return of the Nokia name. Finland’s HMD Global introduced the Nokia 6 to the western market alongside two smaller Android handsets, as well as stealing everyone’s thunder with the relaunch of the Nokia 3310 feature phone. What was missing was a genuine specifications-breaking flagship smartphone. I’ve argued before that the right strategy for HMD is to focus on the lower end of the market where it already has successful relationships with carriers and customers (through the inherited ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Patents boost to offset weak networks for Nokia - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-results-idUSKBN1AA16D</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOuVZddoDzy_JHeubMS4hbMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 10:48:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-results-idUSKBN1AA16D" target="_blank"&gt;Patents boost to offset weak networks for Nokia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jussi Rosendahl HELSINKI (Reuters) - Telecoms gear maker Nokia is likely to see a boost to quarterly earnings on Thursday from a recent patent licensing deal with Apple that offsets weak demand in its main equipment business from network operators. However, investors have grown more nervous on the stock since loss-making Swedish rival Ericsson slashed its forecast on the global network market last week. In a Reuters poll of analysts, Nokia's networks sales are seen falling 3 percent in the second quarter from a year ago, while revenues from its technologies unit, including patent royalti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nokia 8 hopes to beat Apple and Samsung with 'bothie', a new version of the selfie - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/aug/16/nokia-8-bothie-flagship-android-smartphone-apple-samsung</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN2Y_WfIVrVTf2tzkcaBwoIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 18:45:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/aug/16/nokia-8-bothie-flagship-android-smartphone-apple-samsung" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia 8 hopes to beat Apple and Samsung with 'bothie', a new version of the selfie&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nokia has launched the most important new handset in its attempts to revitalise the once world-beating brand for the modern smartphone era dominated by Samsung, Apple and China’s Huawei. The Nokia 8 marks the culmination of efforts to bring the Finnish telecoms brand back to the mainstream handset market, which kicked off six months ago with the nostalgia-inducing remake of the classic Nokia 3310 feature phone. Related: Nokia 3310 review: blast from the past, sore thumbs and all The Android flagship smartphone, designed to compete with the likes of the iPhone 7 and Samsung’s Galaxy S8, feat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Ericsson could shed 25,000 jobs in cost-cutting drive: report - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ericsson-layoffs-idUSKCN1AX0QS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEITBAgzhTJaRb5Pp5VUERccqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 07:54:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ericsson-layoffs-idUSKCN1AX0QS" target="_blank"&gt;Ericsson could shed 25,000 jobs in cost-cutting drive: report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;STOCKHOLM (Reuters) - Mobile telecom gear maker Ericsson may lay off around 25,000 employees outside Sweden as part of its savings program, Swedish daily Svenska Dagbladet reported on Thursday, citing unidentified sources at the company. Ericsson said in July it would accelerate measures to meet a target of doubling its 2016 underlying operating margin of 6 percent and that it aimed to reach an annual cost reduction run rate of at least 10 billion crowns ($1.2 billion) by mid-2018. Ericsson has said actions will be taken primarily in service delivery and common costs while research and deve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Apple and Nokia settle patent dispute and sign new deal - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/apple-nokia-patent-dispute-new-deal-phone-mobile-tech-a7750916.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM_UVhbQmZbgLxqnq_UaTmAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 10:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/apple-nokia-patent-dispute-new-deal-phone-mobile-tech-a7750916.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apple and Nokia settle patent dispute and sign new deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nokia has settled its legal battle with Apple with a new patent licence agreement and also signed a business deal with the US giant, surprising investors who had expected the dispute to drag on. The companies said on Tuesday that Nokia would receive an upfront cash payment and additional revenues from Apple starting from the current quarter, without giving details. Analysts said the revenue was likely to be far higher than a previous deal. Nokia shares, which fell in December when the patent dispute was announced, jumped as much as 8 per cent to their highest since February 2016 and were 6....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Nokia cuts 170 jobs in Finland - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-redundancies-idUSKBN1901OS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH5DHxdT6NJV8dp9TWIbYB0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 12:00:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-redundancies-idUSKBN1901OS" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia cuts 170 jobs in Finland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HELSINKI (Reuters) - Telecom network equipment maker Nokia (NOKIA.HE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) has completed lay-off talks in its home country Finland and will as a result cut 170 jobs, the company said on Friday. Announcing the talks in May, the company said it was preparing to cut up to 200 jobs from network operations and support functions. Nokia, which currently has 6,100 employees in Finland and around 101,000 globally, cut 960 jobs in its home market last year and also said it would do away with 1,400 positions in Germany. The reductions are part of a 1.2 billion euro ($1...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>At The Car Wash - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/221775649/at-the-car-wash-by-imagingpixel</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEJd50eDzSQq2q41dqOx7S4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 12:19:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/221775649/at-the-car-wash-by-imagingpixel" target="_blank"&gt;At The Car Wash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scene at the car wash with the Lumia 720&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Apple and Nokia settle patent dispute - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/05/23/apple-nokia-settle-patent-dispute/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP3Q-Vj7kCc8hIgC1KzopLEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 13:34:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/05/23/apple-nokia-settle-patent-dispute/" target="_blank"&gt;Apple and Nokia settle patent dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple and Nokia have reached a deal after a testy legal dispute over the Finnish company’s patents. The two sides announced the agreement in a joint statement yesterday, five months after they had sued each other over royalty payments. The deal will see Apple make a sizeable one-off payment, as well as future fees, for the use of Nokia’s technology. Analysts estimated the deal was worth hundreds of millions of pounds to Nokia, sending shares up by 7pc. From Nokia to MySpace: The worst tech deals of all time The company suffered immensely at the hands of the iPhone, and no longer makes hands...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Nokia's French jobs cut plan suspended until October 2: French minister - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-france-jobs/nokias-french-jobs-cut-plan-suspended-until-october-2-french-minister-idUSKCN1BU1H6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED7sfKZyl4O_B3SJ7glANmYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 11:42:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-france-jobs/nokias-french-jobs-cut-plan-suspended-until-october-2-french-minister-idUSKCN1BU1H6" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia's French jobs cut plan suspended until October 2: French minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARIS (Reuters) - Nokia's (NOKIA.HE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) plan to cut almost 600 jobs in France is suspended until Oct. 2, French junior economy minister Benjamin Griveaux said on Tuesday after meeting the head of the Finnish telecom equipment maker's French unit. Griveaux will meet with unions and company management on Oct. 2 to check whether Nokia is following on an earlier pledge to increase research and development (R&amp;D) jobs in France. "At this stage, the jobs cut plan is suspended ... at least until this meeting that I will chair on Oct. 2 at the finance ministry," Gr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nokia 5 review: A great-looking Android smartphone that's tantalisingly cheap - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/nokia-5-review-cheap-android-smartphone-price-features-camera-looks-screen-memory-graphics-a7858666.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZlcKy3YwpD0SS-dAZy9gkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 09:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/nokia-5-review-cheap-android-smartphone-price-features-camera-looks-screen-memory-graphics-a7858666.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia 5 review: A great-looking Android smartphone that's tantalisingly cheap&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nokia’s first Android smartphones are on their way. The entry-level model, the Nokia 3, is on sale now for £119.99. The next step-up is the Nokia 5, which goes on sale on 16 August. The Nokia 6 is the highest-specced of the three first handsets and is on sale on 2 August for £219.99. I saw all three back in February and for me, the Nokia 5, at £179.99, is the most interesting. I’ve been trying it out for the last two weeks. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/43 Designed by Pierpaolo Lazzarini from Italian company Jet Capsule. The I.F.O. is f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Telecoms groups outperform growth expectations - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/25421054-72bf-11e7-93ff-99f383b09ff9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJhZIcSHQVqBisRkJIu5JMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 15:20:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/25421054-72bf-11e7-93ff-99f383b09ff9" target="_blank"&gt;Telecoms groups outperform growth expectations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The global telecoms sector started to turn a corner in the second quarter as Telefónica, Orange and Verizon, some of the industry’s biggest hitters, all outperformed growth expectations. The sense of recovery was underlined by results from two of the largest telecoms equipment makers, with Huawei reporting a 15 per cent rise in sales in the first half while Nokia pointed to a “deeper, longer” cycle of investment for 5G networks. Orange, the French telecoms company, reported its best growth in a decade. While it recorded only a 0.5 per cent rise in revenue in France, it was the first time it...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Nokia 8 hands-on review: A great-looking phone that wants to reinvent the selfie - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/nokia-8-review-hands-on-features-camera-battery-screen-cost-selfies-compared-a7896961.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECsWo-uaej0tiazxJTyJ-DkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 08:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/nokia-8-review-hands-on-features-camera-battery-screen-cost-selfies-compared-a7896961.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia 8 hands-on review: A great-looking phone that wants to reinvent the selfie&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since its return on handsets made by HMD Global, the Nokia name has appeared on three middle-tier smartphones. There’s now a top-of-range phone to go with them. The new handset, launched at Tower Bridge in London, is called the Nokia 8. It marks the first collaboration between Nokia and optical masters Zeiss in Nokia’s new life, and is the company’s first two-lens phone. Design The design is closer to the Nokia 5, with its smoothly curved edges, than the blockier Nokia 6, and it certainly feels more comfortable in the hand as a result. In feel alone, this is easily the best phone the new HM...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Continental still interested in mapping firm HERE: CEO - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-autoshow-frankfurt-continental/continental-still-interested-in-mapping-firm-here-ceo-idUSKCN1BN253</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGX1xaZyMpnBJhr7by8EFigqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 15:45:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-autoshow-frankfurt-continental/continental-still-interested-in-mapping-firm-here-ceo-idUSKCN1BN253" target="_blank"&gt;Continental still interested in mapping firm HERE: CEO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FRANKFURT (Reuters) - German automotive supplier Continental (CONG.DE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) is still interested in working with digital mapping firm HERE, Chief Executive Elmar Degenhart said on Tuesday. "We are still in talks and haven't lost our optimism that we will strike a deal sometime in the future," he told Reuters at the Frankfurt auto show. Germany's Manager Magazin in July cited sources as saying that Continental was in talks to acquire an 8 to 10 percent stake in HERE. Carmakers BMW (BMWG.DE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), Daimler (DAIGn.DE: Quote, Profi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Withings is now Nokia: The future of health tech is in safe hands - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/nokia-health-wearable-tech-withings-partnership-features-devices-a7801171.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPFd6sG9mg2sLVGA7-w6cfUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDY0Y8D</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/nokia-health-wearable-tech-withings-partnership-features-devices-a7801171.html" target="_blank"&gt;Withings is now Nokia: The future of health tech is in safe hands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are few names in the world of tech more trusted than Nokia. Many of us grew up with the brand as the go-to company for the easiest-to-use, most reliable, best-designed mobile phones. And French company Withings in recent years has built a fearsome reputation for brilliant home appliances that had wireless connectivity before other companies even got into the smart home game. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - + show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/43 Designed by Pierpaolo Lazzarini from Italian company Jet Capsule. The I.F.O. is fuelled by eight electric engines, which is a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>New Nokia 8 phone targets surging demand for video-streaming - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-phones-idUSKCN1AW2EL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPNjxbQ36Fcc686VhwaH-dIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 18:48:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-phones-idUSKCN1AW2EL" target="_blank"&gt;New Nokia 8 phone targets surging demand for video-streaming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HELSINKI (Reuters) - HMD Global, the Finnish start-up looking to reinvigorate the Nokia phone brand, unveiled the Nokia 8 on Wednesday, hoping to cash in on rising consumer demand for high-quality audio and video features. The Android device, due out in September, will potentially beat rivals on price but will still face fierce competition, with Apple's highly anticipated 10th anniversary iPhone also expected next month and Samsung's Galaxy Note 8 set to hit the market next week. With a suggested price tag of around 599 euros ($703), the Nokia 8 undercuts Apple, which typically offers a str...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>From Colgate Lasagne to Crystal Pepsi: visit the Museum of Failure - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/shortcuts/2017/apr/19/museum-failure-samuel-west-sweden</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIE_W3Sw1x2W4iI3FWFAckIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 15:06:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/shortcuts/2017/apr/19/museum-failure-samuel-west-sweden" target="_blank"&gt;From Colgate Lasagne to Crystal Pepsi: visit the Museum of Failure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ah, nostalgia. Remember back when we were all listening to our Zunes, drinking a Crystal Pepsi munching a McDonald’s Arch Deluxe, smoking our RJ Reynolds Premier, and playing a series of deeply inadequate games on the Apple Pippin? Of course not. These are products that swan-dived from the highest board; failures so legendary they have their own appendix in business-school textbooks. They’re proof that even with a multi-million dollar marketing budget, you still can’t buy someone who’ll see that the emperor’s new soft drink tastes like cat piss. Now, a new museum in Helsingborg, Sweden, is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Huawei overtakes Apple as world's second-biggest smartphone maker - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/09/07/huawei-overtakes-apple-worlds-second-biggest-smartphone-maker/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDx91x1WFuqH5EdRSW__PDQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 12:12:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/09/07/huawei-overtakes-apple-worlds-second-biggest-smartphone-maker/" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei overtakes Apple as world's second-biggest smartphone maker&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple has been overtaken by the Chinese smartphone giant Huawei as the world’s second-biggest smartphone maker by sales, sending the iPhone maker into third place for the first time since Blackberry and Nokia ruled the market. Huawei’s market share surpassed Apple’s in June and July, according to figures from Counterpoint Research. While the dip is likely to be temporary, with Apple announcement of a new range of iPhones next week likely to invigorate sales, breaking the duopoly enjoyed by Samsung and Apple that has existed for five years is a landmark moment. Apple has held one of the top ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Retro tech making a comeback: in pictures - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2016/03/01/retro-tech-making-a-comeback-in-pictures/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDa5_Ii3TGhy6jobs2T4encqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 06:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2016/03/01/retro-tech-making-a-comeback-in-pictures/" target="_blank"&gt;Retro tech making a comeback: in pictures&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;21 Apr 2017 Retro tech making a comeback: in pictures Previous slideNext slide1 of 12View AllSkip Ad 2017 is the year it was announced that Nokia would bring back the historic 3310. First released in 2000, the 3310 is beloved for a days-long battery life, ability to withstand great falls and the classic game Snake. A £50 homage to the nostalgia-inducing phone is expected later this month. Nokia Back to image&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Nokia And BlackBerry Look Like Winners, As Apple's Buzz Cools Off - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/10/04/nokia-and-blackberry-look-like-winners-as-apples-buzz-cools-off/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHo82B_szMRDGBXyHFjuAgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 19:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/10/04/nokia-and-blackberry-look-like-winners-as-apples-buzz-cools-off/" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia And BlackBerry Look Like Winners, As Apple's Buzz Cools Off&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: David Paul Morris/Bloomberg Nokia and BlackBerry are beginning to look like winners on Wall Street, as Apple’s buzz cools off. In the last six months, Nokia’s stock gained 12.20 percent, BlackBerry gained 43.33 percent, while Apple gained only 7.25 percent, underperforming Nasdaq, which was up 10.20 percent. Still, Nokia’s and BlackBerry’s stocks are trading well below their highs back in the old days, before iPhone stole the buzz from them. And their comeback is less a matter of new buzz for the two companies than it is bargain hunting among investors and romantic fans who se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Nokia 3310: Everything you need to know about the most hyped comeback of 2017 - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/nokia-3310-price-release-date-battery-life-snake-features-latest-news-explained-a7616041.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDRCiO7wGVIooO731EQ5p4gqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/features/nokia-3310-price-release-date-battery-life-snake-features-latest-news-explained-a7616041.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia 3310: Everything you need to know about the most hyped comeback of 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nokia 3310 is back, and it’s better than ever. It may only be a feature phone, but the throwback handset has already eclipsed a number of brand new flagship smartphones that will be around ten times more expensive than it, including the Huawei P10, LG G6 and Sony Xperia XZ Premium. The astonishingly popular mobile stays true to the 17-year-old original’s roots, but squeezes in enough new features and improvements to make it a genuinely worthwhile purchase, as well as a nostalgia-fuelled impulse buy. Here’s everything you need to know about the new Nokia 3310 ahead of its release. Nostal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Fast Europe Open: Spain unemployment, Turkey rates decision - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ba740c6c-e5c8-324a-94d9-a96d34245b60</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPaQVxana1jzLPUlZyxynoAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 05:11:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ba740c6c-e5c8-324a-94d9-a96d34245b60" target="_blank"&gt;Fast Europe Open: Spain unemployment, Turkey rates decision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amber Rudd, the UK home secretary has promised British businesses she will not close the door on European workers after Brexit and promised there will be no “cliff edge” when the UK leaves the bloc. Writing in the Financial Times, Ms Rudd showed a significant softening in the government tone on EU immigration as she promised “immigration rules and requirements that will meet the need of UK businesses, but also of wider society.” Ms Rudd said she will ask the independent Migration Advisory committee to carry out an assessment of the relationship between migration from the EU and European Eco...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Vertu manufacturing arm faces liquidation after rescue bid fails - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/07/11/vertu-manufacturing-arm-faces-liquidation-rescue-bid-fails/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBk2IF5aZ6fAUa5P4XQkvNUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 17:31:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/07/11/vertu-manufacturing-arm-faces-liquidation-rescue-bid-fails/" target="_blank"&gt;Vertu manufacturing arm faces liquidation after rescue bid fails&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The manufacturing arm of the British luxury smartphone maker Vertu will be liquidated with the loss of nearly 200 jobs after a rescue plan failed. Vertu Corporation Limited (VCL) made handsets for the super-rich, with handsets clad in titanium and sapphire glass starting at around £10,000 and going up to as much as £280,000 for bespoke, jewel-encrusted devices. Its owner Murat Hakan Uzan, a Turkish exile based in Paris who owns the Vertu brand separately, had sought to buy the company out of administration in a pre-packaged deal. The plan floundered in the High Court today amid concerns ove...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Nokia says to get sales boost after patent ruling - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-patents-lg-elec/nokia-says-to-get-sales-boost-after-patent-ruling-idUSKCN1BT0NT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0TTt9EMLxJb_gMdOf-s-8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 08:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-patents-lg-elec/nokia-says-to-get-sales-boost-after-patent-ruling-idUSKCN1BT0NT" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia says to get sales boost after patent ruling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HELSINKI (Reuters) - Nokia (NOKIA.HE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) will start to book additional revenue from the current quarter after a ruling by an arbitration court on payments from South Korea's LG Electronics (066570.KS: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) for using its smartphone patents. The Finnish company said it would also get a one-off payment, although it did not disclose any of the sums involved. The companies had started the arbitration in 2015. "We believe that this award confirms the quality of Nokia's patent portfolio. We continue to see potential for additional...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Weird Nokia phones you'll wish you owned - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2016/03/02/weird-nokia-phones-youll-wish-you-owned/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKccq8PnHJpmB4slNYAyLY4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 08:30:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2016/03/02/weird-nokia-phones-youll-wish-you-owned/" target="_blank"&gt;Weird Nokia phones you'll wish you owned&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;02 Aug 2017 Weird Nokia phones you'll wish you owned Previous slideNext slide1 of 17View AllSkip Ad Nokia is known for having some out there phone designs. Ahead of the new generation of Nokia feature phones, we take a look at some of the weirdest phones they released. Back to image&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Nokia profits surge after Apple deal and network gains - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/nokia-results-idUSL5N1KI0ZQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOTbOCfs0MJiiLRs1HMDwZ4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 09:24:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/nokia-results-idUSL5N1KI0ZQ" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia profits surge after Apple deal and network gains&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jussi Rosendahl HELSINKI (Reuters) - Network equipment maker Nokia reported a jump in profit on Thursday thanks to a patent deal with Apple and gains in market share though it warned the network business could slow by more than expected this year. Nokia's shares rose 5.5 percent by 0820 GMT after it posted second-quarter operating profit of 574 million euros ($674 million), up 73 percent from a year ago and well above analysts' average forecast of 447 million euros in a Reuters poll. "We are actually taking some share in the market ... early signs look quite promising in terms of market ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nokia 3310 relaunched with 3G internet for first time - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/09/28/nokia-3310-relaunched-3g-internet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFAvZMSLe2B1k4cRNj_qRmEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 09:41:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/09/28/nokia-3310-relaunched-3g-internet/" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia 3310 relaunched with 3G internet for first time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The relaunched Nokia 3310 is to gain 3G connectivity for the first time, bringing enhanced network coverage to the retro phone. Manufacturers HMD will also add two new colours, azure and charcoal, and improve customisation options so users can edit their home screen and icons. The 3G version will launch in the UK in October. The current version costs £49 and HMD have not confirmed the UK price for the upgraded model. Nokia 3310 vs iPhone 7 The 3310 was launched in the UK in May, 17 years after the iconic original was released. The upgrade adds improved connectivity, with the first version o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Nokia plans to sell its undersea cables division: sources - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-underseacables-idUSKBN17Z22U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFl3a8EP5iTJQvwzBYch-rkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 15:07:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-underseacables-idUSKBN17Z22U" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia plans to sell its undersea cables division: sources&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Corrects last paragraph of this May 3 story to show TE Connectivity is a U.S.-listed Swiss company, not a U.S. company.) By Gwénaëlle Barzic and Mathieu Rosemain PARIS (Reuters) - Finland's Nokia plans to sell its undersea cables unit, a business that underpins the global Internet, two union sources and a French government source told Reuters. The division, valued at about 800 million euros ($870 million), is one of the top suppliers of undersea cable networks in the world and was bought by the telecom equipment maker last year as part its 15.6 billion euro ($17 billion) acquisition of Fre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nokia outpaces Ericsson in first quarter as network market recovers - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-results-idUSKBN17T0LU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBNTaConXUxg6a6MdAGKm0cqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 08:02:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-results-idUSKBN17T0LU" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia outpaces Ericsson in first quarter as network market recovers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jussi Rosendahl and Tuomas Forsell HELSINKI (Reuters) - Finnish telecom networks equipment maker Nokia reported a slowing rate of sales decline on Thursday, saying the global networks market was showing signs of recovery, particularly in North America and India. Nokia outpaced its troubled Swedish rival Ericsson in the quarter and analysts said the Finnish company was better positioned to win future business, thanks to its recent acquisition of Franco-American rival Alcatel-Lucent. Network gear vendors have struggled in recent years as telecom operators' demand for faster 4G mobile broad...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nokia 8 best features: What is a 'both-ie' and does it have Snake? - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/08/16/nokia-8-best-features-both-ie-does-have-snake/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIHx341gcEGWl78Tcqfgs-UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 18:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2017/08/16/nokia-8-best-features-both-ie-does-have-snake/" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia 8 best features: What is a 'both-ie' and does it have Snake?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HMD Global has unveiled its first flagship Nokia handset, putting the iconic brand back on the high-end market after a three year hiatus. The Nokia 8 is the first high-spec handset from HMD Global, the eight month old company that has a 10-year licensing deal to manufacture phones with the Finnish brand. Its launch marks the return of Nokia, the once dominant phone company that was pushed out by the likes of Apple and Samsung. The new phone is the first smartphone that can simultaneously livestream a selfie while also using its main camera, called a "both-ie". It also has a dual lens camera...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>No space is safe when even our TVs are spies - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/mar/12/no-channel-is-safe-tvs-are-spies-samsung-cia-wikileaks-nokia-3310-stewart-lee</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtY_kpd4dStoBdZ4wsPCigqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 09:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/mar/12/no-channel-is-safe-tvs-are-spies-samsung-cia-wikileaks-nokia-3310-stewart-lee" target="_blank"&gt;No space is safe when even our TVs are spies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I only got a “smart” television set 18 months ago, so I have already avoided years of covert surveillance by the CIA, the FBI, MI5, CI5 and NWA. No one is safe from Samsung’s all-seeing Eye of Sauron. Apparently, a deeply embedded program currently enables the intelligence agencies to note and monitor anyone who is watching ITV’s The Nightly Show, in the belief that they must be a weird loner-misfit, inexplicably fascinated by human suffering, a ticking social time bomb just waiting to explode. I am a late adopter of new technology. If I had played the ape at the opening of 2001: A Space Od...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Tired of the FANG gang? These 2 tech stocks look like they’re in the same class - MarketWatch</title><link>http://www.marketwatch.com/story/tired-of-the-fang-gang-these-2-tech-stocks-look-like-theyre-in-the-same-class-2017-09-11</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJEc-lFv-ReyEJ-uGpmPofMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 11:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.marketwatch.com/story/tired-of-the-fang-gang-these-2-tech-stocks-look-like-theyre-in-the-same-class-2017-09-11" target="_blank"&gt;Tired of the FANG gang? These 2 tech stocks look like they’re in the same class&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Victor Reklaitis ASML Holding and SAP are leaders with room to run, says fund manager who also advises avoiding Nokia and Ericsson Many investors don’t want to focus on the tech industry’s usual suspects. Getty Images A frequent complaint is that the runup by the FANG stocks appears overdone. Whether that’s true or not, investors still want to hold big tech names showing solid growth. As a result, there are all sorts of efforts to identify such companies, while steering clear of the usual U.S. suspects — Facebook (FB) , Amazon.com (AMZN) , Netflix (NFLX) and Google parent Alphabet (GO...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Sweden's Ericsson faces painful overhaul as it plunges into loss - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-ericsson-results-idUSKBN17R0J4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF5y1E4Z3AtDQgMhIxWjMPQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 12:13:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-ericsson-results-idUSKBN17R0J4" target="_blank"&gt;Sweden's Ericsson faces painful overhaul as it plunges into loss&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Sophie Sassard and Helena Soderpalm LONDON/STOCKHOLM (Reuters) - Mobile telecom equipment maker Ericsson faces a long and painful overhaul after shrinking markets, tough competition and restructuring costs pushed it to a quarterly operating loss on Tuesday. The Swedish company, which is seeking to reposition the business for growth under new chief executive Borje Ekholm, reported an operating loss of 12.3 billion Swedish crowns ($1.4 billion) as previously announced provisions, writedowns and restructuring costs pushed it deep into the red. That compared with a 3.5 billion crown profit i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Nokia 9 Leak Points To 2017's Killer Smartphone - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2017/04/03/nokia9-leak-rumor-specifications-flagship/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOLjqeWH71NSaZwFRrrXj74qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 18:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2017/04/03/nokia9-leak-rumor-specifications-flagship/" target="_blank"&gt;New Nokia 9 Leak Points To 2017's Killer Smartphone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As 2017 started, the Nokia name returned to the smartphone world thanks to HMD. The Finnish-based start-up started with a Chinese mid-range Android handset (the Nokia 6), before introducing this smartphone and two others at MWC (namely the Nokia 5 and the Nokia 3). Details are now coming out of a top of the line handset that could be on sale by the end of the year. HMD’s Nokia 6 (photo: Ewan Spence) Christened the Nokia 9 by Nokia Power User, the report highlights specifications that match the likes of the LG G6, the Huawei P10 and the Samsung Galaxy S8. The rumored specs include an OLED-ba...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Ex-Dividend Reminder: Nokia, NetEase and FLIR Systems - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/dividendchannel/2017/05/22/ex-dividend-reminder-nokia-netease-and-flir-systems/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChl_sUljZGlrNtHTyx0Oo0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 14:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/dividendchannel/2017/05/22/ex-dividend-reminder-nokia-netease-and-flir-systems/" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-Dividend Reminder: Nokia, NetEase and FLIR Systems&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the universe of stocks we cover at Dividend Channel, on 5/24/17, Nokia Corp (NYSE: NOK), NetEase, Inc (NASD: NTES), and FLIR Systems, Inc. (NASD: FLIR) will all trade ex-dividend for their respective upcoming dividends. Nokia Corp will pay its annual dividend of $0.1816 on 6/14/17, NetEase, Inc will pay its quarterly dividend of $1.08 on 6/2/17, and FLIR Systems, Inc. will pay its quarterly dividend of $0.15 on 6/9/17. Click here to learn which 25 S.A.F.E. dividend stocks should be on your radar screen, at DividendChannel.com » As a percentage of NOK’s recent stock price of $6.21...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Nokia and Apple settle patent dispute and sign new licensing deal - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/37c4a1ee-3f9b-11e7-82b6-896b95f30f58</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENe5IxzLVb5mrFlQV8xgXyQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 12:06:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/37c4a1ee-3f9b-11e7-82b6-896b95f30f58" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia and Apple settle patent dispute and sign new licensing deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nokia and Apple have surprised analysts by settling a patent dispute, after the iPhone maker agreed to make an upfront cash payment to the Finnish company and sign a new licensing pact. The battle was expected to run for years with analysts predicting no agreement would be signed until at least the end of 2018. The two companies sued each other in December after a longstanding patent deal signed in 2011 lapsed. But on Tuesday the companies resolved their differences, with the Finnish business also securing an agreement to sell its digital health products in Apple’s online and retail stores....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Nokia warns on challenging telecom market conditions - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/c4108e52-0b83-3741-9e35-0259dfae8976</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA_oBGEw6cS9kMbk-n6OAMoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 06:43:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/c4108e52-0b83-3741-9e35-0259dfae8976" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia warns on challenging telecom market conditions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nokia has warned of a deterioration in the market for telecoms equipment this year in the wake of rival Ericsson’s shock warning last week. The Finnish company however issued a milder view of the market for its kit than Ericsson saying that it expects 2017 to be “slightly more challenging” than it had previously forecast. Ericsson warned that it expected the radio access network market to slump by a “high single digit” percentage but Nokia proved optimistic. Rajeev Suri, chief executive of Nokia, said: We expect our primary addressable market with communication service providers to be sligh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Turkish exile snaps up smartphone maker Vertu for £50m - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/03/12/turkish-exile-snaps-smartphone-maker-vertu-50m/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEInZhIzWDuB5HGV_YJwB9z4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2017/03/12/turkish-exile-snaps-smartphone-maker-vertu-50m/" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish exile snaps up smartphone maker Vertu for £50m&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scion of an exiled and secretive Turkish business dynasty has bought the British smartphone maker Vertu, which targets the wealthy buyers with handsets costing up to £40,000. The Daily Telegraph can reveal that Baferton Ltd, a Cyprus-registered vehicle funded by Hakan Uzan, has paid around £50m to acquire the Hampshire manufacturer from its Chinese owners Godin Holdings. Mr Uzan is part of one of Turkey’s most controversial families and was once found in contempt of court in Britain. He has tangled in court with the current President of the United States and Nokia, the mobile giant that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>U.S. awards AT&amp;T contract to build wireless network for first responders - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-firstnet-at-t-contract-idUSKBN171209</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENs_YrRdgHQh38e4RAxrjzIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 15:00:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-firstnet-at-t-contract-idUSKBN171209" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. awards AT&amp;T contract to build wireless network for first responders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Reuters) - The United States on Thursday awarded a contract to AT&amp;T Inc to build a nationwide wireless broadband network to better equip first responders, years after a federal commission recommended setting up such a system following the 9/11 attacks. FirstNet, an independent arm of the Department of Commerce, will provide No. 2 U.S. wireless carrier AT&amp;T with telecom spectrum and success-based payments of $6.5 billion over the next five years. The effort to set up a public safety network was triggered by communications failures during the Sept. 11, 2001 attacks, when first responders wer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nokia targets gains from web giants with fastest routers - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-routers-idUSKBN1952FG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDVX8rQRk58zXbVsK4V85AIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 19:41:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-routers-idUSKBN1952FG" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia targets gains from web giants with fastest routers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Eric Auchard SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Nokia (NOKIA.HE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) launched the world's fastest network chips on Wednesday, breaking into the Juniper (JNPR.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) and Cisco (CSCO.O: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) dominated core router market and giving its existing network business a boost. The new traffic routers can handle the greater demands of virtual reality programming, cloud-based internet services and next-generation mobile communications, the Finnish company said. Nokia's new products, which grew out of its 15.6...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Android Circuit: Galaxy S8 Launch Delayed, Nokia 8 Flagship Leaks, Google Pixel's Serious Problems - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2017/03/10/android-google-news-samsung-galaxy-s8-delay-leak-rumor-nokia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG7GBsR012Y191rm019Jy6MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 23:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/ewanspence/2017/03/10/android-google-news-samsung-galaxy-s8-delay-leak-rumor-nokia/" target="_blank"&gt;Android Circuit: Galaxy S8 Launch Delayed, Nokia 8 Flagship Leaks, Google Pixel's Serious Problems&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look back at seven days of news and headlines across the world of Android, this week’s Android Circuit includes a delay for the Galaxy S8, new leaked images showing the S8’s mystery button, Google’s pricey Pixel 2, a serious problem for the Pixel, Nokia’s new flagship, South Korea’s love for the LG G6, a review of the Huawei P10, and is MWC about mobile anymore? Android Circuit is here to remind you of a few of the many things that have happened around Android in the last week (and you can find the weekly Apple news digest here). Galaxy S8’s New Street Date One of the biggest Andro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>The Eye Of The 5G Innovation Hurricane Is In The Last Place You'd Expect - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonbloomberg/2017/06/16/the-eye-of-the-5g-innovation-hurricane-is-in-the-last-place-youd-expect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOQs1BIs96Y-fWTcNTw9LF4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 10:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonbloomberg/2017/06/16/the-eye-of-the-5g-innovation-hurricane-is-in-the-last-place-youd-expect/" target="_blank"&gt;The Eye Of The 5G Innovation Hurricane Is In The Last Place You'd Expect&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;5G – the fifth-generation mobile networks standards – promises to disrupt both enterprises and the telecommunications world, as it will enable blisteringly fast communications among people and devices with virtually no latency. Given the broad significance of 5G, the last place you’d expect the center of global 5G innovation to be is Oulu, a city of 200,000 people near the Arctic Circle in Northern Finland. How Oulu became the ‘Silicon Valley’ of 5G innovation is a remarkable story, as any Silicon Valley wannabe requires three essential elements: talent, money, and an ecosystem of vendors a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Nokia's mobile networks head quits, to split business - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-corp-reorganisation-idUSKBN16O1D2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIMl5k-Lho3CPkkxdSWpfmcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 11:26:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-corp-reorganisation-idUSKBN16O1D2" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia's mobile networks head quits, to split business&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HELSINKI (Reuters) - Nokia's (NOKIA.HE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) head of mobile networks, the division which accounted for more than half of Finnish telecom network equipment maker's sales last year, is leaving the company. Nokia said on Friday it would break out services as a distinct business group from mobile networks following the departure of Samih Elhage, who joined the company in 2012 and helped to turn around its network business at a time when it was a troubled joint venture with Siemens (SIEGn.DE: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz). Services were growing in importa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Museum Of Failure Dishes On The Worst Products Of All Time - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/eustaciahuen/2017/04/30/the-museum-of-failure-dishes-on-the-worst-products-of-all-time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDVCBwvCW-fZX8WIyAUndb0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 01:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/eustaciahuen/2017/04/30/the-museum-of-failure-dishes-on-the-worst-products-of-all-time/" target="_blank"&gt;The Museum Of Failure Dishes On The Worst Products Of All Time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proving that literally anything could be a theme for a museum nowadays, there will be a museum opening in downtown Helsingborg, Sweden on June 7 dedicated entirely to failure. More specifically, ”The kind [of products] that were intentionally developed for innovation sake, yet failed to gain commercial success,” said Dr. Samuel West, Organizational Psychologist and founder of the Museum of Failure. As someone who’s tired of the inundation of success stories within business media, West has always been more fascinated by the insight from failure than the glorification of success. Made of rigi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Nokia, China's Xiaomi sign patent deal - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-xiaomi-patents-idUSKBN19Q0G9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKIiv86A6Gr0rJ-UADhq8FcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 07:03:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-xiaomi-patents-idUSKBN19Q0G9" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia, China's Xiaomi sign patent deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HELSINKI (Reuters) - Telecoms network equipment maker Nokia and Chinese smartphone maker Xiaomi Technology have signed a patent licensing agreement, the companies said on Wednesday. The companies did not provide financial details of the agreement, saying it includes a cross license to each company's cellular standard patents. Nokia will also provide network infrastructure equipment to Xiaomi. "Xiaomi is one of the world's leading smartphone manufacturers and we are delighted to have reached an agreement with them," Nokia Chief Executive Rajeev Suri said in a statement. Nokia has license dea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nokia says could cut 597 jobs in France by end-2019 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-france-jobs/nokia-says-could-cut-597-jobs-in-france-by-end-2019-idUSKCN1BH2LZ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKcB8CXf-P6M223-rbmvcogqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 18:13:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-france-jobs/nokia-says-could-cut-597-jobs-in-france-by-end-2019-idUSKCN1BH2LZ" target="_blank"&gt;Nokia says could cut 597 jobs in France by end-2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARIS (Reuters) - Finnish telecom equipment maker Nokia said on Wednesday it could cut 597 jobs in France by end-2019 as part of a plan to save 1.2 billion euros at group level. The job cuts would concern central and support functions within Alcatel-Lucent International and Nokia Solutions Networks France, which employ a combined 4,200 people in the country, a Nokia spokeswoman told Reuters in an e-mail. R&amp;D functions were excluded from the plan and Nokia, which bought former rival Alcatel-Lucent in 2016, will seek to limit as much a possible forced redundancies, she said. The CFDT, CFE-CGC...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>French president says Nokia job cut plan breaks commitment - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-france-jobs-macron/french-president-says-nokia-job-cut-plan-breaks-commitment-idUSKCN1BX2KL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ24LMINCjeloONCqgmORVUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 18:10:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nokia-france-jobs-macron/french-president-says-nokia-job-cut-plan-breaks-commitment-idUSKCN1BX2KL" target="_blank"&gt;French president says Nokia job cut plan breaks commitment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARIS (Reuters) - French President Emmanuel Macron said on Friday a decision by Finnish telecom equipment maker Nokia to cut about 600 jobs in France did not comply with commitments the firm made when it bought rival Alcatel-Lucent in 2016. "Nokia was aided by the French government and it made clear commitments," Macron said during a joint briefing following a visit by Finnish Prime Minister Juha Sipila. He added Nokia's only option was to respect its commitments and he would be "inflexible" towards the firm. Macron, then economy minister, gave his blessing for the takeover of Alcatel by No...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Barriers To Growth: Inability To Go Backwards - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alastairdryburgh/2017/03/25/barriers-to-growth-inability-to-go-backwards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDHB5ZC0IH3ox6fEGi8QqLoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 08:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alastairdryburgh/2017/03/25/barriers-to-growth-inability-to-go-backwards/" target="_blank"&gt;Barriers To Growth: Inability To Go Backwards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest barriers I see to growth, whether it is personal growth or business growth, is not inability to move forward, but the inability to go backwards. The reason for this paradox is very simple. Progress isn’t linear. You can’t move forward in a smooth upward curve; sometimes you need to go backwards before you can go forwards. Take some examples. First example; the manager or leader who can’t delegate. We have all seen this, the leader who has become the biggest bottleneck in their organisation. Nothing can happen without their say-so. The staff are frustrated, the leader is b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item></channel></rss>