<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Cardi B - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZrZUd3d2F6QnJNaElDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-BW&amp;gl=BW&amp;ceid=BW:en</link><language>en-BW</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:05:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Judge: Cardi B must not contact strip club melee victims - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/1260d3e0608b40479411dec8a4655e52</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEFIck5Pw5EfgCBRfyVNTb4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:42:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/1260d3e0608b40479411dec8a4655e52" target="_blank"&gt;Judge: Cardi B must not contact strip club melee victims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Cardi B must not contact, in person or through social media, the victims of a melee she was involved in at a New York strip club, a judge ordered Friday. The platinum rapper appeared in court in New York City after a summons was issued Oct. 1 for misdemeanor reckless endangerment and assault. Her lawyer has said she didn't harm anybody. Police said Cardi B and her entourage were at the club around 3 a.m. when she argued with a 23-year-old bartender. They say a fight broke out during which chairs, bottles and hookah pipes were thrown, slightly injuring the woman and another e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Cardi B's chaotic week: Rapper makes court appearance amid breakup and major Grammy nominations - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/cardi-b-court-offset-relationship-grammy-nominations-charges-strip-club-fight-nicki-minaj-a8673041.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFTVWx10HCfhC3nV5lsJ7fEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/cardi-b-court-offset-relationship-grammy-nominations-charges-strip-club-fight-nicki-minaj-a8673041.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B's chaotic week: Rapper makes court appearance amid breakup and major Grammy nominations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donning Louboutin heels, a black fur coat and a bold new hairstyle, Cardi B arrived at the Queens Criminal Court in New York City to face assault and reckless endangerment charges over a strip club brawl she was allegedly involved in earlier this year. The rapper, whose real name is Belcalis Marlenis Almánzar, smiled to a herd of paparazzi as she entered the court and left shortly after, at one point jokingly asking, "Am I famous?" She was released without bail during a brief hearing. Cardi B initially missed an appearance scheduled five days earlier, receiving a stern warning from the judg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Grammy nominations 2019: Cardi B, Kendrick Lamar and Drake lead the pack - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/dec/07/grammy-nominations-2019-cardi-b-kendrick-lamar-drake-lead</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIlVuvKfjcfFvCwBWElA-EUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:31:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/dec/07/grammy-nominations-2019-cardi-b-kendrick-lamar-drake-lead" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy nominations 2019: Cardi B, Kendrick Lamar and Drake lead the pack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After controversy about the Grammys’ failure to recognise women’s achievements at the 2018 ceremony, female artists dominate key categories in the nominations for the 2019 awards. Country stars Maren Morris and Kacey Musgraves, rapper Cardi B, pop futurist Janelle Monáe and Lady Gaga could all take home major awards at the 61st Grammy award ceremony in Los Angeles next February. Elsewhere, Kendrick Lamar and Drake dominate proceedings, with eight and seven nominations respectively. Along with Childish Gambino, AKA Donald Glover, they could rectify the other dispute that emerged from this ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Faces Down Pissed-Off Judge in Strip-Club Brawl Case - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cardi-b-faces-down-pissed-off-judge-in-strip-club-brawl-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsGbKyIYDRVnpgOohOVFAYqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMKv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:33:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/cardi-b-faces-down-pissed-off-judge-in-strip-club-brawl-case" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Faces Down Pissed-Off Judge in Strip-Club Brawl Case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raymond Hall/Getty Cardi B arrived at Queens Criminal Court on Friday with what could best be described as an air of dour glamour. The “Bodak Yellow” rapper, whose given name is Belcalis Almanzar, sported long rainbow hair (a la Tekshi 6ix9ine’s dye job), a black fur-collared jacket, and Louboutin booties. She had crystal-encrusted nails that sparkled with each minuscule hand movement. She donned a wide-brimmed, Fedora-esque hat upon entering court, as well as large sunglasses, almost reminiscent of the old Hollywood vibe of her Marilyn Monroe getup when she surrendered to cops in October f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Grammy nominations: Kendrick Lamar leads way with eight nods for Black Panther soundtrack - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/grammys-2019-nominations-list-full-drake-cardi-b-taylor-swift-lady-gaga-childish-gambino-a8672396.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDdg9vaLsGZYiKqbmy4axqAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/grammys-2019-nominations-list-full-drake-cardi-b-taylor-swift-lady-gaga-childish-gambino-a8672396.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy nominations: Kendrick Lamar leads way with eight nods for Black Panther soundtrack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Album of the Year H.E.R. – H.E.R. Brandie Carlile – By the Way, I Forgive You Drake - Scorpion Various Artists – Black Panther: The Album Kacey Musgraves – Golden Hour Post Malone – Beerbongs &amp; Bentleys Cardi B – Invasion of Privacy Janelle Monáe – Dirty Computer Record of the Year Cardi B – I Like It Brandi Carlile – The Joke Childish Gambino – This Is America Lady Gaga &amp; Bradley Cooper – Shallow Drake – God’s Plan Kendrick Lamar &amp; SZA – All the Stars Post Malone &amp; 21 Savage – Rockstar Zedd &amp; Maren Morris – The Middle Song of the Year Kendrick Lamar &amp; SZA – All the Stars Ella Mai – Boo’d U...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Learned She Was Nominated For Grammys While Leaving Court - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-grammy-nominations-courtroom_us_5c0af125e4b0a606a9a8acd8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAY7QYpLrReR_84OiOxmgq0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:18:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-grammy-nominations-courtroom_us_5c0af125e4b0a606a9a8acd8" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Learned She Was Nominated For Grammys While Leaving Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B will never forget where she was when learned she’d been nominated for five Grammy awards ― but she’d probably like to. The rapper found out about the nominations on Friday while walking out of a New York City courthouse outfitted in a fur-collared coat, a suede hat and large sunglasses, according to NBC News. Cardi B was in court to answer for her arraignment hearing on misdemeanor charges relating to an August incident where she allegedly ordered an assault on two bartenders employed at a New York strip club. At the hearing, the judge ordered Cardi B to stay away from the two women...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Drake and Lamar lead but women shine through in Grammy nods - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-grammys-nominations/drake-and-lamar-lead-but-women-shine-through-in-grammy-nods-idUSKBN1O61LJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOZzcHmAdaGSEzl12SKoc2YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:48:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-grammys-nominations/drake-and-lamar-lead-but-women-shine-through-in-grammy-nods-idUSKBN1O61LJ" target="_blank"&gt;Drake and Lamar lead but women shine through in Grammy nods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rappers Kendrick Lamar and Drake led Grammy Award nominations on Friday, but Cardi B, Lady Gaga, Brandi Carlile and American newcomer H.E.R helped make it a female-dominated line-up for the year's top prizes in the music industry. Ten-time Grammy winner Taylor Swift, Beyonce, Ariana Grande and Camila Cabello were among the biggest snubs in top categories that were dominated by hip-hop and R&amp;B. Canada's Drake, the most-streamed artist of 2018, won eight nominations, including album of the year for "Scorpion," and both song and record of the year for his single "God's Plan." Five of the expan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Cardi B shows up to court and avoids potential arrest - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/entertainment/cardi-b-court-hearing/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDaaRYMyYd3G_uLdeoax33kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:15:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/entertainment/cardi-b-court-hearing/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B shows up to court and avoids potential arrest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B made it to court just minutes before her scheduled arraignment hearing on Friday. The rapper, whose real name is Belcalis Marlenis Almánzar, faced potential arrest after failing to show for a hearing Monday. Her attorney, Jeff Kern, said she missed the previous court date due to a scheduling conflict. The case stems from Cardi B's alleged involvement in a fight at a Flushing, New York strip club back in August. She has been charged with two misdemeanors counts of reckless endangerment and one misdemeanor count of assault. According to police, Cardi B threw chairs and bottles during ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ozuna, Natti Natasha Shine But U.S. Can't Get Past 'Despacito' &amp; 'Mi Gente' In Year-End Latin Charts - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffbenjamin/2018/12/06/2018-latin-music-charts-ozuna-natti-natasha-bad-bunny/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPXpkXlGASezf8hnDi1SzmcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffbenjamin/2018/12/06/2018-latin-music-charts-ozuna-natti-natasha-bad-bunny/" target="_blank"&gt;Ozuna, Natti Natasha Shine But U.S. Can't Get Past 'Despacito' &amp; 'Mi Gente' In Year-End Latin Charts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, NY – SEPTEMBER 22: Ozuna performs live in concert at Madison Square Garden on September 22, 2018 in New York City. (Photo by Steven Ferdman/Getty Images) After a historic year in 2017, the year-end Billboard chart results for the Latin-music scene indicate some exciting changes on the way, but also warn towards some growing pains when it comes to more artists getting on the mainstream music stage. Among the Top Latin Artist overall, Ozuna takes the top spot this year with the Puerto Rican singer becoming a non-stop force on the charts in 2018 with a major album release in Aura, th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Grammy nominations: Three talking points, from album of the year snubs to new artist contenders - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/grammy-nominations-list-kendrick-lamar-drake-best-album-snubs-taylor-swift-ariana-grande-a8672541.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHx1sqcDkw5eJYdFAOETdjsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/grammy-nominations-list-kendrick-lamar-drake-best-album-snubs-taylor-swift-ariana-grande-a8672541.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy nominations: Three talking points, from album of the year snubs to new artist contenders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nominees for the 2019 Grammy Awards were announced this afternoon, with Cardi B, Kacey Musgraves and Janelle Monae amongst the nominees for the most prestigious category: Album of the Year. Here are the biggest talking points ahead of the ceremony, which takes place in Los Angeles on 10 February. 1) The Albums of the Year category is one of the strongest in years Janelle Monae (PA) There have been some questionable winners in the Album of the Year category of late. Last year, Bruno Mars’s 24K Magic beat out Kendrick Lamar, Lorde and Childish Gambino, all of whom made arguably better alb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cardi B And Offset Fans Are Excited To 'Finally' See Baby Kulture On Instagram - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-offset-kulture-baby-instagram_us_5c0942a9e4b0844cda50d115</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJm2r3kVNdjRV-93WMOzZIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:49:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-offset-kulture-baby-instagram_us_5c0942a9e4b0844cda50d115" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B And Offset Fans Are Excited To 'Finally' See Baby Kulture On Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B has shared a photo of her daughter Kulture on Instagram, much to the excitement of her fans. The rapper posted the photo of her baby girl, shortly after announcing her split from her husband and Kulture’s dad, Offset, this week. “My heart,” she wrote in the caption for the photo. View this post on Instagram A post shared by CARDIVENOM (@iamcardib) on Dec 5, 2018 at 3:17pm PST Kulture Kiari Cephus, who was born in July 2018, can be seen in the photo sporting a sparkly bow and a bib featuring her name. The picture has garnered more than 7 million likes, with people gushing over the sw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Grammy Nominations 2019: Record Of The Year - Where Are Bebe Rexha And Florida Georgia Line? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/07/grammy-nominations-2019-record-of-the-year-where-are-bebe-rexha-and-florida-georgia-line/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKDPjntNRPlHork8-Kz1j44qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/07/grammy-nominations-2019-record-of-the-year-where-are-bebe-rexha-and-florida-georgia-line/" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy Nominations 2019: Record Of The Year - Where Are Bebe Rexha And Florida Georgia Line?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;INGLEWOOD, CA – NOVEMBER 30: Cardi B performs onstage during 102.7 KIIS FM’s Jingle Ball 2018 Presented by Capital One at The Forum on November 30, 2018, in Inglewood, California. (Photo by Rich Fury/Getty Images for iHeartMedia) The Record of the Year Grammy is awarded to the producer and musicians who put out the song that people will remember decades from now as the inescapable, beloved, perfect (in some eyes, at least) track from one period in time. What was that piece of music for this past eligibility period? It’s going to be one of these eight songs, for sure. Here are the nominees f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Grammy Nominations 2019: Album Of The Year - How Did Brandi Carlile Beat Beyonce? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/07/grammy-nominations-2019-album-of-the-year-analysis-how-did-brandi-carlile-beat-beyonce/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBMYJL7cwCQgyu6-TEHeKU8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/07/grammy-nominations-2019-album-of-the-year-analysis-how-did-brandi-carlile-beat-beyonce/" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy Nominations 2019: Album Of The Year - How Did Brandi Carlile Beat Beyonce?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PASADENA, CA – SEPTEMBER 22: Beyonce (L) and JAY-Z perform onstage during the ‘On The Run II’ Tour at Rose Bowl on September 22, 2018, in Pasadena, California. (Photo by Larry Busacca/PW18/Getty Images for Parkwood Entertainment) Album of the Year remains the single greatest honor a musician can earn in their career, and only the best of the best have taken one of these golden gramophones home. This year, the four biggest categories expanded to include eight nominees, which gives more artists the chance to make their dreams come true. Here are the nominees for Album of the Year in 2019. You...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>61st Grammy Award nominees announced - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/12/07/nominations-61-grammy-awards-album-of-the-year-mxp-vpx.hln</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEORlYjaotcjtxEITKK_3L7cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:13:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/12/07/nominations-61-grammy-awards-album-of-the-year-mxp-vpx.hln" target="_blank"&gt;61st Grammy Award nominees announced&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nominations for the 61st Grammy Awards for album of the year included Janelle Monáe, Cardi B and Drake. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B appears at court for strip club brawl - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VjUgu-RjMOI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOM4f54KfhVgGYxwP18ZIz4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6OVAw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:50:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VjUgu-RjMOI" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B appears at court for strip club brawl&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(7 Dec 2018) Rapper Cardi B appeared in court Friday after a summons was issued on Oct. 1 for misdemeanor reckless endangerment and assault. A judge issued orders of protection against the rapper in a case involving a melee at a New York strip club. (Dec. 7) Subscribe for more Breaking News: http://smarturl.it/AssociatedPress Website: https://apnews.com Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP Facebook: https://facebook.com/APNews Google+: https://plus.google.com/115892241801867723374 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/ ​ You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Factbox: Key nominations for the 2019 Grammy Awards - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-grammys-nominations-factbox/factbox-key-nominations-for-the-2019-grammy-awards-idUSKBN1O61UQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECzXrnK1E24QnMkyM4GIabYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:57:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-grammys-nominations-factbox/factbox-key-nominations-for-the-2019-grammy-awards-idUSKBN1O61UQ" target="_blank"&gt;Factbox: Key nominations for the 2019 Grammy Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nominations for the Grammy Awards, the highest awards in the music industry, were announced on Friday. Following is a list of major nominations, which will be handed out at a ceremony in Los Angeles on Feb. 10. Album of the Year: Invasion of Privacy — Cardi B By The Way, I Forgive You — Brandi Carlile Scorpion — Drake H.E.R. — H.E.R. Beerbongs &amp; Bentleys — Post Malone Dirty Computer — Janelle Monae Golden Hour — Kacey Musgraves Black Panther: The Album - Various Artists Record of the Year: “I Like It” — Cardi B, Bad Bunny &amp; J Balvin “The Joke” — Brandi Carlile “This Is America” — Childi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Grammy nominations are here - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/entertainment/grammy-nominations-2018/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENHkg1KchuKZFnYqsIY7V6AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:52:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/entertainment/grammy-nominations-2018/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy nominations are here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nominations for the 61st Grammy Awards were announced Friday and one of the nominees was brought to tears live on television. Singer Janelle Monáe -- along with Alessia Cara and Shawn Mendes -- announced some the nominees on "CBS This Morning." Monáe became emotional when her "Dirty Computer" was announced for album of the year. She said she was moved because the project is "about community," especially the LGBT community of which she is a part. "I hope they feel seen," Monáe said. "I hope they feel loved and I hope they feel celebrated." Rap artists Kendrick Lamar and Drake received the mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B parties at Miami's Art Basel after announcing split - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/c5a9b54c4d3b46349df839e0d148bc3c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEElMrdAp154___0YCm4xSiYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwruxQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:19:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/c5a9b54c4d3b46349df839e0d148bc3c" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B parties at Miami's Art Basel after announcing split&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MIAMI BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Less than 24 hours after announcing her split from her husband, Cardi B was spotted partying at a nightclub to kick off Miami's Art Basel. The rapper sported long, rainbow streaked hair and a skin-tight black dress at 24/7 ultra-club E11EVEN MIAMI on Wednesday night. When the DJ played her hits, including "Bodak Yellow" and "Drippin," which features her ex, Offset, Cardi B grabbed the microphone and sang along. She posted an Instagram video saying she'd been trying to work things out with Offset: "I guess we just grew out of love. But we're not together anymore." Sh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Cardi B shares first photo of her daughter, Kulture Kiari - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/entertainment/cardi-b-kulture-first-photo-trnd/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGJArgi4Sx3A9tJI0FHmQYgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:50:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/entertainment/cardi-b-kulture-first-photo-trnd/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B shares first photo of her daughter, Kulture Kiari&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not even 24 hours after announcing her split from husband and fellow rapper Offset, Cardi B shared the first photo of their baby girl, Kulture Kiari. In the photo posted to Cardi B's Instagram account, four-month-old Kulture sits in her car seat wearing a pink headband with a white bow and a striped bib with her name on it. Cardi B, whose birth name is Belcalis Almánzar, simply captioned the photo "My Heart." The internet was all for this adorable photo, and the post has gained over 5 million likes in the past three hours. Born on July 10, Kulture Kiari Cephus is the 26-year-old rapper's fi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>These Are The 10 Most Watched Music Videos On YouTube Of 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/06/these-were-the-10-most-watched-videos-on-youtube-in-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED0J1ZwltltB4sphDCD9YoIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/06/these-were-the-10-most-watched-videos-on-youtube-in-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;These Are The 10 Most Watched Music Videos On YouTube Of 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;05 December 2018, Berlin: A man runs in front of a YouTube logo on YouTube Space Berlin during the YouTube annual review 2018. Photo: Christoph Soeder/dpa (Photo by Christoph Soeder/picture alliance via Getty Images) While streaming music sites like Spotify and Apple Music continue to sign up new listeners and rack up billions upon billions of streams every day, millions of people all around the world continue to head to YouTube to hear their favorite smashes. Now, as 2018 approaches its end point, the company has shared insight into which videos collected the most plays this year, and to t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Cardi B announces split with Offset - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/12/05/cardi-b-offset-breakup-announcement-epr-orig.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK6wRwaPBVzxm0TSJ-I3fpAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:08:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/12/05/cardi-b-offset-breakup-announcement-epr-orig.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B announces split with Offset&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper Cardi B posted a video on her Instagram account announcing that she and her husband Offset have broken up. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Grammy nominations 2019 could be surprising - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/grammy-nominations-2019-look-ahead/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECAIW7IXMZSqhvCtgSndL3sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:41:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/entertainment/grammy-nominations-2019-look-ahead/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grammy nominations 2019 could be surprising&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We may not know who will be nominated, but there's already controversy over who won't be. Both Cardi B and Post Malone have had breakout years in music, but neither is eligible to be nominated in the best new artist category at the Grammys. Nominations will be announced Friday, but it was reported months ago that the pair had been knocked out of new-artist contention -- Cardi, because her nominations last year disqualified her, and Post Malone, because Recording Academy voters reportedly decided he didn't fit the requirements for new artists. Jason Lipshutz, editorial director at Billboard,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Drake Continues To Dominate 2018 By Topping Billboard's Year-End Charts - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewleimkuehler/2018/12/05/drake-continues-to-dominate-2018-by-topping-billboards-year-end-charts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOoGNDwP0wVpqXpPojCPUOEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewleimkuehler/2018/12/05/drake-continues-to-dominate-2018-by-topping-billboards-year-end-charts/" target="_blank"&gt;Drake Continues To Dominate 2018 By Topping Billboard's Year-End Charts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper Drake poses in the press room with his awards during the 2017 Billboard Music Awards at T-Mobile Arena on May 21, 2017 in Las Vegas, Nevada. (Photo by David Becker/Getty Images) Billboard joined Spotify and Apple Music this week in crowning Drake as 2018’s top artist. Drake clocked a monster year on the Billboard charts, landing 12 times in the all-genre Hot 100 top 10, breaking a record that dated back to the 1960s and Lennon/McCartney domination. His latest studio album, Scorpion, scored three No. 1 songs on the Hot 100 in 2018: “In My Feelings,” “God’s Plan” and “Nice For What.” E...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Khloe Kardashian And Cardi B Aren't Selling Tea, They're Selling Body Dysmorphia In A Bag. - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-jameela-jamil-celebrity-teas_us_5c0150f4e4b0d04f48b394e1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHbaco2oswB0HcYtv8Lq-0AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-jameela-jamil-celebrity-teas_us_5c0150f4e4b0d04f48b394e1" target="_blank"&gt;Khloe Kardashian And Cardi B Aren't Selling Tea, They're Selling Body Dysmorphia In A Bag.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actress Jameela Jamil has had it with celebrities who hawk diet products on social media. For months, she’s been calling them out. In May, she said Kim Kardashian West is a “terrible and toxic influence on young girls” for promoting appetite suppressant lollipops. This week, she scolded Cardi B for crediting a laxative tea for her post-baby snapback. They got Cardi B on the laxative nonsense “detox” tea. GOD I hope all these celebrities all shit their pants in public, the way the poor women who buy this nonsense upon their recommendation do. Not that they actually take this shit. They just ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Let's give Cardi B a minute - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/entertainment/cardi-b-needs-a-minute/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJmgWJrDiy4Kb2w_QrqSEAQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:05:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/entertainment/cardi-b-needs-a-minute/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Let's give Cardi B a minute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before you tweet me asking, "Why is Cardi B's marital split news?" I will beat you to the punch and say it's not, really. Cardi shot to the top of Twitter trends Wednesday after she announced her split from husband and fellow rapper Offset on Instagram. Celebrity couples who eventual break up is almost a given these days, unless they are in the rarefied air of a few. (You have the power to destroy us Tom Hanks and Rita Wilson, so please keep hanging in there.) Cardi has earned her right to grieve the end of her year-long marriage in private, should she so choose. But given Offset's success ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B announces split from husband Offset: 'I guess we fell out of love' - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/cardi-b-offset-relationship-over-split-husband-new-single-a8667791.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFUf5ba-EE-qGlLjYs0wvN8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/cardi-b-offset-relationship-over-split-husband-new-single-a8667791.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B announces split from husband Offset: 'I guess we fell out of love'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B has revealed she has split from her husband Offset, in a video announcement posted on Instagram. I’ve been trying to work things out with my baby father… we’re really good friends, we’re really good business partners and he’s always somebody I run to, to talk to, and we got a lot of love for each other,” the rapper said in the video. “But things just haven’t been working out between us for a long time, and it’s nobody’s fault, I guess we fell out of love," she continued. Read more - Spotify reveals its most streamed albums, artists and tracks of 2018 - The 40 best albums of 2018, fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cardi B warned of potential arrest if she skips next court date - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/entertainment/cardi-b-skips-court-date-arrest/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELV7NDHdUHabhdo3dF-XFo8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:21:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/entertainment/cardi-b-skips-court-date-arrest/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B warned of potential arrest if she skips next court date&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B could face jail time if she doesn't show up to a court hearing on Friday. The warning comes after the rapper, whose real name is Belcalis Marlenis Almánzar, failed to appear in arraignment court Monday for her alleged involvement in a fight at a Flushing, New York strip club in August. A spokesperson for the Queens District Attorney's Office told CNN that "no formal motion" was made to issue a bench warrant for Cardi B's arrest, but a warrant could be issued if she does not show up to court later this week. Cardi B's attorney, Jeff Kern, told the judge his client had a previously sc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ariana Grande And Drake Top Spotify's 2018 Most-Streamed Artists List - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adriennegibbs/2018/12/04/ariana-grande-and-drake-top-spotifys-2018-most-streamed-artists-list/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-PjaB_2sTBLvPS0-J6ST0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/adriennegibbs/2018/12/04/ariana-grande-and-drake-top-spotifys-2018-most-streamed-artists-list/" target="_blank"&gt;Ariana Grande And Drake Top Spotify's 2018 Most-Streamed Artists List&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ariana Grande performing on Broadway. Photo by: Eric Liebowitz/NBC/NBCU Photo Bank via Getty Images Ariana Grande and Drake have done it again. For the global stage, they both top Spotify’s list of the most-streamed female and male artists of 2018. This information and other tantalizing tidbits about Spotify user habits and likes will be revealed in full when the Wrapped microsite run by Spotify is released later this week with a new look. Meanwhile, here are some of Spotify’s global stats. Drake’s Scorpion has been the talk of every teen since it dropped in June, and since then the Canadia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Adam Levine plays coy about Super Bowl Halftime show - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/entertainment/adam-levine-superbowl-halftime/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED_jZ7dm3npScoZuueSJBtgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 23:05:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/entertainment/adam-levine-superbowl-halftime/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Adam Levine plays coy about Super Bowl Halftime show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adam Levine is not giving up a great deal about reports that Maroon 5 will be performing at the next Super Bowl halftime show. "I'm still formulating a lot of things," he told Variety in a recent interview. Reaction had been mixed to early reports the group would headline the halftime show. Fans are upset over Maroon 5 Super Bowl halftime show report The NFL has not officially confirmed the entertainment lineup for the next Super Bowl. "It's a Super Bowl tradition to speculate about the performers for the Pepsi Halftime Show," a league rep said in a statement earlier this fall. "We are cont...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Drake Scores Spotify's Most-Streamed Song And Album Of 2018 In The U.S. - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/04/drake-scores-spotifys-most-streamed-song-and-album-of-2018-in-the-u-s/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQ_0VdyjHrU1svBh6RAmJ0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/12/04/drake-scores-spotifys-most-streamed-song-and-album-of-2018-in-the-u-s/" target="_blank"&gt;Drake Scores Spotify's Most-Streamed Song And Album Of 2018 In The U.S.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK, NY – AUGUST 30: Drake performs onstage at Barclays Center of Brooklyn on August 30, 2018, in New York City. (Photo by Kevin Mazur/Getty Images) It may only be early December, but the year-end lists have already started rolling out, and a familiar name rules one particular ranking. Drake has been named the king of streaming platform Spotify when it comes to the U.S., and a quick look at all the lists of what pieces of music Americans consumed the most this past year shows he was truly unbeatable. According to the streaming platform, Drake is not only the most-streamed musician in t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Rapper Cardi B fails to show up for hearing over fight at New York club - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-cardib/rapper-cardi-b-fails-to-show-up-for-hearing-over-fight-at-new-york-club-idUSKBN1O211U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM64Uv2voHai71T2PLoqzisqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 17:41:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-cardib/rapper-cardi-b-fails-to-show-up-for-hearing-over-fight-at-new-york-club-idUSKBN1O211U" target="_blank"&gt;Rapper Cardi B fails to show up for hearing over fight at New York club&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A New York judge on Monday rescheduled Cardi B's court hearing to Friday after she failed to appear in criminal court to face charges of assault in connection with a fight at a strip club but warned that she risked arrest if she did not show up again. The 26-year-old performer, whose real name is Belcalis Almanzar, surrendered to police in October after being accused of involvement in the Aug. 15 incident at the Angels NYC strip club in the borough of Queens. Judge Scott Dunn told her lawyer "to convey to her that it’s not acceptable that she’s not here today," after she failed to show up f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Jameela Jamil Wants These Celebrities To 'S**t Themselves In Public' For Promoting Detox Tea - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/jameela-jamil-detox-tea_us_5bfc087ee4b0771fb6bbe31d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENy1H5ddffZWurmBbBXayzYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 18:05:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/jameela-jamil-detox-tea_us_5bfc087ee4b0771fb6bbe31d" target="_blank"&gt;Jameela Jamil Wants These Celebrities To 'S**t Themselves In Public' For Promoting Detox Tea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jameela Jamil is sick of celebrities’ s**t. Literally. The “Good Place” actress called out Cardi B and Khloe Kardashian on Twitter over the weekend for promoting a crappy detox product she claims is targeted at young women. “They got Cardi B on the laxative nonsense ‘detox’ tea. GOD I hope all these celebrities all shit their pants in public, the way the poor women who buy this nonsense upon their recommendation do,” Jamil said. “Not that they actually take this shit. They just flog it because they need MORE MONEY,” the actress added. They got Cardi B on the laxative nonsense “detox” tea. G...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Cardi B threatened with arrest warrant after skipping court in strip club brawl case - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/cardi-b-arrest-strip-club-brawl-court-case-arraignment-judge-queens-county-a8665486.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEk0THAJJVWuO6VeQMdVWa4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 18:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/cardi-b-arrest-strip-club-brawl-court-case-arraignment-judge-queens-county-a8665486.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B threatened with arrest warrant after skipping court in strip club brawl case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B was issued a stern warning after not attending a court date on Monday, it has been reported. The rapper, 26, was due to appear in New York City criminal court facing charges of assault and reckless endangerment in connection with a fight at a strip club. She did not show up to the arraignment and a judge threatened to issue a bench warrant for her arrest if she misses her next appointment, NBC New York reported. - Read more A brief history of pop-culture feuds The performer – real name Belcalis Almanzar – skipped Monday morning's court date due to a prior engagement, which the judge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Rapper Cardi B Misses Court Appearance - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rapper-cardi-b-misses-court-appearance</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELIfD-QDwH7fAiJMcoa73hYqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 17:34:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/rapper-cardi-b-misses-court-appearance" target="_blank"&gt;Rapper Cardi B Misses Court Appearance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mike Blake/Reuters, Rapper Cardi B failed to show up to her arraignment hearing at Queens County Criminal Court Monday for charges of assault and reckless endangerment. The rapper was charged in October after she was allegedly involved in an August strip-club fight that left two bartenders injured. Cardi B’s lawyer blamed her absence in court on her busy schedule. “As you probably know she is a fairly notable hip-hop artist. My client knew the date but there was a previously scheduled commitment for today and tomorrow,” said attorney Jeff Kern, according to Page Six. The hearing was postpon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Jameela Jamil calls out celebrities who promote laxative ‘detox’ teas on Instagram - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/jameela-jamil-cardi-b-kardashians-detox-tea-controversy-instagram-twitter-good-place-a8651641.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAXOzTQ6rFW3W3CajBkqy3YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 09:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/jameela-jamil-cardi-b-kardashians-detox-tea-controversy-instagram-twitter-good-place-a8651641.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jameela Jamil calls out celebrities who promote laxative ‘detox’ teas on Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jameela Jamil has heavily criticised celebrities such as Cardi B and the Kardashians who promote “detox” teas on their social media channels, explaining that the laxative effect of the products can be detrimental for your health. Jamil, who's currently starring as Tahani Al-Jamil on The Good Place, has been very outspoken about healthy living in the past, having previously called out Kim Kardashian for promoting appetite suppressant lollipops on Instagram and having created the "I Weigh" movement earlier this year in an effort to promote body positivity. Over the weekend, Cardi B shared a v...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Billboard's Latin Top 10 Stays Unchanged From Last Week - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/11/20/billboards-latin-top-10-stays-unchanged-from-last-week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEICaPcDydLMnOyr7ZDbF6boqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/11/20/billboards-latin-top-10-stays-unchanged-from-last-week/" target="_blank"&gt;Billboard's Latin Top 10 Stays Unchanged From Last Week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo of Ozuna by Steven Ferdman/Getty Images) Those who follow Billboard’s Hot Latin Songs, the multi-metric chart that ranks Spanish-language singles consumption in the U.S., are used to a bit of monotony. Week after week, its upper reaches can look maddeningly familiar, with longstanding stalwarts like Luis Fonsi’s “Despacito” and, to a relatively lesser extent, Daddy Yankee’s “Dura” essentially blocking newer entrants from desirable peaks. This week perfectly encapsulates Hot Latin Songs’ sameness problem, as all of the top 10 singles there remain unchanged from last week, each one hol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>New J Balvin &amp; David Guetta Single Shows Growing Affinity For Latin-EDM Collaborations - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffbenjamin/2018/11/21/j-balvin-say-my-name-david-guetta-bebe-rexha-dance-latin-music/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGo3NpM4WbhreoCzCFCMtr8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffbenjamin/2018/11/21/j-balvin-say-my-name-david-guetta-bebe-rexha-dance-latin-music/" target="_blank"&gt;New J Balvin &amp; David Guetta Single Shows Growing Affinity For Latin-EDM Collaborations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colombian singer J Balvin performs during the 19th Annual Latin Grammy Awards in Las Vegas, Nevada, on November 15, 2018. (Photo by Robyn Beck / AFP) (Photo credit should read ROBYN BECK/AFP/Getty Images) Since his breakout pop moment with “Mi Gente” featuring Beyoncé, J Balvin has constantly been pushing the scope of Latin music’s reach. The Colombian star has landed himself on singles in the hip-hop world (hitting No. 1 on Cardi B’s “I Like It” with Bad Bunny), pop (collaborating with Liam Payne on “Familiar”), while expanding and diversifying the growing influence of reggaeton where he b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Cardi B achieves ‘childhood dream’ of buying her mother a house - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/cardi-b-buys-mother-house-childhood-dream-money-a8642676.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ8G7zU0vjnjk1lyO2FN-_4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/cardi-b-buys-mother-house-childhood-dream-money-a8642676.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B achieves ‘childhood dream’ of buying her mother a house&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B has achieved her “childhood dream” of buying her mother a house. The 26-year-old rapper said it was the “happiest day of my life” as she gave fans a video tour of the property in her home state of New York. Cardi B, who was brought up in the Bronx, admitted she was “emotional” and had been crying as she walked fans through the mansion, which features its own gym. - Read more Nicki Minaj addresses Cardi B fight at New York Fashion Week She captioned the post on Instagram: “Stay down till you come up! It’s always been a dream to buy my mother a house. “Last year I was so thirsty to bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cardi B buys 'dream home' for her mom - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/11/21/cardi-b-buys-house-for-mother-orig-vstan-bdk.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMT0a_cD2VRIVeHRtgkZhWUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 04:04:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/entertainment/2018/11/21/cardi-b-buys-house-for-mother-orig-vstan-bdk.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B buys 'dream home' for her mom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper Cardi B shared her pride in an Instagram video after purchasing a "dream home" for her mother. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>White, "Yellow," And Green: Cardi B's Longtime Collaborator J. White On Success &amp; Struggle - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/cmalone/2018/11/23/white-yellow-and-green-cardi-bs-longtime-collaborator-j-white-on-success-struggle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXN0E3shXRfaHaLwSupNHIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 23:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/cmalone/2018/11/23/white-yellow-and-green-cardi-bs-longtime-collaborator-j-white-on-success-struggle/" target="_blank"&gt;White, "Yellow," And Green: Cardi B's Longtime Collaborator J. White On Success &amp; Struggle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;J. White arrives at the 60th annual Grammy Awards at Madison Square Garden on Sunday, Jan. 28, 2018, in New York. (Photo by Evan Agostini/Invision/AP) For producer J. White, making a hit record wasn’t just a marker of success; it was the key to survival. Music has been in J’s blood since he was an infant. His whole family were active church singers in his native Kansas City, and his father performed famous gospel songs during their services. His parents and grandparents brought him with them to rehearsals when he was as young as 6 months old. Because music had become part of his DNA at such...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Netflix snags Cardi B, Chance and T.I. for music competition show - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/entertainment/cardi-b-ti-chance-netflix/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGQFG_8EXB4wV-OMV4IgGFkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:47:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/14/entertainment/cardi-b-ti-chance-netflix/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Netflix snags Cardi B, Chance and T.I. for music competition show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix is getting into the music competition business with some major star power. The streaming giant has announced that superstar rappers Cardi B, Chance the Rapper, and T.I. will search for the next breakout hip-hop star as part of "Rhythm + Flow," Netflix's first music competition show set to debut in 2019. The trio will serve as the main judges for the competition looking for unsigned, undiscovered talent. They will be joining forces with additional artists and industry VIPs who will be announced in the coming weeks. The three rappers all promoted the news Tuesday on their social media...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Anuel AA Returns To The Hot 100 With Romeo Santos' Help - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/11/13/anuel-aa-returns-to-the-hot-100-with-romeo-santos-help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO8eJAxV3zV7XYOcrp17HwgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/11/13/anuel-aa-returns-to-the-hot-100-with-romeo-santos-help/" target="_blank"&gt;Anuel AA Returns To The Hot 100 With Romeo Santos' Help&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo of Anuel AA by Omar Vega/Getty Images) While DJ Snake’s Latin star-studded “Taki Taki” and the Bad Bunny-meets-Drake duet “MIA” continue to duke it out week after week for the top spot on Billboard’s Hot Latin Songs, another noteworthy team-up has arrived to challenge their dueling chart supremacy. “Ella Quiere Beber,” a remix of trap rapper Anuel AA’s “Quiere Beber” featuring bachata superstar Romeo Santos, hits No. 5 on the Spanish-language singles chart this week. The winning combination also takes the refurbished track straight to the Hot 100, where it debuts at No. 86. Prior to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Halsey And Wes Scheck Land Top 10 Hits Behind Maroon 5 And Cardi B's Massive No. 1 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/05/halsey-and-wes-scheck-land-top-10-hits-behind-maroon-5-and-cardi-bs-massive-no-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARoYLsoxylSXi2_qhkgdZkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 21:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/11/05/halsey-and-wes-scheck-land-top-10-hits-behind-maroon-5-and-cardi-bs-massive-no-1/" target="_blank"&gt;Halsey And Wes Scheck Land Top 10 Hits Behind Maroon 5 And Cardi B's Massive No. 1&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US singer Halsey performs during the MTV Europe Music Awards at the Bizkaia Arena in the northern Spanish city of Bilbao on November 4, 2018. (Photo by LLUIS GENE / AFP) (Photo credit should read LLUIS GENE/AFP/Getty Images) Despite the fact that it waited in second place for weeks before it finally rose to No. 1 on the Hot 100, Maroon 5 and Cardi B’s “Girls Like You” has now ruled the all-genre singles listing for seven consecutive turns, a lengthier-than-expected stay for a tune that has already enjoyed so many frames so close to the peak. Behind the popular pairing, two newly-released si...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj and Cardi B 'call truce' after day of fighting on Instagram - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/nicki-minaj-cardi-b-beef-instagram-truce-fight-nyfw-twitter-a8608241.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0cKsiua7eOFCT4ZmXS6MUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 08:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/nicki-minaj-cardi-b-beef-instagram-truce-fight-nyfw-twitter-a8608241.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nicki Minaj and Cardi B 'call truce' after day of fighting on Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicki Minaj and Cardi B have seemingly called a truce after a day of fighting on social media. The two rappers have been feuding ever since a physical altercation earlier this year at New York Fashion Week. Since then, the pair have exchanged barbed words on multiple occasions, their rivalry flaring up once more last night (29 October) after Minaj once again addressed the New York incident on her Beats 1 show Queen Radio. Minaj claimed that Cardi B's Love and Hip Hop co-star Rah Ali had attacked Cardi, punching her "nine or 10 times" in the head. Minaj also offered $100,000 for security foo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cardi B, Juice WRLD And Tekashi69 Give Standout Performances At Powerhouse NYC - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kerycehenry/2018/10/29/cardi-b-juice-wrld-and-tekashi69-give-standout-performances-at-powerhouse-nyc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJTDbR2eRx75UDx1-MFk1SoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 19:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kerycehenry/2018/10/29/cardi-b-juice-wrld-and-tekashi69-give-standout-performances-at-powerhouse-nyc/" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B, Juice WRLD And Tekashi69 Give Standout Performances At Powerhouse NYC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEWARK, NJ – OCTOBER 28: Rapper Cardi B performs at Power 105.1′s Powerhouse 2018 at Prudential Center on October 28, 2018 in Newark, New Jersey. (Photo by Bennett Raglin/Getty Images for Power 105.1) Last night, New Jersey’s Prudential Center was taken over by Powerhouse NYC. Hosted by iHeartMedia station Power 105.1—home of the Breakfast Club morning show, serving New York, New Jersey and Connecticut—the annual concert made its move from Brooklyn’s Barclays Center for this year’s show, but otherwise proved to be no different in terms of spotlighting some of the year’s most talked-about ac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj And Cardi B Beef Gets Brutally Shut Down By Jimmy Kimmel Guest - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/jimmy-kimmel-cardi-b-nicki-minaj_us_5bd96dc7e4b01abe6a1971cd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBYBlltkJBgjBYe1e7bI4h4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:59:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/jimmy-kimmel-cardi-b-nicki-minaj_us_5bd96dc7e4b01abe6a1971cd" target="_blank"&gt;Nicki Minaj And Cardi B Beef Gets Brutally Shut Down By Jimmy Kimmel Guest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jimmy Kimmel asked “some of our wiser and elder individuals” visiting a farmer’s market to take sides in Cardi B’s rap beef with Nicki Minaj. And one unidentified woman didn’t hold back, as she broke down what she believed was the pointlessness of it all. “That feud is a waste of energy,” she said in the segment that aired on Tuesday’s broadcast of “Jimmy Kimmel Live!” She added: “Life is meant to be enjoyed. I think they say in America, ‘Get a life.’” The beef between the two rap stars appears, for the time being at least, to be on pause. After watching this segment, the musician pair may ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj and Cardi B call a truce - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/30/entertainment/nicki-minaj-cardi-b-truce/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIicN0ccVqJhQ37xUStW6LcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 14:06:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/30/entertainment/nicki-minaj-cardi-b-truce/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nicki Minaj and Cardi B call a truce&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rappers Nicki Minaj and Cardi B took their feud to new heights when the two got into a fight leaving a New York Fashion Week party in September. Partygoers posted video of the fight on social media. The pair traded insults in the public eye after and appeared to call a truce in October. Getty Images Rappers Curtis "50 Cent" Jackson and Ja Rule have a long history of beefing which began in 1999. Their latest incident happened in October 2018 when 50 Cent said he bought 200 tickets to Ja Rule's concert to keep the seats empty. Ja Rule retaliated with some non-flattering, photoshopped images o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>A brief history of pop culture feuds: From John Keats and Lord Byron to Nicki Minaj and Cardi B - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/features/nicki-minaj-cardi-b-feud-celebrities-kanye-taylor-madonna-cher-a8608886.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIw7-EEFIqS1Bz7FTMvXjqkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 12:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/features/nicki-minaj-cardi-b-feud-celebrities-kanye-taylor-madonna-cher-a8608886.html" target="_blank"&gt;A brief history of pop culture feuds: From John Keats and Lord Byron to Nicki Minaj and Cardi B&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Always forgive your enemies. Nothing annoys them so much.” Oscar Wilde’s advice was expertly deployed by Cardi B this week when she gained the upper hand in her long-running feud with Nicki Minaj by suggesting a ceasefire following a vicious exchange of hostilities on social media. With 50 Cent trolling Ja Rule by buying up 200 gig tickets to ensure empty seats, we appear to be living in a new golden age of the pop-culture beef. Here’s a selection of some of the juiciest feuds and rivalries from the history of the genre. John Keats vs Lord Byron “He describes what he sees – I describe what...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Faces Backlash for Telling Internet Trolls to ‘Cut Veins’ - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cardi-b-faces-backlash-for-telling-internet-trolls-to-cut-veins</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECegCF8-4g-KvmSRfrwwqtIqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 03:03:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/cardi-b-faces-backlash-for-telling-internet-trolls-to-cut-veins" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Faces Backlash for Telling Internet Trolls to ‘Cut Veins’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mario Anzuoni/Reuters, Cardi B has triggered an uproar on social media after telling internet trolls to commit suicide in a rant on Instagram Live. The rapper aimed the comments at online trolls targeting her sister Hennessy. “You should just fucking throw yourself off a balcony,” she said, addressing those who she said were “talking shit” online. Despite someone off camera apparently urging her to tone down her language, she went on to say, “You need a fucking life. You need to cut your motherfucking veins.” More than 40,000 people were tuned in when Cardi B made the remarks, and many were...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Beyoncé Channels Her Inner Toni For 'Phoni Braxton' Halloween Costume - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/beyonce-toni-braxton-halloween-costume_us_5bd8ef68e4b019a7ab5827dc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELkjM8QP3P22hqy6PBjuQCAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 02:34:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/beyonce-toni-braxton-halloween-costume_us_5bd8ef68e4b019a7ab5827dc" target="_blank"&gt;Beyoncé Channels Her Inner Toni For 'Phoni Braxton' Halloween Costume&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyoncé’s at it again with another flawless Halloween costume, this time channeling “Un-Break My Heart” singer Toni Braxton. Snaps of Bey recreating Braxton’s self-titled 1993 album were posted to Instagram on Tuesday night. “Sending love and adoration to one of our talented legends. Thank you for the countless bops. Your tone, your beauty, your range, and your God-given talent is treasured. Loving you always. Have a Happy Halloween my Kings and Queens,” she wrote. View this post on Instagram A post shared by Beyoncé (@beyonce) on Oct 30, 2018 at 12:51pm PDT View this post on Instagram A po...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Post Malone And Swae Lee Debut Inside The Top 10 While Travis Scott Looks Poised To Hit No. 1 Next - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/10/29/post-malone-and-swae-lee-debut-inside-the-top-10-while-travis-scott-looks-poised-to-hit-no-1-soon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIL_qfpask8S-UCFwE-6-2UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 18:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/10/29/post-malone-and-swae-lee-debut-inside-the-top-10-while-travis-scott-looks-poised-to-hit-no-1-soon/" target="_blank"&gt;Post Malone And Swae Lee Debut Inside The Top 10 While Travis Scott Looks Poised To Hit No. 1 Next&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LOS ANGELES, CA – OCTOBER 09: Post Malone attends the 2018 American Music Awards at Microsoft Theater on October 9, 2018, in Los Angeles, California. (Photo by Axelle/Bauer-Griffin/FilmMagic) Despite tough competition from one of the biggest rappers on the planet, Maroon 5 and Cardi B hold onto the No. 1 spot on the Hot 100 singles chart for another week, giving the powerful pairing six straight frames of domination. Fellow hip-hop superstar Travis Scott moves up on the listing with his latest single as a lead and is now just one position away from running the show. “Sicko Mode,” which is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Cardi B hands out winter coats in Brooklyn - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/entertainment/cardi-b-winter-coats-brooklyn/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHzc1_LupOd7BE_UbTCN1AIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 15:24:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/entertainment/cardi-b-winter-coats-brooklyn/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B hands out winter coats in Brooklyn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B is kicking off the holiday season a bit early with some good will. The rapper handed out free winter coats in Brooklyn, New York on Thursday, where a massive crowd swarmed the "I Like It" performer. Cardi B, a native of the Bronx, was seen at The Marlboro Houses, a housing project in Gravesend, New York. Her good deed comes as New York was hit with unusually cold temperatures this week. "I didn't know it was gonna be so big," Cardi B told WABC about the large crowds who braved the chilly temperatures to see her. "My home boy Chuck, he told me, 'Hey, let's give out coats to our commu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cardi B hands out free winter coats in New York - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/ccb880653a1949e9953932afa935ada1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF2KUsxztQm2LGox1ApD_FMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 13:13:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/ccb880653a1949e9953932afa935ada1" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B hands out free winter coats in New York&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Hundreds of people have lined up in New York City as rapper Cardi B handed out free winter coats. The Bronx-born rapper met with residents and fans on Thursday evening at the Marlboro Houses in Brooklyn during brisk fall weather. The 26-year-old also was given balloons and a cake to celebrate her recent birthday. Cardi B says she cares a lot about kids and the community and feels it's important to set a good example. On Oct. 1, she got a summons in connection with a melee at a New York strip club. Her lawyer says the star didn't cause any harm. About three weeks earlier, Car...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Says Her Baby 'Broke My Vagina' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-baby-baby-broke-vagina_us_5bc8585ee4b055bc947dc169</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMaF4XMVqHOvB6MZcrOarRsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 11:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-baby-baby-broke-vagina_us_5bc8585ee4b055bc947dc169" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Says Her Baby 'Broke My Vagina'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B’s account of giving birth to her baby girl left the “Jimmy Kimmel Live” audience in stitches on Wednesday. It seems the rapper had no idea that she would literally be left in stitches after the delivery. The revelation emerged as the “Bodak Yellow” chart-topper and host Kimmel made small talk about motherhood. Then it got real. Asked by Kimmel if childbirth was easier or harder than she expected, Cardi responded: “It was totally harder. She broke my vagina.” The performer said she was not informed of certain “things” about the experience. “Nobody told me they was gonna stitch my vag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Cardi B Hands Out Free Winter Coats To Residents In New York - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-free-winter-coats-new-york-brooklyn_us_5bc9fba4e4b0a8f17eebe436</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELz8rKA6BCvBefAup4HjMCkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 18:24:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/cardi-b-free-winter-coats-new-york-brooklyn_us_5bc9fba4e4b0a8f17eebe436" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B Hands Out Free Winter Coats To Residents In New York&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B handed out free winter coats to residents in Brooklyn as cooler temperatures hit New York. The Bronx native told New York’s WABC-TV on Thursday that she was excited when she learned about the opportunity from a friend to help give out free coats at a public housing community in Gravesend, Brooklyn. Crowds of fans gathered outside nearby to see the “Invasion of Privacy” rapper during the coat giveaway. Local wholesaler Daniels Leather donated the coats, while NY Tent Sale and TraxNYC provided shoe donations and additional sponsorship, according to Footwork Entertainment, an organizer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Aided By Drake, Bad Bunny Logs 4 Simultaneous Billboard Latin Hits - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/10/23/bad-bunny-drake/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0GbnCH9-JdU_GUZh0HvXsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 16:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/garysuarez/2018/10/23/bad-bunny-drake/" target="_blank"&gt;Aided By Drake, Bad Bunny Logs 4 Simultaneous Billboard Latin Hits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo by David Crotty/Patrick McMullan via Getty Images) Bad Bunny is officially having a great week over at Billboard. Following its debut last week on Hot Latin Songs at No. 9, the Puerto Rican rapper’s Drake team-up “MIA” tops the chart in its first full qualifying week. The song also takes No. 1 on both Latin Digital Song Sales and Latin Streaming Songs. Additionally, “MIA” reaches No. 5 with its first appearance on the all-genre Hot 100 and, thanks to 26,000 paid downloads, No. 4 on overall Digital Song Sales. A broad hit with platforms like Apple Music and Spotify, it comes in at No....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>BET Hip Hop Awards 2018 winners list in full: Cardi B scoops four prizes - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/bet-hip-hop-awards-2018-winners-list-cardi-b-drake-kendrick-lamar-a8587756.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFMSM4xo7Iq998IsA6Z-hJAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 08:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/bet-hip-hop-awards-2018-winners-list-cardi-b-drake-kendrick-lamar-a8587756.html" target="_blank"&gt;BET Hip Hop Awards 2018 winners list in full: Cardi B scoops four prizes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2018 BET Hip Hop Awards took place last night (16 October), with Cardi B managing to scoop the most trophies, as well as stunning attendees with a performance of her tracks “Get Up 10” and “Backin’ It Up”. She managed to beat stiff competition from Drake, who headed into the awards show with 11 nominations compared to her 10. “I’m thankful and I’m grateful,” she said, accepting an award, handed over by host DeRay Davis. Other big winners included Jay Z and Beyoncé, whose collaboration Everything is Love won Album of the Year, while their track “Apesh*t” won Single of the Year. Lil Wayne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>See all the American Music Awards winners - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/entertainment/american-music-awards-winners-list/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsqAplcg6oIaVPqopXVd-QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 04:06:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/entertainment/american-music-awards-winners-list/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;See all the American Music Awards winners&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American Music Awards were held in Los Angeles on Tuesday night. The following is a list of this year's nominees and winners, Taylor Swift and Camila Cabello led the night with four awards each. ARTIST OF THE YEAR Drake Imagine Dragons Post Malone Ed Sheeran Taylor Swift *WINNER NEW ARTIST OF THE YEAR PRESENTED BY CAPITAL ONE Camila Cabello *WINNER Cardi B Khalid Dua Lipa XXXTENTACION COLLABORATION OF THE YEAR Camila Cabello ft. Young Thug, "Havana" *WINNER Post Malone ft. 21 Savage, "Rockstar" Bruno Mars &amp; Cardi B, "Finesse" Bebe Rexha &amp; Florida Georgia Line, "Meant To Be" Zedd, Maren ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Lady Gaga, Bradley Cooper, Marshmello, Bastille, Lil Baby And Gunna Hit The Top 10 With New Singles - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/10/15/lady-gaga-bradley-cooper-marshmello-bastille-lil-baby-and-gunna-hit-the-top-10-with-new-singles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDyASkx6wVJjAtrB4hs9A4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hughmcintyre/2018/10/15/lady-gaga-bradley-cooper-marshmello-bastille-lil-baby-and-gunna-hit-the-top-10-with-new-singles/" target="_blank"&gt;Lady Gaga, Bradley Cooper, Marshmello, Bastille, Lil Baby And Gunna Hit The Top 10 With New Singles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON, UNITED KINGDOM – SEPTEMBER 27: Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper attend the UK film premiere of ‘A Star Is Born’ at Vue West End in London. September 27, 2018, in London, United Kingdom. (Wiktor Szymanowicz / Barcroft Media via Getty Images) This week on the Hot 100 singles chart, three new songs break into the top 10, giving six musical acts new successes to their credit. While some of these artists have been in this space several times before, three of the six collect their first top 10 in the U.S. While a lot changes inside the uppermost region on the Hot 100 this time around, the No....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>AMAs 2018: Five biggest talking points, from Taylor Swift's call to vote to Gladys Knight’s Aretha Franklin tribute - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/amas-2018-taylor-swift-vote-acceptance-speech-aretha-franklin-cardi-b-talking-points-a8576936.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELYG3aIGmqU6Q4BNiYHhqhUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 10:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/amas-2018-taylor-swift-vote-acceptance-speech-aretha-franklin-cardi-b-talking-points-a8576936.html" target="_blank"&gt;AMAs 2018: Five biggest talking points, from Taylor Swift's call to vote to Gladys Knight’s Aretha Franklin tribute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American Music Awards took place last night (9 October), with Taylor Swift taking home the majority of awards and becoming the most-decorated female artist in AMA history, beating Whitney Houston’s record. Although the winners were notable, the speeches and performances have captured everyone’s attention. Below are five of the biggest talking points. Taylor Swift’s call to vote American Music Awards 2018: Best-dressed celebrities on the red carpet - 20 show all American Music Awards 2018: Best-dressed celebrities on the red carpet - 1/20 Cardi B The American rapper stole the hearts of f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Taylor Swift wins big at AMAs and encourages fans to vote - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/71d4976f018240a88838fdb048835a55</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENLCdLEe2qjYn5ulgO_PNOUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 10:54:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/71d4976f018240a88838fdb048835a55" target="_blank"&gt;Taylor Swift wins big at AMAs and encourages fans to vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taylor Swift kicked off her week with a rare political post on social media, and at the American Music Awards she continued the conversation by encouraging fans to vote in the upcoming midterm elections. Swift won four honors including artist of the year at the fan-voted show on Tuesday in Los Angeles, beating out Drake, Ed Sheeran, Imagine Dragons and Post Malone for the top prize. "This award and every single award given out tonight were voted on by the people, and you know what else is voted on by the people," she said, "the midterm elections on November 6." Swift announced on Sunday tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Cardi B on what sparked that Nicki Minaj fight - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/10/entertainment/cardi-b-interview-minaj/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJaw5WsYmanN5xiEsElCLUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 14:28:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/10/entertainment/cardi-b-interview-minaj/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cardi B on what sparked that Nicki Minaj fight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We now know what exactly sparked Cardi B going after Nicki Minaj at a New York Fashion Week party. In a profile with W, the rapper opened up about everything from her feud with Minaj to her insecurities over husband rapper Offset's potential for infidelity. The rappers were seen leaving New York Fashion Week's annual Harper's Bazaar Icons party last month when some attendees documented Cardi B yelling, throwing a shoe and being restrained while attempting to charge Minaj. After the altercation, Minaj lashed out at Cardi B on her Beats 1's "Queen Radio" show. Nicki Minaj fires back at Cardi ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj Is Now Openly Mocking Cardi B With The Pettiest Merch - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/nicki-minaj-drops-the-pettiest-merch-to-openly-mock-cardi-b_us_5bb781e4e4b028e1fe3d3f64</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE1GYOIn-a2yCd1QKibe6OoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:00:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/nicki-minaj-drops-the-pettiest-merch-to-openly-mock-cardi-b_us_5bb781e4e4b028e1fe3d3f64" target="_blank"&gt;Nicki Minaj Is Now Openly Mocking Cardi B With The Pettiest Merch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicki Minaj is the one making the money moves off her Fashion Week dustup with Cardi B. If you were wondering whether the “Barbie Dreams” rapper is ready to put the feud behind her after a physical altercation with Cardi at the Harper’s Bazaar ICONS party last month, it’s a hard no. On Thursday, Minaj announced a new line of merchandise, including backpacks, T-shirts and jackets with the phrase “Nicki Stopped My Bag” branded on them to poke fun at a note Cardi released on Instagram after their fight. The products, which come in a variety of colors, are now available for purchase on the rapp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Taylor Swift sets new American Music Award record, urges people to vote - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-americanmusic/taylor-swift-sets-new-american-music-award-record-urges-people-to-vote-idUSKCN1MK02A</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKsqtr2-A-8Fy4nUCd9IW3YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 09:52:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-americanmusic/taylor-swift-sets-new-american-music-award-record-urges-people-to-vote-idUSKCN1MK02A" target="_blank"&gt;Taylor Swift sets new American Music Award record, urges people to vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taylor Swift, straight off a controversial dive into U.S. politics, was the big winner at the American Music Awards on Tuesday where she used her platform to again urge her fans to get out and vote. The 28-year-old pop singer won a record fourth artist of the year trophy at the fan-voted American Music Awards, beating rappers Drake and Post Malone, as well as Britain's Ed Sheeran and rock band Imagine Dragons for the top prize. She also picked up three other awards, for best female pop artist, best tour, and best pop album for "reputation," the biggest seller of 2017. On Sunday, Swift provo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>AMAs 2018: The full winners list as Taylor Swift makes history - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/amas-2018-winners-list-taylor-swift-camila-cabello-bts-carrie-underwood-american-music-awards-a8576801.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN8z-NmcIPMnoov8kf0Q7FwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 07:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/amas-2018-winners-list-taylor-swift-camila-cabello-bts-carrie-underwood-american-music-awards-a8576801.html" target="_blank"&gt;AMAs 2018: The full winners list as Taylor Swift makes history&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taylor Swift was the biggest winner at the American Music Awards this year, taking home a total of four prizes which made her the most-decorated female artist in AMA history. The pop star, who released her critically-acclaimed album reputation last year, now has a total of 23 wins. At the 2018 ceremony she was awarded the prizes for Tour of the Year, Favourite Female Artist (Pop/Rock), Favourite Album (Pop/Rock), and the top prize, Artist of the Year. Other artists who received awards were Camila Cabello, Rihanna, Post Malone, Migos, Cardi B, and Carrie Underwood. Read more - Taylor Swift p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Key winners at the 2018 American Music Awards - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-americanmusic-winners-factbox/key-winners-at-the-2018-american-music-awards-idUSKCN1MK08Y</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDTZAb_AkP782SEUlXQGWX0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 06:19:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-awards-americanmusic-winners-factbox/key-winners-at-the-2018-american-music-awards-idUSKCN1MK08Y" target="_blank"&gt;Key winners at the 2018 American Music Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American Music Awards were handed out on Tuesday at televised performance show in Los Angeles. Following are winners in key categories for the awards, which are chosen by fans. ARTIST OF THE YEAR Taylor Swift NEW ARTIST OF THE YEAR Camila Cabello TOUR OF THE YEAR Taylor Swift SOCIAL ARTIST BTS MALE ARTIST – POP/ROCK Post Malone FEMALE ARTIST - POP/ROCK Taylor Swift ALBUM – POP/ROCK Taylor Swift “Reputation” SONG- POP/ROCK Camila Cabello ft. Young Thug “Havana” MALE ARTIST – COUNTRY Kane Brown FEMALE ARTIST – COUNTRY Carrie Underwood ARTIST – RAP/HIP-HOP Cardi B ALBUM - SOUL/R&amp;B XXXTenta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Music was the surprising star of the American Music Awards - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/entertainment/american-music-award-performances/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOnlIO7YZuhdkoJtr1_kG20qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMNHPpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/09/entertainment/american-music-award-performances/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Music was the surprising star of the American Music Awards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2018 American Music Awards were, surprisingly, mostly about the music. There were some moments, including comedian Billy Eichner going off script to urge people to vote and XXXTentacion's mother, Cleopatra Bernard, accepting the award for favorite soul/R&amp;B album for her late son. But it was the performances at Tuesday's ceremony that captured attention. Taylor Swift, who just wrapped the North American leg of her "Reputation" tour, kicked off the show with her single "I Did Something Bad." It marked Swift's first live awards show performance in three years. She also made history by snag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Taylor Swift urges fans to vote as she sets American Music Awards record - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/taylor-swift-american-music-awards-vote-2018-politics-record-whitney-houston-a8576786.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDMMnVvEphmLlM_lwFYJwiEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 08:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/news/taylor-swift-american-music-awards-vote-2018-politics-record-whitney-houston-a8576786.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taylor Swift urges fans to vote as she sets American Music Awards record&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taylor Swift has continued her recent foray into US politics as she celebrated a big win at the American Music Awards by urging her fans to vote in the midterm elections in November. Swift won her fourth artist of the year trophy at the fan-voted awards, beating out Drake, Ed Sheeran, Imagine Dragons and Post Malone. The 28-year-old also picked up three other awards, for best female pop artist, best tour, and best pop album for “reputation”, which was the biggest seller of 2017. Read more - Taylor Swift pro-Democrat statement causes spike in voter registration - Trump hits back at Taylor Sw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj launches merchandise line based on Cardi B fight - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/05/entertainment/nicki-minaj-cardi-b-merchandise/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGO3P5tRzAmJgOayAW1htAAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 12:48:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/05/entertainment/nicki-minaj-cardi-b-merchandise/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nicki Minaj launches merchandise line based on Cardi B fight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardi B accused Nicki Minaj of trying to mess with her money, pointing to that as one of the reasons behind their infamous New York Fashion Week run-in. But now Cardi is helping to make her reported rival some cash. Minaj is selling merchandise inscribed with the words "Nicki stopped my bag," a nod to Cardi B's quote after the September 7 incident. The phrase refers to an attempt to stop someone from making money, the opposite of the slang phrase "securing the bag." The rappers were seen leaving New York Fashion Week's annual Harper's Bazaar Icons party when some attendees documented Cardi ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item></channel></rss>