<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Hello Games - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR1JuY0dSMGFoSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-BW&amp;gl=BW&amp;ceid=BW:en</link><language>en-BW</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:58:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>The studio behind 'No Man's Sky' has a new, bite-sized game - Engadget</title><link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/12/06/no-mans-sky-new-game-last-campfire-hello-games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780129301251</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:39:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.engadget.com/2018/12/06/no-mans-sky-new-game-last-campfire-hello-games/" target="_blank"&gt;The studio behind 'No Man's Sky' has a new, bite-sized game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Engadget&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/12/07/no-mans-sky-developer-just-announced-a-new-game-and-it-looks-excellent/" target="_blank"&gt;'No Man's Sky' Developer Hello Games Just Announced 'The Last Campfire'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/no-mans-sky-dev-reveals-a-new-game-the-last-campfi/1100-6463734/" target="_blank"&gt;No Man's Sky Dev Reveals A New Game, The Last Campfire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;GameSpot&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vg247.com/2018/12/07/hello-games-the-last-campfire-trailer/" target="_blank"&gt;The Last Campfire: a new indie title from Hello Games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VG247&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.techspot.com/news/77759-no-man-sky-creators-reveal-new-game.html" target="_blank"&gt;No Man's Sky creators reveal new game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TechSpot&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqcggKImxDQklTU3pvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NqNEtFUWlENXU2bWpZQU1FWS03UG9hcjVKT1ZFaWxPYnlCTllXNG5jeUJUYTNrZ1pHVjJaV3h2Y0dWeUlHRnVibTkxYm1ObGN5QnVaWGNnWjJGdFpTZ0FQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.engadget.com">Engadget</source></item><item><title>Leaked Video Introduces Awesome New 'Visions' Update For 'No Man's Sky' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/21/leaked-video-shows-awesome-new-visions-update-for-no-mans-sky/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGmgh73ITdwEuzSip6BwVAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/11/21/leaked-video-shows-awesome-new-visions-update-for-no-mans-sky/" target="_blank"&gt;Leaked Video Introduces Awesome New 'Visions' Update For 'No Man's Sky'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello Games has been killing it since they released the Next update for No Man's Sky in July. Next turned the widely disparaged game into what it was originally ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Last Campfire - Rock Paper Shotgun</title><link>https://www.rockpapershotgun.com/game/the-last-campfire/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiOGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnJvY2twYXBlcnNob3RndW4uY29tL2dhbWUvdGhlLWxhc3QtY2FtcGZpcmUv0gEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:46:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rockpapershotgun.com/game/the-last-campfire/" target="_blank"&gt;The Last Campfire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Rock Paper Shotgun&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello Games, the English studio behind No Man's Sky and Joe Danger, announced The Last Campfire tonight. While they're still working on No Man's Sky, this ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rockpapershotgun.com">Rock Paper Shotgun</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/-7HUEQqChD8laF1rst77KYQVxpShGncIqCvHBhO63tTxS6sFi6JZmWstECGBYg4-XKb4OYnSgcM2r3Q3Pi5rcalSy64XEdFvAa-JJQ2Vvoj0DmpRBCob9bBIye-6tIpKdCZWywzibRGPtPBocsLdkNkfk4KgZw=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>A Deep Dive Into No Man's Sky's Strange 'Foundation' Update - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/11/28/a-deep-dive-into-no-mans-skys-strange-foundation-update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAgPuHXXHcYFNlQA5IibkxcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/11/28/a-deep-dive-into-no-mans-skys-strange-foundation-update/" target="_blank"&gt;A Deep Dive Into No Man's Sky's Strange 'Foundation' Update&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: Paul Tassi/Hello Games I had no idea I would spend the vast majority of my Sunday playing No Man’s Sky, a game I have not touched in months, but Hello Games decided to spring the game’s biggest patch since launch upon its playerbase, the “Foundation” Update. While promising that it would be a sign of larger things to come, Hello Games has dumped a lot into the Foundation patch, even if it’s just laying the groundwork for future updates. Chief among the additions are a new base-building mode, which has the ability to establish a “home planet” that you can travel to and from via a new ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>That Mysterious, Deleted 'No Man's Sky' Tweet Wasn't A Hack [Updated] - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/10/28/that-mysterious-deleted-no-mans-sky-tweet-wasnt-a-hack/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED25fdQeadt1NKJfX_CNEbUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 13:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/10/28/that-mysterious-deleted-no-mans-sky-tweet-wasnt-a-hack/" target="_blank"&gt;That Mysterious, Deleted 'No Man's Sky' Tweet Wasn't A Hack [Updated]&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Was No Man’s Sky a mistake? One Hello Games employee thinks so. (Credit: Hello Games) Developer Hello Games has been strangely silent since the summer release of their game, No Man’s Sky. It’s been one of those silences that somehow grows louder and louder the longer it remains. Then, this morning, all that changed. “No Man’s Sky was a mistake,” the developer’s Twitter feed proclaimed, shockingly, for all the world to see. The tweet was quickly taken down (Update: It’s still visible on the company’s website at the time of this writing) and Hello Games changed the status of their account to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>No Man's Sky: can an update save this beautiful, frustrating game? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/aug/14/no-mans-sky-atlas-rises-update-game</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAMWMb1cTtNde2YVdJQQ63UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 11:49:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/aug/14/no-mans-sky-atlas-rises-update-game" target="_blank"&gt;No Man's Sky: can an update save this beautiful, frustrating game?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost a year to the day since its controversial release, No Man’s Sky is still frequently awe inspiring. There’s beauty in its hyper-saturated sunsets and navy-hued space-scapes; there’s fascination in the occasionally hilarious procedurally generated creatures, or the rush of fear as a radioactive solar storm ravages a planet’s dusty surface. There’s still a thrill in diving below the top layer of cloud to find out what kind of biome lies beneath – even if a world’s surface can often look completely different to how it appeared from the dark blueness of space. “What is No Man’s Sky?” was ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>This One Simple Trick Will Get You Millions In 'No Man's Sky' (Gek Hate It!) - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/11/30/this-one-simple-trick-will-get-you-millions-in-no-mans-sky-gek-hate-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEsVYxYXUvmSaQCNEQfKmHcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 16:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/11/30/this-one-simple-trick-will-get-you-millions-in-no-mans-sky-gek-hate-it/" target="_blank"&gt;This One Simple Trick Will Get You Millions In 'No Man's Sky' (Gek Hate It!)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: Paul Tassi/Hello Games If you’ve been following my writing the past few days, you’ll know that I’ve gotten lost deep down the rabbit hole of No Man’s Sky’s new Foundation Update, which has brought freighters, base-building and farming to the beleaguered game, among other changes. I remarked yesterday that I had “beaten” the update, doing pretty much everything there was to do, from chasing down quests for rare minerals to buying the coolest freighter I could find. But now? There’s only one thing left to do: Get filthy rich and wait for something cool to buy in the next update. And I’...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Hello Games Shows Off No Man's Sky's New 'Path Finder' Update With Land Vehicles - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/03/08/hello-games-shows-off-no-mans-skys-new-path-finder-update-with-land-vehicles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH87-hruy8pWgMwPlxrAlp8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 19:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/03/08/hello-games-shows-off-no-mans-skys-new-path-finder-update-with-land-vehicles/" target="_blank"&gt;Hello Games Shows Off No Man's Sky's New 'Path Finder' Update With Land Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;No Man’s Sky’s Path Finder Update Hello Games is hard at work continuing to try and redeem No Man’s Sky with an ongoing series of free updates that hopefully moves the game closer to what it was originally meant to be. The first “Foundation” update, which added base-building, farming and freighter ships, was meant to set the stage for things to come, and now one of those things has arrived. The new trailer below shows off what’s new in this 1.2 “Path Finder” update. It includes the addition of a permadeath mode, where players try to reach the center of the galaxy in one life. There are doze...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'No Man's Sky' Is A Lesson In How Not To Manage A Post-Launch Crisis - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/10/14/no-mans-sky-is-a-lesson-in-how-not-to-manage-a-post-launch-crisis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL60bQcI0idwpDbUC9P5qjgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 15:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/10/14/no-mans-sky-is-a-lesson-in-how-not-to-manage-a-post-launch-crisis/" target="_blank"&gt;'No Man's Sky' Is A Lesson In How Not To Manage A Post-Launch Crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: Hello Games Two months after the release of No Man’s Sky, Hello Games seems to be doing everything it possibly can to enshrine the fact that their game is going to be hated well into the future. Their total, eerie silence regarding both the issues with the released game, what it did and didn’t deliver, as well as no clear indication of future plans, is cementing the legacy of the troubled title in a way that’s simply a master class in how to not handle a post-launch crisis. While No Man’s Sky is its own unique sort of problem, we see troubled video game launches all the time, from th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>There's Only One Thing That Would Ever Make Me Pick Up 'No Man's Sky' Again - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/11/08/theres-only-one-thing-that-would-ever-make-me-pick-up-no-mans-sky-again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA88yP-nbHw7NSkJwAorNRkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 15:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2016/11/08/theres-only-one-thing-that-would-ever-make-me-pick-up-no-mans-sky-again/" target="_blank"&gt;There's Only One Thing That Would Ever Make Me Pick Up 'No Man's Sky' Again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo: Hello Games) In Max Brooks’ novel, World War Z, he tells dozens of different stories about how various countries around the world reacted to a global zombie menace. The rich of Hollywood, California tear one another apart, while the Queen of England stands strong and lets refugees into her palace. North Korea, meanwhile, disappears completely. Its population filters into mines and tunnels and is never seen or heard from again, even after the war is over. That’s sort of what it seems like happened to Hello Games in the wake of No Man’s Sky. Outside of a few bug patches back in Septem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'No Man's Sky' May Never Be The Game We Wanted, But It Could Still Be Something Great - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2016/11/27/foundation-update-no-mans-sky-may-never-be-the-game-we-wanted-but-it-could-still-be-something-great/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOssKOX04TtVWTly4X_9f_0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 20:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2016/11/27/foundation-update-no-mans-sky-may-never-be-the-game-we-wanted-but-it-could-still-be-something-great/" target="_blank"&gt;'No Man's Sky' May Never Be The Game We Wanted, But It Could Still Be Something Great&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;photo: Hello Games There’s a game out there, at least in our imaginations. It’s the No Man’s Sky that Hello Games trotted out for big shows like The Game Awards and E3: a game about exploration in discovery in a vast, mysterious universe, where the player shot through uncharted territory discovering galaxies and planets awash with strange, beautiful things, no two moments ever the same. What we got tried to emulate this, but never on a scale to make it truly manageable: it was a game about zapping rocks and samey plants while occasionally documenting one of a limited number of variants on t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'No Man's Sky' Developers Have Something To Say After Two Months Of Silence - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2016/11/26/no-mans-sky-developers-have-something-to-say-after-two-months-of-silence/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQkeIX-RLJey2zUdmr6ueEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 08:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2016/11/26/no-mans-sky-developers-have-something-to-say-after-two-months-of-silence/" target="_blank"&gt;'No Man's Sky' Developers Have Something To Say After Two Months Of Silence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Credit: Hello Games/YouTube If video games could have mental health problems, No Man’s Sky would be the poster child for bipolar mood disorder. First came the extraordinary high when No Man’s Sky was presented as Sony’s indie game darling at their E3 stage show in 2014. This was followed by two years of incessant hype when the game’s lead developer Sean Murray seemed to be everywhere, all the time, telling anyone who would listen about all the wonderful things the game was going to have. Players bought into it and the anticipation was intense. Then came the extraordinary low when No Man’s S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>I Would Pay For 'No Man's Sky' DLC - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/02/05/i-would-pay-for-no-mans-sky-dlc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFmpSUjz3TKoggFfrNsWsSAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 15:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2017/02/05/i-would-pay-for-no-mans-sky-dlc/" target="_blank"&gt;I Would Pay For 'No Man's Sky' DLC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo: Paul Tassi/Hello Games As I sit around and wait for new patches and content to come to games like Destiny, The Division, Overwatch, Titanfall and Final Fantasy, there’s one game I really want to see continue to update itself more than most: No Man’s Sky. Yes, it’s the biggest “cautionary tale” of 2016, but despite the game’s (many) flaws, I’ve always been something of an apologist for it. Yes, the game lacks depth and certain features that were promised, but what is there is still pretty cool, and I really quite enjoyed the game’s first major “Foundation” update which added freighter...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'No Man's Sky' Subreddit Goes Full 'Mr. Robot' To Poke Fun At Hello Games - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/10/29/no-mans-sky-subreddit-goes-full-mr-robot-to-poke-fun-at-hello-games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED-L_dH3utNdhKXpy0wUfCIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 21:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2016/10/29/no-mans-sky-subreddit-goes-full-mr-robot-to-poke-fun-at-hello-games/" target="_blank"&gt;'No Man's Sky' Subreddit Goes Full 'Mr. Robot' To Poke Fun At Hello Games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;No Man’s Robot (Credit: Erik Kain/USA/Hello Games) Yesterday morning, the official account of Sean Murray, the creator of No Man’s Sky and Hello Games chief, tweeted: “No Man’s Sky was a mistake.” The tweet was quickly taken down, but what followed was even more bizarre. I inquired as to whether the account had been hacked, and was told by Hello Games via email that it was a disgruntled employee. Other outlets got similar responses, while still others were told that Murray himself had made the tweet. Finally, Murray got back on Twitter and told the world it was a hack after all. But he did ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>It Sure Seems Like 'Fallout 76' Will Be The 'No Man's Sky' Of 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/24/it-sure-seems-like-fallout-76-will-be-the-no-mans-sky-of-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEiT2SaX2vBnXqpGRpI6-2QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/24/it-sure-seems-like-fallout-76-will-be-the-no-mans-sky-of-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;It Sure Seems Like 'Fallout 76' Will Be The 'No Man's Sky' Of 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is Fallout 76 ready for the big leagues? Just before the launch of No Man’s Sky back in August of 2016, Hello Games chief Sean Murray released an open letter to fans. There was something just a tiny bit odd about the note. After all, it opened with this line: I feel sick writing this. You are about to play ‘No Man’s Sky’ and I don’t know what you’ll think. “Believe the hype” this was decidedly not. And sure enough, upon its release the gaming community descended into that place only the gaming community really can: Collective fury, a sense of betrayal, and feckless outrage all mixed into a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'No Man's Sky Next's Galactic Atlas Has Been Enhanced With New And Useful Information - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/09/02/no-mans-sky-nexts-galactic-atlas-has-been-enhanced-with-new-and-useful-information/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELbMmowB7ukkztNAJgK-5Y0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 17:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kevinmurnane/2018/09/02/no-mans-sky-nexts-galactic-atlas-has-been-enhanced-with-new-and-useful-information/" target="_blank"&gt;'No Man's Sky Next's Galactic Atlas Has Been Enhanced With New And Useful Information&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘No Man’s Sky Next’s Galactic Atlas No Man’s Sky’s Galactic Atlas is a website set up by Hello Games that encourages explorers to band together and map out regions in the Euclid Galaxy and share what they find with the wider community of players. It launched with portal addresses for a selection of points of interest Hello Games gathered with a player survey based on the Atlas Rises expansion. Now it’s been greatly enhanced with a cargo hold of new features from No Man’s Sky Next. A new survey invites all Next players to submit planetary points of interest for inclusion in the Atlas. In add...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>No Man's Sky Next review – wider horizons than ever before - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/aug/02/no-mans-sky-next-review-wider-horizons-than-ever-before-hello-games</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFvW2mJFdBMmJD5kllHgG2IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 08:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/aug/02/no-mans-sky-next-review-wider-horizons-than-ever-before-hello-games" target="_blank"&gt;No Man's Sky Next review – wider horizons than ever before&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two-year-old No Man’s Sky is an extraordinary game. Its procedurally generated galaxy has marked it out for inclusion in the forthcoming V&amp;A exhibition Videogames: Design/Play/Disrupt, and developer Hello Games says people have spent more than 200m hours in its near-infinite universe, where every planet and life form is unique. But No Man’s Sky’s has a lingering reputation as a game that failed to live up to expectations when it was launched. Hello Games has methodically introduced free features to what was initially a shallow game. The Foundation update added new modes (Creative and Su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>No Man’s Sky developer Sean Murray: ‘It was as bad as things can get’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/jul/20/no-mans-sky-next-hello-games-sean-murray-harassment-interview</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELX1pFnG2TH9JFBfWssdi6gqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 11:00:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/jul/20/no-mans-sky-next-hello-games-sean-murray-harassment-interview" target="_blank"&gt;No Man’s Sky developer Sean Murray: ‘It was as bad as things can get’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sean Murray does not like talking to the press. He says this several times when we meet at the Guildford offices of Hello Games, the development studio he founded in 2008 with Grant Duncan, Ryan Doyle and David Ream. He is loquacious, but nervous. No one at the studio has spoken to any journalists for nearly two years, since the release of Murray’s pet project No Man’s Sky, an extraordinarily ambitious space exploration game that aimed to put an infinite universe on a games console – a game that, when it didn’t meet some players’ high expectations, triggered an appalling internet harassment...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>What Is 'No Man's Sky Next'? Here's Everything You Need To Know - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/07/18/what-is-no-mans-sky-next-heres-everything-you-need-to-know/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDCw4cGU0_BumrWnHw1YoZ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/07/18/what-is-no-mans-sky-next-heres-everything-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank"&gt;What Is 'No Man's Sky Next'? Here's Everything You Need To Know&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;No Man’s Sky’s biggest expansion so far, Next, is coming soon. No Man’s Sky launched in August of 2016 to scathing reviews and mystified customers. The much ballyhooed game felt to many like an unfinished product—something you’d expect to be in Early Access rather than a full-priced release. Now, nearly two years later, Hello Games is aiming to win back the faith of the gaming community with its largest free update to the game so far: No Man’s Sky Next. So what is ‘Next’ anyways? Below, find everything you need to know about the expansion—from release date to major changes to the brand new ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Two Years Later, 'No Man's Sky' Is Finally Getting True Multiplayer In Its 'NEXT' Update - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/05/18/two-years-later-no-mans-sky-is-finally-getting-true-multiplayer-in-its-next-update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG8lPN7HmI0-INQPQhBQ_dsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/05/18/two-years-later-no-mans-sky-is-finally-getting-true-multiplayer-in-its-next-update/" target="_blank"&gt;Two Years Later, 'No Man's Sky' Is Finally Getting True Multiplayer In Its 'NEXT' Update&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;No Man’s Sky Of the many broken promises in the aftermath of the launch of No Man’s Sky, one that players would never stop bringing up was Sean Murray’s pre-launch statement that the game would let you run into other people out in the galaxy. When it was released, the ability to play with your friends or run into other players was nowhere to be found, but now, that’s about to change, almost two years later. July 24th brings both No Man’s Sky to Xbox One, and also its big NEXT update, which Hello Games promises is the largest one for the game to date. Chief among the new additions is going t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>'No Man's Sky' Is Coming To Xbox One And Getting Another Big Free Update - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/03/29/no-mans-sky-is-coming-to-xbox-one-and-getting-another-big-free-update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC0Kspn0-u1dT_iYpoOg1SsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 14:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/insertcoin/2018/03/29/no-mans-sky-is-coming-to-xbox-one-and-getting-another-big-free-update/" target="_blank"&gt;'No Man's Sky' Is Coming To Xbox One And Getting Another Big Free Update&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;No Man’s Sky At long last, whatever Faustian bargain Hello Games had with Sony appears to be fully dissolved, and No Man’s Sky will soon becoming to Xbox One, thanks to distribution from 505 Games. The announcement was made today, along with “No Man’s Sky Next,” which appears to be the working title of a new, big update for the game slated to hit in 2018, as Hello Games continues to toil to right wrongs and expand the game into what everyone had hoped it would be originally. No Man’s Sky is still a name that will make people wince, like when I compared Sea of Thieves to it recently, but in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item></channel></rss>