<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Rudy Giuliani - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFpuYmpjU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-AU&amp;gl=AU&amp;ceid=AU:en</link><language>en-AU</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:43:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Rudy Giuliani blamed Twitter for his tweet calling Donald Trump a 'traitor'. Here's why he's wrong - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-06/giuliani-blames-twitter-for-his-tweet-calling-trump-a-traitor/10588934</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780125431861</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:02:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-06/giuliani-blames-twitter-for-his-tweet-calling-trump-a-traitor/10588934" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy Giuliani blamed Twitter for his tweet calling Donald Trump a 'traitor'. Here's why he's wrong&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6467691/Rudy-says-getting-Trump-answer-Muellers-written-questions-nightmare.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy says getting Trump to answer Mueller's written questions was 'a nightmare'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Daily Mail&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.smh.com.au/world/north-america/rudy-giuliani-s-typo-became-an-anti-trump-message-thanks-to-this-prankster-20181206-p50kh2.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy Giuliani's typo became an anti-Trump message thanks to this prankster&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Sydney Morning Herald&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.news.com.au/technology/online/social/trump-is-a-traitor-fury-as-twitter-prank-sees-antipresident-website-go-viral/news-story/10ca7be48f7cec1eedad44fba2bac590" target="_blank"&gt;Donald Trump traitor website goes viral after Rudy Giuliani Twitter typo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;NEWS.com.au&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/05/rudy-giuliani-helps-create-anti-trump-protest-website-with-twitter-typo" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy Giuliani Twitter typo sparks anti-Trump protest website&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWkxMElLbGpZQU1FYktPVnY5dkp0VFVLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani: Feds 'F*cking' Angry With 'Pathetic' Michael Cohen - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rudy-giuliani-feds-fcking-angry-wiith-pathetic-michael-cohen</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM1ZDImT7pSVeRGVIt46DbQqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:06:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/rudy-giuliani-feds-fcking-angry-wiith-pathetic-michael-cohen" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy Giuliani: Feds 'F*cking' Angry With 'Pathetic' Michael Cohen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alex Wong/Getty President Trump’s lawyer Rudy Giuliani told The Daily Beast the most recent court documents on Trump's former personal attorney Michael Cohen were “pathetic.” Giuliani said they indicate the feds are “fucking angry with” Cohen and want to put him in prison “for four years.” Cohen, said Giuliani, “believe me, can’t handle jail.” Giuliani added that he felt “sorry for him” and described Cohen's situation and his behavior as a “sad” attempt to avoid prison time. In a memo Friday, prosecutors recommended “substantial” prison time for Cohen, who they say made hush-money payments ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Giuliani’s Report Will Hit All Of Trump’s Favorite Fox News Conspiracy Theory Villains - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/rudy-giuliani-mueller-report_us_5c0ab85ce4b035a7bf5aefdc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwclRgs9NzDLdYKi8Y0DJMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:24:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/rudy-giuliani-mueller-report_us_5c0ab85ce4b035a7bf5aefdc" target="_blank"&gt;Giuliani’s Report Will Hit All Of Trump’s Favorite Fox News Conspiracy Theory Villains&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― Donald Trump’s legal team has prepared a response to Robert Mueller’s probe that features the president’s favorite conspiracy-theory villains, from Peter Strzok and his lover to those who financed a dossier that Trump falsely claims sparked the investigation against him. Strzok, Lisa Page, Bruce and Nellie Ohr, Christopher Steele and Hillary Clinton’s campaign lawyers will all be covered in the report, which Trump boasted was “already 87 pages” in a tweet Friday morning. When asked Friday whether the report would attack the various players involved in the investigation, Trump a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Giuliani says Mueller has accused Manafort of lying about Trump - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/giuliani-mueller-manafort-lying/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH8yYQWu1j6j_8uqB1MswWsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:12:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/giuliani-mueller-manafort-lying/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Giuliani says Mueller has accused Manafort of lying about Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller's team has made clear to Paul Manafort's attorneys that they believe the former Trump campaign chair is lying to them about President Donald Trump, according to the President's attorney Rudy Giuliani. "In the questioning of Manafort, they did tell them at the time that they believed he was lying about certain things related to us that he's not lying about," Giuliani told CNN. Mueller's team will describe to a federal court on Friday the alleged lies told by Manafort that led to the disruption of the cooperation agreement. The filing will be closely read for an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump reveals 87-page response to Mueller findings already created, despite no Russia probe report released yet - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-mueller-investigation-russia-report-response-twitter-rudy-giuliani-a8672386.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPN9LFx6mjYniU7mZ8xt85wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 13:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-mueller-investigation-russia-report-response-twitter-rudy-giuliani-a8672386.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump reveals 87-page response to Mueller findings already created, despite no Russia probe report released yet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has revealed an 87-page response to Robert Mueller's investigation has already been compiled by his lawyer, despite the special counsel not having released a report on his findings yet. The president followed up a barrage of detailed and often misspelled early morning tweets about the wide-ranging probe with a post that said: "It has been incorrectly reported that Rudy Giuliani and others will not be doing a counter to the Mueller Report. "That is Fake News. Already 87 pages done, but obviously cannot complete until we see the final Witch Hunt Report." In a bellicose stream of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Giuliani: Mueller accused Manafort of lying - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/giuliani-mueller-manafort-lying-brooke-baldwin-cunningham-nr-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECQ6Vh2VWEmjXNTeEEtAFYUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:08:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/giuliani-mueller-manafort-lying-brooke-baldwin-cunningham-nr-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Giuliani: Mueller accused Manafort of lying&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller's team has made clear to Paul Manafort's attorneys that they believe the former Trump campaign chair is lying to them about President Donald Trump, according to the President's attorney Rudy Giuliani. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Seth Meyers Roasts Rudy Giuliani’s ‘Terrible’ Twitter Fail - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/seth-meyers-roasts-rudy-giulianis-terrible-twitter-fail</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGUm54ZfmMX88onlcn37qgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:28:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/seth-meyers-roasts-rudy-giulianis-terrible-twitter-fail" target="_blank"&gt;Seth Meyers Roasts Rudy Giuliani’s ‘Terrible’ Twitter Fail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NBC During his latest “A Closer Look” segment Thursday night, Seth Meyers took a detour from breaking down new developments in the Russia investigation to check in on his old friend Rudy Giuliani. The Late Night host noted that as Donald Trump’s lawyer, Giuliani tried to argue this week that Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s sentencing memo for Michael Flynn was actually good news for the president. “Although I really can’t follow his logic or his syntax,” Meyers said, pointing to an incoherent text message Giuliani sent to a Politico reporter this week. “Wow big crime for a SPECIAL WHATEVER...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani Calls Getting Trump Through Robert Mueller's Questions 'A Nightmare' - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/giuliani-trump-mueller-questions-nightmare_us_5c097190e4b04046345a3181</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDEkU2YLSATTvEJ3VQHgQwcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:07:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/giuliani-trump-mueller-questions-nightmare_us_5c097190e4b04046345a3181" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy Giuliani Calls Getting Trump Through Robert Mueller's Questions 'A Nightmare'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The process of getting President Donald Trump to answer special counsel Robert Mueller’s questions concerning the ongoing investigation into Russian interference in the U.S. elections was “a nightmare,” according to the president’s lawyer Rudy Giuliani. “It took him about three weeks to do what would normally take two days,” Giuliani told The Atlantic in an interview published Thursday. In November, the president addressed the topic of the special counsel’s questions, telling reporters that he “was asked a series of questions” and that he “answered them very easily.” Trump’s legal team subm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Internet Users Are Finding Creative Ways To Mess With Giuliani's Old Tweets - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/giuliani-tweet-pranksters-collusion_us_5c0950c1e4b069028dc7a12d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcgsM1MqvSVzU9CrpQh7aAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:41:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/giuliani-tweet-pranksters-collusion_us_5c0950c1e4b069028dc7a12d" target="_blank"&gt;Internet Users Are Finding Creative Ways To Mess With Giuliani's Old Tweets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One day, Rudolph Giuliani will learn to add spaces when he writes sentences on social media. Until then, Donald Trump’s attorney will have to deal with internet users messing with his tweets. On Friday, Giuliani took to Twitter to angrily criticize Robert Mueller. Mueller filed an indictment just as the President left for https://t.co/8ZNrQ6X29a July he indicted the Russians who will never come here just before he left for Helsinki.Either could have been done earlier or later. Out of control!Supervision please? — Rudy Giuliani (@RudyGiuliani) November 30, 2018 But a typo in the former New ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Prosecutors: Illegal hush-money paid at Trump's 'direction' - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f47819630d1045768a8fe9c68054c676</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIoUy6c1EWzNrQj1ItRseUIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:18:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f47819630d1045768a8fe9c68054c676" target="_blank"&gt;Prosecutors: Illegal hush-money paid at Trump's 'direction'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department says that President Donald Trump directed illegal payments to buy the silence of two women whose claims of extramarital affairs threatened his presidential campaign, the first time prosecutors have connected Trump to a federal crime. In a court filing, prosecutors said former Trump lawyer and fixer Michael Cohen arranged the secret payments at the height of the 2016 campaign "in coordination with and at the direction of" Trump. Cohen has previously said Trump was involved in the hush-money scheme, but court documents filed ahead of Cohen's sentencing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump lashes out at Russia probe ahead of expected new details - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-rosenstein/trump-lashes-out-at-russia-probe-ahead-of-expected-new-details-idUSKBN1O61BO</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEekHG4lFzMHUtpGo-U3JfoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:12:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-rosenstein/trump-lashes-out-at-russia-probe-ahead-of-expected-new-details-idUSKBN1O61BO" target="_blank"&gt;Trump lashes out at Russia probe ahead of expected new details&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Trump on Friday lashed out at Special Counsel Robert Mueller's investigation into possible collusion between Russia and Trump's 2016 election campaign, and suggested Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein had a conflict of interest without offering any evidence. Trump's series of early morning tweets came ahead of the expected filing of legal documents on Friday that could shed more light on how two of Trump's closest former aides have helped or hindered Mueller's Russia probe. Representatives for the U.S. Department of Justice declined to comment on the Trump tweets. In a la...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Prankster Mocks Another Giuliani Twitter Typo - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/prankster-mocks-another-giuliani-twitter-typo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKlfoVSASxyaNUyik0F4-T4qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:11:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/prankster-mocks-another-giuliani-twitter-typo" target="_blank"&gt;Prankster Mocks Another Giuliani Twitter Typo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alex Wong/Getty, Just two days after Trump lawyer Rudy Giuliani accidentally posted a link in one of his tweets—which a clever prankster bought and directed to an anti-Trump site—another typo in an older tweet was redirected to a law blog about the Mueller investigation. On September 15, Giuliani tweeted “#REALNEWS: Woodward says no evidence of collusion.So does Manafort’s team. Mueller can investigate endlessly and he will find no evidence. The only conspiracy, using criminal means, is the campaign to stop and then remove President Trump.” But he forgot to put a space between “collusion” a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Trump's cybersecurity adviser Rudy Giuliani blames Twitter after embarrassing typo - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/06/trumps-cybersecurity-adviser-rudy-giuliani-blames-twitter-embarrassing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE5UAvL2lZmdVWPtxYnOXIsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/12/06/trumps-cybersecurity-adviser-rudy-giuliani-blames-twitter-embarrassing/" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's cybersecurity adviser Rudy Giuliani blames Twitter after embarrassing typo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rudy Giuliani, the former Republican presidential nominee who is advising President Trump on cyber security, has mistakenly accused Twitter of linking one of his tweets to "a disgusting anti-President message" after a typo in one of his tweets led to a prank. Mr Giuliani failed to insert a space in between two sentences in a tweet he posted last week. When used in a tweet, a full stop in between two words is automatically turned into a hyperlink. Shortly after the tweet was published, an enterprising internet user took advantage of the situation to purchase the web domain from the typo: “G...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani Says Twitter Sabotaged His Tweet. Actually, He Did It Himself. - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/05/us/politics/rudy-giuliani-twitter-links.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKWguhUEM-jQuVDyA_tDD1QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 23:59:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/05/us/politics/rudy-giuliani-twitter-links.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy Giuliani Says Twitter Sabotaged His Tweet. Actually, He Did It Himself.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;To Rudolph W. Giuliani, the former New York mayor who is one of President Trump’s lawyers, it was an example of how low Twitter would stoop to carry out its anti-Trump agenda. It was, decidedly, no such thing. It was just a typo, followed by an opportunistic prank by an improv actor in Atlanta. In a tweet on Tuesday, Mr. Giuliani said the social network had “allowed someone to invade my text with a disgusting anti-President message.” He was referring to a Nov. 30 tweet in which Mr. Giuliani — by failing to put a space after a period, and starting the next sentence with the word “In” — had i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Michael Cohen Was Paid More Than $4 Million by Promising Access to Trump, Prosecutors Say - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-cohen-was-paid-more-than-dollar4-million-by-promising-access-to-trump-prosecutors-say</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDtL46z2tib49HO-0iAi3D8qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:13:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-cohen-was-paid-more-than-dollar4-million-by-promising-access-to-trump-prosecutors-say" target="_blank"&gt;Michael Cohen Was Paid More Than $4 Million by Promising Access to Trump, Prosecutors Say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drew Angerer Federal prosecutors on Friday provided new details on the extent of former Donald Trump fixer Michael Cohen’s attempts to cash in on his access to President Trump, detailing more than $4 million that Cohen extracted from major corporations in return for his supposed insight into White House policy making. According to prosecutors, Cohen, who has pleaded guilty to eight federal criminal charges, immediately sought to monetize his connections to Trump in the wake of his former boss’ 2016 election victory. “Cohen successfully convinced numerous major corporations to retain him as ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Whoops, Rudy Giuliani: Your tweet indirectly called President Trump a traitor - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/whoops-rudy-giuliani-your-tweet-indirectly-called-president-trump-a-traitor-2018-12-03</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM7NBl38znPv6ISP4Z85JH8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 13:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/whoops-rudy-giuliani-your-tweet-indirectly-called-president-trump-a-traitor-2018-12-03" target="_blank"&gt;Whoops, Rudy Giuliani: Your tweet indirectly called President Trump a traitor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE MARGIN By Shawn Langlois Update: Giuliani blames Twitter, the company He’s Donald Trump, and he did not approve Rudy Giuliani’s message. Reuters Rudy Giuliani on Friday tweeted out what seemed a typical missive from the Trump camp aimed at Robert Mueller and his investigation into Russia’s alleged cyberattack on the 2016 election: See tweet embed What wasn’t so typical was the link in the tweet. If you click the “G-20.In” — a hyperlink created by Giuliani’s omission of spaces after the terminal punctuation marks in his tweet, presumably to make room for more typographical characters — i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Retro Report: For Shame: A Brief History of the Perp Walk - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/02/us/perp-walk.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF06-41llx2RNhLtRGGjP34qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 23:30:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/02/us/perp-walk.html" target="_blank"&gt;Retro Report: For Shame: A Brief History of the Perp Walk&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parading the accused and the condemned before the citizenry is an age-old tactic used by those holding power. The most famous example goes back some 2,000 years, when a Jewish preacher from Nazareth was forced to trudge painfully to Calvary. William Wallace, the Scottish independence leader, experienced it being dragged through London before his execution in 1305. French monarchists, during the revolution, endured it as well in the tumbrels carrying them to the guillotine. That sort of public shaming has not disappeared, even if conducted in 21st-century America with less brutality. The mod...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Trump aide Rudy Giuliani lashes out at Twitter as he tries to blame site for his own embarrassing mistake - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/trump-rudy-giuliani-twitter-tweet-g20-in-post-conspiracy-theory-a8667931.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEORCAZijv-tvjaZjHqhry5MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/trump-rudy-giuliani-twitter-tweet-g20-in-post-conspiracy-theory-a8667931.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump aide Rudy Giuliani lashes out at Twitter as he tries to blame site for his own embarrassing mistake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rudy Giuliani, one of Donald Trump's closest aides, has posted a bizarre and angry tweet after falling victim to a prank. Mr Giuliani, who served as the president's lawyer and also his cybersecurity advisor, suggested that Twitter had pulled a trick on him because they dislike Mr Trump. But nothing of the sort happened, and Mr Giuliani actually appears to have tricked himself. Now he appears to be spreading conspiracy theories about Twitter in an attempt to deflect from that mistake. Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 42 show all Gadgets and tech news in pictures - 1/42 5G wireless interne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani Goes Full Conspiracy Theory Because He Doesn't Understand The Internet - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/rudy-giuliani-twitter-conspiracy-theory_us_5c079cb5e4b0fc23611189e9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBm0TrrkkPlfzgLslQ-agPoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 11:35:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/rudy-giuliani-twitter-conspiracy-theory_us_5c079cb5e4b0fc23611189e9" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy Giuliani Goes Full Conspiracy Theory Because He Doesn't Understand The Internet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rudy Giuliani pushed out a conspiracy theory about Twitter on Tuesday because he apparently doesn’t know how the internet works. The saga began before the weekend when Giuliani, who is President Donald Trump’s lawyer and adviser on cybersecurity issues, inadvertently created a URL with this typo-ridden tweet: Mueller filed an indictment just as the President left for https://t.co/8ZNrQ6X29a July he indicted the Russians who will never come here just before he left for Helsinki.Either could have been done earlier or later. Out of control!Supervision please? — Rudy Giuliani (@RudyGiuliani) No...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Paul Manafort's Nonstop Lying May Have Done Robert Mueller A Huge Favor - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-paul-manafort-mueller-trump-lying_us_5bfed363e4b0388c1770ac83</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGY2a8YmSpGHCX16SXyb5DgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:21:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-paul-manafort-mueller-trump-lying_us_5bfed363e4b0388c1770ac83" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Manafort's Nonstop Lying May Have Done Robert Mueller A Huge Favor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After lying to the IRS and lying to banks and then asking witnesses to lie to the government, former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort also lied to prosecutors when he was supposed to be cooperating as part of a plea deal, special counsel Robert Muelleralleged on Monday. In a status report presented in the former Trump campaign manager’s criminal case, Mueller’s team asserted that, in spite of a plea deal promising to cooperate truthfully and forthrightly, “Manafort committed federal crimes by lying to the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the Special Counsel’s Office on a variety of s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>The frantic scramble before Mueller got the job - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/rosenstein-comey-firing-obstruction-probe/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECTi0a6RJku05hAuMKBLcgYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:32:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/06/politics/rosenstein-comey-firing-obstruction-probe/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The frantic scramble before Mueller got the job&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the hectic eight days after President Donald Trump fired FBI Director James Comey, Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein and top FBI officials viewed Trump as a leader who needed to be reined in, according to two sources describing the sentiment at the time. They discussed a range of options, including the idea of Rosenstein wearing a wire while speaking with Trump, which Rosenstein later denied. Ultimately, then-acting FBI Director Andrew McCabe took the extraordinary step of opening an obstruction of justice investigation even before special counsel Robert Mueller was appointed, the s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump Kept Praising Michael Flynn, Only Now Robert Mueller Is Praising Him Too - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-michael-flynn-robert-mueller_us_5c084e4ee4b0844cda4fa488</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBIZu3PXI_o-QrqXKzq4X1AqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 23:07:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-michael-flynn-robert-mueller_us_5c084e4ee4b0844cda4fa488" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Kept Praising Michael Flynn, Only Now Robert Mueller Is Praising Him Too&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON — President Donald Trump’s repeated praise for his first national security adviser as a good man who was treated badly by prosecutors appears to have ended, now that special counsel Robert Mueller is praising him. Mueller revealed Tuesday night that he is recommending that retired Army Gen. Michael Flynn serve no jail time because of his “substantial assistance” in various investigations regarding Trump and his dealings with Russia. Just a day earlier, Trump lauded a former business and campaign adviser for refusing to cooperate with prosecutors: “Nice to know that some people st...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>John Dean: Giuliani might be deluding Trump - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/06/john-dean-trump-rudy-giuliani-michael-flynn-mueller-filing-ctn-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELWWjYpWEFqPLdxvlitcmHcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:34:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/06/john-dean-trump-rudy-giuliani-michael-flynn-mueller-filing-ctn-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;John Dean: Giuliani might be deluding Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Nixon White House counsel John Dean says that President Trump's lawyer Rudy Giuliani may be deluding his client by dismissing special counsel Robert Mueller's court filing revealing the cooperation of Trump's former national security adviser Michael Flynn in the Russia investigation. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Manafort accused of lying to Mueller probe, blowing up plea deal - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort-idUSKCN1NW00Z</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJQ6aRom-lVELeCpRdrahH0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 02:41:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort-idUSKCN1NW00Z" target="_blank"&gt;Manafort accused of lying to Mueller probe, blowing up plea deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort breached his plea deal by lying to federal investigators, according to a court filing on Monday, in a potential setback to the special counsel's probe into Russia's meddling in the 2016 U.S. presidential election. Manafort said in the same filing that he disagreed with Special Counsel Robert Mueller's assertion that he had lied, but both sides agreed the impasse meant that the court should move ahead and sentence him for his crimes. Without a pardon, Manafort could spend the rest of his life in prison, experts said. The surprise developm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Harold O. Levy, Progressive New York City Schools Chief, Dies at 65 - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/27/obituaries/harold-levy-dead.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEByl_QYNBzriMgN9N8Qwvj0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwl4YY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 22:06:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/27/obituaries/harold-levy-dead.html" target="_blank"&gt;Harold O. Levy, Progressive New York City Schools Chief, Dies at 65&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Correction: November 29, 2018 This article has been revised to reflect the following correction: An earlier version of this obituary misstated the given name of Mr. Levy’s father. He was Hugo Levy, not Hugh. Harold O. Levy, who as the chancellor of New York City’s vast public school system from 2000 to 2002 waged war on its bureaucracy, created specialized high schools and attracted thousands of new teachers by insisting on higher starting wages, died on Tuesday at his home in Manhattan. He was 65. His wife, Pat Sapinsley, said the cause was amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, known as Lou Gehri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Trump sends finished written answers to Mueller - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/20/politics/trump-mueller-questions-done/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGYRMoJuHxwEvtWaaqEyh0IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:50:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/20/politics/trump-mueller-questions-done/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump sends finished written answers to Mueller&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump on Tuesday submitted written answers to questions from special counsel Robert Mueller related to the investigation of possible collusion between Trump associates and Russians. The responses from the President signify a major development in the Mueller probe following months of negotiations between the special counsel's office and Trump's legal team, and could be a sign of the end stages of the investigation. Trump told reporters before boarding Marine One to travel to Mar-a-Lago in Florida that he finished the written answers on Monday and provided them to his lawyers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Originator Of The Trump Penthouse For Putin Idea Says He Doesn't Know How Far It Went - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/felix-sater-donald-trump-michael-cohen-moscow-tower_us_5c05a549e4b07aec57519c5e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM6VQBUMoNGcxhDWKVNcDNgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 23:33:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/felix-sater-donald-trump-michael-cohen-moscow-tower_us_5c05a549e4b07aec57519c5e" target="_blank"&gt;Originator Of The Trump Penthouse For Putin Idea Says He Doesn't Know How Far It Went&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― The originator of the idea of giving Vladimir Putin a free $50 million penthouse in a proposed Trump Tower in Moscow said Monday he has no idea if the plan was ever presented to the Russian ruler or his associates. Felix Sater, who at the time was a “senior adviser” to then-presidential candidate Donald Trump, also downplayed its significance, calling it a mere marketing concept in an early stage of the project. “This was a marketing conversation. No more, no less,” he told HuffPost, describing his late 2015 meeting with Trump lawyer Michael Cohen. “The whole thing was a very p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump told Mueller he had no prior knowledge of 2016 Trump Tower meeting: Giuliani - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-meeting/trump-told-mueller-he-had-no-prior-knowledge-of-2016-trump-tower-meeting-giuliani-idUSKCN1NX2RU</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENg2LUBpnYfOPq8vCWa2lAIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 21:57:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-meeting/trump-told-mueller-he-had-no-prior-knowledge-of-2016-trump-tower-meeting-giuliani-idUSKCN1NX2RU" target="_blank"&gt;Trump told Mueller he had no prior knowledge of 2016 Trump Tower meeting: Giuliani&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump told the special counsel investigating possible collusion between his campaign and Russia that he was not aware ahead of time of a meeting in June 2016 between campaign officials and Russians, Trump attorney Rudy Giuliani said on Wednesday. Trump's response, in written answers to questions posed by Special Counsel Robert Mueller, was first reported by CNN. "Almost all the answers he gave are consistent with what he said publicly, and publicly he said he did not know about it," Giuliani said. Trump's oldest son, Donald Trump Jr., has said he agreed to the meeting ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump Answers Mueller’s Questions on Russian Interference - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/us/politics/trump-mueller-questions-answers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBoZxro7TysQeXC6BaFzPpAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 23:59:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/20/us/politics/trump-mueller-questions-answers.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Answers Mueller’s Questions on Russian Interference&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON — President Trump laid out for the special counsel his defense in the investigation into possible ties between his associates and Russia’s election interference, the president’s lawyers said in a statement on Tuesday. The details of Mr. Trump’s responses were not immediately clear, but his lawyers said that now that he had handed over answers to questions from the special counsel, Robert S. Mueller III, the time had come to end the investigation. “The special counsel has been provided with more than 30 witnesses, 1.4 million pages of material, and now the president’s written resp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Ex-Trump lawyer Michael Cohen pleads guilty to lying over Russia investigation - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ex-trump-lawyer-michael-cohen-pleads-guilty-to-lying-over-russia-investigation-2018-11-29</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEENVb3rRDmUCGAtZsoqQ7O4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 20:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ex-trump-lawyer-michael-cohen-pleads-guilty-to-lying-over-russia-investigation-2018-11-29" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-Trump lawyer Michael Cohen pleads guilty to lying over Russia investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Steve Goldstein Trump calls Cohen a ‘weak person’ trying to get a reduced sentence Michael Cohen, former personal attorney to Trump, exits federal court Thursday in New York City. At the court hearing, Cohen pleaded guilty to making false statements to Congress about a Moscow real-estate project Trump pursued during the 2016 presidential campaign. Getty Images The former personal attorney to President Donald Trump on Thursday pleaded guilty to lying about the Russia investigation. Michael Cohen pleaded guilty in a Manhattan court to misleading Congress about the investigation into whethe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Mueller may not be done questioning Trump over obstruction, says Giuliani - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/robert-mueller-donald-trump-rudy-giuliani-russia-investigation-special-counsel-questions-a8647036.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDx3Wv_xIssIwRYNB6JtmpcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 17:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/robert-mueller-donald-trump-rudy-giuliani-russia-investigation-special-counsel-questions-a8647036.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller may not be done questioning Trump over obstruction, says Giuliani&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump’s lawyer has admitted Robert Mueller may seek fresh answers from the US president over alleged obstruction of justice. Rudy Giuliani told CNN further questions for Mr Trump were “not on the table, but could be put back on the table” after the president submitted written answers to queries from the special counsel earlier this week. The president answered questions surrounding alleged collusion between Russia and the Trump team during the 2016 presidential campaign, but refused to answer questions about issues of obstruction while in office, citing executive privilege. Read more...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Cohen believed Trump would pardon him, but then things changed - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/politics/michael-cohen-pardon-expectation-donald-trump/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECD8cIRt-psjduAWMW5TmYQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 20:32:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/politics/michael-cohen-pardon-expectation-donald-trump/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cohen believed Trump would pardon him, but then things changed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Cohen, the former personal attorney for President Donald Trump who is now a key witness in special counsel Robert Mueller's Russia investigation, was under the impression Trump would offer him a pardon in exchange for staying on message in support of the President in discussions with federal prosecutors, according to two sources. After a March 2018 visit to Mar-a-Lago, the President's private club in Florida, Cohen returned to New York believing that his former boss would protect him if he faced any charges for sticking to his story about the 2016 payments to adult film actress Stor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Giuliani Says Trump Doesn't Know If Paul Manafort Met With WikiLeaks’ Julian Assange - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/paul-manafort-julian-assange-giuliani_us_5bfd975ae4b03b230fa7b70d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP7hy1elhiWz6iRYqIGHETcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 21:26:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/paul-manafort-julian-assange-giuliani_us_5bfd975ae4b03b230fa7b70d" target="_blank"&gt;Giuliani Says Trump Doesn't Know If Paul Manafort Met With WikiLeaks’ Julian Assange&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― President Donald Trump does not know whether his former campaign chairman ever met with Julian Assange before Assange released stolen emails in an effort to help him win the presidency, Trump’s lawyer said Tuesday. “I have no idea if Paul Manafort met with Julian Assange. The president has no idea if Paul Manafort met with Julian Assange,” Rudy Giuliani told HuffPost, adding that it wouldn’t prove anything nefarious even if Manafort had done so. “I don’t care if he met Assange over the years. I know there were no conversations between the president and Manafort about Assange.” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump’s Recall of Moscow Deal Matches Cohen’s, President’s Lawyers Say - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/29/us/politics/trump-cohen-moscow-trump-tower.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGO0R_ORepw0yW8PFgn6t5YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww9oEY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:45:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/29/us/politics/trump-cohen-moscow-trump-tower.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump’s Recall of Moscow Deal Matches Cohen’s, President’s Lawyers Say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest criminal charges against Michael D. Cohen, President Trump’s longtime fixer, for lying about a Moscow hotel deal raised questions of whether Mr. Cohen created new legal risks for Mr. Trump or his family members, possibly by contradicting what they told investigators about the same project. The answer, at least according to the president’s lawyers and people close to his family, is no. Although Mr. Trump’s lawyers have long worried that the special counsel, Robert S. Mueller III, is trying to catch Mr. Trump in a lie, they said Mr. Cohen’s new account of the Trump Organization’s a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Mueller starts to piece together Russia puzzle in most significant move yet - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/politics/donald-trump-michael-cohen-robert-mueller/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAxZqrZ7jy7cBNI9S-KGWdkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:15:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/politics/donald-trump-michael-cohen-robert-mueller/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller starts to piece together Russia puzzle in most significant move yet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Silent for so long, Robert Mueller is beginning to show the public the building blocks of a case that could imperil Donald Trump's presidency. In the process, the special counsel is beginning to expose the lies and obfuscations that people around Trump, and the President himself, erected to try to hide multiple, unexplained ties to Russians in, and before, 2016. He is offering implicit explanations along the way for the President's oddly solicitous relationship with Russian President Vladimir Putin. And Mueller is now crossing a red line Trump once warned could prompt his firing -- by probi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump submits answers to Robert Mueller questions in Russia probe - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-russia-probe-mueller-questions-fbi-rudy-giuliani-answers-a8643966.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI83oMA2pUUmBNYUaQK9qwEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-russia-probe-mueller-questions-fbi-rudy-giuliani-answers-a8643966.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump submits answers to Robert Mueller questions in Russia probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has submitted written answers to questions from Special Counsel Robert Mueller as part of the probe into Russian meddling in the 2016 election and possible collusion with the Trump campaign. “We answered every question they asked that was legitimately pre-election and focused on Russia,” Trump lawyer Rudy Giuliani said in an interview. “Nothing post-election. And we've told them we're not going to do that.” Mr Giuliani said Trump did not plan to answer any questions from Mr Mueller on whether he tried to obstruct the investigation once he won office, such as by firing former FB...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani: There is 'no contradiction' between Cohen and Trump responses to Mueller - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/politics/giuliani-cohen-response/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEdysS4ezsXu-_IHHms91H4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:54:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/politics/giuliani-cohen-response/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy Giuliani: There is 'no contradiction' between Cohen and Trump responses to Mueller&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rudy Giuliani said Thursday the latest revelations on Michael Cohen misleading Congress about his business dealings with Russia during the 2016 campaign on behalf of the Trump Organization have "no contradiction" to what President Donald Trump has already said to special counsel Robert Mueller's team. Giuliani, the former New York mayor who currently serves as Trump's lawyer, said Mueller did ask about the proposed Trump Tower Moscow deal, which Cohen had previously said had ended in January 2016 ahead of the Iowa caucuses. When asked about Trump's knowledge of the business deal at the time...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Michael Cohen Thought President Trump Would Pardon Him, But Changed His Mind - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-cohen-thought-president-trump-would-pardon-him-but-changed-his-mind</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMkb_vPYAi2NJ0Iq06le1WIqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 17:28:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-cohen-thought-president-trump-would-pardon-him-but-changed-his-mind" target="_blank"&gt;Michael Cohen Thought President Trump Would Pardon Him, But Changed His Mind&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Kelly/REUTERS, Former President Trump lawyer Michael Cohen, now a main witness in special counsel Robert Mueller’s Russian investigation, once thought that his former boss would pardon him if he stayed loyal, according to CNN. In March 2018, after returning to New York City from Trump’s Mar-a-Lago club in South Florida, Cohen thought the President would protect him from federal prosecutors if he stayed on message. In the wake of the April 2018 FBI raid on his office, Trump’s cronies promised Cohen he would be OK, one source told CNN. Cohen and Trump’s attorneys even had a “legal def...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Trump and Jerome Corsi Have a Defense Agreement, Giuliani Confirms - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-and-jerome-corsi-have-a-defense-agreement-giuliani-confirms</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEONNp6GNqOCNA26C-FF7mGoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 14:25:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-and-jerome-corsi-have-a-defense-agreement-giuliani-confirms" target="_blank"&gt;Trump and Jerome Corsi Have a Defense Agreement, Giuliani Confirms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shannon Stapleton.Reuters President Donald Trump, who built his political rise on promoting far-right birther claims against President Barack Obama, does in fact have a joint defense agreement with leading birther conspiracy theorist Jerome Corsi, The Daily Beast has confirmed. Rudy Giuliani, Trump’s attorney handling special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation, said in a brief phone interview morning that the joint defense agreement that Corsi had earlier claimed existed does actually exist. Giuliani said he confirmed this with Jane Raskin, another member of the Trump legal team, adding...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani tells CNN that Mueller is not done with seeking answers from Trump - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/21/politics/rudy-giuliani-robert-mueller/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG9xF1Mc1Dbjc-k5K2A8v64qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 17:10:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/21/politics/rudy-giuliani-robert-mueller/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy Giuliani tells CNN that Mueller is not done with seeking answers from Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump's lawyer Rudy Giuliani said Wednesday that special counsel Robert Mueller could still try to seek additional answers from Trump on questions of potential obstruction of justice, but he signaled they will fight any questions they believe violate executive privilege. "It's not on the table, but could be put back on the table," Giuliani told CNN of obstruction questions. Trump submitted written responses to the special counsel's office on Tuesday to respond to questions surrounding collusion between Russian officials and Trump's team during the campaign. But Giuliani mad...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump ex-lawyer pleads guilty to lying about Moscow tower project - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia/trump-ex-lawyer-pleads-guilty-to-lying-about-moscow-tower-project-idUSKCN1NY1TE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOLiYNjvF7WDZpGkQi5YEcAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 12:43:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia/trump-ex-lawyer-pleads-guilty-to-lying-about-moscow-tower-project-idUSKCN1NY1TE" target="_blank"&gt;Trump ex-lawyer pleads guilty to lying about Moscow tower project&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Cohen, President Donald Trump's former longtime personal lawyer, pleaded guilty on Thursday to lying to Congress about a proposed Trump Organization skyscraper in Moscow, prompting the president to lash out at Cohen as a liar and "weak person." The unexpected plea stemmed from Special Counsel Robert Mueller's intensifying investigation into Russia's role in the 2016 election and whether Trump's campaign conspired with Moscow to boost his chances, and put new pressure on the president. Cohen, a former member of Trump's inner circle who in the past called himself the president's "fixe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump submits written answers to questions from special counsel - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-giuliani-idUSKCN1NP2JQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFCl2v0jEclO24Yt0ULIG64qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:28:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-giuliani-idUSKCN1NP2JQ" target="_blank"&gt;Trump submits written answers to questions from special counsel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump has submitted written answers to questions from Special Counsel Robert Mueller in his probe of Russian meddling in the 2016 election and possible collusion with the Trump campaign, Trump's lawyer Rudy Giuliani said on Tuesday. "We answered every question they asked that was legitimately pre-election and focused on Russia," Giuliani said in an interview. "Nothing post-election. And we've told them we're not going to do that." Giuliani said Trump did not plan to answer any questions from Mueller on whether he tried to obstruct the investigation once he won office, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump says Manafort pardon not 'off the table' - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/politics/ny-post-trump-manafort-pardon-on-the-table/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQDV1cYdvIOEWZJeRM6HX8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 22:46:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/politics/ny-post-trump-manafort-pardon-on-the-table/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says Manafort pardon not 'off the table'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump declined in a new interview to rule out the possibility that he could pardon Paul Manafort, his former campaign chairman. "It was never discussed, but I wouldn't take it off the table. Why would I take it off the table?" Trump told the New York Post. The President's comments come following special counsel Robert Mueller's accusation that Manafort violated his plea agreement and lied to Mueller's team after being found guilty on eight counts of financial crimes in August. On Tuesday, White House press secretary Sarah Sanders said there had been no conversations about a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Donald Trump's campaign chief refutes claims he 'secretly met with Julian Assange' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/27/trumps-campaign-chief-secretly-met-julian-assange-months-wikileaks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDSbRx1RxhVDsiaOALtHF4cqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 04:47:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/27/trumps-campaign-chief-secretly-met-julian-assange-months-wikileaks/" target="_blank"&gt;Donald Trump's campaign chief refutes claims he 'secretly met with Julian Assange'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The breakdown of a plea deal with former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort and reports about alleged contacts he may have had with WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange threw a new element of uncertainty into the Trump-Russia investigation on Tuesday Donald Trump's former campaign chairman has been accused of repeatedly lying to prosecutors, undermining his plea deal and potentially depriving the Russia investigation of a star witness. Paul Manafort, Mr Trump's one-time campaign chief, agreed to co-operate with investigators looking at potential collusion between the Trump campaign and Russi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Trump Has Answered Mueller’s Questions, His Lawyers Say - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-has-answered-muellers-questions-his-lawyers-say</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHq-Oqhnp7qNO3skMkHMSH4qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-has-answered-muellers-questions-his-lawyers-say" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Has Answered Mueller’s Questions, His Lawyers Say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reuters President Donald Trump has given written answers to questions from Special Counsel Robert Mueller, according to his lawyers. “The President today answered written questions submitted by The Special Counsel’s Office,” said his attorney Jay Sekulow in a statement. “The questions dealt with issues regarding the Russia-related topics of the inquiry. The President responded in writing.” Another of the president’s attorneys, Rudy Giuliani, took aim at Mueller. “It has been our position from the outset that much of what has been asked raised serious constitutional issues and was beyond the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>What Is Robert Mueller Thinking? - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/28/opinion/robert-mueller-paul-manafort-trump.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEBXGzRCM0EZ310RJxalO8EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 18:05:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/28/opinion/robert-mueller-paul-manafort-trump.html" target="_blank"&gt;What Is Robert Mueller Thinking?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since his investigation into Russian election interference began 18 months ago, the special counsel, Robert Mueller, has had very little to say. Mr. Mueller, in fact, has let court filings and appearances by his team of lawyers do all of the talking, at least publicly, as the law and facts have led to more indictments, convictions, sentences and rulings — mostly in his favor. Friday, however, could bring Mr. Mueller’s richest revelation yet. A federal judge has ordered Paul Manafort, President Trump’s former campaign chairman, and prosecutors to her courtroom that day to learn more about th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>On SNL’s cold open, Trump is jealous of Putin and MBS’s budding bromance - Vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/culture/2018/12/2/18122091/snl-cold-open-trump-jealous-putin-mbs-budding-bromance</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEz3BoswujVQ6qFR51p9674qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowlOzSATCaiDUwk7tz</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 15:34:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/culture/2018/12/2/18122091/snl-cold-open-trump-jealous-putin-mbs-budding-bromance" target="_blank"&gt;On SNL’s cold open, Trump is jealous of Putin and MBS’s budding bromance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t cry for Trump, Argentina. The truth is he’s “very guilty.” On Saturday Night Live’s G20-themed cold open, Donald Trump found himself out in the cold. In Alec Baldwin’s unexpectedly-long-awaited return, Trump contemplated the latest findings in the Mueller investigation, being abandoned in turn by Cecily Strong’s Melania, Beck Bennett’s Russian President Vladimir Putin, Ben Stiller’s returning cameo as Michael Cohen, and a fabulous new cameo: Fred Armisen’s Prince Mohammed bin Salman. Kate McKinnon’s Rudy Giuliani hung by him, however. (Quite literally — her vampiric Giuliani appeared ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.vox.com">Vox.com</source></item><item><title>Rudy: Trump Talking About Manafort Pardon Was ‘Not a Signal’ - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rudy-trump-talking-about-manafort-pardon-was-not-a-signal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAN-mvYbXtt_0n4oIBJ2wrcqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 02:41:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/rudy-trump-talking-about-manafort-pardon-was-not-a-signal" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy: Trump Talking About Manafort Pardon Was ‘Not a Signal’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOSHUA ROBERTS Move along, nothing to see here, Donald Trump’s legal team is saying once again. A day after, Donald Trump told the New York Post that pardoning Paul Manafort is “not off the table,” the president’s lawyer dismissed the idea that he was sending a message to his besieged former campaign chairman that relief was on the way. Rudy Giuliani told The Daily Beast on Thursday that the president’s interview remarks were “not a signal” to Manafort—but, merely, a comment on the extent of his constitutional prerogatives. “He has the constitutional power to, some time in the future, eithe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>New developments put Manafort back in Russia probe spotlight - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/f605e84b2a484e1a9b9c28aa56d98413</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMQwpM0Adz6HaTt-Rg6nUZ8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 17:48:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/f605e84b2a484e1a9b9c28aa56d98413" target="_blank"&gt;New developments put Manafort back in Russia probe spotlight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The breakdown of a plea deal with former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort and an explosive British news report about alleged contacts he may have had with WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange threw a new element of uncertainty into the Trump-Russia investigation. On Tuesday, a day after prosecutors accused Manafort of repeatedly lying to them, trashing his agreement to tell all in return for a lighter sentence, he adamantly denied a report in the Guardian that he had met secretly with Assange around March 2016. That's the same month Manafort joined the Trump campaign and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump appears consumed by Mueller investigation as details emerge - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/politics/donald-trump-robert-mueller-behavior/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPYDU-6dRhGweIBXalGpaTgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:27:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/28/politics/donald-trump-robert-mueller-behavior/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump appears consumed by Mueller investigation as details emerge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump's behavior isn't doing much to bolster White House assurances that he's got nothing to worry about from Robert Mueller's probe, after a series of potentially ominous turns in the Russia investigation. The President's recent barrage of tweets and comments and testimony from sources close to him -- coinciding with thickening intrigue around the special counsel -- hint instead at deep concern on Trump's part. "While the disgusting Fake News is doing everything within their power not to report it that way, at least 3 major players are intimating that the Angry Mueller Gang of Dems ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump Tower Moscow concept included idea of giving penthouse to Putin - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/politics/trump-tower-moscow-putin-penthouse/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBPdT8wn8Luxzf3HhJQiyrgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:17:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/politics/trump-tower-moscow-putin-penthouse/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Tower Moscow concept included idea of giving penthouse to Putin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One idea considered for the proposed Trump Tower in Moscow was to offer Russian President Vladimir Putin the penthouse, according to Felix Sater, who was working on the project with Michael Cohen. RELATED: Michael Cohen pleads guilty, says he lied about Trump's knowledge of Moscow project Sater, a Russian-born onetime business associate of Trump's, described the concept as a "marketing ploy" and explained that the idea was to try to enhance the value and attraction for buyers by having Putin in the building. BuzzFeed, which first reported on the plan, reported that Cohen, who was then-candi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>6 takeaways from Michael Cohen’s new plea deal with Mueller - Vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/11/29/18117945/michael-cohen-mueller-trump-russia-plea</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAMJYdvfoTjMv-iQweDIas8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowlOzSATCaiDUw1aKsBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 20:15:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/11/29/18117945/michael-cohen-mueller-trump-russia-plea" target="_blank"&gt;6 takeaways from Michael Cohen’s new plea deal with Mueller&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Cohen Drew Angerer/Getty Images News on the Trump Tower Moscow project, Cohen’s cooperation, and the president’s answers. The news that Michael Cohen is cooperating with special counsel Robert Mueller’s probe is significant, but not exactly surprising. He’s been signaling he planned to do so for months, and he already pleaded guilty to separate charges in New York in August. The big surprise is that Mueller’s new charge against Cohen focuses so heavily on lying to Congress about a project to build a Trump Tower in Moscow. Trump Tower Moscow (which didn’t end up being built) has been...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.vox.com">Vox.com</source></item><item><title>Trump lawyer Rudy Giuliani says Mueller team is trying to intimidate president’s allies - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-rudy-giuliani-mueller-investigation-michael-cohen-paul-manafort-russia-special-counsel-a8663991.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_MEMVlTt2TWpLpw2GYxnQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 18:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-rudy-giuliani-mueller-investigation-michael-cohen-paul-manafort-russia-special-counsel-a8663991.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump lawyer Rudy Giuliani says Mueller team is trying to intimidate president’s allies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump’s personal lawyer has accused special counsel Robert Mueller of trying to intimidate allies of the president as he reiterated his belief that the investigation into Russian meddling in the 2016 election is simply a “witch hunt”. Rudy Giuliani made the remarks during an appearance on New York’s AM 970's The Answer, where he was asked about the recent guilty plea of Michael Cohen in relation to the investigation. “They obviously exerted a lot of pressure on him. Mr Cohen unfortunately has a history of significant lies in the past,“ Mr Giuliani said. - Read more Special ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Alec Baldwin's Trump returns with worries about the Mueller investigation - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/media/trump-alec-baldwin-saturday-night-live/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3l3JKYJbUQQnln8o2VlpMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 08:19:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/02/media/trump-alec-baldwin-saturday-night-live/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Alec Baldwin's Trump returns with worries about the Mueller investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alec Baldwin's Donald Trump returned to "Saturday Night Live" and he brought his worries over the Mueller investigation with him. Baldwin's Trump found himself on a balcony in Argentina with first lady Melania Trump, played by Cecily Strong. "Melania, I'm having trouble sleeping," Baldwin said. "I keep having a nightmare that I'm walking through a forest of blood." "No, no, that's just my Christmas decorations," Strong's Melania Trump responded, referring to the first lady's much talked about bright red Christmas trees that were put up in the White House. The fake first lady then asked what...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Document says Corsi tipped off Stone about leaks - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/65405c8c93b74c218ab59f8dc34b59a6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGf8E9WKuSrY-QFCZbHpXM4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 01:51:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/65405c8c93b74c218ab59f8dc34b59a6" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Document says Corsi tipped off Stone about leaks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort (all times local): 8:45 p.m. Prosecutors believe a conservative author tipped off Trump confidant Roger Stone months before WikiLeaks released thousands of emails stolen from Hillary Clinton's campaign. That's according to a document drafted as part of a plea offer to Jerome Corsi. The document was published Tuesday by the Washington Post. The document says Stone asked Corsi to get in touch with WikiLeaks so he could learn about information that could be relevant to Trump's campaign. The document...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump submits written answers to Mueller’s questions - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-submits-written-answers-to-muellers-questions-2018-11-20</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDkTJfaAGcqHT8K-wo6F6UsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-submits-written-answers-to-muellers-questions-2018-11-20" target="_blank"&gt;Trump submits written answers to Mueller’s questions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WALL STREET JOURNAL By Rebecca Ballhaus President still unlikely to do in-person interview with special counsel’s investigation President Donald Trump speaks to members of the media prior to his departure from the White House on Tuesday. Getty Images WASHINGTON — Lawyers for President Donald Trump said they have submitted written responses to questions posed by special counsel Robert Mueller about possible collusion with Russia during the 2016 presidential election. Jay Sekulow, a lawyer for the president, said the questions were on “Russia-related topics” of the Mueller investigation. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Trump Floats Potential Pardon For Paul Manafort In Mueller Probe - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/paul-manafort-pardon_us_5bfef4fde4b0388c1770d7fe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI2JCOyvPtZtwevcqBv5iHkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 20:25:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/paul-manafort-pardon_us_5bfef4fde4b0388c1770d7fe" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Floats Potential Pardon For Paul Manafort In Mueller Probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― President Donald Trump publicly floated the possibility that he’d pardon former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort in connection with the special counsel investigation led by Robert Mueller. Trump, in an interview with the New York Post, made the dubious claim that he’d never discussed pardoning Manafort, but said he wouldn’t “take it off the table.” Rudy Giuliani, one of Trump’s lawyers, previously told HuffPost that he discussed pardoning Manafort over the summer. “We both agreed that it made sense not to pardon anybody during the pendency of the investigation,” Giuliani s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump team turns over written answers to Mueller's questions - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/bcca758b43c949e9a0a3295f591d71c6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEENat0WpKpD89-TJhMwP1AkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/bcca758b43c949e9a0a3295f591d71c6" target="_blank"&gt;Trump team turns over written answers to Mueller's questions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has provided the special counsel with written answers to questions about his knowledge of Russian interference in the 2016 election, his lawyers said Tuesday, avoiding at least for now a potentially risky sit-down with prosecutors. It's the first time he has directly cooperated with the long investigation. The step is a milestone in the negotiations between Trump's attorneys and special counsel Robert Mueller's team over whether and when the president might sit for an interview. The compromise outcome, nearly a year in the making, offers some benefit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Trump Defends Pursuit of Russia Deal in 2016 as ‘Very Legal’ - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/30/us/politics/trump-defends-pursuit-of-russia-deal-in-2016-as-very-legal.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ15T0YIOgQ6UqKaqzWY-s8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:59:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/30/us/politics/trump-defends-pursuit-of-russia-deal-in-2016-as-very-legal.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Defends Pursuit of Russia Deal in 2016 as ‘Very Legal’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON — President Trump woke up in balmy Buenos Aires early Friday, but his mind was back in Washington as he defended his decision to continue pursuing business deals as he ran for president in 2016, including looking “lightly” at constructing a building in Russia. Oh, I get it! I am a very good developer, happily living my life, when I see our Country going in the wrong direction (to put it mildly). Against all odds, I decide to run for President &amp; continue to run my business-very legal &amp; very cool, talked about it on the campaign trail... — Donald J. Trump (@realDonaldTrump) Novembe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Trump says he has answered Mueller's questions but not submitted them - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/16/trump-robert-mueller-russia-investigation-questions-answered</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3vmykQF4jIsZ66M-e32TYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 18:09:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/16/trump-robert-mueller-russia-investigation-questions-answered" target="_blank"&gt;Trump says he has answered Mueller's questions but not submitted them&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump said on Friday that he has answered written questions from special counsel Robert Mueller but has not yet submitted them. Related: Jeff Flake threatens to block judicial appointments over Mueller inquiry bill The president told reporters in the Oval Office that he answered the questions “very easily” this week about the special counsel’s ongoing investigation into 2016 election interference and possible ties between Russia and the president’s campaign. “You have to always be careful when you answer questions with people that probably have bad intentions,” said Trump in his late...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Giuliani: Trump protected under executive privilege on obstruction questions - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/11/21/lead-alex-marquardt-trump-submits-answers-to-mueller-live-jim-sciutto.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHHxeKPQoOVBioTtZax-Zv4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 22:48:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/11/21/lead-alex-marquardt-trump-submits-answers-to-mueller-live-jim-sciutto.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Giuliani: Trump protected under executive privilege on obstruction questions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Trump's lawyer Rudy Giuliani told CNN that any questions about obstruction related to the Trump Presidency would fall under executive privilege and therefore go unanswered. CNN's Alex Marquardt reports. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Paul Manafort’s Lawyer Told Trump Team What His Client Said To Mueller: Report - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/paul-manafort-lawyer-trump_us_5bfdf5f8e4b0f43bf2661440</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECnjf9v-gkq_dbXn4UhqkpsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 02:16:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/paul-manafort-lawyer-trump_us_5bfdf5f8e4b0f43bf2661440" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Manafort’s Lawyer Told Trump Team What His Client Said To Mueller: Report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Paul Manafort’s lawyers regularly briefed President Donald Trump’s legal team about his client’s conversations with federal investigators as part of special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation into Russian meddling in the 2016 election, The New York Times reported on Tuesday. The Times, citing Trump lawyer Rudy Giuliani and two other sources familiar with the conversations, said attorney Kevin Downing regularly briefed the president’s legal team about what Manafort had discussed during interviews and what angles of inquiry Mueller was investigating. The alleged conversations happe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump's Ex-Lawyer Pleads Guilty to New Charge - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-s-ex-lawyer-to-plead-guilty-to-new-charge/4679585.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFkNDuCbp6O5APbBDDxgjpMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:51:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-s-ex-lawyer-to-plead-guilty-to-new-charge/4679585.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's Ex-Lawyer Pleads Guilty to New Charge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump's former personal lawyer, Michael Cohen, pleaded guilty Thursday to a new charge of lying to Congress about a Russian real estate venture Trump sought to develop during his presidential campaign. The charge was filed by special counsel Robert Mueller, who is leading a probe into Russian interference in the 2016 U.S. election. Cohen, who previously pleaded guilty to violating campaign finance laws, directed efforts to construct a Trump-branded complex in Moscow. He admitted to a federal judge in New York he lied about the timing of negotiations and other information in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>SNL: Alec Baldwin’s Trump Plays ‘Side Piece’ to ‘Bros’ Putin and Saudi Crown Prince - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/snl-alec-baldwins-trump-plays-side-piece-to-bros-putin-and-saudi-crown-prince</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPQ2O89xUZzPpj6TqeyaU5wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 05:35:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/snl-alec-baldwins-trump-plays-side-piece-to-bros-putin-and-saudi-crown-prince" target="_blank"&gt;SNL: Alec Baldwin’s Trump Plays ‘Side Piece’ to ‘Bros’ Putin and Saudi Crown Prince&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump is 5,000 miles away in Argentina for the G20 Summit and Alec Baldwin is back on Saturday Night Live. A month after his arrest for allegedly assaulting a stranger over a parking space, Baldwin made his first SNL appearance as Trump since early October. The scene opened on the balcony of the Park Hyatt hotel where Baldwin’s Trump was suffering insomnia. “Melania, I'm having trouble sleeping,” he said. “I keep having this nightmare where I'm walking in a forest of blood.” “No, no, that was just my Christmas decorations,” Cecily Strong’s first lady replied. In reality, Tr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Trump: 'Probably' Won't Sit for Interview in Russia Investigation - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-probably-won-t-sit-for-interview-in-russia-investigation/4663656.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHZEK4hG7Na21-7hmJe9K1YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 16:04:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-probably-won-t-sit-for-interview-in-russia-investigation/4663656.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump: 'Probably' Won't Sit for Interview in Russia Investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump is declaring that he "probably" won't sit for an in-person interview with special counsel Robert Mueller probing links between his 2016 campaign and Russia, suggesting that his written answers to the prosecutor's questions will be his final response. Trump told Fox News Sunday host Chris Wallace that in recent days he gave "very, very complete answers to questions I shouldn't have been asked. Probably this is the end." In an interview at the White House taped Friday and broadcast Sunday, Trump said his lawyers are completing answers to Mueller's two dozen or so q...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Trump hands over written responses to Mueller's Russia probe questions - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/444497-trump-mueller-questions-sumbits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELl7oHw3dfysYutJTJ0KT8UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/444497-trump-mueller-questions-sumbits/" target="_blank"&gt;Trump hands over written responses to Mueller's Russia probe questions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lawyer for Donald Trump has confirmed that the US President has submitted answers to the questions penned by FBI Special Counsel Robert Mueller's team. The questions refer to the Trump campaign's alleged collusion with Moscow. "The president today answered written questions submitted by the special counsel's office," Trump's attorney Jay Sekulow said in a statement, as cited by AP. The issues Trump covered in his responses are "the Russia-related topics of the inquiry," Sekulow said. Trump's legal team has indicated that the president would not answer any additional questions aside from p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Jerome Corsi’s new story about WikiLeaks is really hard to buy - Vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/11/29/18117777/jerome-corsi-wikileaks-mueller-divine-intervention-msnbc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAGLtqxMCrleTUNkhY1ETMIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowlOzSATCaiDUwo9dy</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 18:30:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/11/29/18117777/jerome-corsi-wikileaks-mueller-divine-intervention-msnbc" target="_blank"&gt;Jerome Corsi’s new story about WikiLeaks is really hard to buy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Vox.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MSNBC Corsi claims God, not Assange, provided him with foreknowledge of WikiLeaks’ plans. Seriously. Right-wing conspiracy theorist and Donald Trump ally Jerome Corsi wants you to believe that God, not Julian Assange or any other human source, provided him with foreknowledge about WikiLeaks’ plans to publish emails hacked from the Clinton campaign in the weeks leading up to the 2016 presidential election. Seriously. According to draft court documents obtained by NBC, while he was vacationing in Italy on August 2, 2016, Corsi emailed longtime Trump confidante Roger Stone and told him, “Word ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.vox.com">Vox.com</source></item><item><title>letters: The Legal Maneuvering Over Manafort - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/29/opinion/letters/trump-manafort.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN9DOgPoMazvvhnX7m6STnEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwpoIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 20:06:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/29/opinion/letters/trump-manafort.html" target="_blank"&gt;letters: The Legal Maneuvering Over Manafort&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;To the Editor: Re “Trump Raises Idea of Pardon for Manafort” (front page, Nov. 29): I understand that the pardon power given to the president of the United States is a powerful tool; however, should this power be allowed to be used in the case where the pardon is being given to an individual whose crimes directly involve or are related to the actions of the president himself? Should the president, although not yet named as an unindicted co-conspirator, be permitted to issue a pardon to Paul Manafort, as this would directly serve his own personal interests? Steven Skolnick Westlake Village, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Manafort team briefed Giuliani on Mueller meetings - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/11/28/manafort-lawyers-keeping-trump-lawyers-giuliani-updated-mueller-probe-bash-sot-nr-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPOaTh0CTqqBVlafLD3SJwUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:31:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/11/28/manafort-lawyers-keeping-trump-lawyers-giuliani-updated-mueller-probe-bash-sot-nr-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Manafort team briefed Giuliani on Mueller meetings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump's lawyer Rudy Giuliani told CNN's Dana Bash that Paul Manafort's legal team has kept Trump's lawyers updated on developments with the Mueller probe. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani Tries to Distance Trump From Trump Tower Moscow: ‘This Was Cohen's Deal’ - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rudy-giuliani-tries-to-distance-trump-from-trump-tower-moscow-this-was-cohens-deal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI0uQh5IfmHgvU0x0XRy0NMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 19:58:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/rudy-giuliani-tries-to-distance-trump-from-trump-tower-moscow-this-was-cohens-deal" target="_blank"&gt;Rudy Giuliani Tries to Distance Trump From Trump Tower Moscow: ‘This Was Cohen's Deal’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast Special counsel Robert Mueller revealed Thursday that Michael Cohen said he repeatedly briefed Trump about a potential business deal in Russia during the 2016 campaign. In response, Trump’s legal team has tried to distance the president from a project that literally had his name on it. Cohen, the president’s former lawyer and fixer, worked with real-estate developer Felix Sater on a proposal to develop a Trump Tower in Moscow beginning in 2015 and continuing well into 2016—contrary to what he told Congress. Cohen admitted this morning that he lied when ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item></channel></rss>