<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Aussie - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREU0TURGNUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-AU&amp;gl=AU&amp;ceid=AU:en</link><language>en-AU</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:01:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>The U.K.’s 2019 Great Escape fest will focus on Australia - The Industry Observer</title><link>https://www.theindustryobserver.com.au/the-u-k-s-2019-great-escape-fest-will-focus-on-australia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWluZHVzdHJ5b2JzZXJ2ZXIuY29tLmF1L3RoZS11LWstcy0yMDE5LWdyZWF0LWVzY2FwZS1mZXN0LXdpbGwtZm9jdXMtb24tYXVzdHJhbGlhL9IBuwFodHRwczovL3d3dy10aGVpbmR1c3RyeW9ic2VydmVyLWNvbS1hdS5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy50aGVpbmR1c3RyeW9ic2VydmVyLmNvbS5hdS90aGUtdS1rLXMtMjAxOS1ncmVhdC1lc2NhcGUtZmVzdC13aWxsLWZvY3VzLW9uLWF1c3RyYWxpYS9hbXAvP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:54:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theindustryobserver.com.au/the-u-k-s-2019-great-escape-fest-will-focus-on-australia/" target="_blank"&gt;The U.K.’s 2019 Great Escape fest will focus on Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Industry Observer&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next year's Great Escape will have a strong Aussie flavour.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theindustryobserver.com.au">The Industry Observer</source></item><item><title>Home-town hero leads Aussie resistance - Lismore Echo</title><link>https://www.echonews.com.au/news/should-aussies-have-used-drs-with-cheteshwar-pujar/3595402/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiXGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmVjaG9uZXdzLmNvbS5hdS9uZXdzL3Nob3VsZC1hdXNzaWVzLWhhdmUtdXNlZC1kcnMtd2l0aC1jaGV0ZXNod2FyLXB1amFyLzM1OTU0MDIv0gEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:00:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.echonews.com.au/news/should-aussies-have-used-drs-with-cheteshwar-pujar/3595402/" target="_blank"&gt;Home-town hero leads Aussie resistance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Lismore Echo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia's middle order crumbled around him but South Australian Travis Head has steered Australia to stumps and within sight of India's first innings total.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.echonews.com.au">Lismore Echo</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/LwoUwGdkpoECqQJYM73z0G1ePcd8hTaXbOdNayjuUFPKtjOhQuJKLuG3zI6zalYV6kqjW5N5AzrXHjSdKguzrnXsL8HTNiorwLRjNUFPap2z5nSstBXggzkFWd5CZ7gmRNSaEMlwwsgXP9H2N6thTEXJQECQuzIWmvt2yXT1zNAW8FMbWPF8yB_HKbJaha2Q=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Aussies cashing in on $28b global swimwear market - Fraser Coast Chronicle</title><link>https://www.frasercoastchronicle.com.au/news/aussie-fashion-brands-cashing-in-on-28b-global-swi/3589819/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZyYXNlcmNvYXN0Y2hyb25pY2xlLmNvbS5hdS9uZXdzL2F1c3NpZS1mYXNoaW9uLWJyYW5kcy1jYXNoaW5nLWluLW9uLTI4Yi1nbG9iYWwtc3dpLzM1ODk4MTkv0gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.frasercoastchronicle.com.au/news/aussie-fashion-brands-cashing-in-on-28b-global-swi/3589819/" target="_blank"&gt;Aussies cashing in on $28b global swimwear market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fraser Coast Chronicle&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's how we sell ourselves to the world - the sun-soaked Aussie on the beach in a beautiful swimsuit. Think Elle Macpherson in the high-cut neoprene one-piece ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.frasercoastchronicle.com.au">Fraser Coast Chronicle</source></item><item><title>M&amp;C Saatchi and Digitas handed Tourism Australia creative and digital - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/mc-saatchi-and-digitas-handed-tourism-australia-creative-and-digital-555878</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMozVcilqv7O1CXtePGjDMkqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 02:05:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/mc-saatchi-and-digitas-handed-tourism-australia-creative-and-digital-555878" target="_blank"&gt;M&amp;C Saatchi and Digitas handed Tourism Australia creative and digital&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;M&amp;C Saatchi and Digitas have won the creative and digital accounts for Tourism Australia, Mumbrella understands. The result, which comes eight months after the creative account first went to pitch, is a huge win for M&amp;C Saatchi, adding Tourism Australia to its client list, which includes Lexus, Commonwealth Bank, Woolworths and Plush. M&amp;C Saatchi’s win comes after the agency lost its place on Optus’ creative roster and closed its retail division 1440. Earlier in the year the agency also merged its PR arm Hidden Characters into M&amp;C Saatchi Sports &amp; Entertainment. It comes at a loss for incum...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Shaun Tait and Shibani have a typical Aussie breakfast - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wmiDE4M3ybQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOHBevUlIDWyoTLuMiAOjrMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowwooT</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:08:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wmiDE4M3ybQ" target="_blank"&gt;Shaun Tait and Shibani have a typical Aussie breakfast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Undiscover Australia with Shibani Dandekar. Subscribe to ESPNcricinfo: http://bit.ly/1jnGh6S Get our apps: Android: http://bit.ly/2vFVfzX iOS: http://apple.co/2vGj8rg Website: http://www.espncricinfo.com/ You can also find us at: https://www.facebook.com/Cricinfo https://twitter.com/ESPNcricinfo https://www.instagram.com/espncricinfo/&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Smith frustrated at the team - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/video</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDQJicG3DVKEbtRkRTGZkQqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 22:21:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/video" target="_blank"&gt;Smith frustrated at the team&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cricket: Steve Smith says the Aussies failed to learn from past mistakes&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.adelaidenow.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Aussies need cheaper Scotch: Boris - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/nsw/boris-johnsons-scotch-whisky-comment-a-sweetener-in-free-trade-talks/news-story/bd6d2ee4ac96662d7581431d1db9b75c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP-zqFUDbNIdsz_ig7iXyfwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 08:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/news/nsw/boris-johnsons-scotch-whisky-comment-a-sweetener-in-free-trade-talks/news-story/bd6d2ee4ac96662d7581431d1db9b75c" target="_blank"&gt;Aussies need cheaper Scotch: Boris&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a jovial press conference in Sydney today, the charismatic British Foreign Secretary backed up his case for Aussies to get cheaper whisky by noting Bundaberg Rum didn’t attract the same import duties in the UK. Asked by a British journalist whether Australian wine would be cheaper under a future free trade deal, Mr Johnson said “never mind Australian wine, which is, of course, delicious. “There are tariffs on Scotch whisky in this country which seem to me to be a cruel deprivation of the Australian people of Scotch whisky at the price they could have it. I merely throw it out there. Wher...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Aldi builds on its enthusiastic Americans campaign for Christmas - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/aldi-enthusiastic-americans-six-new-spots-by-bmf-412992</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAPFed5EEWwEr0QZLBBcMMoqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDDH4g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 04:31:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/aldi-enthusiastic-americans-six-new-spots-by-bmf-412992" target="_blank"&gt;Aldi builds on its enthusiastic Americans campaign for Christmas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aldi has added a slew of new ads to its Christmas campaign featuring a family of overbearing, sweater-wearing, grinning Americans. The supermarket launched the campaign two weeks ago through BMF with an ad showing the family arriving on the doorstep of an unsuspecting Australian home. A series of six 15-second ads extends the campaign, with a focus on a range of products including prawns, ham, turkey and Christmas lights. The campaign has been anchored with this ad which features the family arriving in Australia. Credits: - Executive Creative Director: Cam Blackley - Creative Director: Alex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Which household brands are still Aussie owned? - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-01-19/which-household-brands-are-still-aussie-owned/8193788</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHCs3_-c4hBSOEN_akroFMIqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 04:28:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-01-19/which-household-brands-are-still-aussie-owned/8193788" target="_blank"&gt;Which household brands are still Aussie owned?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arnott's, Uncle Tobys, Bushells, Golden Circle — you could be forgiven for thinking these brand were Australian owned. This morning, it was announced dairy brand Bega would purchase Vegemite from US company Mondelez International and put it back in local hands. It was a reminder that many Australian pantry staples are foreign-owned despite their Aussie roots. Arnott's Key products: TimTam, Shapes, Jatz From its humble beginnings in a Newcastle bakery the biscuit and cracker maker became one of the largest food companies in the Asia-Pacific region. But while the product is still manufactured...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Grant Kenny calls for more prestige and fewer competitors at the Aussies - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-03-29/grant-kenny-says-aussies-need-a-revamp/8397420</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENMdt3z5GQ6dPm0wW9D7Kh4qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 03:28:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-03-29/grant-kenny-says-aussies-need-a-revamp/8397420" target="_blank"&gt;Grant Kenny calls for more prestige and fewer competitors at the Aussies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Australia's greatest ironmen, Grant Kenny, believes the iconic Aussies surf life saving championships needs a revamp. "I think it has lost its way," he said, while competing in the masters competition at the annual Australian Surf Life Saving Championships on the southern Gold Coast. "On the part of surf life saving, there's been this ambition to grow it to an enormous size … it has then almost become almost unmanageable." External Link: Grant Kenny shows he still has it at the Aussies The Australian championship event involves more than 7,000 competitors from more than 300 surf club...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Welcome! (Kind of.) The problem with being declared ‘Aussie’ - Overland magazine</title><link>https://overland.org.au/2017/03/welcome-kind-of-the-problem-with-being-declared-aussie/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIVHc3NOChBbtW5U8XVTOa8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowifhAMOfACDDRhhM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 01:29:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://overland.org.au/2017/03/welcome-kind-of-the-problem-with-being-declared-aussie/" target="_blank"&gt;Welcome! (Kind of.) The problem with being declared ‘Aussie’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Overland magazine&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Reena Gupta If you're a city-dwelling human armed with basic perceptual skills, chances are you've come across a visually striking poster collection that showcases portraits of unidentified individuals emblazoned with the word 'AUSSIE' in large, capitalised print. The poster campaign, launched by Adelaide artist Peter Drew, has been enthusiastically embraced by much of the Australian public. While Drew was initially the sole distributor of these posters, they have since been made available for purchase on his website, meaning that anyone can help circulate the campaign's message. The sen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://overland.org.au">Overland magazine</source></item><item><title>The Aussie slang we’re losing - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/are-boomers-the-last-fluent-speakers-of-aussie-slang/news-story/9a9644b2cc37ad63c9881cb2aef7c276</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMNwx93mMm2V6PZ1WUVauwEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwxeOkAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/are-boomers-the-last-fluent-speakers-of-aussie-slang/news-story/9a9644b2cc37ad63c9881cb2aef7c276" target="_blank"&gt;The Aussie slang we’re losing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;My father and his mates could carry on a conversation almost in code, using slang terms that just about everybody understood in the 1940s, and ’50s. It was colourful and it was entertaining. Where did they pick it up? Well my Dad wouldn’t miss an episode of radio’s Mo McCackie and McCackie Mansions. It was Australian comedy at its best. Adelaide-born Roy Rene began as a stage actor and comedian, but then turned to performing on stage for radio in about 1946. Every week you could bet it would be the subject of new expressions of the Australian language in barber shops and bars across Austral...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Davis Cup: Aussies dominate - The Australian</title><link>http://www.theaustralian.com.au/sport/tennis/davis-cup-live-australia-vs-czech-republic-day-2-doubles/news-story/8deff05a438d579029be8a7cac9d33ab</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIFDZ2yRTPhasmfcuPi0JKUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowga_TBDDc734wxJjEAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 01:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.theaustralian.com.au/sport/tennis/davis-cup-live-australia-vs-czech-republic-day-2-doubles/news-story/8deff05a438d579029be8a7cac9d33ab" target="_blank"&gt;Davis Cup: Aussies dominate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Australian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.10pm:Aussies take second set 6-2 The Aussies are really dominating this game, taking the second set 6-2. They’re just one set away from a spot in the quarter finals. 12.40pm: Australia takes first set Peers and Groth have taken the first set. John Peers mother Elizabeth says she’s “so proud” of her son. 12.15pm: Aussies hold first set The Australians hold the first set 4-3 12.00:We’re off The Aussies win first toss and elect to serve.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.theaustralian.com.au">The Australian</source></item><item><title>Don Smallgoods wants to feature Aussie ‘Dons’ in latest campaign - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/don-smallgoods-wants-to-feature-aussie-dons-in-latest-campaign-423114</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAcKne4Kwgh7mPP2jDh4yyoqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 01:50:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/don-smallgoods-wants-to-feature-aussie-dons-in-latest-campaign-423114" target="_blank"&gt;Don Smallgoods wants to feature Aussie ‘Dons’ in latest campaign&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don Smallgoods is on the hunt for Australians named Don to promote the brand’s meat products in its latest campaign. Created by DDB Melbourne, the ad features different men, women and children of Australia who enjoy eating meat and are named Don. The tongue-in-cheek ad encourages people named Don to sign up for the chance to feature as the new spokesperson for Don Smallgoods. The winning spokesperson will showcase how Don Smallgoods is a part of everyday Australian life. The campaign is the first since the brand launched its ‘Don’t settle for less’, work in 2014, featuring a Don character w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Bundy celebrates Australia in ad fronted by Gyton Grantley - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/bundy-launches-no-one-rum-like-us-work-429970</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3n-K0e27eh3s4lIzrwSoAqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 08:59:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/bundy-launches-no-one-rum-like-us-work-429970" target="_blank"&gt;Bundy celebrates Australia in ad fronted by Gyton Grantley&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bundaberg Rum has refreshed its branding, shifting from the “Men Like Us” position of the past two years to celebrate Australian life and the home-grown rum in a $20m push for increased market share. Bundaberg Rum’s new campaign celebrates the unique nature of Australia. Under the banner of “Unmistakably Ours” the campaign by Leo Burnett focuses on unique elements of Australia and the 90 second launch ad features actor Gyton Grantley taking on overseas critics and making a call for Australians to stand proud. Featuring cameos from surfer Julian Wilson, who swam towards a shark attack, and A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Four’N Twenty launches campaign to save Aussie slang - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/fourn-twenty-launches-campaign-save-aussie-slang-441190</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGUeV4uH4QvnP_zru-3q2s0qFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDDH4g4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 05:43:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/fourn-twenty-launches-campaign-save-aussie-slang-441190" target="_blank"&gt;Four’N Twenty launches campaign to save Aussie slang&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four’N Twenty Pies has launched a new campaign to save Australian slang, rebranding its pies and sausage rolls with popular local phrases which are falling out of favour with the younger generation. The campaign will see the products rebranded with 70 popular slang terms. as part of its 70th birthday celebrations. Fronted by AFL star Jonathan Brown, the campaign will include words such as Bloke, Bogan, Grouse and ‘Straya. At the same time the the campaign will roll out on social media with Brown urging Aussies to name their favourite slang. Four’N Twenty marketing manager Mario Matchado sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Aldi’s Americans try to take over Christmas in new work by BMF - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/aldi-americans-try-tampering-aussie-christmas-406613</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJmXF1Ub0BH7a9-jVzK1r5kqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 02:05:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/aldi-americans-try-tampering-aussie-christmas-406613" target="_blank"&gt;Aldi’s Americans try to take over Christmas in new work by BMF&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aldi has tackled the Americanisation of the traditional Aussie Christmas head-on with a crazed campaign featuring a frightening family of Americans trying to change our ways. The latest instalment of the cut-price retailer’s increasingly ‘out there’ marketing efforts, created by BMF introduces the Tinkeltons, who barge into a family home and try to turn the traditional Aussie sun-soaked Christmas into something reflecting the worst American nightmare. The ad opens with the Tinkleton family arriving at the front door of and unsuspecting Australian family, dressed in matching sweaters, sporti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Gatorade launches G Active water in new campaign - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/gatorade-launches-g-active-water-new-campaign-442223</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGXOGxyAD0lIBeq6O12MK7MqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 06:27:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/gatorade-launches-g-active-water-new-campaign-442223" target="_blank"&gt;Gatorade launches G Active water in new campaign&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gatorade has launched its new electrolyte water G Active with a new campaign asking audiences ‘what if your water was as active as you?’. Created by TBWA, the four television spots feature a man made by G Active water doing box jumps, running and kick boxing. Highlighting its three flavours of lemon, berry and orang, the campaign is set to roll out across TV with one 30 second and three 15 second ads. Sister agency Eleven PR also contributed to the campaign by launching a ‘fitness hotspot’ last weekend. The fitness hotspot was located on Sydney Harbour as a fitness pop-up area where partici...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Fair dinkum: Amazon has a job for an Aussie slang expert - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-07-28/want-a-job-amazon-are-looking-for-someone-to-teach-them-aussie/8753128</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOt5pdhmO4RXA2kBFV2Ux9IqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 05:10:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-07-28/want-a-job-amazon-are-looking-for-someone-to-teach-them-aussie/8753128" target="_blank"&gt;Fair dinkum: Amazon has a job for an Aussie slang expert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking for a new job? Tech giant Amazon is in search for a linguist who can teach it the intricacies of the Australian accent. Key points: - Job is likely to involve work on Amazon's voice recognition device - Expert says "there's a lot of work here" as Australians are famous for playing with language - The vowels will cause the most problems, he says The company that was once a simple online bookstore has dramatically expanded in recent years, and now invests in voice recognition technology. Amazon's job ad offers little detail, however, the successful applicant would likely find themselv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Who is the typical Australian? - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-11/typical-australian-revealed-in-2016-census-data-release/8434178</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO1So26tlV2sRb0qwXgvsJYqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 03:16:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-11/typical-australian-revealed-in-2016-census-data-release/8434178" target="_blank"&gt;Who is the typical Australian?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first data from last year's controversial census is in — and it has been used to form a profile of the typical Australian. She is a 38-year-old woman who was born in Australia, has English ancestry, is married with two kids, lives in a home she owns and has finished Year 12. She lives in a three-bedroom home — owned with a mortgage — and has two cars. The data released by the Australian Bureau of Statistics (ABS) from the 2016 census also includes profiles of the typical Australian in each state and territory. The typical Aussie in Tasmania is significantly older than the national avera...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Mates, we present peak Straya - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.news.com.au/technology/online/social/kindly-enjoy-this-list-of-the-most-australian-things-to-ever-happen/news-story/c517176896360d9d68abd9bffc8fa5a6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECR20xYm-e2cp8vjBcAhfncqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwufCxAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 02:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.news.com.au/technology/online/social/kindly-enjoy-this-list-of-the-most-australian-things-to-ever-happen/news-story/c517176896360d9d68abd9bffc8fa5a6" target="_blank"&gt;Mates, we present peak Straya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, a Reddit user posed an important question: “What do you think of Australian people?” Some of the responses were generous: “They’re really chill. Love their sun, love to drink and generally have cheery dispositions.” Others were a little too generous: “Look and sound like Hugh Jackman.” But for the most part, people seem to think we’re an alien planet with deadly wildlife where it’s kill-or-be-killed. No, really. “Australian exchange students told us about something called ‘bunny bashing’ they did back home to control the rabbit population that kind of horrified me but different s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>The innings that lit up the World Cup - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/swoop/one-womans-record-knock-just-set-the-icc-womens-world-cup-alight/news-story/a88192c671316fca84918fbf649e4092</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAr1DMxG-pY2V-Z2tcTRFngqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwxOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 19:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/swoop/one-womans-record-knock-just-set-the-icc-womens-world-cup-alight/news-story/a88192c671316fca84918fbf649e4092" target="_blank"&gt;The innings that lit up the World Cup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Sri Lankan number three, Chamari Athapaththu, has an answer to everything the Australians threw at her and recorded one of the greatest one day knocks with 178 not out. She played shots all around the ground and set records in the process, racking up the biggest total ever scored against the Australians. MATCH REPORT: Aussies chase down huge total Pacquiao vs. Horn promo (small) And her efforts will surely have put her on the radar of Australian BBL clubs, something she would be open to. “I’d really like to play the Big Bash and England league,” Athapaththu said. “We are playing for Asi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Man finds bizarre list on used laptop - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.news.com.au/technology/home-entertainment/computers/man-buys-5-laptop-online-finds-bizarre-star-trek-theme-and-list-of-aussie-slang/news-story/0e007f71dc99e59eb34a433a4165d25c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFgR1nI5LQNOLR5DFcTVQ2QqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwufCxAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 03:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.news.com.au/technology/home-entertainment/computers/man-buys-5-laptop-online-finds-bizarre-star-trek-theme-and-list-of-aussie-slang/news-story/0e007f71dc99e59eb34a433a4165d25c" target="_blank"&gt;Man finds bizarre list on used laptop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imgur user chrisman01 recently shared the bizarre content he uncovered when he fired up his IBM Thinkpad 365XD. As the user pointed out, the strangest find on the laptop was a text file containing a list of Australian Slang and its meanings. Here is a list of some of what was on the computer: • Ace! — Excellent! Very good! • Aerial ping-pong — Australian rules football • Amber fluid — Beer • Ankle biter — Small Child • Apple’s, she’ll be right: It’ll be all right. • Arvo: Afternoon • Aussie (pron. Ozzie): Australian • Aussie salute: Brushing away flies with the hand • Avos: Avocado • Banana...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Is your business marketing to millennials properly? - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/now-australian-millennials-second-lowest-rate-home-ownership-world-471510</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJSgJ1oQxX0p7dTCfW1F5lkqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 06:00:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/now-australian-millennials-second-lowest-rate-home-ownership-world-471510" target="_blank"&gt;Is your business marketing to millennials properly?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australian millennials have the second-lowest rate of home ownership in the world A smaller percentage of Aussie millennials own their own homes compared to every other country in the world bar the UAE, according to HSBC. A survey of 9,000 young people found only 28% of Australians aged 18-36 had a place to call their own, compared to 70% in China and 35% in the US. While 83% said they intended to buy in the next five years, the bank predicts that is unrealistic in today’s market. A clothing brand’s online store has a huge impact on its popularity Nike, Victoria’s Secret and Sephora are th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Aussie Farmers Direct and Gocatch offer tractor ride through Sydney CBD - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/aussie-farmers-gocatch-offer-tractor-ride-sydney-cbd-429714</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAlQDThAp7x_SgpDwFCjpE0qFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 04:55:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/aussie-farmers-gocatch-offer-tractor-ride-sydney-cbd-429714" target="_blank"&gt;Aussie Farmers Direct and Gocatch offer tractor ride through Sydney CBD&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aussies Farmers Direct and Gocatch have teamed up as part of a new initiative, giving consumers the chance to drive around Sydney CBD in a tractor. The announcement: Amidst the usual hubbub of Sydney traffic tomorrow, commuters will have the opportunity to get a free ride through the CBD on a tractor. National online fresh food retailer Aussie Farmers Direct has partnered with leading nation-wide taxi booking platform GoCatch to offer commuters the once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to ride in a tractor through the Sydney CBD. Eligible customers[i] wanting to take part in this experience need t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Remember the time McDonald’s created the #DownUnderBigMac hashtag and nobody used it? - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/remember-time-mcdonalds-created-downunderbigmac-hashtag-nobody-used-422736</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBJcbLbU0e8S9QWC6MC-vqoqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 01:52:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/remember-time-mcdonalds-created-downunderbigmac-hashtag-nobody-used-422736" target="_blank"&gt;Remember the time McDonald’s created the #DownUnderBigMac hashtag and nobody used it?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes when brands attempt to tap into social media it resonates. And sometimes… it doesn’t. Take the push from McDonald’s to tap into Australia Day by getting people to eat their burgers upside down. Surely you know the one? That one they were doing news site takeovers to promote three days after Australia Day. Along with an outdoor advertising campaign. You see, in Australia, because we’re at the opposite end of the world to civilisation, we do everything upside down. Which makes eating Big Macs upside down the epitome of Australianity. McDonald’s implored: Since 1971, the Big Mac has ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Jillaroos expect a fight from Ferns - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/swoop/australian-jillaroos-name-squad-for-anzac-test-v-kiwi-ferns/news-story/89fe6737cc6dccbeb32d050d6152868c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE7-ZQC9pX9BG4ofxH7o1EMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwxOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/swoop/australian-jillaroos-name-squad-for-anzac-test-v-kiwi-ferns/news-story/89fe6737cc6dccbeb32d050d6152868c" target="_blank"&gt;Jillaroos expect a fight from Ferns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Aussies will take on the Kiwis on Friday May 5 in Canberra and will be confident of their chances after defeating their trans-Tasman rivals in the Auckalnd Nines for the first time this year. It’s a strong 25-player squad with Indigenous All Stars halfback Simone Smith, who was also player of the match in that fixture, named. A couple of key players still remain injured in Kezie Apps, who broke her leg at the Nines, and Allana Ferguson also not named. Jillaroos coach Brad Donald said he was taking the team’s Nines victory to mean the Test would be a done victory and that the Ferns side ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Fuze Tea celebrates Australians’ love of food in brand awareness push - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/fuze-tea-celebrates-australians-love-food-brand-awareness-push-420250</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDo-EvyZoTYZGemxsmE4pqsqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDDH4g4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 23:21:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/fuze-tea-celebrates-australians-love-food-brand-awareness-push-420250" target="_blank"&gt;Fuze Tea celebrates Australians’ love of food in brand awareness push&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coca-Cola’s Fuze Tea has launched its new summer campaign encouraging consumers to enjoy the iced beverage with friends and food as part of a multimillion-dollar integrated marketing campaign. The brand, which launched in Australia last year, aims to align itself with Australians’ love of food through an outdoor-focused campaign as well as through activations which will distribute more than 300,000 samples to consumers. A showcase of the different fusions including Wild Raspberry &amp; Hibiscus and Summer Mango &amp; Chamomile will feature on the Kings Cross Coke sign, as well as food courts across...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Memories on the line - The Australian</title><link>http://www.theaustralian.com.au/life/weekend-australian-magazine/memories-on-the-line/news-story/e46dc19024ded9b24ae6260ac7780a2d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcsYPAEfRO7OeCgVXbJYWAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowga_TBDDc734w45HEAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.theaustralian.com.au/life/weekend-australian-magazine/memories-on-the-line/news-story/e46dc19024ded9b24ae6260ac7780a2d" target="_blank"&gt;Memories on the line&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Australian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m talking South Australia’s finest export, of course, the Hills Hoist. It warms an Aussie back yard to the right level of memory; makes a house instantly feel like home. Oh, the recollections of all those quarter-acre blocks of our childhoods, if you were lucky enough to have a youth marinated in our singular, glorious, Aussie light. Memories of chooks roaming. Choko vines choking. Mums yakking over back fences in quilted, zip-fronted dressing gowns, rollers in their hair. The bedraggled vegie patch. The lemon tree. The neglected swing set. Strips of coloured plastic across the back door....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.theaustralian.com.au">The Australian</source></item><item><title>How Aussie is Google Home? - The Australian</title><link>http://www.theaustralian.com.au/video</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELCLOUsDCDrQqf0ZzAsXig8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowga_TBDDc734w4pLEAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 22:05:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.theaustralian.com.au/video" target="_blank"&gt;How Aussie is Google Home?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Australian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matt Dunn puts Google Home to the ultimate Aussie slang test&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.theaustralian.com.au">The Australian</source></item><item><title>DRS, umpires frustrate Australia on day three - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-03-18/india-v-australia-drs-frustrates-aussies-on-day-three/8366500</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPx0EIOMEVTBXu7ymQfYJQMqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 06:22:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-03-18/india-v-australia-drs-frustrates-aussies-on-day-three/8366500" target="_blank"&gt;DRS, umpires frustrate Australia on day three&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In successive balls across the 18th and 19th overs of day three (the 58th and 59th in India's innings), Australia was brutalised by the decision review system. Having burned one of its two reviews seemingly out of frustration on the second night, skipper Steve Smith only had one to play with come day three. First, the tourists thought they had Cheteshwar Pujara LBW to Steve O'Keefe. The first drop was certainly hit in line by a ball straightening towards the middle of the stumps, but umpire Chris Gaffaney turned down the Aussies' appeal. Smith was relatively quick to review the decision con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Buy a little slice of Australia - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/news/south-australia/gum-tree-drive-south-australia-one-drive-among-aussie-street-names-with-houses-for-sale/news-story/b05e2bf2a95e6cd04ecf88d8bfd94fb4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBohlRv9qxyZpdyg0qD43gkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwpOOkAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/news/south-australia/gum-tree-drive-south-australia-one-drive-among-aussie-street-names-with-houses-for-sale/news-story/b05e2bf2a95e6cd04ecf88d8bfd94fb4" target="_blank"&gt;Buy a little slice of Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the lead-up to Australia Day next week, we’ve taken a look at Aussie streets around Adelaide with houses for sale, to give you a chance to own a property in a fair-dinkum location. If you’re seeking a home among the gum trees, 122 Gum Tree Drive, Littlehampton might be the place to start. For sale is 1.64ha property with a 2015-built home, surrounded by quintessentially Australian landscape studded with century-old gum trees, according to Arabella Hooper of Harris, who is selling the property. “Gum Tree Drive was called that because it’s studded with gums, and it offers a real Australian...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.adelaidenow.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>For Aussies By Aussies: Bonds follows Australians’ creative lives in content series - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/aussies-aussies-bonds-follows-australians-creative-lives-content-series-446073</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANWLGvxhlq2lyeb00iTnr4qFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 23:44:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/aussies-aussies-bonds-follows-australians-creative-lives-content-series-446073" target="_blank"&gt;For Aussies By Aussies: Bonds follows Australians’ creative lives in content series&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bonds has launched a content series which follows the lives for Australians who lead creative lives, such as musicians, artists and designers. ‘For Aussies By Aussies’ sees Bonds follow everyday Australians for a day, as they pursue their passions, while wearing a particular item of clothing from the brand. The content series features interviews with each person about their life, as well as what they love most about the piece of clothing they enjoy wearing. A link to the clothing each person promotes is also available on the ‘For Aussies by Aussies’ page. One content piece tells the story o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>500+ Women Were On The Waitlist For This Swimsuit - Look Magazine UK</title><link>http://www.look.co.uk/fashion/une-piece-swimwear-580454</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKZDigE1iFbceO1hOKfaaJoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7r-fCTCPlG8wjeifAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 15:40:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.look.co.uk/fashion/une-piece-swimwear-580454" target="_blank"&gt;500+ Women Were On The Waitlist For This Swimsuit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Look Magazine UK&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It'll suit you all Aussie label Une Piece launched in Australia three months ago and is set to come to the Europe next month Swimwear is one of those things. You can try on hundreds and still be so far from The One. Well, brace yourselves, ladies, because this article holds the key to ultimate swimwear success: Une Piece. So excited to see UNE PIECE featured in The Huffington Post today See link in bio. A post shared by UNE PIECE – Life Is Beautiful (@une_piece) on Mar 20, 2017 at 2:09pm PDT Designed by the former Senior Marketing Manager for UBER Carly Brown, the Aussie label launched thre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.look.co.uk">Look Magazine UK</source></item><item><title>Inside the 2017 Sports Illustrated Swimsuit launch party - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/entertainment/inside-the-2017-sports-illustrated-swimsuit-launch-party/image-gallery/fa29227f891f64c9e30b1f02b7e7b08d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXBU0llzLNiCq1YdTWUevYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwmfGxAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 02:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/entertainment/inside-the-2017-sports-illustrated-swimsuit-launch-party/image-gallery/fa29227f891f64c9e30b1f02b7e7b08d" target="_blank"&gt;Inside the 2017 Sports Illustrated Swimsuit launch party&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUSSIE models Kelly Gale and Robyn Lawley were among the VIP guests who partied at the 2017 Sports Illustrated Swimsuit launch party in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.adelaidenow.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Orange growers urged to increase plantings or risk supply issues, says Citrus Australia - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-03-10/potential-supply-problem-for-aussie-oranges/8342700</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFngI25bkshO1zX2tMCebqYqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 03:25:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-03-10/potential-supply-problem-for-aussie-oranges/8342700" target="_blank"&gt;Orange growers urged to increase plantings or risk supply issues, says Citrus Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong international demand and the popularity of mandarins could see Australian oranges being in short supply in coming years. According to the country's peak citrus body, Australia's citrus industry will be faced with insufficient stocks of the popular fruit in future years if current plantings of oranges do not increase. Citrus Australia marketing and quality information manager Nathan Hancock said a shortage of oranges would be detrimental to satisfying demand from consumers. "At our current planting rate, we are going to have an issue where we do not have enough oranges to meet demand,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>My Aussie accent: ‘Man, it’s so gone now’ - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.news.com.au/entertainment/nailing-an-aussie-accent-was-tough-for-dev-patel/news-story/aa659450c6c7b1907c57389dd55b761e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOmBu-dVKaJLVgawhNtbURAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwmfGxAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 02:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.news.com.au/entertainment/nailing-an-aussie-accent-was-tough-for-dev-patel/news-story/aa659450c6c7b1907c57389dd55b761e" target="_blank"&gt;My Aussie accent: ‘Man, it’s so gone now’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Aussie accent can be notoriously difficult to nail even for the most talented actors.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Advance Australia Fair shouldn’t be a sacred cow - The Advertiser</title><link>https://myaccount.news.com.au/adelaidenow/subscribe?pkgDef=AA_PDO_P0415A_W04&amp;directSubscribe=true&amp;b=true&amp;sourceCode=AAWEB_WRE170_a&amp;mode=premium&amp;dest=http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/rendezview/tory-shepherd-because-of-history-isnt-a-good-reason-to-hate-change/news-story/4448c73cdf34a63bfa45c9cd09bd961f?nk%3Dfcef083125c9790db9e1b645e0a3311f-1495544534&amp;memtype=anonymous&amp;nk=c4cb790c595f5eda9196548a6a4d7185-1495544536</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN72BUtv8bsDnmoLRcTS43AqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhPakAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://myaccount.news.com.au/adelaidenow/subscribe?pkgDef=AA_PDO_P0415A_W04&amp;directSubscribe=true&amp;b=true&amp;sourceCode=AAWEB_WRE170_a&amp;mode=premium&amp;dest=http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/rendezview/tory-shepherd-because-of-history-isnt-a-good-reason-to-hate-change/news-story/4448c73cdf34a63bfa45c9cd09bd961f?nk%3Dfcef083125c9790db9e1b645e0a3311f-1495544534&amp;memtype=anonymous&amp;nk=c4cb790c595f5eda9196548a6a4d7185-1495544536" target="_blank"&gt;Advance Australia Fair shouldn’t be a sacred cow&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;But swags of Aussies don’t know them all. Odd, then, that such a yotta of words has been written about whether we should change the national anthem. (A yotta is 10 to the power of 24; suffice to say it’s a lotta words). For an irreverent mob with only a passing knowledge of its contents, Australians are defensively fond of the national anthem. I’ve only ever heard it sung on sombre, formal occasions. A dirge-like melody mumbled through for form’s sake. On days of national importance it’s “Aussie Aussie Aussie Oi Oi Oi” that’s more likely to be spontaneously sung. Or Waltzing Matilda, or Men...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://myaccount.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>The American dream: Why it can turn into an Aussie’s nightmare - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/american-dream-can-turn-aussies-nightmare-454976</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPoG9LBA9XvkMwGlvvYt9ngqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:11:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/american-dream-can-turn-aussies-nightmare-454976" target="_blank"&gt;The American dream: Why it can turn into an Aussie’s nightmare&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start spreading the news, I’m leaving today, I want to be a part of it, New York, New York. Frank Sinatra sang the song and for the past few years Aussies have been humming it as they made their way across the Pacific. But recently success in the antipodes has not been translating to Madison Avenue as easily as their US sponsors might have liked and the industry has seen a retreat of form in recent months as the Big Apple reveals its core. Brash, ambitious, entrepreneurial and in demand, there was something attractive in the Australian media success story that saw some of our top talents le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Why South Aussies can handle the heat - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/messenger/city/rebecca-morse-reckons-south-aussies-can-handle-the-heat-shes-not-so-sure-about-sydneysiders/news-story/b75995ac7e0abadda993165e4369d3d7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG9xeKm_gNpyppggUMRgpqkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwpPWkAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/messenger/city/rebecca-morse-reckons-south-aussies-can-handle-the-heat-shes-not-so-sure-about-sydneysiders/news-story/b75995ac7e0abadda993165e4369d3d7" target="_blank"&gt;Why South Aussies can handle the heat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those Sydneysiders bang on about how hot it is but in an eastern-states heatwave, us South Aussies would still be rocking a hoodie without breaking a sweat. Heatwaves are not to be taken lightly, though, as our authorities made clear last week, issuing advice to look after yourself, your elderly relatives and neighbours and pets and prepare your bushfire action plan. Once you’ve ticked all those boxes, here are some ways to keep cool in an Adelaide summer. Stay hydrated DRINK plenty of water. When you get the jug out of the fridge, stick your head in there for a little while. Coffee is a di...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.adelaidenow.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>‘CONFUSING’ BAN: Tangled in Trump’s immigration policy - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.news.com.au/travel/travel-updates/australian-ceo-the-human-face-of-donald-trumps-confusing-order/news-story/ec23a9b7642081a70bbe3e8ec49d8146</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECyx3bji7b_B3pIe3AcG-PkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 13:32:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.news.com.au/travel/travel-updates/australian-ceo-the-human-face-of-donald-trumps-confusing-order/news-story/ec23a9b7642081a70bbe3e8ec49d8146" target="_blank"&gt;‘CONFUSING’ BAN: Tangled in Trump’s immigration policy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HE’S an Aussie CEO used to doing business throughout the world. But now he’s unsure about whether he can set foot in the US again.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Surprising truth about this insane spot - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.escape.com.au/news/stavanger-norway-is-one-of-the-hottest-destinations-for-aussies-in-2017/news-story/a3bc049193fc2d17910132a7d9ec1617</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDZF7b94MLnlHS2ADr5B_gqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwxeOkAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 01:54:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.escape.com.au/news/stavanger-norway-is-one-of-the-hottest-destinations-for-aussies-in-2017/news-story/a3bc049193fc2d17910132a7d9ec1617" target="_blank"&gt;Surprising truth about this insane spot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.escape.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Aussie make their mark at NYFW - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/entertainment/sydney-confidential/aussie-modelling-sisters-jess-ashley-hart-and-designers-zimmermann-esber-shine-on-the-big-stage/news-story/0bce39fa5690840173a82604ac6efaa2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSiQkYeF6WnHAOiXm_th4EqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 06:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/entertainment/sydney-confidential/aussie-modelling-sisters-jess-ashley-hart-and-designers-zimmermann-esber-shine-on-the-big-stage/news-story/0bce39fa5690840173a82604ac6efaa2" target="_blank"&gt;Aussie make their mark at NYFW&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fashion houses Zimmermann and Christopher Esber showed their latest collections for New York’s fashion crowd. It was an A list front row for the ethereal brand’s showing. Australian sisters Jessica and Ashley Hart sported cool jumpsuits as they mingled with the celebs in attendance. The girls were spotted chatting to Pretty Little Liars star Shay Mitchell and singer and actor Kiersey Clemons. New York “it girl” Olivia Palermo slotted the Aussie designers into her hectic fashion week schedule. Model of the moment Bridget Malcolm sent the paparazzi into a spin when she arrived for the show lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Aussie gains against US dollar - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.news.com.au/finance/markets/australian-dollar/aussie-gains-against-us-dollar/news-story/760f1d8011447437b58c71e224d8b925</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMl6pKx8g_00QoUVQbEj_HwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 20:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.news.com.au/finance/markets/australian-dollar/aussie-gains-against-us-dollar/news-story/760f1d8011447437b58c71e224d8b925" target="_blank"&gt;Aussie gains against US dollar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The local currency was trading at 73.61 US cents at 0635 AEDT on Tuesday, up from 73.08 US cents on Monday. The Aussie dollar also firmed up against the yen and the euro. CURRENCY SNAPSHOT AT 0635 AEDT ON TUESDAY One Australian dollar buys: * 73.61 US cents, from 73.08 US cents on Monday * 85.48 Japanese yen, from 84.85 yen * 69.66 euro cents, from 69.45 euro cents (*Currency closes taken at 1700 AEDT previous local session)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Hugo Weaving’s niece in nude photo leak - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/entertainment/sydney-confidential/hugo-weavings-niece-samara-in-nude-photo-leak/news-story/41bdb324f5991f46cb57ea53617c978a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDQw_zkitA5Kg59lsp1Uc8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 11:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/entertainment/sydney-confidential/hugo-weavings-niece-samara-in-nude-photo-leak/news-story/41bdb324f5991f46cb57ea53617c978a" target="_blank"&gt;Hugo Weaving’s niece in nude photo leak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Daily Telegraph can reveal pictures allegedly of the former Home and Away star have been posted on notorious website Celeb Jihad, claiming to show her naked and partially naked. It is unclear if the pictures are originals or doctored for the website, which has recently claimed to publish pictures of A-listers including Amanda Seyfried, Miley Cyrus and Emma Watson. At least 15 frames claiming to be Weaving have been uploaded. In the racy series the 25 year old is seen exposing her breasts and vagina as she takes selfies in a mirror. She is also photographed lying naked on a bed. Last nig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Barton feels the heat in narrow loss - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/archive/australian-open/sydney-international-latest-news-aussie-qualifier-matt-barton-falls-short-of-maiden-atp-quarterfinal/news-story/45342ff04424721c54f94db60e97f50a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDZth6RVBdj4embCD3AewgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 03:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/archive/australian-open/sydney-international-latest-news-aussie-qualifier-matt-barton-falls-short-of-maiden-atp-quarterfinal/news-story/45342ff04424721c54f94db60e97f50a" target="_blank"&gt;Barton feels the heat in narrow loss&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barton fought back from one set down in the stifling heat to send the match into a deciding set at, but was eventually outed 6-1 3-6 6-4 in just under two hours. The sixth-seeded Muller will next meet world No. 22 Pablo Cuevas, who became the first player into the final eight on day four with a 6-4 2-6 6-2 win over Nicolas Mahut. With the mercury nudging 40 degrees at Homebush, the second seed Cuevas got one back on the Frenchman after losing their first meeting in Rome last year. Australia has two more locals aiming to reach the quarter-finals at Sydney Olympic Park, including Jordan Thomp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Sorry Bali, this is Australia’s new No.1 - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.escape.com.au/news/nepal-japan-pakistan-poland-where-aussies-are-going-for-winter/news-story/b10ba695780427c746d5fc4ba66c22f8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAftrijxYj7iakSGGmy5xeEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwxeOkAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 20:48:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.escape.com.au/news/nepal-japan-pakistan-poland-where-aussies-are-going-for-winter/news-story/b10ba695780427c746d5fc4ba66c22f8" target="_blank"&gt;Sorry Bali, this is Australia’s new No.1&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.escape.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Kiwi raid continues as Bonneval claims Oaks - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/superracing/nsw-racing/kiwi-star-bonneval-dominates-group-1-australian-oaks-for-baker-bowman/news-story/0b5abc1a21688c8a569e24e8d06808f1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECdODKrfnQYNLtRUEumQO1cqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwxOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 04:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au/sport/superracing/nsw-racing/kiwi-star-bonneval-dominates-group-1-australian-oaks-for-baker-bowman/news-story/0b5abc1a21688c8a569e24e8d06808f1" target="_blank"&gt;Kiwi raid continues as Bonneval claims Oaks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was the warning from Hugh Bowman on Saturday after New Zealand Oaks winner Bonneval gave her Aussie rivals a fair dinkum walloping in yesterday’s Australian Oaks at Randwick. Bonneval was about 20 lengths off tearaway leader Lasqueti Spirit coming to the home turn but her tremendous staying qualities came to the fore as she streaked clear to win by a widening 4 ½ lengths. The victory gave champion New Zealand trainer Murray Baker his 20th Australian Group 1 triumph as Baker and co-trainer Andrew Forsman became the first stable to win the Australian Derby and Oaks in the same year since...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.dailytelegraph.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Irish link has Raack turn rival - The Australian</title><link>https://myaccount.news.com.au/sites/theaustralian/subscribe.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBTtVIJUYEkt0WX4w_81s4sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowga_TBDDc734w44_EAQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://myaccount.news.com.au/sites/theaustralian/subscribe.html" target="_blank"&gt;Irish link has Raack turn rival&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Australian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Born in western Sydney with an unmistakeable Aussie accent, Celeste Raack is an unlikely enemy. But the Hobart physiotherapist has changed allegiances and today could make her debut for her grandmother’s birth country, Ireland, against Australia at the World T20 in the West Indies. She could pit herself against her junior teammates including Ellyse Perry and Alyssa Healy. “I was born in western Sydney — as Australian as it gets,” said Raack, whose surname can be traced to her father’s German heritage. “I went to Ireland to play a season in March this year in between my seasons with Tasmania...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://myaccount.news.com.au">The Australian</source></item><item><title>Letters to the Editor, November 8 - The Advertiser</title><link>https://myaccount.news.com.au/sites/adelaidenow/subscribe.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPoOred_bDmEf23lhSychogqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhPakAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://myaccount.news.com.au/sites/adelaidenow/subscribe.html" target="_blank"&gt;Letters to the Editor, November 8&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aussie culture MICHAEL McGuire fears Australia will become like the US (The Advertiser, 7/11/18). Fear not, Michael, it will never happen — I hope. I, too, wondered what ScoMo was on about with the flag pins antic. As for the national anthem, I struggle with the first verse, let alone the second. I sometimes cringe at the sweeping statement: “It’s un-Australian”. What? Are we all robots programmed to think the same? As for vegemite, Cold Chisel, pictured, and Australian stand-up comics, unlike Michael, I just love them. The Virgin offer of priority boarding for veterans was ridiculous: offe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://myaccount.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Sco Mo’s un-Australian playlist backfires - The Advertiser</title><link>https://www.news.com.au/entertainment/music/scott-morrisons-unaustralian-spotify-playlist-backfires/news-story/49ef6d5123a268f83e0151efa308eb62</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDSNjic1WXToH7E6eqiTL28qGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 09:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.news.com.au/entertainment/music/scott-morrisons-unaustralian-spotify-playlist-backfires/news-story/49ef6d5123a268f83e0151efa308eb62" target="_blank"&gt;Sco Mo’s un-Australian playlist backfires&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;From INXS to AC/DC, Midnight Oil to Jimmy Barnes, the music industry was riding high. Not to mention Kylie Minogue, Australian Crawl, The Divinyls, Nick Cave, Hoodoo Gurus, The Models, Icehouse and John Farnham. But according to Scott Morrison, only one Aussie act was a standout during the decade that spawned some of our all-time rock classics — pop-funk band Wa Wa Nee. The PM is copping serious backlash after producing a Spotify playlist that apparently reveals what he really thinks about Aussie music. The playlist, titled Eighties Plus, features 146 songs by 92 artists. But there’s only o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Wotif asks Australians to find the next big tourist attraction - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/wotif-asks-australians-what-the-next-big-thing-is-541953</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECkFJdzsVzKD9m2Hi25jXv8qFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDDH4g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 06:23:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/wotif-asks-australians-what-the-next-big-thing-is-541953" target="_blank"&gt;Wotif asks Australians to find the next big tourist attraction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online travel site Wotif has asked Australians what ‘The Next Big Thing’ is to create a new Australian icon to match the Big Banana and the Big Pineapple. The PR-driven campaign created by Ogilvy and Opr, asks Australians to vote on what they think the next big Australian landmark should be, Wotif will then release a shortlist out of the thousands of suggestions and eventually the public will vote on Australia’s new landmark. The campaign is part of Wotif’s 18th birthday celebrations. Hosted on Facebook, a social video gives Australians some suggestions for The Next Big Thing, including the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>How can you tell if your steak really is Aussie when you're overseas? Technology may soon have the answer - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-09-04/technology-aims-to-stop-fake-aussie-branded-beef/10132720</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBr36ylEhGswhlMkgrhE6C4qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 20:22:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-09-04/technology-aims-to-stop-fake-aussie-branded-beef/10132720" target="_blank"&gt;How can you tell if your steak really is Aussie when you're overseas? Technology may soon have the answer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you bought a steak overseas and it was labelled 'Australian beef', you would probably presume the meat came from Australia. But that is not always the case. Counterfeit 'Australian beef' is a trade worth billions of dollars worldwide. So how can you tell the difference between real Aussie beef and overseas meat that is fraudulently branded as Australian? Pricewaterhouse Coopers [PwC] is developing technology which can identify Australian meat when it is scanned with a smartphone. Craig Heraghty, national agribusiness leader at PwC, said the first part of the process was engraving the mea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Aussie icons star in Thinkerbell’s first work for Vegemite - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/aussie-icons-star-in-thinkerbells-first-work-for-vegemite-532797</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGdaitvnjxIIqDfRnI-utXsqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDDn4g4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 23:05:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/aussie-icons-star-in-thinkerbells-first-work-for-vegemite-532797" target="_blank"&gt;Aussie icons star in Thinkerbell’s first work for Vegemite&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thinkerbell has launched its first work for Vegemite since winning the account from JWT after 74 years creating a ‘Tastes Like Australia’ campaign. For its first campaign in six years, Vegemite’s ‘Tastes Like Australia’ advertising features legendary Australian icons including Pauline Hanson, The Big Prawn, Rebel Wilson and Ned Kelly. The campaign aims to celebrate Australia’s diversity by showing a range of iconic faces and moments played in short snippets against the backdrop of a Vegemite jar. Adam Ferrier, Jim Ingram and Ben Couzens, Thinkerbell’s co-founders, wanted the campaign to sta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Have your say on Mumbrella’s July Ad of the Month - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/have-your-say-on-mumbrellas-july-ad-of-the-month-532293</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHu_LiJ5AdXrJhjAq-BSbbMqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDDn4g4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 02:29:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/have-your-say-on-mumbrellas-july-ad-of-the-month-532293" target="_blank"&gt;Have your say on Mumbrella’s July Ad of the Month&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shortlist for the June Ad of the Month includes Lynx, Australia Post, Westpac, Royal Far West and Kia. Which ad will take the crown and become Mumbrella’s July Ad of the Month? You can vote in the survey embedded underneath the ads. Lynx Australia Post Westpac Royal Far West Kia The anonymous survey takes approximately one minute to complete. https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/C8JLT93 Create your own user feedback survey - Agencies and brands involved in creating ads that first run during July are invited to put them forward for consideration. Please email abigail@mumbrella.com.au The post ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Canadians slammed for ‘Aussie’ burger - The Advertiser</title><link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/food/restaurants-bars/mcdonalds-canada-slammed-over-new-aussie-burger/news-story/7a3e20965ee11ffae1685fb31f4ee7d4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKpjNdXp85YmIF_xafJZu4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwpcX2BQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 01:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/food/restaurants-bars/mcdonalds-canada-slammed-over-new-aussie-burger/news-story/7a3e20965ee11ffae1685fb31f4ee7d4" target="_blank"&gt;Canadians slammed for ‘Aussie’ burger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fast food chain McDonald’s has introduced a new “Aussie BBQ and Egg” burger to its range, but people aren’t so impressed with the interpretation of what makes a burger Australian. The burger was launched this month as part of the chain’s “World Taste Tour” promotion, but people were quick to notice that it lacked pretty much all the elements of a classic Australian burger. There is no beetroot or pineapple — instead the burger is made up of 100 per cent Canadian beef, eggs, beet chips, processed cheese, lettuce and barbecue sauce. Encouraging customers to “enjoy a taste of Australia”, socia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>How to repair your hair post-festival, according to experts - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/fashion/how-to-repair-hair-after-festival-damage-dryness-dulled-shine-tangles-aussie-ben-cooke-a8409916.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8oECuWQ7G1quYoxvNLs9QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 13:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/fashion/how-to-repair-hair-after-festival-damage-dryness-dulled-shine-tangles-aussie-ben-cooke-a8409916.html" target="_blank"&gt;How to repair your hair post-festival, according to experts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Festivals are great for a good time, but not so great for your locks. A weekend spent in a field, braving the elements and dancing the night away can leave hair feeling a little worse for wear and in need of some TLC. Three of the biggest telltale signs of festival damage? Dryness, dulled shine and tons of tangles. Here, celebrity hairstylists reveal their tips on how to spot them and more importantly, how to treat your hair to the post-festival recovery it’s crying out for. Dryness The distinct lack of shower facilities at festivals can leave your hair feeling like a hay bale, meaning the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>24 things you'll never understand about Australia until you've lived there - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/lists/living-in-australia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG0dj2qwAVvkcZz90Un_idQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 13:59:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/lists/living-in-australia/" target="_blank"&gt;24 things you'll never understand about Australia until you've lived there&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life in Australia is sold as the answer to all your worries. An English-speaking country with infinitely better weather and a deeply laid-back lifesytle, where people take off after work to laze on the beach and cook up a storm on the barbie. This is propagated, to an extent, by programmes such as the BBC’s Wanted Down Under – aweekend show that sees families flown across the world to experience life in Australia for a week before they decide whether or not to make a move. But a week just won’t cut it. In some cases, neither will a year. And the reality of moving to Australia couldn’t be mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Where and when to see Australia v France - The Advertiser</title><link>https://www.adelaidenow.com.au/thesourcesa/australia-v-france-french-connection-or-backyard-barbie/news-story/f43b027c868e28eb8f15edcdfeaf08a7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFLkVRxX9YRzpusj_veoPiYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 03:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.adelaidenow.com.au/thesourcesa/australia-v-france-french-connection-or-backyard-barbie/news-story/f43b027c868e28eb8f15edcdfeaf08a7" target="_blank"&gt;Where and when to see Australia v France&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I was there; it was chaos,” says the owner of La Buvette Drinkery, who moved to Australia in 2004. “I was in a bar and it was so full, people would come in and out of the bar through the windows. I guess liquor licenses were a bit easier, then!” Tonight, Dom welcomes all soccer — aka football — fans to come through his city bar’s front door to watch France v Australia on a big screen, and enjoy $6 pints of French beer, Kronenbourg. Punters can also nosh on typical French snacks such as escargot, steak frites and croque monsieur — a very decadent toasted sandwich. “That’s a crowd pleaser,” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.adelaidenow.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Lake Disappointment and Useless Loop Road - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/13/world/australia/indigenous-aussie-place-names.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEb4TdgI2m50Y06nr7uIv5AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww54UY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 08:39:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/13/world/australia/indigenous-aussie-place-names.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lake Disappointment and Useless Loop Road&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indigenous Australians choose spiritual and poetic names for their roads and lakes. The rest of Australians, not so much.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>The Helper - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/260577279/the-helper-by-james-stewart</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEERGVXOCloB1U2MWrb60ex0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 22:49:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/260577279/the-helper-by-james-stewart" target="_blank"&gt;The Helper&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a photo of Buddy, an Australian Shepherd, or Aussie, as so many call them. He is sitting in the bed of a pickup truck, resting after a hard day in the country.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Odd fact about Aussie accents - The Advertiser</title><link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/real-life/news-life/how-are-aussie-accents-really-formed/news-story/0380bc4f1adf82f6acffd40589706bbe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENNGdaVEjyxeZEvDhpHQwegqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/real-life/news-life/how-are-aussie-accents-really-formed/news-story/0380bc4f1adf82f6acffd40589706bbe" target="_blank"&gt;Odd fact about Aussie accents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some circles, saying “afternoon” instead of “arvo” is a cardinal sin. In others you’d be considered lowbrow if you didn’t pronounce ev-e-ry sin-gle syll-a-ble, and a rogue “youse” would have you socially ostracised for life (fack ‘em!) We also know different states use different words. Sydneysiders wear “swimmers”, Queenslanders wear “togs”. East coast residents eat “potato scallops”, while Victorians enjoy “potato cakes”. Thirsty? Head to your nearest bubbler — or is it a drinking fountain? It’s as if the C-word is the only thing we can all agree on. But what about the way we actually s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>How the Aussie accent was born - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-30/aussies-accents-american-canadian-kiwi-british/9814746</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBKA6mi_bYdLvhS1emUJoPsqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtiw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 01:19:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-30/aussies-accents-american-canadian-kiwi-british/9814746" target="_blank"&gt;How the Aussie accent was born&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why do Aussies have a different accent to Canadians, Americans, the British and New Zealanders? The answer, it seems, has a lot to do with who you hang out with as a kid. The accent you have depends on the people you grew up with and the history of the place that you live in. If you grew up in Australia, your accent is shaped by the history of Australia's European settlement; if you grew up in New Zealand, your accent is shaped by a different history, so it sounds different. It's automatic for us to talk in a similar way to the people around us and this feature is really strong in kids. Fri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Amazon to block Australians from global websites due to tax - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/adacafc69df0448d8e79d38eb9c4ca95</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAEfvCvwxEuC3KVte9HPrI4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 03:42:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/adacafc69df0448d8e79d38eb9c4ca95" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon to block Australians from global websites due to tax&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Amazon will block Australians from buying from its international e-commerce websites and restrict them to a smaller local platform from July in response to new tax rules that consumer advocates fear will reduce the range of choice for customers in Australia. Shoppers visiting the U.S. store Amazon.com will be redirected to the Australian version, Amazon.com.au, from July 1 when Australia starts applying new tax rules, Amazon said in a statement on Friday. From that date, Australia will impose a 10 percent consumption tax on online retailers for goods bought from o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Australian Avocados poke fun at ‘Millennial mortgage woes’ in first campaign by Ikon Sydney - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/australian-avocados-poke-fun-at-millennial-mortgage-woes-in-first-campaign-by-ikon-sydney-515279</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIZFmg38nxy0wpD4-50IywkqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDDn4g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 03:21:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/australian-avocados-poke-fun-at-millennial-mortgage-woes-in-first-campaign-by-ikon-sydney-515279" target="_blank"&gt;Australian Avocados poke fun at ‘Millennial mortgage woes’ in first campaign by Ikon Sydney&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australian Avocados is pushing back against the notion it responsible for the younger generation’s inability to purchase housing, in a campaign which says the fruit actually makes everything better. Everything – from breakfast, bodies, facials, health, barbecues, bowls and babies – is improved, rather than worsened, with the addition of avocados, the ad says. The ‘Smash an Avo’ campaign forms part of a complete brand refresh for Australian Avocados, and this is the first piece of work since Ikon Sydney won the account earlier this year. Rob Martin Murphy, ECD at Ikon, said in a statement: “...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Three Aussie Farmers hold auditions to find the face of their brand - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/three-aussie-farmers-hold-auditions-to-find-another-farmer-to-launch-new-pork-brand-515532</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBEucAAGZt_GtHOh-imEMrQqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDDn4g4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 01:29:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/three-aussie-farmers-hold-auditions-to-find-another-farmer-to-launch-new-pork-brand-515532" target="_blank"&gt;Three Aussie Farmers hold auditions to find the face of their brand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New pork brand, Three Aussie Farmers, has created a campaign where three growers hold an audition to find some faces to front their brand. Created by Khemistry, a Trimantium GrowthOps agency, the 30 second commercial stars three farmers from Queensland as they recruit people to inform consumers about the new pork brand by holding auditions. This is the first campaign a Trimantium GrowthOps business has launched since the digital business acquired a group of agencies, including Khemistry, in November. Stefanie Miller, SunPork senior marketing coordinator, said in a statement: “It was a pleas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>What a global shortage of wine means for Australia - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-04-24/what-impact-will-australia-see-in-europes-wine-shortage/9687408</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIvveXckHfqppDZijVZwBeUqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 21:59:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-04-24/what-impact-will-australia-see-in-europes-wine-shortage/9687408" target="_blank"&gt;What a global shortage of wine means for Australia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A downturn in European wine production has led to a shortage of wine, but the true impact on Australia is still be calculated. A nightmare vintage in the large production areas of Europe had wiped out a big chunk of global wine supply, according to industry body Wine Australia. Chief Executive Officer of Wine Australia, Andreas Clark, said Australia's bulk wine sector was trying to fill the enormous void it currently faced. "The big three producers in the northern hemisphere have had historically low harvests this year," Mr Clark said. "There is a shortage of wine around the world at the mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Ad watchdog clears ‘offensive’ Meat &amp; Livestock Australia ad of being ‘racist’ and ‘homophobic’ - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/ad-watchdog-clears-offensive-meat-livestock-australia-ad-racist-homophobic-504026</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGMN_GXp3VG7hgZEdOzlkUqFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDDH4g4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 23:32:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/ad-watchdog-clears-offensive-meat-livestock-australia-ad-racist-homophobic-504026" target="_blank"&gt;Ad watchdog clears ‘offensive’ Meat &amp; Livestock Australia ad of being ‘racist’ and ‘homophobic’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The advertising watchdog has cleared Meat &amp; Livestock Australia’s political musical Summer Lamb campaign of vilifying a person or being discriminatory. MLA’s Summer Lamb campaign, which turned the wars between Australia’s left and right into a ‘satirical’ West Side Story-style musical, was labelled in a complaint as “offensive”, “outdated, racist” and “homophobic”. “This ad is offensive to literally anyone who has ever held any point of view ever. It’s humour is outdated, racist, homophobic – I could go on. It seems to think it’s satire but it’s just genuinely offensive. In such a climate a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>Campaign Review: The verdict on Qantas’ missed opportunity and NAB’s forgettable ad - mUmBRELLA*</title><link>https://mumbrella.com.au/campaign-review-the-verdict-on-qantas-missed-opportunity-and-nabs-forgettable-ad-502023</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECcgeIogj_HRl9Vgm_s-LN8qFggEKg4IACoGCAoww90-MNejCDC34g4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 23:50:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://mumbrella.com.au/campaign-review-the-verdict-on-qantas-missed-opportunity-and-nabs-forgettable-ad-502023" target="_blank"&gt;Campaign Review: The verdict on Qantas’ missed opportunity and NAB’s forgettable ad&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;mUmBRELLA*&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brand: Qantas Agency: Brand+Story, Ape, The Butchery and Noise The Verdict: A missed opportunity that lacks a strong idea Wellison D’Assuncao, creative director, LOUD, says: D’Assuncao says the ad is on brand but lacks a strong idea “Just like Johnny Farnham, gone again… back again, it’s time to give the Peter Allen classic a respectful retirement. And if you’re tempted to open the 80’s music volute – which is not a bad thing, by the way – it should be reserved for iconic pieces of brand work. Qantas has leveraged this track so successfully over the years with big brand ads that it feels co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://mumbrella.com.au">mUmBRELLA*</source></item><item><title>How the Aussies fared on day 15 in Pyeongchang - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-02-24/how-the-aussies-fared-on-day-15-in-pyeongchang/9481722</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMn_g8A4eQJeUvReb2Zo26YqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtiw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 09:33:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-02-24/how-the-aussies-fared-on-day-15-in-pyeongchang/9481722" target="_blank"&gt;How the Aussies fared on day 15 in Pyeongchang&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team-best run in the men's bobsleigh and a pair of gutsy efforts in the men's cross-country ski headlined Australia's penultimate day at the Winter Olympics. External Link: Aus Olympic Team tweet: Our Aussie 4man looking fire. Sitting in 24th after runs 1 and 2. #GoAUS Australia's four-man bobsleigh crew recorded its personal best time in the first two runs, with a time of 49.72 seconds enough to see them sit in 24th place ahead of Sunday's third run. Though it would take an incredible effort to move into the medal places after the third and fourth runs, an improved performance — and plen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item></channel></rss>