<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Dodge Challenger - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRE13WWw4eUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-AU&amp;gl=AU&amp;ceid=AU:en</link><language>en-AU</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:08:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>2019 Dodge Challenger Demon stolen from Melbourne workshop - WhichCar</title><link>https://www.whichcar.com.au/news/2019-dodge-challenger-demon-stolen-from-melbourne-workshop</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780127368931</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 01:34:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.whichcar.com.au/news/2019-dodge-challenger-demon-stolen-from-melbourne-workshop" target="_blank"&gt;2019 Dodge Challenger Demon stolen from Melbourne workshop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;WhichCar&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.9news.com.au/2018/12/06/07/09/dodge-challenger-muscle-car-missing-after-dealership-heist" target="_blank"&gt;Rare Dodge Challenger, valued at $320,000, missing after car dealership heist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;9news.com.au&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.perthnow.com.au/news/crime/rare-stolen-dodge-challenger-demon-stolen-ng-s-1910640" target="_blank"&gt;Rare stolen Dodge Challenger Demon stolen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;PerthNow&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpqN2ZpbGpZQU1FWUFpZG9xc19GalpLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.whichcar.com.au">WhichCar</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/qxAWe_Kj7IHXWQeUPjGVw_ygYV6V2Nx4HC-uvnzbRex3DsJ5IcbkJTZwQwv_Z_Vf5kN6qBMniJNRuS-rd6mVN0U2egnI4SXf07OW7WVmyRC3FvfFs0QHVLynpt8oV_wmlJGCU4DanQxytqz1Wk0Qg3Xfh4SPozhFzyvLUEhvkmvqI2jxVWu4SjRvi4NtQTax22XAPPz4CNGKY7RSQn6rNeOHc-v0guPd=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>SRT adds a dash of Demon to Challenger Hellcat Widebody - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/dodge-srt-challenger-hellcat-widebody-durango/50247/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDh8FRXNfFUdWpDPx_eeQbEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 06:07:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/dodge-srt-challenger-hellcat-widebody-durango/50247/" target="_blank"&gt;SRT adds a dash of Demon to Challenger Hellcat Widebody&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dodge set the internet alight with the Challenger SRT Demon earlier this year, but it's been busy working on other projects as well. It doesn't get the full gamut of drag-ready features from the Demon, but the new Hellcat Widebody borrows from its unhinged big brother to deliver more grip and a meaner, more imposing stance. From the outside, the Hellcat Widebody instantly looks more aggressive than the regular car, thanks largely to a new fender flare kit and fresh 20 x 11 inch wheels. They're wrapped in wider 305 section Pirelli P-Zero tires, designed to make it easier to deploy the engine...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>Fiat Chrysler Recalls 1.34 Million Vehicles - The Wall Street Journal.</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/fiat-chrysler-recalls-1-34-million-vehicles-worldwide-1500038885</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEBeL4WDOXAAD2Yi-XsKVCkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1tzJATDnyxUw54IY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/fiat-chrysler-recalls-1-34-million-vehicles-worldwide-1500038885" target="_blank"&gt;Fiat Chrysler Recalls 1.34 Million Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Wall Street Journal.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiat Chrysler Automobiles NV said Friday it will voluntarily recall 1.34 million vehicles across the globe, amid concerns component failures could lead to inadvertent air bag deployments or be a potential fire hazard. The Italian-American auto maker said it is recalling 770,853 crossover vehicles after discovering wiring that chafes against steering-wheel trim pieces could cause a short circuit, triggering a process that could deploy the driver-side front air bag. The company warned the incident could be preceded by an illuminated air-bag warning light, unintended wiper operation, or inoper...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.wsj.com">The Wall Street Journal.</source></item><item><title>Lewis Hamilton and Mercedes 'communicating better than ever' - Motorsport Week</title><link>https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/13871</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJcorI0sYwV09lX5o1yFT0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAows7DjATC75Q0wxtFi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 16:17:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/13871" target="_blank"&gt;Lewis Hamilton and Mercedes 'communicating better than ever'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Motorsport Week&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lewis Hamilton says communication between himself and Mercedes is “better than ever” after a tough 2016, adding he is in a “positive place”. Hamilton missed out on last year’s championship to his team-mate Nico Rosberg after an intense battle and ignoring team orders put further strain on his relationship with Mercedes. But, after a winter of reflection and conversations between Mercedes, Hamilton – who is joined by Valtteri Bottas, after Rosberg’s retirement - said communication is now the best it has ever been. “I'm feeling in a positive place with the team - we talked about a lot of stuf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.motorsportweek.com">Motorsport Week</source></item><item><title>Toro Rosso to unveil STR12 on February 26 in Barcelona - Motorsport Week</title><link>https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/13734</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAz-kHbxN-822Qj8iJyxPTwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAows7DjATC75Q0wxtFi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 13:24:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/13734" target="_blank"&gt;Toro Rosso to unveil STR12 on February 26 in Barcelona&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Motorsport Week&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toro Rosso will unveil its 2017 Formula 1 challenger, the STR12, on Sunday 26 February at the Circuit de Barcelona-Catalunya. The team will take the wraps off its car in the pit lane on the afternoon before official pre-season testing begins at the home of the Spanish Grand Prix. Toro Rosso has retained Carlos Sainz Jr. and Daniil Kvyat for a further season, having classified seventh overall in last year’s standings. Toro Rosso, which will switch to current-year Renault power units, is the latest team to confirm its launch plans for the new season, which will welcome radically different car...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.motorsportweek.com">Motorsport Week</source></item><item><title>Hot dang - The Australian</title><link>https://myaccount.news.com.au/theaustralian/subscribe?pkgDef=TA_SDO_P0415A_W04&amp;directSubscribe=true&amp;b=true&amp;sourceCode=TAWEB_WRE170_a&amp;mode=premium&amp;dest=http://www.theaustralian.com.au/hero/2018-dodge-challenger-srt-demon/news-story/1def007de19ab382562ae42e7174b61b?nk%3D2fe83bf41cbc037beeede47ad22bb2ed-1506693908&amp;memtype=anonymous&amp;nk=b68050e6e5da2f512b7ab5b46308a1c2-1506693910</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRN5C_bE6JPpho-yCtSGB8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowga_TBDDc734w45HEAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://myaccount.news.com.au/theaustralian/subscribe?pkgDef=TA_SDO_P0415A_W04&amp;directSubscribe=true&amp;b=true&amp;sourceCode=TAWEB_WRE170_a&amp;mode=premium&amp;dest=http://www.theaustralian.com.au/hero/2018-dodge-challenger-srt-demon/news-story/1def007de19ab382562ae42e7174b61b?nk%3D2fe83bf41cbc037beeede47ad22bb2ed-1506693908&amp;memtype=anonymous&amp;nk=b68050e6e5da2f512b7ab5b46308a1c2-1506693910" target="_blank"&gt;Hot dang&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Australian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Demon is unique: a mass-produced racing machine that’ll go from zero to 160km/h in an eye-crossing 5.1 seconds. But it’s not clear how many of the 3300 Demons produced annually will ever see a drag strip. For starry-eyed collectors, the car may be like the good couch that grandma keeps the plastic on. Speaking of plastic: take a look at those wheel-arch extensions that shroud, just barely, the foot-wide Nitto drag slicks. I think they look like hell. Considering the Demon’s price tag and the production volume, these flares should have been stamped out of steel, but Fiat Chrysler Automob...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://myaccount.news.com.au">The Australian</source></item><item><title>Detroit Taps Its Roots With Throwback Names For Brand-New Vehicles - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2017/01/30/detroit-taps-its-roots-with-throwback-names-for-brand-new-vehicles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPX7appKB_IKbyPDw9reEI0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 18:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2017/01/30/detroit-taps-its-roots-with-throwback-names-for-brand-new-vehicles/" target="_blank"&gt;Detroit Taps Its Roots With Throwback Names For Brand-New Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jeep is planning on resurrecting its classic Grand Wagoneer, only it will be far more upscale than the 1991 version shown here and is not likely to feature its faux wood body trim. After an extended period during which far too many new-vehicle names seem to have been slurped at random from bowls of alphabet soup – alphanumeric appellations like “BMW Z4 sDrive 35is” hardly fall trippingly off the tongue – the industry is bringing back some hallowed actual car names from the past. This is mostly a domestic-branded phenomenon, where the vehicular heritage is rich, and classic nameplates with b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Best of the Big Apple: The most exciting cars from the New York Auto Show - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/new-york-auto-show-gallery/48993/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENb_-6iS0aWtZOtEAR5iAqsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 00:40:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/new-york-auto-show-gallery/48993/" target="_blank"&gt;Best of the Big Apple: The most exciting cars from the New York Auto Show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Detroit might be Motor City, but the annual New York Auto Show is arguably the biggest car show in America. Electric power was in the spotlight at the Paris Motor Show last year, but it would appear that trend hasn't made it across the Atlantic yet, because much of the new metal in New York was about old-fashioned, gasoline-powered muscle. Here are some of the highlights from the Big Apple. Dodge Demon Without doubt, the highlight of the New York Auto Show was the (long-awaited) reveal of the Dodge Demon. There are so many crazy details on the Demon – from the extreme engineering lengths ta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>VIDEO: Dodge's Challenger SRT Hellcat - Not The Demon, But A Ferocious Alternative - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/joshmax/2017/05/16/video-dodges-challenger-srt-hellcat-not-the-demon-but-a-ferocious-alternative/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKti6iFgbkDpzwYRVzs8utQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 17:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/joshmax/2017/05/16/video-dodges-challenger-srt-hellcat-not-the-demon-but-a-ferocious-alternative/" target="_blank"&gt;VIDEO: Dodge's Challenger SRT Hellcat - Not The Demon, But A Ferocious Alternative&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bad news: It’s not the Demon. We’ll get our paws on that monster soon enough. 2017 Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat The good news: It’s the SRT Hellcat. 2017 Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat Who among us will poo-poo at the 707 horses the Hellcat delivers, or paste a “My other Dodge is a Demon” bumper sticker on their Hellcat? None. In a year when there are no less than 15 Challenger trims available, the SRT Hellcat is the (other) vehicle you must have – if you have the $71,970 you’ll fork over for the pleasure. Summer is coming, and there isn’t any better time to enjoy a muscle car providing s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Holden V8 fans rejoice: Camaro is coming - The Advertiser</title><link>http://www.news.com.au/technology/innovation/motoring/chevrolet-camaro-is-go-for-australia-in-holden-showrooms-next-year/news-story/2c017ccfeb536056b8e68e752d17bef8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFb7CXVgkdRnQ5VOSaajtsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwxeOkAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.news.com.au/technology/innovation/motoring/chevrolet-camaro-is-go-for-australia-in-holden-showrooms-next-year/news-story/2c017ccfeb536056b8e68e752d17bef8" target="_blank"&gt;Holden V8 fans rejoice: Camaro is coming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The iconic Chevrolet Camaro muscle car will fill the V8 void in Holden showrooms next year, almost five years ahead of schedule — and ahead of the next generation flagship Corvette sports car due in 2020. These exclusive photos show Holden is preparing to import the Camaro SS and have it converted to right-hand-drive in Melbourne by its longstanding performance-car partner Holden Special Vehicles. The two Camaros caught on camera near HSV’s secret engineering centre are yet to be switched to right-hand-drive, but the plans are well progressed, with direct support from Detroit. Holden wasn’t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.news.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon: A Drag-Racing Devil, Unleashed - The Wall Street Journal.</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/2018-dodge-demon-a-drag-racing-beast-unleashed-1500572281</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO3-oVe0B_CC6ik39IZIeZcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAow1tzJATDnyxUwuK20AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/2018-dodge-demon-a-drag-racing-beast-unleashed-1500572281" target="_blank"&gt;2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon: A Drag-Racing Devil, Unleashed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Wall Street Journal.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BECAUSE DRAG RACERS like to get to the finish line fast: The 2018 Dodge Demon ($86,090) is a wheelie-pulling, 840-hp version of the Dodge Challenger, extensively re-engineered for quarter-mile racing and offered as sizzle for the brand’s aging, underselling steak. Mmmm, smell those roasted meats. Last winter the National Hot Rod Association (NHRA) certified a quarter-mile E.T. (elapsed time) of 9.65 seconds with a trap speed of 140 mph, making this rocket-propelled pachyderm the quickest production car the organization had ever tested, exceeding even the all-electric Tesla Model S, which, b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.wsj.com">The Wall Street Journal.</source></item><item><title>RUMBLE: 2018 Challenger SRT Hellcat Widebody VS. 2018 Corvette Grand Touring (Plus video) - Forbes Now</title><link>//www.forbes.com/sites/joshmax/2017/09/07/rumble-2018-challenger-srt-hellcat-widebody-vs-2018-corvette-grand-touring-plus-video/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHWz_16tdfuRPNjlskFiORkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 18:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="//www.forbes.com/sites/joshmax/2017/09/07/rumble-2018-challenger-srt-hellcat-widebody-vs-2018-corvette-grand-touring-plus-video/" target="_blank"&gt;RUMBLE: 2018 Challenger SRT Hellcat Widebody VS. 2018 Corvette Grand Touring (Plus video)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We drove ‘em both for about 20 minutes each, and we weren’t nice to either car. 2018 Challenger SRT Hellcat Widebody Vs. 2018 Corvette Grand Sport Coupe “Which one did you like best?” you ask. Hard to say. We could be a greedy sumbitch and say “Both. Please have them delivered to this address.” But a winner must be declared, and it was the Challenger. 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat Widebody Not a fair fight, but can you blame us? 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat Widebody It was louder. It’s better looking. It has an actual back seat that fits actual people. At $76,180 loaded, it’s $23,5...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Review: A week with the monstrous 2017 Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/2017-dodge-challenger-srt-hellcat-review/50456/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ9M7L9lhZvzofo17nKjD34qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 07:33:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/2017-dodge-challenger-srt-hellcat-review/50456/" target="_blank"&gt;Review: A week with the monstrous 2017 Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are three things to know about the Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat: it's fast, it's loud, and you're going to have to budget for speeding tickets. These attributes also mean the Challenger SRT Hellcat is extreme fun and wherever you go, heads will turn to look. Those were the lessons we learned after a week in this truly American muscle car. The 2017 Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat is big, wide, heavy, low, mean, and insanely muscular. Packing 707 horsepower (527 kW) under its hood, it can take the rubber off of its rear tires in just seconds. Yet it remains family-friendly, or at least fam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>'Fast &amp; Furious' Star Vin Diesel Puts It All On the Line for Dodge In New TV Ads - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dalebuss/2017/05/01/fast-furious-star-vin-diesel-puts-it-all-on-the-line-for-dodge-in-new-tv-ads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFYPsXZWxXp16JFavGjmh5cqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 17:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dalebuss/2017/05/01/fast-furious-star-vin-diesel-puts-it-all-on-the-line-for-dodge-in-new-tv-ads/" target="_blank"&gt;'Fast &amp; Furious' Star Vin Diesel Puts It All On the Line for Dodge In New TV Ads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vin Diesel has driven Dodge performance vehicles for more than 15 years in his Fast &amp; Furious movies. And now Dodge has gained the ultimate imprimatur from the reigning hero of silver-screen chase scenes and spectacular car crashes: Diesel himself is starring in a new series of TV ads for Dodge. Fresh off a boffo worldwide box-office performance over the weekend by Diesel’s The Fate of the Furious, making it the globe’s top-grossing movie for the third straight week, Dodge is hatching three new TV ads starring Diesel under the slogan, “The Brotherhood of Muscle.” The one 60-second and two 3...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Jeep Said To Be More Valuable Than FCA -- Is A Spinoff Coming? - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2017/07/20/jeep-said-to-be-more-valuable-than-fca-is-a-spinoff-coming/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMyDrX0q9N52sZJwBF34ZCEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 17:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2017/07/20/jeep-said-to-be-more-valuable-than-fca-is-a-spinoff-coming/" target="_blank"&gt;Jeep Said To Be More Valuable Than FCA -- Is A Spinoff Coming?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo credit: MARCO BERTORELLO/AFP/Getty Images) Earlier this week it was reported that Morgan Stanley analyst Adam Jonas suggested the Jeep brand itself was actually worth more than its parent company, Fiat-Chrysler. Specifically, he pegged Jeep’s value at 120% of FCA’s market capitalization. It doesn’t take a financial whiz to wonder whether the question shouldn’t be if FCA will divest itself of the Jeep brand, but when. Back in April, FCA CEO Sergio Marchionne confided in an earnings call that spinning off either or both the Jeep and Ram brands was a possibility, though no steps have ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Should the 840-HP Dodge Challenger Demon Be Banned From Public Roads? - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2017/04/25/should-the-840-hp-dodge-challenger-demon-be-banned-from-public-roads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELM8wJ305GvyM1QL_AOd2hoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2017/04/25/should-the-840-hp-dodge-challenger-demon-be-banned-from-public-roads/" target="_blank"&gt;Should the 840-HP Dodge Challenger Demon Be Banned From Public Roads?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon is insanely fast, but is it too fast for public roads? When the rip-roaring street-legal drag racer known as the Dodge Challenger SRT Demon was unveiled at the New York International Auto Show earlier this month, we cracked wise about how, with a raging 840-horsepower supercharged V8 engine, the hellacious coupe was actually deemed “too fast” for NHRA racing. At least not without first installing a roll cage and the driver wearing a helmet and fire suit, packing a fire extinguisher, and earning an NHRA Competition License. But by the same logic, wouldn’t ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Sauber to unveil C36-Ferrari on February 20 - Motorsport Week</title><link>https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/13763</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaBhJXKWSYNniFvg2ko7JIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAows7DjATC75Q0wxtFi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:18:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/13763" target="_blank"&gt;Sauber to unveil C36-Ferrari on February 20&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Motorsport Week&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sauber has confirmed that it will unveil its 2017 challenger, the C36-Ferrari, on February 20, meaning the team is set to be the first to launch its new Formula 1 car. Sauber had already informed Motorsport Week that it intended to run its C36-Ferrari at the Circuit de Barcelona-Catalunya for the first time during a filming day on February 22, with its launch plans to be determined. Those plans have now been finalised, with images of the squad's new car set to be released two days before the C36-Ferrari hits the circuit in Spain. Confirmed 2017 Launch Dates Team Date Sauber February 20 Rena...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.motorsportweek.com">Motorsport Week</source></item><item><title>Dodge prepares to unleash the Demon in New York - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/dodge-demon-challenger-srt-new-york-auto-show/48831/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENkYbZnBEThkrlD4UvP2NkIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 06:37:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/dodge-demon-challenger-srt-new-york-auto-show/48831/" target="_blank"&gt;Dodge prepares to unleash the Demon in New York&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We usually loathe long, drawn out teaser campaigns, but we're willing to overlook that fact when it comes to the Dodge Challenger SRT Demon. The hyper-Hellcat will debut at the New York Auto Show next week, but a stream of details from Dodge means we already have an idea of what the car will be like. Suffice to say, Demon is an appropriate name. Step one in the transformation from Hellcat to Demon is, presumably, a strict diet and exercise plan. Dodge has shed 200 pounds (91 kg) from the regular Hellcat, pairing lightweight suspension, wheels and brakes with a single-seat interior. That's r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>475-hp Dodge Durango SRT is a muscle car in SUV clothing - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/dodge-durango-srt/47791/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOA5Q7zKjBc7lIC-6e41SfEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMMKDAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 04:23:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/dodge-durango-srt/47791/" target="_blank"&gt;475-hp Dodge Durango SRT is a muscle car in SUV clothing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once wild animals full of wanderlust, SUVs have long been domesticated into quiet, loyal family haulers used for bringing home groceries and shuttling sports and spectator gear to the field. Dodge believes that there's still some feral nature left in these still-formidable beasts and it's drawing it out in a big way with the all-new Durango SRT. Dubbed the "Dodge Charger of the full-size SUV segment," the new Durango packs power and performance previously unimaginable for a factory Durango. We'll have to wait until the New York Auto Show in April to see the all-new Challenger SRT Demon, the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>Haas to launch VF-17 on February 26 - Motorsport Week</title><link>https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/13803</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAegXfFCoLH9YZG4LvHTr74qFwgEKg8IACoHCAows7DjATC75Q0wxtFi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 14:02:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/13803" target="_blank"&gt;Haas to launch VF-17 on February 26&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Motorsport Week&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Haas will launch its 2017 Formula 1 challenger, the VF-17, on the eve of Formula 1's opening pre-season test. More soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.motorsportweek.com">Motorsport Week</source></item><item><title>In pictures: Highlights from the 2017 Chicago Auto Show - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/chicago-auto-show-2017-photos-news/47868/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA3J-pXMx6NmqN-XssGQY2wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 01:00:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/chicago-auto-show-2017-photos-news/47868/" target="_blank"&gt;In pictures: Highlights from the 2017 Chicago Auto Show&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The annual Chicago Auto Show is the most consumer-driven of the automotive spectacles that happen in the United States. Always fun to visit, the CAS also has more floor space and ride-and-drive events included than any other show. This year, along with blacked-out trim packages, famous race cars and new reveals, there was also something for Star Wars and Lego fans. The 2017 Chicago Auto Show officially opened to the general public on Saturday, February 11. Here's what you can look forward to if you attend CAS this year. A prominent unveil at the Chicago Auto Show this year was the latest Ni...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>Suspect in Charlottesville Attack Had Displayed Troubling Behavior - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/08/13/us/suspect-in-charlottesville-attack-had-displayed-troubling-behavior.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENLWHK6UqObVCmOQsAGOzr0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww9oEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 00:58:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/08/13/us/suspect-in-charlottesville-attack-had-displayed-troubling-behavior.html" target="_blank"&gt;Suspect in Charlottesville Attack Had Displayed Troubling Behavior&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Family members, acquaintances and internet postings suggested that James Alex Fields had gone mostly unnoticed, even as he seemingly trafficked in radical views.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Dodge prices 2018 Durango SRT at $133 per horse - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/dodge-durango-srt-priced/50383/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKfrBhCiNnBo7F_1qJPnGsQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMMKDAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 07:33:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/dodge-durango-srt-priced/50383/" target="_blank"&gt;Dodge prices 2018 Durango SRT at $133 per horse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dodge has put a price tag on the 475-hp sport utility/muscle car hybrid it unveiled at the Chicago Auto Show in February. At a mere US$133 per horse, the 2018 Dodge Durango SRT provides 392 cubic inches of HEMI V8 power that can do 0-60 mph (0-92 km/h) sprints in 4.4 seconds, quarter miles in 12.9 seconds, and even tow up to 8,700 lb (3,946 kg) of trailer. The 2018 Durango SRT is priced at US$62,995 before delivery. That places it in the semi-attainable bracket for a lot of buyers, though it makes the SRT the highest-priced of the Durango models. The next highest is currently the Citadel mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>2018 Dodge Demon: Even In Today's Homogenized Automotive World, Some Brands Still Do Crazy - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/kbrauer/2017/07/19/2018-dodge-demon-even-in-todays-homogenized-automotive-world-some-brands-still-do-crazy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIKhVnl0zeccTh2IJJO8Vo4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 04:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/kbrauer/2017/07/19/2018-dodge-demon-even-in-todays-homogenized-automotive-world-some-brands-still-do-crazy/" target="_blank"&gt;2018 Dodge Demon: Even In Today's Homogenized Automotive World, Some Brands Still Do Crazy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Demon’s intimidating look screams “Get out of the way!” “What’s this car’s story?” That’s a reasonable question anyone might ask after glancing through the 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon’s spec sheet. If this high-performance Challenger’s 840 horsepower V8 doesn’t raise your eyebrows, the contract every owner must sign surely will. Its stipulations include not driving it in the rain (its drag radial tires offer minimal wet grip) and not letting passengers ride where the passenger and rear seat used to be (assuming that’s how you spec your Challenger SRT Demon). This is also the first s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>New Ferrari SF70H hits the track for the first time - Motorsport Week</title><link>https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/13879</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELKASNh-MnQ3VEZPDR50Fs0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAows7DjATC75Q0wxtFi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 12:12:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/13879" target="_blank"&gt;New Ferrari SF70H hits the track for the first time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Motorsport Week&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following the launch of Ferrari’s new 2017 Formula 1 car, the SF70H has now hit the track for the first time at Fiorano. 2007 world champion Kimi Räikkönen took to the Ferrari test circuit to put the SF70H through its paces. The team’s 2017 challenger was officially unveiled in an online video on Friday morning, shortly before it emerged on track. Ferrari shared a video of the car heading out onto the circuit with Raikkonen behind the wheel. VIDEO: Watch the SF70H hit the race track The car will make its public track debut at the Circuit de Barcelona-Catalunya on February 27, the first day ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.motorsportweek.com">Motorsport Week</source></item><item><title>Review: Going Hazzard in a 2017 Dodge Challenger GT - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/2017-dodge-challenger-gt-review/49163/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGVzw64sw0wEYw2ON5IwUHcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 21:17:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/2017-dodge-challenger-gt-review/49163/" target="_blank"&gt;Review: Going Hazzard in a 2017 Dodge Challenger GT&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bo and Luke Duke may have been driving a Charger back in the day, but the 1969 Charger's successor is definitely the current-generation Challenger. Put behind the wheel of the 2017 Dodge Challenger GT in bright orange paint – as we drove it – you may want to change your name, too. The Challenger GT is Dodge's all-wheel-drive muscle coupe, offering something that those of us living in the land of inclement weather and dirt roads have long wanted. When the 2017 Challenger GT was shown as a concept back in November of 2015, we were drooling. When it finally dropped a year later, there was some...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon Test Drive And Review: Draggin' The Line - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonfogelson/2017/07/31/2018-dodge-challenger-srt-demon-test-drive-and-review-draggin-the-line/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE4RoTNE_RbwXoB53MSiiFQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonfogelson/2017/07/31/2018-dodge-challenger-srt-demon-test-drive-and-review-draggin-the-line/" target="_blank"&gt;2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon Test Drive And Review: Draggin' The Line&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m not a drag racer, but the 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon could convert me to the sport. In the what may be the coup de grace of the muscle car wars, Dodge has created the ultimate straight-line weapon. The numbers are staggering: • 0-30 mph in 1.0 seconds • 0-60 mph in 2.3 seconds (Fastest production car in the world) • 1.8g acceleration (Highest g-force of any production car) • 9.65 seconds and 140 mph for the quarter-mile (Fastest quarter-mile production car) • 840 hp and 770 lb-ft of torque 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon No other production V8 comes close. It’s been decades since a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Fiat Chrysler recalls 1.33 million vehicles over fire, air bag risks - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-fiat-chrysler-recall-idUSKBN19Z0U7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEc10ikgNivgDrAQEjr3KA0qFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 13:17:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-fiat-chrysler-recall-idUSKBN19Z0U7" target="_blank"&gt;Fiat Chrysler recalls 1.33 million vehicles over fire, air bag risks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By David Shepardson WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Fiat Chrysler Automobiles NV (FCHA.MI: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) said on Friday it is recalling 1.33 million vehicles worldwide in two separate campaigns for potential fire risks and inadvertent airbag deployments. The Italian-American automaker said it is recalling about 770,000 sport utility vehicles because of a wiring issue that may lead to inadvertent deployment of the driver-side air bag and is linked to reports of five related minor injuries, but no crashes. The company said wiring could chafe against pieces of steering-wheel tri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>2017 Dodge Challenger T/A: As Good As Retro Gets - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kbrauer/2017/08/14/2017-dodge-challenger-ta-as-good-as-retro-gets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFcdINjmttwdR3PsBdmNLRgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kbrauer/2017/08/14/2017-dodge-challenger-ta-as-good-as-retro-gets/" target="_blank"&gt;2017 Dodge Challenger T/A: As Good As Retro Gets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some things hold up well after 47 years, like the Challenger T/A’s styling Holding up well for 47 years isn’t easy. Ask anyone in that age range and, if they’re honest, they’ll confirm it. Same goes for art, fashion, literature and design. The best-selling book (and top-grossing movie) in 1970 was “Love Story”. Bell-bottoms were all the rage, and wall-to-wall shag carpet (often in avocado green) covered many a living room floors. But 1970 also gave us “The Godfather” to read, a “Bridge Over Troubled Water” to hear, Andy Warhol’s Marilyn Monroe screenprint to look at, and the 1970 Dodge Chal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Dodge Demon pricing reveals it's good bang for your buck - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/dodge-demon-challenger-pricing/49704/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO-dd2rpXcMyLaRdLwtTSEUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 04:31:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/dodge-demon-challenger-pricing/49704/" target="_blank"&gt;Dodge Demon pricing reveals it's good bang for your buck&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dodge Demon caused a serious stir when it launched at the New York Auto Show in April, but some details remained unclear: namely, how much it would cost. Now we have a price tag, it's clear the road-legal dragster offers more horsepower-per-dollar than you can get almost anywhere else. Dodge will be selling the Demon for US$84,995 without any options, making it $35,000 more expensive with the (slightly) less powerful, (significantly) less focused SRT Hellcat. That's a lot of money for what is, at its core, the same unsophisticated Challenger first shown in 2008. Although there are a few...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>Dodge &amp; Burn - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/221896481/dodge-burn-by-rune-christiansen</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH699987qPHHlCdlFotk0jcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 07:55:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/221896481/dodge-burn-by-rune-christiansen" target="_blank"&gt;Dodge &amp; Burn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dodge Challenger. 1973 or 1974 I think?&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Special Dodge Challenger lights the birthday candles for Mopar - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/mopar-dodge-challenger-80-chicago/47861/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOEbq_bdB-rGxJwQ8BrwfpEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 19:03:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/mopar-dodge-challenger-80-chicago/47861/" target="_blank"&gt;Special Dodge Challenger lights the birthday candles for Mopar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chicago Auto Show might not have produced the same stack of big-ticket reveals as Detroit, but that doesn't mean McCormick Place was completely devoid of cool new cars. Along with the Hyundai Elantra GT Sport and Toyota RAV4 Adventure, the show played host to the Dodge Challenger Mopar, a two-tone special designed to celebrate 80 years worth of big wings, hood scoops and antifreeze from Mopar. In the Mopar Challenger, power comes from the same 392 HEMI V8 you'll find in a base Challenger R/T 392, which means it makes 485 hp (362 kW) and 644 Nm of torque. The motor is fitted with the Sha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>Team New Zealand boat capsizes in America’s Cup challenger semi-final - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2017/jun/06/team-new-zealand-boat-capsizes-americas-cup-challenger-semi-final-land-rover-bar</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENcz8QYbA9tcXvAtIRfLIZIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 20:36:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2017/jun/06/team-new-zealand-boat-capsizes-americas-cup-challenger-semi-final-land-rover-bar" target="_blank"&gt;Team New Zealand boat capsizes in America’s Cup challenger semi-final&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Team New Zealand capsized during the run-in to the second race of their America’s Cup challenger semi-final against Great Britain’s Land Rover BAR in Bermuda. All crew members were later reported safe. Related: Great Britain’s Land Rover BAR fall 2-0 behind in America’s Cup pursuit After winning the first race on Tuesday against Sir Ben Ainslie’s syndicate to move 3-0 ahead in the first-to-five contest, the New Zealanders were heading towards the start line under strong winds when the boat rose up on its foils and plunged forward into the water. Ainslie said in a statement on BAR’s official...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Ferocious 840-Horsepower Dodge Challenger SRT Demon Elevates All Dodge Products - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/joshmax/2017/04/14/ferocious-840-horsepower-dodge-challenger-srt-demon-elevates-all-dodge-products/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFDLE6wII3FJhHVL_vPTmOUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/joshmax/2017/04/14/ferocious-840-horsepower-dodge-challenger-srt-demon-elevates-all-dodge-products/" target="_blank"&gt;Ferocious 840-Horsepower Dodge Challenger SRT Demon Elevates All Dodge Products&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon All car nuts have no doubt gawked and day-ummed over the 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon, the fastest production car in the world (for now) as revealed during this week’s NY Auto show and of which Dodge says: “is shaking the foundation of the entire performance car industry.” 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon Some Demon highlights, if you’re not in the loop: 840 horsepower and 770 pounds-feet of torque from supercharged 6.2-liter HEMI® Demon V-8 engine - Highest horsepower V-8 production car engine ever produced - First-ever front-wheel lift in production car...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>New York International Auto Show 2017: Luxury, Utility Vehicles And Power - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/stephaniebrinley/2017/04/10/new-york-international-auto-show-2017-luxury-utility-vehicles-and-power/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH7uwo5bfpSGU9GrBsjPzskqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/stephaniebrinley/2017/04/10/new-york-international-auto-show-2017-luxury-utility-vehicles-and-power/" target="_blank"&gt;New York International Auto Show 2017: Luxury, Utility Vehicles And Power&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;2018 Jeep® Grand Cherokee Trackhawk Image courtesy of Jeep The 2017 New York International Auto Show opens to the public at the end of this week, with media introductions throughout the week. As we head into the last large North American auto show for the season, the most buzzworthy and attention-getting reveals are expected to include a 707-hp Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk and drag-race-ready Dodge Challenger SRT Demon. The show will also feature a number of new utility vehicles, including a concept from Toyota teasing a possible FJ Cruiser followup. Here’s my take on what to watch for thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Fiat Chrysler Recalls 771,000 Vehicles For Inadvertent Air Bag Deployment - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/jensen/2017/07/14/fiat-chrysler-recalls-771000-vehicles-for-inadvertent-air-bag-deployment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGHIfuP5jJ60OhxKr1HT9jcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 10:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/jensen/2017/07/14/fiat-chrysler-recalls-771000-vehicles-for-inadvertent-air-bag-deployment/" target="_blank"&gt;Fiat Chrysler Recalls 771,000 Vehicles For Inadvertent Air Bag Deployment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GIUSEPPE CACACE/AFP/Getty Images By Christopher Jensen Fiat Chrysler is recalling about 1.3 million vehicles, including almost 771,000 because a wiring problem could cause the driver’s airbag to deploy without the vehicle being in an accident, according to reports from the automaker posted Friday on the website of the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. The remaining 565,000 vehicles have problem with the alternator that could cause the vehicle to stall. The automaker said airbag deployment could be caused if wiring chafes and causes a short circuit. It said it was aware of five...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Trans Teen Gavin Grimm Responds To Laverne Cox Shout Out At The Grammys - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/gavin-grimm-laverne-cox_us_58a1d422e4b03df370d88bd3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGVP9KdesgdvHw8FB14gx0IqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 16:58:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/gavin-grimm-laverne-cox_us_58a1d422e4b03df370d88bd3" target="_blank"&gt;Trans Teen Gavin Grimm Responds To Laverne Cox Shout Out At The Grammys&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A transgender teen whose fight for civil rights is headed to the Supreme Court in March received the shock of a lifetime when Laverne Cox used her stage time at the Grammys on Sunday to draw visibility to his case. Gavin Grimm is a 17-year-old transgender boy who fought against the Gloucester County School Board in Virginia for rights to use the public school bathroom that corresponds with his gender identity. With his upcoming March 28 SCOTUS case having major, historic implications for the trans community, Cox dedicated her intro to Lady Gaga and Metallica’s performance to tell viewers, “...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>All-weather Challenger makes muscle more accessible - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/dodge-challenger-gt-awd/46846/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDj62Oldctofpm2ag57DVHkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 10:21:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/dodge-challenger-gt-awd/46846/" target="_blank"&gt;All-weather Challenger makes muscle more accessible&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Classic muscle cars weren't known for being easy, approachable vehicles to drive. With lots of power running to the rear wheels, the middle of winter wasn't the best time to pull out your pony car. It's a very different story in 2016, with the advent of traction control turning big, powerful muscle cars into pussycats. Now Dodge is making life easier again, adding all-wheel drive to the Challenger. This all-weather muscle car has been a long time coming. Rumors of a Challenger with all-wheel drive have been circling for the past 12 months, and Dodge fanned the fire by releasing the Challeng...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>The 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon to Make Hellcat a Tame Kitten - Men's Health</title><link>http://www.menshealth.com/guy-wisdom/2018-dodge-challenger-srt-demon</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH84_pO6VxA7YxmcJgjVhSEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowkJcIMIFmMPqVBA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 18:50:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.menshealth.com/guy-wisdom/2018-dodge-challenger-srt-demon" target="_blank"&gt;The 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon to Make Hellcat a Tame Kitten&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Men's Health&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because 707-horsepower just wasn’t enough. Cue the drool Image by Youtube/dodge We’re in an era where muscle car horsepower isn’t just creepingly steadily skyward; it’s rocketing up like a ballistic missile. A bombastic projectile descriptor seems quite apt, given Dodge’s latest announcement that the 2018 Dodge Challenger SRT Demon will dethrone the Hellcat as the marque’s ultimate performance halo car. Full details are still murky, but the demotion of the tire-shredding, face-melting, howling 707-horsepower Hellcat from a savage, feral beast to subdued house cat seems imminent as Dodge ram...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.menshealth.com">Men's Health</source></item><item><title>Dodge unveils one-seat 840-horsepower muscle car - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2017/04/11/autos/dodge-challenger-demon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJhzPqAjqGZFCs5VuFxPrUYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 13:54:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2017/04/11/autos/dodge-challenger-demon/" target="_blank"&gt;Dodge unveils one-seat 840-horsepower muscle car&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dodge Challenger SRT Demon is not a car for normal people. For starters, it comes standard with only one seat. Because passenger seats, and passengers, weigh too much and would slow it down. Your friends aren't worth that. Then there's the engine. The Demon's 840-horsepower 6.2-liter supercharged V8 is the most powerful V8 engine ever put into a regular production car. That makes the Demon the most powerful factory-produced muscle car ... ever. That record had previously been held by the 707-horsepower Dodge Challenger Hellcat, which seems like a house cat compared with the Demon, a car...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Dodge Demon: An unhinged 840 hp dragster in civilian clothes - New Atlas</title><link>http://newatlas.com/dodge-demon-new-york-auto-show-reveal/48953/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIvPXofttFaa8VX8DvyYd2UqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMMKDAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 03:25:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://newatlas.com/dodge-demon-new-york-auto-show-reveal/48953/" target="_blank"&gt;Dodge Demon: An unhinged 840 hp dragster in civilian clothes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After one of the longest teases in history, Dodge has unchained the Demon in New York. As predicted, it's one of the wildest production cars ever created, with 840 hp (626 kW) being put to a set of drag radials. It'll match a Tesla off the line, and makes the Hellcat look leisurely over the quarter-mile thanks to a focus previously unseen in muscle cars. Meet the new king of all-American performance. There are so many crazy details on the Demon it's hard to focus on just one, but lets start with the thing that defines any good muscle car: what's under the hood. The engine is a supercharged ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>Heather Heyer, Charlottesville Victim, Cannot Be Silenced, Mother Says - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/08/16/us/charlottesville-heather-heyer-memorial-mother.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELquunJFClC4m9FzFAFJGCEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwloEY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 20:10:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/08/16/us/charlottesville-heather-heyer-memorial-mother.html" target="_blank"&gt;Heather Heyer, Charlottesville Victim, Cannot Be Silenced, Mother Says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At a memorial service, Ms. Heyer was remembered for a quality described as her most frustrating, and most admired — a passion for fighting injustice.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Gallery: Customs, classics and absolute car chaos at SEMA 2018 - New Atlas</title><link>https://newatlas.com/cars-of-sema-2018/57080/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENhCs_gUW_6isMIcr0z4YYEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 04:17:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newatlas.com/cars-of-sema-2018/57080/" target="_blank"&gt;Gallery: Customs, classics and absolute car chaos at SEMA 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Late October is the time of year when Americans young and old dress up and become someone - or something - else for a day or two. It's also the time when American vehicles young and old get dressed into something else and parade around the annual SEMA Show. Some are pretty, some pretty terrifying. This year's show proved a bit tamer than last year (no all-new 300-mph supercars or $1.5 million off-road motorhomes, we're aware of), but it was still wall-to-wall with lusty sports cars, delicious retromods and all other styles of wild one-of-a-kinds. We're focusing solely on cars (and things th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>State Farm Mocks Lemonade's Use Of AI, Doubles Down On 48,000 Human Agents. Not A Great Idea. - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/chunkamui/2018/10/24/state-farm-mocks-lemonades-use-of-ai-doubles-down-on-48000-human-agents-not-a-great-idea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHWWLYTUjnr3_wOeB4Q-dPoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 17:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/chunkamui/2018/10/24/state-farm-mocks-lemonades-use-of-ai-doubles-down-on-48000-human-agents-not-a-great-idea/" target="_blank"&gt;State Farm Mocks Lemonade's Use Of AI, Doubles Down On 48,000 Human Agents. Not A Great Idea.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Source: Getty. An unmanned car driven by a search engine company? We’ve seen that movie. It ends with robots harvesting our bodies for energy. That is a line from a 2011 Chrysler car commercial mocking Google’s self-driving car project. Another Chrysler commercial was even more blunt: “Robots can take our food, our clothes and our homes. But, they will never take our cars.” Chrysler’s early mocking of Google’s efforts exemplifies the fact that few cling to the status quo tighter than the companies that best understand it and have the most stake in preserving it. It is just human nature to v...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Jeep wants you to take this Grand Cherokee on the racetrack - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/09/25/jeep-grand-cherokee-trackhawk-orig.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHTAyOwXx-g8dcexy1-LvvoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/09/25/jeep-grand-cherokee-trackhawk-orig.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;Jeep wants you to take this Grand Cherokee on the racetrack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new 707hp Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk has the same supercharged Hemi engine as the Dodge Challenger Hellcat muscle car. Why put 707hp in an SUV? Because you can. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Dodge Demon: Take off in most powerful muscle car ever - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/09/25/dodge-demon-powerful-muscle-car-orig.cnn-business</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPq1o6XzvGzTtl1sgtpCEGQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 15:10:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/09/25/dodge-demon-powerful-muscle-car-orig.cnn-business" target="_blank"&gt;Dodge Demon: Take off in most powerful muscle car ever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2018 Dodge Challenger Demon claims to go from 0 to 60 in 2.3 seconds, making it the fastest production car in history. See the Demon standout on the drag strip and underwhelm on the road. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Dodge pops a wheelie in test - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2017/04/13/dodge-challenger-demon-fast.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPzG9sN-jD3snJ8Q3KCqj9AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 02:30:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2017/04/13/dodge-challenger-demon-fast.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;New Dodge pops a wheelie in test&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new Dodge Challenger Demon is setting multiple records for a production car, but Dodge had to leave out some key things, like passenger seats, to make that happen. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Dodge's SRT Hellcat Redeye launches with a scorching 797 horsepower - New Atlas</title><link>https://newatlas.com/2019-dodge-challenger-srt-hellcat-redeye/55284/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDzqPUXJxzp8xpPDq0TyrEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 04:31:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newatlas.com/2019-dodge-challenger-srt-hellcat-redeye/55284/" target="_blank"&gt;Dodge's SRT Hellcat Redeye launches with a scorching 797 horsepower&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sun's out, guns out! Dodge has ripped the sleeves off its flannel shirt to present the new king of production muscle cars. The 2019 Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat Redeye makes 797 hp (594 kW) and 707 lb-ft (959 Nm) of torque. It hits 60 mph (96.5 km/h) in 3.4 seconds, does 203 mph (327 km/h) flat out, starts at 70 grand and produces more smoke than the crowd at a Phish concert. Buoyed by the success of its high-performance Scat Pack, Dodge has upgraded the nasty end of its catalog for 2019. We should've seen it coming; mess around with the Scat Pack for too long, and you're bound to end up wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>Fiat Chrysler Turns Up The Boost Yet Again For The 2019 Dodge Challenger Hellcat Redeye - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/samabuelsamid/2018/06/28/fiat-chrysler-turns-up-the-boost-yet-again-for-the-2019-dodge-challenger-hellcat-redeye/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_v6J6YgSBpOEN_hOjydggqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 15:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/samabuelsamid/2018/06/28/fiat-chrysler-turns-up-the-boost-yet-again-for-the-2019-dodge-challenger-hellcat-redeye/" target="_blank"&gt;Fiat Chrysler Turns Up The Boost Yet Again For The 2019 Dodge Challenger Hellcat Redeye&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;2019 Dodge Challenger Hellcat Redeye At the recent Fiat Chrysler capital markets day, the Dodge and Chrysler brands were notable for the lack of any reference in the 5 year plan. Just because they weren’t mentioned, it doesn’t mean that at least Dodge has been completely forgotten . For the 2019 model year the long running Challenger coupe gets yet another performance upgrade with the 797-hp Hellcat Redeye variant. While most other FCA brands including the premium Maserati lineup are getting a range of electrification options in the next few years, Dodge is staying old school with more pow...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Why The Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk Is A Truly Extraordinary SUV - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2018/06/26/why-the-jeep-grand-cherokee-trackhawk-is-a-truly-extraordinary-suv/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFHfj_7Xhr4yV__gvJhokXMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2018/06/26/why-the-jeep-grand-cherokee-trackhawk-is-a-truly-extraordinary-suv/" target="_blank"&gt;Why The Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk Is A Truly Extraordinary SUV&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo credit: Mark Kauzlarich/Bloomberg. Think of it as a Ferrari that can carpool, carry up to 68.3 cubic feet of stowage, and tow up to 7,200 pounds. The new-for-2018 Trackhawk version of the popular Jeep Grand Cherokee SUV packs the 6.2-liter 707-horsepower supercharged V8 engine that otherwise resides under the hoods of the Dodge Challenger and Charger Hellcat models and, along with suspension and other performance-minded enhancements, imbues the popular people mover with abilities that leaves mere mortal SUVs in its dust. We were fortunate to put a Grand Cherokee Trackhawk on loan from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Review: 2018 Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk - we pity the fool that don’t drive one - New Atlas</title><link>https://newatlas.com/2018-jeep-grandcherokee-trackhawk-review/55144/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOua8oj2xe_pZKbXhalbSskqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMIKEAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 19:44:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newatlas.com/2018-jeep-grandcherokee-trackhawk-review/55144/" target="_blank"&gt;Review: 2018 Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk - we pity the fool that don’t drive one&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Grand Cherokee Trackhawk is 700+ horsepower worth of sport utility vehicle. It's crazy and awesome at the same time. We're convinced that if The A-Team were remade as a television show in 2018, B.A. Baracus would drive a Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk. Is stuffing 707 horsepower (527 kW) into a big, family-sized sport utility ludicrous? Of course it is. That hasn't stopped Fiat-Chrysler from doing so, though. If our time in the 2018 Durango SRT taught us anything, it's that nothing is sacred when it comes to the wanton power-stuffing that FCA is willing to do. And we're giddy with deligh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>In Praise Of Five All-American 2018 Cars - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/joshmax/2018/05/29/in-praise-of-five-all-american-2018-cars/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwlGCON_OnXjBFHJzBfFM4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 16:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/joshmax/2018/05/29/in-praise-of-five-all-american-2018-cars/" target="_blank"&gt;In Praise Of Five All-American 2018 Cars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;American cars are some of our favorite machines for a variety of reasons. Here are five Yankee Doodle Dandy vehicles that have particularly pleased us of late. 2018 Ford Expedition 2018 Ford Expedition The all-new Expedition is gorgeously wide, long, heavy (6,000 pounds, though it’s a little less chubby than last year’s model due to aluminum and lightweight components) and fit for celebs, CEOs or Mike and Carol Brady in 1969, before the kids hit puberty. It’s a throwback to those heady pre-electric, pre-hybrid days of yore, when big was better and everyone automaker hadn’t yet gotten into ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Fiat Chrysler recalls 4.8 million vehicles because they can get stuck in cruise control - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/40578013/fiat-chrysler-recalls-4-8-vehicles-because-they-can-get-stuck-in-cruise-control</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJtw8t9rGZdzCFc5j_9RZDYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 13:02:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/40578013/fiat-chrysler-recalls-4-8-vehicles-because-they-can-get-stuck-in-cruise-control" target="_blank"&gt;Fiat Chrysler recalls 4.8 million vehicles because they can get stuck in cruise control&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiat Chrysler announced a recall for 4.8 million of its vehicles Friday over an issue that causes them to get stuck in cruise control. The problem occurs when the vehicle is forced to accelerate while cruise control is engaged, something that might happen while it’s climbing a steep hill, for instance. That acceleration can cause a short circuit, which causes the vehicle to be locked in cruise control. Drivers are still able to slow down their vehicle by hitting the breaks or shifting into neutral, CNN reports. No injuries have been reported, and the issue has reportedly only happened once....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>vanishing point - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/247959031/vanishing-point-by-roblfc1892-roberto-pavic</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEApZhPDwi4_38B1IN3vxWWMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 18:09:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/247959031/vanishing-point-by-roblfc1892-roberto-pavic" target="_blank"&gt;vanishing point&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;for you...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>2018 Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk, Fast, Loud, Expensive And Yet Still Useful - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/samabuelsamid/2018/02/26/2018-jeep-grand-cherokee-trackhawk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMnMJqdwrHMM0nn6VWzY7wcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 13:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/samabuelsamid/2018/02/26/2018-jeep-grand-cherokee-trackhawk/" target="_blank"&gt;2018 Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk, Fast, Loud, Expensive And Yet Still Useful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;2018 Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk When I was a budding young car geek back in the late 1970s, the first car magazine I ever bought was a copy of Road &amp; Track with the Ferrari 308 GTS on the cover. This was more than two years before anyone ever heard of Magnum P.I. In those days before supercar or hypercar were terms of art, a Ferrari was an exotic. The early carbureted 308s would “sprint” from 0-60 in a leisurely 7.5 seconds or so. Somehow in 2018, you can wander into your local Jeep dealer and buy an SUV that weighs nearly two and a half times as much, has nearly three times the power an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Video: Ferrari fires up its 2018 challenger for the first time - Motorsport Week</title><link>https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/16883</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMS476N9ZbWBEjY9XGKyK7MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAows7DjATC75Q0wxtFi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 14:44:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.motorsportweek.com/news/id/16883" target="_blank"&gt;Video: Ferrari fires up its 2018 challenger for the first time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Motorsport Week&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ferrari has fired up its 2018 challenger for the first time, a major milestone for any team ahead of its February 22nd launch.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.motorsportweek.com">Motorsport Week</source></item><item><title>Turning up the heat at the 2018 Rocky Mountain Redline Ice Driving Adventure - New Atlas</title><link>https://newatlas.com/redlineice2018-ice-driving-colorado/53173/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPN_FkO7z0fVLHoIUzqi2G0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMMKDAQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 06:00:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newatlas.com/redlineice2018-ice-driving-colorado/53173/" target="_blank"&gt;Turning up the heat at the 2018 Rocky Mountain Redline Ice Driving Adventure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Driving a vehicle on ice usually means being careful and very slow so as not to slide or lose control. These things were completely thrown out the window on our visit to Winter Park, Colorado, for the 2018 Rocky Mountain Redline Ice Driving Adventure, where we were lucky enough to drive a variety of vehicles on ice under the supervision of race drivers. Here's what ensued. Several great vehicles from brands like Acura, Alfa Romeo, Dodge, Honda, Lexus, Mercedes-Benz, Porsche, and Toyota were in attendance for this ice driving event, all wearing winter tires from Pirelli, Blizzak, and Micheli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>Winter Driving: Exotic Cars, Performance Cars And SUVs Play In The Snowy Colorado Rockies - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kbrauer/2018/01/29/winter-driving-exotic-cars-performance-cars-and-suvs-play-in-the-snowy-colorado-rockies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILDBZfGiWz9T1m19OlGywMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kbrauer/2018/01/29/winter-driving-exotic-cars-performance-cars-and-suvs-play-in-the-snowy-colorado-rockies/" target="_blank"&gt;Winter Driving: Exotic Cars, Performance Cars And SUVs Play In The Snowy Colorado Rockies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Acura NSX’s Super Handling All-Wheel Drive offered superb control The most intersecting aspect of driving a car in winter weather is how the basic rules haven’t changed in over 100 years. Whether you’re in a skinny-tired 1918 Ford Model T or the latest Super Handling All-Wheel-Drive Acura the laws of physics still apply. Yeah, we’ve bent those laws and increased the safety of driving a car on ice- and snow-packed roads, but we haven’t eliminated them. I was just given a refresher course on the rules of winter driving in Colorado. As a Colorado native, one who has spent the last 24 years...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>U.S. carmakers have a remedy for slower sales: pickups and more pickups - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-autoshow-detroit-outlook/u-s-carmakers-have-a-remedy-for-slower-sales-pickups-and-more-pickups-idUSKBN1F634V</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF_ulMu9nkW04MmRW2wOTbsqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 23:27:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-autoshow-detroit-outlook/u-s-carmakers-have-a-remedy-for-slower-sales-pickups-and-more-pickups-idUSKBN1F634V" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. carmakers have a remedy for slower sales: pickups and more pickups&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Nick Carey DETROIT (Reuters) - Overall U.S. new vehicle sales could fall for the second year in a row in 2018, but Detroit's automakers are betting they can sell more high-margin pickup trucks and sport utilities to prop up profits. At this week's Detroit auto show, auto industry executives and economists predicted that overall car and light truck sales will fall to about 16.8 million vehicles this year from about 17.2 million vehicles in 2017. Rising interest rates, reduced access to easy credit and an influx of millions of nearly new vehicles that are cheaper than new models and are ex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Ford's most powerful street car ever: New 700 horsepower Mustang - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2018/01/16/luxury/ford-gt500/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPlM6R3NLxJPMySt8LP9z8QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 17:45:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2018/01/16/luxury/ford-gt500/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ford's most powerful street car ever: New 700 horsepower Mustang&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new Ford Mustang Shelby GT500 will have over 700 horsepower, making it be the most powerful street-legal production car the company has ever made. Ford made the announcement at the Detroit Auto Show, and screened a dimly lit teaser video that gave a glimpse of a few of the car's parts, including a large rear wing. The GT500 will exceed even the power output of the Ford GT, Ford's $450,000 exotic supercar. That car can produce 647 horsepower from a turbocharged V6 engine. Since the GT500 will have over 700 horsepower, it also has a good chance of out-powering the Dodge Challenger Hellcat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>2018 Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk: The Most Powerful SUV Ever? - The Wall Street Journal</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/2018-jeep-grand-cherokee-trackhawk-the-most-powerful-suv-ever-1515691262</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQX2Yv6BmobSwUtf9lJXiQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow1tzJATDnyxUw54IY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/2018-jeep-grand-cherokee-trackhawk-the-most-powerful-suv-ever-1515691262" target="_blank"&gt;2018 Jeep Grand Cherokee Trackhawk: The Most Powerful SUV Ever?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Wall Street Journal&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE FIAT Chrysler Automobiles (FCA) family, the Jeep Grand Cherokee ($31,690-$86,995) is the good son: a fine and thoroughly fastened midsize premium SUV, beloved in North America and quite profitable. The Dodge Challenger SRT Hellcat ($67,090) is the bad seed: a muscle car, a time capsule of entitled masculinity putting its smoldering rubber boots on the dinner table while people are still eating. The Hellcat’s Alpha-ness comes courtesy of its supercharged 6.2-liter pushrod V8, producing 707 hp and a sound like a tornado trapped in an elevator. While the Hellcat brand has been a masters...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.wsj.com">The Wall Street Journal</source></item><item><title>These were the exotic supercars of 2017 - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2017/12/27/luxury/2017-exotic-supercars/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDscwPa57uLavGwPQmgUs2MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 15:16:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2017/12/27/luxury/2017-exotic-supercars/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;These were the exotic supercars of 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More automakers are getting into the insane, high-horsepower supercar thing these days. That's great: The trend provided a variety of outrageously expensive and totally impractical cars to write about in 2017. There's the Ford GT, for instance. It's essentially a racecar that was engineered to be legally driven on the street. I would say that practical considerations took a back seat here -- but, of course, there aren't any. The thing resembling a trunk is so small, you could barely fit lunch in it. The GT is also quite impractical to buy. First, you must apply and be approved by Ford. Seco...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>White Nationalist Now Faces First-Degree Murder in Charlottesville Killing - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/12/14/us/charlottesville-fields-white-supremists.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEu8KkZ6yZmUJoOoW91wYkcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 01:38:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/12/14/us/charlottesville-fields-white-supremists.html" target="_blank"&gt;White Nationalist Now Faces First-Degree Murder in Charlottesville Killing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors increased the top charge against James Fields Jr., who is accused of driving his car into counterprotesters, killing Heather Heyer&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Charge upgraded against suspect in Charlottesville rally killing - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/12/14/us/charlottesville-james-alex-fields-court-appearance/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBeTyfWwFpcSA9Nd4z4yiyAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 06:01:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/12/14/us/charlottesville-james-alex-fields-court-appearance/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Charge upgraded against suspect in Charlottesville rally killing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dodge Challenger crept up, reversed, then accelerated toward the crowd. As he watched a surveillance video of that moment -- the car barreling toward people protesting a white nationalist rally in Charlottesville, Virginia last summer -- Marcus Martin grew angry and cursed out loud. "Take me out," Martin yelled during a hearing in Charlottesville on Thursday for James Alex Fields Jr., the man who prosecutors say drove the Challenger. Martin, who was injured as he pushed his fiancée out of the car's path, stormed out the courtroom. Prosecutors say Fields killed Heather Heyer, a 32-year-o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Tesla's X 100D Is "Vehicle Of The Year" In Our 2017's "Best And Worst" - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/joshmax/2017/12/11/teslas-x-100d-is-vehicle-of-the-year-in-our-2017s-best-and-worst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPl1eTHdNHfKW1Ye3R-Vqx0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/joshmax/2017/12/11/teslas-x-100d-is-vehicle-of-the-year-in-our-2017s-best-and-worst/" target="_blank"&gt;Tesla's X 100D Is "Vehicle Of The Year" In Our 2017's "Best And Worst"&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s the “best” and what’s the “worst” car? It varies from person to person, of course. For someone who just wants to get from “point A to point B,” a car that runs wins. Others with a feverish interest in vehicles will be more picky. For this year’s “best” list, we included some cars we’ve driven and had a ball in as well as some we’re still looking forward to driving. For the worst, well, read on. CAR OF THE YEAR: 2018 Tesla X 100D 2017 Tesla X 100D So much about Tesla’s X 100D just plain makes sense; not only its lack of emissions, but its self-driving mechanism, which, when all the b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Launching the Dodge Demon on a drag strip - CNN</title><link>http://money.cnn.com/2017/10/26/autos/dodge-challenger-demon-review/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGwx-8bIm8j3jEG_iahMvgwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrWrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 20:48:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://money.cnn.com/2017/10/26/autos/dodge-challenger-demon-review/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Launching the Dodge Demon on a drag strip&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have mixed feelings about the Dodge Challenger Demon. It's both an engineering masterpiece and, frankly, kind of dumb. It's an 840 horsepower Dodge Challenger muscle car that has been engineered specifically to do two things: Run the quarter mile in under 10 seconds and lift its front wheels off the ground during a hard launch. So, at the big automaker party where all the other car companies are talking about solving the world's transportation issues with electric cars and automated driving, Fiat Chrysler Automobiles, Dodge's parent company, is challenging everyone to a chugging contest. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://money.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>2018 Dodge Durango SRT review: Only in America - New Atlas</title><link>https://newatlas.com/2018-dodge-durango-srt-review/51956/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMFSKexpXsJRYRM5WWOC6y8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow8oA-MLswMJKBAQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 16:36:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://newatlas.com/2018-dodge-durango-srt-review/51956/" target="_blank"&gt;2018 Dodge Durango SRT review: Only in America&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Atlas&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dodge likes to build muscular-looking vehicles and then make special editions that really live up to that look – with some kind of blackout or gunmetal color thrown in to further bring the point home. The Durango SRT is the latest in the "shove horses under the hood" phenomenon that is Dodge. Imagine, if you can, an executive meeting in which a lead engineer stands in front of a group of suits and says "Ya, so, our latest plan is to take a family-hauling vehicle and let the SRT guys put their bigass V8 in it. Maybe put some Pirellis on there too." This being a corporate meeting at Dodge, th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://newatlas.com">New Atlas</source></item><item><title>FCA To Sell Aftermarket 707-HP Hellcat Engine, But There's A Catch - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2017/10/30/fca-to-sell-aftermarket-707-hp-hellcat-engine-but-theres-a-catch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDXN6hnD1jcV_RxbJB9DDUAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 18:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimgorzelany/2017/10/30/fca-to-sell-aftermarket-707-hp-hellcat-engine-but-theres-a-catch/" target="_blank"&gt;FCA To Sell Aftermarket 707-HP Hellcat Engine, But There's A Catch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new Mopar “Hellcrate” HEMI Engine kit provides what the automaker says is “relatively simple plug and play” with the 6.2-liter supercharged Crate HEMI Engine assembly. FCA’s Mopar division is unveiling a crate version of its 707-horsepower 6.2-liter supercharged V8 engine this week at the Specialty Equipment Market Association (SEMA)show in Las Vegas to help sate the voraciousness of power-hungry restomodders. Dubbed the “Hellcrate,” this is the same engine that powers the Hellcat versions of the full-size Dodge Challenger coupe and Charger sedan, and the new-for-2017 Trackhawk renditio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Dodge Demon: Most powerful muscle car ever - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2017/10/27/dodge-demon-muscle-car.cnnmoney</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJR9YJ5j67d_1HobgHzxNAoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 13:55:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/cnnmoney/2017/10/27/dodge-demon-muscle-car.cnnmoney" target="_blank"&gt;Dodge Demon: Most powerful muscle car ever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2018 Dodge Challenger Demon claims to go from 0 to 60 in 2.3 seconds, making in the fastest production car in history. See the Demon standout on the drag strip. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item></channel></rss>