<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>New Caledonia - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFZqTVRjU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-AU&amp;gl=AU&amp;ceid=AU:en</link><language>en-AU</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:50:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Magnitude-7.5 earthquake sparks tsunami warning for New Caledonia, Vanuatu, but no major damage reported - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-05/new-caledonia-vanuatu-tsunami-warning/10586412</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHO5g52dtBR6q0rdZnwbZH0qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:04:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-05/new-caledonia-vanuatu-tsunami-warning/10586412" target="_blank"&gt;Magnitude-7.5 earthquake sparks tsunami warning for New Caledonia, Vanuatu, but no major damage reported&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pacific Tsunami Warning Centre says the threat of tsunami waves has passed after a strong, shallow earthquake hit off the coast of New Caledonia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpPdjh1bGpZQU1FZFZBVTBISzVrNlJLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Buildings Evacuated in New Caledonia as Earthquake Hits - The Mercury</title><link>https://www.themercury.com.au/news/national/buildings-evacuated-in-new-caledonia-as-earthquake-hits/video/a1ac16c5574f89048f8e0355e2ff9616</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiigFodHRwczovL3d3dy50aGVtZXJjdXJ5LmNvbS5hdS9uZXdzL25hdGlvbmFsL2J1aWxkaW5ncy1ldmFjdWF0ZWQtaW4tbmV3LWNhbGVkb25pYS1hcy1lYXJ0aHF1YWtlLWhpdHMvdmlkZW8vYTFhYzE2YzU1NzRmODkwNDhmOGUwMzU1ZTJmZjk2MTbSAQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 22:15:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.themercury.com.au/news/national/buildings-evacuated-in-new-caledonia-as-earthquake-hits/video/a1ac16c5574f89048f8e0355e2ff9616" target="_blank"&gt;Buildings Evacuated in New Caledonia as Earthquake Hits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Mercury&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;People evacuated buildings in the French territory of New Caledonia in the South Pacific on the afternoon of Wednesday, December 5, after a 7.6-magnitude ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.themercury.com.au">The Mercury</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/I3OO8XIng4uQoLbbHGAjzmbPlPXmpoSaWb3r84u66dEjMoOAI_d4eUBjgBOpxtuGSSyL44qJ8jTdbSs4EttGjeXCksmUL8usQEwh61d4TcVpc-3Vq2X2uM2Jj6R8YfQLa_UaCpeliUAvaEi_3AEMNTjEmI87bXVE-xFM-Jv6WHr2sxm4xCdaiaOdzu5TK7nB7Hb_8Bjmq2oSoptv6BDfvt8-XXfdICX0J5Sxo1FsfK57yYP7MqD7i7_xjc89tNB7=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Tsunami warning after New Caledonia quake - The Advertiser</title><link>https://www.adelaidenow.com.au/news/world/big-magnitude-76-earthquake-hits-new-caledonia/news-story/ef78ba5a30d8700153f465d749101cee</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL7GlFjdUyQPYozWKJciex0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAow7--NCDDMtXIwhOSkAQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.adelaidenow.com.au/news/world/big-magnitude-76-earthquake-hits-new-caledonia/news-story/ef78ba5a30d8700153f465d749101cee" target="_blank"&gt;Tsunami warning after New Caledonia quake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Advertiser&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first quake, which struck about 3.30pm AEDT, appears to have been shallow — at just 10km beneath the Earth’s surface. At least five aftershocks also hit, ranging in magnitude from 5.6 to 6.0, within about 90 minutes. New Caledonia Earthquake TSUNAMI FEARS The Pacific Tsunami Warning Centre immediately issued a warning that hazardous tsunami waves could possibly affect locations up to 1000km away — including New Caledonia and Vanuatu - and that tsunami waves had been observed. The PTWC said tsunami waves of between one and three metres were possible, while waves of up to one metre were p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.adelaidenow.com.au">The Advertiser</source></item><item><title>Tsunami warning for Vanuatu and New Caledonia after 7.6 magnitude earthquake - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/earthquake-tsunami-warning-vanuatu-new-caledonia-76-magnitude</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPpHa-hnckWSRjyGTJeMTpwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 04:58:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/earthquake-tsunami-warning-vanuatu-new-caledonia-76-magnitude" target="_blank"&gt;Tsunami warning for Vanuatu and New Caledonia after 7.6 magnitude earthquake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A tsunami warning has been issued for the Pacific island of New Caledonia, after a shallow 7.6-magnitude earthquake struck off the country’s coast, prompting warnings that hazardous tsunami waves up to three metres high could reach New Caledonia and Vanuatu. The earthquake was a shallow 10km (6 miles) deep and occurred about 155km (95 miles) southeast of the Loyalty Islands, which are part of New Caledonia, a French territory, on Wednesday afternoon local time. “Based on the preliminary earthquake parameters, hazardous tsunami waves are possible for coasts located within 1,000km of the eart...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Magnitude 7.5 quake strikes in Pacific near New Caledonia - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/385642518b0b4efc8c4902d33d97b8fe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKkZvLZzuksyEv3ekOpBDDoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:34:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/385642518b0b4efc8c4902d33d97b8fe" target="_blank"&gt;Magnitude 7.5 quake strikes in Pacific near New Caledonia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — A powerful earthquake that struck in the southern Pacific Ocean on Wednesday sent jitters around the region after authorities warned of possible tsunamis, but there were no initial reports of destructive waves or major damage. The magnitude 7.5 quake hit in the afternoon near the French territory of New Caledonia at a shallow depth, where earthquakes are generally more damaging. It was felt as far away as Vanuatu, about 630 kilometers (390 miles) away Tsunami sirens blared across New Caledonia minutes after the quake. The Pacific Tsunami Warning Center said ts...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>7.6 quake hits near New Caledonia, hazardous tsunami waves possible - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445598-new-caledonia-quake-tsunami/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN-pdER137XHr4gMv3gEj-QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 04:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445598-new-caledonia-quake-tsunami/" target="_blank"&gt;7.6 quake hits near New Caledonia, hazardous tsunami waves possible&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A strong 7.6-magnitude undersea quake has hit off the coast of the French territory of New Caledonia in the South Pacific at a shallow depth, prompting a tsunami warning up to 1,000 km (600 miles) away. The quake struck some 168.2 km (104.5 mi) from the small town of Tadine of the Loyalty Islands, New Caledonia, United States Geological Survey (USGS) reported. Tsunami alerts have been issued for both New Caledonia and nearby Vanuatu, a state in the South Pacific consisting of some 80 islets with a population of 270,000 people. The depth of the quake is just 10 km (6.2 mi), meaning that is i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Pacific Island Hopper: The world's most scenic flight? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/pacific-island-hopper/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJzEiTC66D4pXFj5tFPgbCcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 09:39:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/pacific-island-hopper/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pacific Island Hopper: The world's most scenic flight?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spectacular scenic flight: Aviation geeks call it "the holy grail of flight routes" -- welcome on board United Airlines 154, the Island Hopper. Chris Dwyer Incredible experience: The Island Hopper flight connects seven islands in a 16-hour flight, four times weekly. Chris Dwyer 50 year anniversary: 2018 marks half a century since the route was first flown. Back in 1968 Continental Micronesia was the carrier. Chris Dwyer First stop: There are four pilots on board the plane to share the route. First stop? Marjuro, in the Marshall Islands. Courtesy Chris Dwyer Marjuro harbor: The Marshall Isla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Caledonia earthquake: Tsunami warning issued after massive 7.6-magnitude quake - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/new-caledonia-earthquake-tsunami-warning-vanuatu-pacific-usgs-a8667706.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChxYeNVKna7JpIVKSGWK2MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/new-caledonia-earthquake-tsunami-warning-vanuatu-pacific-usgs-a8667706.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Caledonia earthquake: Tsunami warning issued after massive 7.6-magnitude quake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A tsunami warning has been issued for some southern Pacific islands after a huge 7.6-magnitude earthquake struck off the coast of New Caledonia. Monitors detected the epicentre of the earthquake at a shallow 10km (6 miles) deep, about 155 km (95 miles) southeast of the Loyalty Islands on New Caledonia's east coast. The Pacific Tsunami Warning Center issued a statement saying: "Hazardous tsunami waves from this earthquake are possible within 1,000 km (600 miles) of the epicentre along the coasts of Vanuatu and New Caledonia." Tsunami waves of between 3ft and 10ft were possible along the east...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>New Caledonia, Vanuatu order evacuations after powerful quake, but suffer little impact - Reuters</title><link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-quake-newcaledonia/massive-7-6-quake-prompts-tsunami-warning-off-new-caledonia-ptwc-idUKKBN1O40DL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFKtTzXV3YI2SGgcSvRSlPUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:08:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-quake-newcaledonia/massive-7-6-quake-prompts-tsunami-warning-off-new-caledonia-ptwc-idUKKBN1O40DL" target="_blank"&gt;New Caledonia, Vanuatu order evacuations after powerful quake, but suffer little impact&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Caledonia and Vanuatu ordered coastal evacuations on Wednesday after a powerful undersea earthquake triggered tsunami warnings in the South Pacific, but appeared to have suffered little damage. The quake tmsnrt.rs/2QdrtkL of magnitude 7.6, which struck east of New Caledonia, was just 10 km (6 miles) deep and about 155 km (95 miles) east-southeast of the Loyalty Islands, the Pacific Tsunami Warning Centre said. Authorities in the French territory urged people to move to locations more than 300 meters (984 ft) away from the shore, and if possible, to sites higher than 12 meters (39 ft) ab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://uk.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Australia's climate change inaction nulls 'Pacific pivot': Tuvalu PM - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/tuvalu-pm-says-australian-pacific-pivot-undermined-by-emissions/10579424</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBhg6fGrUkJH5bx4dHNxTgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 19:39:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/tuvalu-pm-says-australian-pacific-pivot-undermined-by-emissions/10579424" target="_blank"&gt;Australia's climate change inaction nulls 'Pacific pivot': Tuvalu PM&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Prime Minister of Tuvalu Enele Sopoaga has warned Australia that its "Pacific pivot" risks being fatally undermined by its climate change policies ahead of crucial talks in Poland. Key points - Tuvalu's PM made the comments ahead of COP24, the most important climate talks since the Paris agreement - He says Australia's return to the Pacific undermined by climate change inaction - Tuvalu is particularly vulnerable to climate change, being made up of low-lying atolls Australia has unveiled an ambitious suite of policies to cement its position in the region and push back against China, inc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Aftershock 7.0 earthquake hits New Caledonia coast - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/445602-aftershock-earthquake-hits-caledonia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBfZu_Ot_YHNxpl6d0ovklsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/445602-aftershock-earthquake-hits-caledonia/" target="_blank"&gt;Aftershock 7.0 earthquake hits New Caledonia coast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A magnitude 7.0 aftershock has struck off the coast of New Caledonia, hours after the French territory was hit by an earthquake. An initial tsunami threat has now passed, however. The aftershock comes after an earthquake struck 168.2 km (104.5 miles) from the small town of Tadine on the Loyalty Islands, New Caledonia. Tsunami alerts have been issued for both New Caledonia and nearby Vanuatu, a state in the South Pacific consisting of 80 islets with a population of 270,000 people. Authorities in New Caledonia have called for an “immediate evacuation” of people to designated areas. New Caledo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Nauru mental health situation akin to 'victims of torture', MSF says - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-03/msf-says-nauru-is-equivalent-to-torture-victims/10575818</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBgPFJTBaQtiOIQFqX1ZpgsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 23:36:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-03/msf-says-nauru-is-equivalent-to-torture-victims/10575818" target="_blank"&gt;Nauru mental health situation akin to 'victims of torture', MSF says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mental health situation on Nauru is equivalent to that of victims of torture, Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF) says, in what it describes as the first independent medical data on mental health conditions on the island. Key points: - MSF says offshore processing is to blame for the poor mental health on Nauru - Independent Kerryn Phelps plans to table a bill to bring asylum seekers to Australia for treatment - MSF said the bill does not go far enough and everyone should be removed from the island MSF treated 208 asylum seekers and refugees in the 11 months its medical staff were on Nauru, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Strong aftershock follows magnitude 7.5 quake off New Caledonia - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/tsunami-warning-magnitude-76-quake-strikes-caledonia-181205043532165.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPcoZoQgZG6tQCVzBOGP4roqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:42:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/tsunami-warning-magnitude-76-quake-strikes-caledonia-181205043532165.html" target="_blank"&gt;Strong aftershock follows magnitude 7.5 quake off New Caledonia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A powerful aftershock hit off New Caledonia on Wednesday just hours after a magnitude 7.5 earthquake struck the Pacific region, which triggered a tsunami warning, authorities said. The US Geological Survey said the new earthquake measured 6.6, downgrading it from from an initial measurement of 7.0. Earlier on Wednesday, a shallow and powerful magnitude 7.5 earthquake struck off the east coast of New Caledonia , with the epicentre reported some 300 kilometres east of Noumea. The undersea quake was only 10km deep and about 155km east-southeast of the Loyalty Islands off New Caledonia's east c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Group of Manus Island refugees move to Nauru amid worsening health crisis - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/29/group-of-manus-island-refugees-move-to-nauru-amid-worsening-health-crisis</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELII4K9nGx4ZPBl937e515IqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:59:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/29/group-of-manus-island-refugees-move-to-nauru-amid-worsening-health-crisis" target="_blank"&gt;Group of Manus Island refugees move to Nauru amid worsening health crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of refugees have left Manus Island and are moving to Nauru while they wait for resettlement in a third country. Guardian Australia has confirmed at least eight men were told they could transfer from the immigration facility on the Papua New Guinea island to its equivalent in Nauru. It is understood they departed on Thursday morning amid a worsening health crisis on Manus. The group will arrive in Nauru on Thursday afternoon and will spend the night in the RPC1 section of the detention centre, before moving into the community accomodation units. Related: ‘Sam could have been saved’: ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The world's most scenic flight? - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/gallery/worlds-most-scenic-flight/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECNTMQv0P1SXzErSVrfURY8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:22:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/gallery/worlds-most-scenic-flight/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The world's most scenic flight?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spectacular scenic flight: Aviation geeks call it "the holy grail of flight routes" -- welcome on board United Airlines 154, the Island Hopper. Chris Dwyer Incredible experience: The Island Hopper flight connects seven islands in a 16-hour flight, four times weekly. Chris Dwyer 50 year anniversary: 2018 marks half a century since the route was first flown. Back in 1968 Continental Micronesia was the carrier. Chris Dwyer First stop: There are four pilots on board the plane to share the route. First stop? Marjuro, in the Marshall Islands. Courtesy Chris Dwyer Marjuro harbor: The Marshall Isla...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Analysis: What's in the secret documents signed by China and Vanuatu at APEC? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/the-secret-documents-china-and-vanuatu-signed-at-apec/10557438</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHj6aslaT48Cngy696VtV-cqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 19:47:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-27/the-secret-documents-china-and-vanuatu-signed-at-apec/10557438" target="_blank"&gt;Analysis: What's in the secret documents signed by China and Vanuatu at APEC?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's a window into Chinese diplomacy in the Pacific. Key points: - China agreed to hand Vanuatu $60m for a "Container Inspection Equipment Project" - Beijing will lend Vanuatu about $70m to upgrade roads on Tanna and Malekula islands - China also agreed to "forgive" one of Vanuatu's "debts" — a 2004 loan worth almost $4m Last week Chinese President Xi Jinping sat down with a host of Pacific Island leaders just before the APEC summit in Papua New Guinea. The much-anticipated gathering was held against the backdrop of growing competition between China and the West in the Pacific, with lurid r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Vanuatu says it may sue fossil fuel companies and other countries over climate change - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/22/vanuatu-says-it-may-sue-fossil-fuel-companies-and-other-countries-over-climate-change</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB5Vd9xAu0hM0iZmFgaTCyIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 07:00:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/22/vanuatu-says-it-may-sue-fossil-fuel-companies-and-other-countries-over-climate-change" target="_blank"&gt;Vanuatu says it may sue fossil fuel companies and other countries over climate change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Republic of Vanuatu says it will explore whether it can take legal action against fossil fuel companies and countries for their role in causing climate change. The Pacific nation says it is growing desperate for financial assistance to deal with the loss and damage it is increasingly experiencing due to extreme weather and global warming. In a statement on Thursday to the Climate Vulnerable Forum, an international summit focused on those most at risk to the effects of climate change, Vanuatu’s foreign minister, Ralph Regenvanu, said he was putting the fossil fuel industry “and the state...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>China gives Tonga five years' grace on loan repayments - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-19/china-defers-tongas-loan-payments-as-nation-signs-up-to-bri/10509140</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIHv-uGak7umSQtRaZk-1pcqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:47:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-19/china-defers-tongas-loan-payments-as-nation-signs-up-to-bri/10509140" target="_blank"&gt;China gives Tonga five years' grace on loan repayments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tonga has signed up to China's Belt and Road initiative and received a reprieve from Beijing on the timing of debt payments shortly before an onerous schedule to repay loans was due to start. Lopeti Senituli, political adviser to Tongan Prime Minister Akilisi Pohiva, said Tonga had signed a Belt and Road memorandum of understanding, and the concessional loan had been deferred for five years. Tonga is one of eight island nations in the South Pacific that owe a significant debt to China. The deferment came just as Tonga was set to commence principal repayments on its debt, which is expected t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Medics failed us, had to go: Nauru - The Australian</title><link>https://myaccount.news.com.au/sites/theaustralian/subscribe.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMto6xeLxA-iymVHeWtPtrgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowga_TBDDc734wxJjEAQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://myaccount.news.com.au/sites/theaustralian/subscribe.html" target="_blank"&gt;Medics failed us, had to go: Nauru&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Australian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nauru has offered an explanation for why it sensationally kicked out international humanitarian organisation Medecins Sans Frontieres, accusing the respected charity of not doing enough to help Nauruan citizens while focusing on getting refugees on planes to Australia. MSF strongly rejects Nauru President Baron Waqa’s claims about what happened during the 11 months the organisation was contracted to provide psychological and psychiatric services on Nauru. “They were going to take care of our local people,” Mr Waqa said. “We have some mental cases. You will see them on the side of the road. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://myaccount.news.com.au">The Australian</source></item><item><title>Just 10 People Will See Next Year's Total Solar Eclipse From A Remote Island In The Pacific - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2018/11/16/just-10-people-will-see-next-years-total-solar-eclipse-from-a-remote-island-in-the-pacific/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGbne7amJa-zQSokFOkKWkwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2018/11/16/just-10-people-will-see-next-years-total-solar-eclipse-from-a-remote-island-in-the-pacific/" target="_blank"&gt;Just 10 People Will See Next Year's Total Solar Eclipse From A Remote Island In The Pacific&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oeno Island in the South Pacific is the only place where July 2, 2019′s Path of Totality strikes land until its hits Chile. Experiencing a total solar eclipse is one thing. So how about seeing one from a tiny tropical atoll in the South Pacific? In July 2019 a dramatic total solar eclipse will plunge parts of the southern hemisphere into darkness for a few minutes, just as happened on August 21, 2017 in 14 U.S. states. In 2019, most eclipse-chasers are headed for Chile or Argentina, thinking them the only places that the Path of Totality will cross. From there, a spectacular pre-sunset tota...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Brisbane construction firm Canstruct made $43m profit running Nauru detention centre last year - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/15/brisbane-construction-firm-made-43m-profit-running-nauru-detention-centre-last-year</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH7fNrscgZGj_p6eg5-dOOYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 01:02:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/15/brisbane-construction-firm-made-43m-profit-running-nauru-detention-centre-last-year" target="_blank"&gt;Brisbane construction firm Canstruct made $43m profit running Nauru detention centre last year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Brisbane construction firm made a profit of more than $43m for running Australia’s immigration detention centre on Nauru last financial year. Canstruct International’s sole contract is with the Australian government to provide garrison and welfare services at the regional processing centre on Nauru, which it has done since October 2017. In its first reporting period as a company, Canstruct International has disclosed it made an after tax profit of $43.16m, with a turnover of almost $212m. Almost $140m was spent on suppliers and employees, and it paid $8.6m in tax. Canstruct International ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Ethnic division clear as New Caledonians head to the polls for independence referendum - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-04/new-caledonians-head-to-the-polls-to-vote-on-referendum/10463822</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOSxns5TQIYvBPvHNk_0MEYqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 04:38:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-04/new-caledonians-head-to-the-polls-to-vote-on-referendum/10463822" target="_blank"&gt;Ethnic division clear as New Caledonians head to the polls for independence referendum&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Pacific affairs reporter Stephen Dziedzic Voters have been flocking to the polls in the French territory of New Caledonia for a historic vote on independence. The referendum has exposed social and economic fault lines in New Caledonia, but a clear ethnic divide was on display this morning in the capital, Noumea. The atmosphere in Noumea was calm this morning, with voters quietly forming long, orderly queues at polling stations. They will vote Yes or No to a simple question: "Do you want New Caledonia to accede to full sovereignty and become independent?" In contrast, many New Caledonians...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>New Caledonia votes to remain part of France: What comes next - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/04/asia/new-caledonia-independence-referendum-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtrxSHXkb42LrEigCYSFNIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 08:11:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/04/asia/new-caledonia-independence-referendum-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Caledonia votes to remain part of France: What comes next&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tiny Pacific territory of New Caledonia has voted to remain part of France in a long-awaited independence referendum which saw a much closer final result than expected. A colonial legacy of an empire that no longer officially exists, New Caledonia is one of a handful of territories in the region which have long been governed from afar but are increasingly pushing for self-rule. The islands came closest to independence than ever before Sunday, with 56% of voters choosing to remain part of France in the first of three possible referenda on the territory's future. Another independence vote...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New Caledonia votes on independence from France in landmark test - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/04/new-caledonia-voting-france</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2n_vyUzZ1Pg6zYiBem4boqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 01:18:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/04/new-caledonia-voting-france" target="_blank"&gt;New Caledonia votes on independence from France in landmark test&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voting is under way on the French Pacific islands of New Caledonia on whether to become an independent nation, in a closely watched test of support for France in one of its many territories scattered around the globe. New Caledonia, which is 18,000 kilometres (11,000 miles) from France, is home to a quarter of the world’s known supplies of nickel – a vital electronics component – and is a strategic foothold for France in the Pacific. Home to 269,000 people, New Caledonia is one of a handful of French island outposts – a legacy of the country’s 19th-century empire – which retain strategic im...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Marshall Islands' president accuses Chinese interests of backing opponents - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/09/marshall-islands-president-accuses-chinese-interests-of-backing-opponents</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM1JIm8FXiA4G-CDDuzhDNAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 01:21:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/09/marshall-islands-president-accuses-chinese-interests-of-backing-opponents" target="_blank"&gt;Marshall Islands' president accuses Chinese interests of backing opponents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Marshall Islands’ president, Hilda Heine, says accusations that she is destroying the country’s financial reputation by adopting a cryptocurrency are “baseless” and her opponents are being unduly influenced by pressure from China. Earlier this week eight senators moved to pass a vote of no confidence in Heine, the first female leader of any Pacific Island. The vote is scheduled to take place next week. Heine’s opponents said she had bought the country’s financial reputation into disrepute by pushing ahead with the adoption of the cryptocurrency Sovereign as the country’s second legal te...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Pacific archipelago votes on independence from France - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/94cc0073241c499e997bdb557c71366d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELHMeNFN5NesLjYIlMz0sOcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 21:32:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/94cc0073241c499e997bdb557c71366d" target="_blank"&gt;Pacific archipelago votes on independence from France&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOUMEA, New Caledonia (AP) — Voters in New Caledonia are deciding whether the French territory in the South Pacific should break free from the European country that claimed it in the mid-19th century. The polls opened Sunday morning in a referendum that's a milestone in the process of the archipelago's three-decade-long decolonization — one that will help define New Caledonia's future as an independent country or as a continuing part of France. More than 174,000 registered voters are invited to answer the question: "Do you want New Caledonia to gain full sovereignty and become independent?"...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Tension as New Caledonians in idyllic south Pacific poised to vote on independence from France - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/03/tension-new-caledonians-idyllic-south-pacific-poised-vote-independence/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIn53fL5HQ-C8unQaH7VYl4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 18:12:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/03/tension-new-caledonians-idyllic-south-pacific-poised-vote-independence/" target="_blank"&gt;Tension as New Caledonians in idyllic south Pacific poised to vote on independence from France&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Escalating tension in the French Pacific territory of New Caledonia ahead of an independence referendum on Sunday has prompted the authorities to ban the sale of alcohol and the carrying of firearms this weekend. The vote in the archipelago east of Australia has polarised its nearly 270,000 inhabitants along ethnic lines, pitting indigenous Kanaks who mostly favour independence against white and south-east Asian settlers. The vote was a condition of a 1988 agreement between separatists and the government that ended four years of violent unrest culminating in the killings of 25 people during...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Cannibalism, murder and chronic obesity: 10 island paradises with dark and deadly secrets - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/lists/island-paradises-with-dark-secrets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsBZ2xISmNx-3mfO6AEQSkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/lists/island-paradises-with-dark-secrets/" target="_blank"&gt;Cannibalism, murder and chronic obesity: 10 island paradises with dark and deadly secrets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s winter sun season, when thousands of lucky Britons escape the chill on some far-flung tropical isle. But many of these idyllic outposts have a little-known sinister side. Here are 10 island paradises with dark or deadly secrets. 1. The Maldives is the divorce capital of the world Ironically, given that it’s so popular with honeymooners, the Maldives is the divorce capital of the world. The island nation has a divorce rate of 10.97 per 1,000 inhabitants per year, according to the United Nations, earning it recognition from the Guinness Book of Records. Why is the rate so high in the Mal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>New Caledonia votes to remain part of France - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/11/05/new-caledonia-france-independence-vote-sot-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPXOTrpSjcqrUdULArQmFVAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 08:10:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/11/05/new-caledonia-france-independence-vote-sot-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;New Caledonia votes to remain part of France&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tiny Pacific territory of New Caledonia has voted to remain part of France in a long-awaited independence referendum which saw a much closer final result than expected. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>After Long Struggle, New Caledonia Set for Independence Vote - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/after-long-struggle-new-caledonia-set-for-independence-vote-/4643774.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPM2jK6JZtCRHs2ChH2zABwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:32:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/after-long-struggle-new-caledonia-set-for-independence-vote-/4643774.html" target="_blank"&gt;After Long Struggle, New Caledonia Set for Independence Vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Caledonia, a French archipelago in the South Pacific, votes Sunday on whether to become the world's newest state in a referendum on independence that is the result of a 30-year decolonization process. It is the first auto-determination vote to be held in a French territory since Djibouti in the Horn of Africa voted for independence in 1977. Tensions have long run deep between pro-independence indigenous Kanaks and descendants of colonial settlers who remain loyal to Paris. A "yes" vote would not only dent the pride of France, once a colonial power whose reach spanned the Caribbean, sub-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Macron: New Caledonians back keeping French ties - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/f6c26bec8b064ad0a181beb25f44a810</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAMCsKHna1TEa2yfeVJLNWEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 12:14:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/f6c26bec8b064ad0a181beb25f44a810" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Macron: New Caledonians back keeping French ties&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOUMEA, New Caledonia (AP) — The Latest on New Caledonia's independence referendum (all times local): 11:10 p.m. French President Emmanuel Macron says the majority of New Caledonians who voted in a referendum on independence chose to remain part of France. In a televised address from Paris, Macron pledged "there is no other path than that of dialogue" on the future of the South Pacific archipelago that has been part of France since 1853. French Prime Minister Edouard Philippe will meet with officials in New Caledonia to discuss future plans. The referendum was the result of a process that s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Oui or non: French colony in the Pacific set for crucial independence vote - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-01/new-caledonia-set-to-vote-for-independence-from-france/10452376</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPjgxO4YtDUcj4NwuLEFckQqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 19:24:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-01/new-caledonia-set-to-vote-for-independence-from-france/10452376" target="_blank"&gt;Oui or non: French colony in the Pacific set for crucial independence vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Pacific affairs reporter Stephen Dziedzic And on Sunday many of the 270,000 people who live there will head to the polls and make a momentous decision. Will they make a decisive break from Paris, and strike out into the world as a fully sovereign and independent nation? Or will they vote No and stay part of France — at least for now? New Caledonia's history has echoes of Australia's colonial past. France took possession of the tropical archipelago in 1853, and like Australia it began its life under foreign rule as a penal colony. The fault lines of that history run through the nation tod...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Macron hails New Caledonia vote to 'remain French' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/caledonia-rejects-independence-france-181104131715681.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECknaRcsiRqysV5aTGFy2XIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 13:36:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/caledonia-rejects-independence-france-181104131715681.html" target="_blank"&gt;Macron hails New Caledonia vote to 'remain French'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The French archipelago of New Caledonia in the South Pacific appears set to remain part of France, according to partial results of an independence referendum. Local TV network NC La 1ere reported that nearly 57 percent of voters had rejected secession in Sunday's poll, with nearly two thirds of the ballots counted. Turnout stood at almost 80 percent, it said. French President Emmanuel Macron said the "majority" of New Caledonians had declared they wanted the territory to "remain French". "Voters were allowed to make a sovereign choice, with full knowledge of the facts and the relationship b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Vive la France: New Caledonia rejects independence in historic referendum - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-05/new-caledonia-rejects-independence-from-france/10464248</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECZ6NngQiBq3I7ELnCUx-J4qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 18:53:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-05/new-caledonia-rejects-independence-from-france/10464248" target="_blank"&gt;Vive la France: New Caledonia rejects independence in historic referendum&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Pacific affairs reporter Stephen Dziedzic and Prianka Srinivasan Late last night the French government released provisional results showing 78,361 people voted No in yesterday's historic referendum, while 60,573 cast their ballot for Yes — a margin of 56.4 per cent to 43.6 per cent. But the unexpectedly tight result ensures the debate for sovereignty will continue to dominate political life in this Pacific territory, with activists vowing to continue their struggle. Some anti-independence politicians had been predicting they would win a handsome victory, suggesting that the No campaign c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>The Nauru Experience: Zero-Tolerance Immigration and Suicidal Children - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/05/world/australia/nauru-island-asylum-refugees-children-suicide.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPrt8xoyGKlHfB-z-LPNTzYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 03:36:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/05/world/australia/nauru-island-asylum-refugees-children-suicide.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Nauru Experience: Zero-Tolerance Immigration and Suicidal Children&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TOPSIDE, Nauru — She was 3 years old when she arrived on Nauru, a child fleeing war in Sri Lanka. Now, Sajeenthana is 8. Her gaze is vacant. Sometimes she punches adults. And she talks about dying with ease. “Yesterday I cut my hand,” she said in an interview here on the remote Pacific island where she was sent by the Australian government after being caught at sea. She pointed to a scar on her arm. “One day I will kill myself,” she said. “Wait and see, when I find the knife. I don’t care about my body. ” Her father tried to calm her, but she twisted away. “It is the same as if I was in war...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>New Caledonia Voters Reject Independence - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/new-caledonia-voters-reject-independence-/4643937.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHIr8Xh3bZD04b4HJJA5vtAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 14:04:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/new-caledonia-voters-reject-independence-/4643937.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Caledonia Voters Reject Independence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pacific islands of New Caledonia have voted to remain part of France in an independence referendum. Voters answered the question, "Do you want New Caledonia to gain full sovereignty and become independent?" Nearly 57 percent of the islands' 174,000 voters decided to remain part of France, which claimed the archipelago in the mid-19th century. French President Emmanuel Macron said the vote was "a sign of confidence in the French republic, in its future and its values." New Caledonia's economy is supported by about $1.5 billion in French subsidies each year and many fear the economy would...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>New Caledonia votes against independence from France - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-newcaledonia-referendum/after-long-separatist-struggle-new-caledonia-votes-on-independence-idUSKCN1N80MT</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPWPNXnNDnoEeKtteqlC3psqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 13:29:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-newcaledonia-referendum/after-long-separatist-struggle-new-caledonia-votes-on-independence-idUSKCN1N80MT" target="_blank"&gt;New Caledonia votes against independence from France&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The South Pacific archipelago of New Caledonia voted against independence from France on Sunday in a long-awaited referendum that capped a 30-year long decolonization process. A "yes" vote would have deprived Paris of a foothold in the Indo-Pacific region where China is expanding its presence, and dented the pride of a former colonial power whose reach once spanned the Caribbean, sub-Saharan Africa and the Pacific Ocean. Based on provisional results and with a participation rate of nearly 80 percent, the "No" vote stood at 56.9 percent around 1300 GMT, local TV station NC La 1ere reported o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>New Caledonia to vote on independence from France - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/caledonia-vote-independence-france-181031025958306.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDwhYTWhpp5U7-Jg_mvZoyIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 02:58:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/caledonia-vote-independence-france-181031025958306.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Caledonia to vote on independence from France&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canberra, Australia - The people of New Caledonia will vote on Sunday on whether they want full independence from France, which has ruled the small archipelago in the Pacific since the 19th century. The islands, a nearly three-hour flight east of Australia, secured more autonomy amid growing calls for independence by the indigenous Kanak people in the 1980s. When an estimated 174,000 voters who qualify as long-term residents head to the polls on Sunday, it will be the second referendum on New Caledonia's political status. The first, held in 1987, was widely boycotted by the Kanaks, resultin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>New Caledonia in Pacific to vote on independence from France - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/d2a081e395df45dba7a15dafd99bab82</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI0IjJR_moxFHWFKxDIQQykqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 08:48:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/d2a081e395df45dba7a15dafd99bab82" target="_blank"&gt;New Caledonia in Pacific to vote on independence from France&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARIS (AP) — New Caledonia, a French archipelago in the South Pacific, is preparing for an independence referendum — the last step in a three-decades-long decolonization effort. Sunday's vote is key to settling tensions between the native Kanaks, who once suffered from strict segregation policies, and descendants of European colonizers. It is also a test of the depth of the links between France and the territory, which lies east of Australia and has about 270,000 inhabitants. Voters have to answer the question "Do you want New Caledonia to gain full sovereignty and become independent?" Obse...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Early results show New Caledonia votes to remain part of France - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/early-results-show-caledonia-votes-remain-part-france-181104104613756.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDqmIZbHqAp8OlFdK0QpYAsqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 11:23:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/early-results-show-caledonia-votes-remain-part-france-181104104613756.html" target="_blank"&gt;Early results show New Caledonia votes to remain part of France&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The "No" vote against independence for New Caledonia is in the lead with about half the ballots counted in the French Pacific territory, reports say. Public broadcaster La1ere Nouvelle Caledonie reported that 59 per cent of votes counted were against independence, with 41 per cent in favour. But results varied widely in the ethnically diverse territory; some areas dominated by the native Kanak population had more than 90 per cent "Yes" votes, while other communes with a mainly European population voted strongly for "No". The broadcaster also cited police as saying that some cars had been st...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>'No' vote well ahead in New Caledonia independence referendum - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-newcaledonia-referendum-partia/no-vote-well-ahead-in-new-caledonia-independence-referendum-idUSKCN1N90C2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPrgHupXXdPCdEXMBOxTQFcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 11:56:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-newcaledonia-referendum-partia/no-vote-well-ahead-in-new-caledonia-independence-referendum-idUSKCN1N90C2" target="_blank"&gt;'No' vote well ahead in New Caledonia independence referendum&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The French archipelago of New Caledonia in the South Pacific voted 59.5 percent against independence from France in a referendum on Sunday, with two thirds of the ballots counted, local TV station NC La 1ere reported on its website. It said that participation rate stood at 80.7 percent. Full results were due from 1130 GMT onwards. The referendum, the result of a 30-year long decolonization process, is the first auto-determination vote to be held in a French territory since Djibouti in the Horn of Africa voted for independence in 1977. (Reporting by Geert De Clercq and Sophie Louet; Editing ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>UK can now use foreign aid budget to help richer overseas territories hit by natural disasters - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/foreign-aid-budget-caribbean-overseas-territories-british-virgin-islands-anguilla-penny-mordaunt-a8612021.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFAfS4QGTeweVlF_tFtap50qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 09:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/foreign-aid-budget-caribbean-overseas-territories-british-virgin-islands-anguilla-penny-mordaunt-a8612021.html" target="_blank"&gt;UK can now use foreign aid budget to help richer overseas territories hit by natural disasters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wealthy UK overseas territories will be allowed to receive foreign aid after the government secured a “significant” change to international rules. The Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) will now include richer countries that have been affected by natural disasters on a list of nations deserving of aid. It comes after the UK government urged other developed nations to change the rules, pointing out that Caribbean countries damaged by hurricanes last year had not received official assistance because they were deemed too wealthy. - Read more Government warned over ‘u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Australia to move child refugees from island camps - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1039e0c6-dd7e-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE1u2k1w9IXzbJhLlSSyGBYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 04:09:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/1039e0c6-dd7e-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c" target="_blank"&gt;Australia to move child refugees from island camps&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia is to move children in its offshore refugee processing camps on to its territory by the end of the year in response to a medical crisis that has prompted a political backlash against the conservative government. George Brandis, Australia’s high commissioner to the UK, said on Thursday the problem of children living on the tiny Pacific islands of Nauru and Manus island in Papua New Guinea had “largely gone away” following recent transfers to Australia. His comments follow a report in The Australian, a newspaper, which said Canberra had decided to move the remaining 40 children from...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>The Cook Islands: 'Everyone’s happy. If you’re not happy, you’re in the wrong place' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2018/oct/30/the-cook-islands-everyones-happy-if-youre-not-happy-youre-in-the-wrong-place</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKv-oV0CLeTb0tfUb7JsZ6sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCw3Gc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 17:00:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2018/oct/30/the-cook-islands-everyones-happy-if-youre-not-happy-youre-in-the-wrong-place" target="_blank"&gt;The Cook Islands: 'Everyone’s happy. If you’re not happy, you’re in the wrong place'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re just over the last crest of Maunga Pu when we see it. Here, at Aitutaki’s highest point, the true glory of the island’s sprawling lagoon reveals itself. Its outer edge encircles the tiny island, splitting crystal clear waters from the heaving dark blue of the Pacific beyond. It lends the atoll – the second most populous of the 15 Cook Islands – an air of stillness. “Pretty amazing view, hey?,” I say to a rare group of American tourists we find at the top of the hillside. “Yeah, incredible,” one responds, smiling. Related: Australia's top eight Indigenous travel destinations | Marcia L...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Tony Abbott describes conditions on Nauru as 'very, very pleasant' - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-29/tony-abbott-describes-conditions-on-nauru-as-pleasant/10442694</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFH257087NX7SZ9LWT3Cm-oqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 07:11:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-29/tony-abbott-describes-conditions-on-nauru-as-pleasant/10442694" target="_blank"&gt;Tony Abbott describes conditions on Nauru as 'very, very pleasant'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By political reporter Nick Dole Former prime minister Tony Abbott says Nauru is being unfairly portrayed as a "hell-hole" when it is in fact a "very pleasant" place. Mr Abbott was responding to growing calls to remove asylum seeker children from the Pacific island. "Nauru is no hell-hole by any means. I've been there," Mr Abbott told radio station 2GB. "If you like living in the tropics, it's a very, very pleasant island." Medical groups including the Australian Medical Association and Medicin Sans Frontieres (Doctors Without Borders) have called for the immediate removal of children from t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Laughing Meghan serenaded by mosquito choir in Tonga - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-26/meghan-serenaded-by-mosquito-choir-in-tonga/10435054</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEClbF9nylDqKNWkM3WyimWEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 07:01:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-26/meghan-serenaded-by-mosquito-choir-in-tonga/10435054" target="_blank"&gt;Laughing Meghan serenaded by mosquito choir in Tonga&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Tongan choir had Meghan, the Duchess of Sussex, in tears of laughter as she and Prince Harry wrapped up their tour of Tonga and hopped on a plane to return to Australia for the end of the Invictus Games. The pair, who are expecting a child of their own in the Spring, were serenaded by students at Tupou College. They laughed when boys from the college sang about mosquitoes, complete with dance moves, at a ceremony to dedicate two forest reserves on the campus. But mosquito-born diseases have been raised before on this tour — the World Health Organisation identified recent cases of the zika...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Prince Harry and Meghan arrive in Tonga after unveiling statue of SAS hero - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-25/prince-harry-and-meghan-unveil-statue-in-fiji-head-to-tonga/10428918</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENjxJ0do5ygAx4mhdefSgpAqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 06:40:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-25/prince-harry-and-meghan-unveil-statue-in-fiji-head-to-tonga/10428918" target="_blank"&gt;Prince Harry and Meghan arrive in Tonga after unveiling statue of SAS hero&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Duke and Duchess of Sussex have arrived in the tiny Pacific kingdom of Tonga after taking a short flight from Fiji, where they spent the morning unveiling a statue of a British-Fijian SAS sergeant. Prince Harry and wife Meghan were greeted at the airport in Tonga by Princess Angelika Latufuipeka. People gathered wearing traditional outfits, playing guitars and singing at the airport to welcome the Royal couple. Harry and Meghan were scheduled to meet with Tonga's King and Queen and to attend a reception and dinner with traditional Tongan entertainment. Prior to their arrival in Tonga, P...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Island life becomes royal couple - The Australian</title><link>https://www.theaustralian.com.au/news/world/royal-family/royals-touch-down-in-tonga-as-royal-tour-continues/news-story/d6b4a780b8b0dfb84a5703fc35a88f25</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDd0kqJ-Ub38Ih6-P4hgzt8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowga_TBDDc734wxJjEAQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theaustralian.com.au/news/world/royal-family/royals-touch-down-in-tonga-as-royal-tour-continues/news-story/d6b4a780b8b0dfb84a5703fc35a88f25" target="_blank"&gt;Island life becomes royal couple&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Australian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Tongan royals rolled out the red carpet for their British counterparts yesterday as Harry and Meghan touched down on the ­Pacific island nation. The Duke and Duchess of Sussex landed at Fua’amotu International Airport to hundreds of well-wishers. Some wore traditional clothing, sung and played guitars. Others waved Union Jacks. They also received a warm welcome from Princess Angelika Latufuipeka, the only daughter and oldest child of King Tupou VI and Queen Nanasipau’u Tuku’ah. The usually impeccably dressed Meghan looked the part, wearing the red of the island’s national flag, but made...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theaustralian.com.au">The Australian</source></item><item><title>Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, seen with tag dangling from dress in Tonga - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/royal-tour-tonga-meghan-dress-label-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH_zMkAmhw5OkT6J0OhePIsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMIbnyQU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 11:54:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/style/article/royal-tour-tonga-meghan-dress-label-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, seen with tag dangling from dress in Tonga&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The British Royal family isn't known for scrimping on its wardrobe budget, but Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, has left some wondering whether she hopes to return her latest outfit for a refund. As the newly wed royal stepped off a Qantas charter flight in Tonga, a tag could be seen flapping from the hem of her dress as she walked down the red carpet. It was spotted by Sophie Walsh, a reporter for Australian CNN affiliate Channel 9 News, who tweeted, "With so many outfit changes I think the Duchess can be forgiven for this." The Duchess was wearing a green Jason Wu crepe sheath dress -- listed a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Inflight hiccup as Harry and Meghan's plane aborts Sydney landing - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-royals-tonga/inflight-hiccup-as-harry-and-meghans-plane-aborts-sydney-landing-idUSKCN1N00K1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENQQknehnQ5w-1WlCn6djjEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 10:13:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-royals-tonga/inflight-hiccup-as-harry-and-meghans-plane-aborts-sydney-landing-idUSKCN1N00K1" target="_blank"&gt;Inflight hiccup as Harry and Meghan's plane aborts Sydney landing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prince Harry and his wife Meghan returned to Australia on Friday from a tour of Pacific islands after their plane was forced to abort a first landing because another aircraft was in the way. Their Qantas plane charter flight QF6031, approaching Sydney, dropped to 125 feet before performing a "go-around", according to FlightRadar24. In aviation terminology, a go-around is a when a pilot pulls out of a landing and makes another attempt after circling the airport. According to the Civil Aviation Safety Authority a go-around is a "common and very safe practice". A Reuters witness on the plane s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Plane carrying Harry and Meghan aborts landing, flies around - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/efbd65ec39ea4015ba971d73d95c5c18</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKo66ytOq5TtMjvwGM-55yAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 08:59:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/efbd65ec39ea4015ba971d73d95c5c18" target="_blank"&gt;Plane carrying Harry and Meghan aborts landing, flies around&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NUKU'ALOFA, Tonga (AP) — A plane carrying the Duke and Duchess of Sussex had to abort its landing at Sydney airport on Friday evening and flew around because there was another aircraft on the runway. Prince Harry and wife Meghan were returning from a visit to Tonga back to Australia, where they began their 16-day tour of four nations, when a message from the flight deck announced: "There was an aircraft on the runway a little slow to roll so the decision was taken to abort the landing." The flight landed safely a few minutes later. Earlier Friday, the couple dedicated two forest reserves in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Nauru denies deporting Australian doctor, saying she is 'welcome' to return - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-18/nauru-denies-deporting-australian-doctor-nicole-montana/10390792</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECWTriZEC-asPEwl_fy0BfwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 01:46:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-18/nauru-denies-deporting-australian-doctor-nicole-montana/10390792" target="_blank"&gt;Nauru denies deporting Australian doctor, saying she is 'welcome' to return&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Government of Nauru has denied that it forced a senior Australian doctor to leave the island, saying she would be "welcome" to return in the future. Key points: - Nauru said Dr Montana was "briefly questioned" over unauthorised photos of a child - But sources have told the ABC that Nauru made it clear the Dr Montana had to leave the island - The Nauru Government has called reporting by the ABC and Australian media outlets "false" Dr Nicole Montana flew out of Nauru yesterday after being stood down from her position as senior medical officer for the health contractor IHMS. The ABC has be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Tonga's rugby league team will play Australia for the first time tomorrow night - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-19/tonga-australia-rugby-leage-match-auckland/10395452</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDgqfJTnPv2wA31CK8PR8zMqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 04:22:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-19/tonga-australia-rugby-leage-match-auckland/10395452" target="_blank"&gt;Tonga's rugby league team will play Australia for the first time tomorrow night&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's the game that could change the face of international rugby league, when Tonga take on the world champions Australia in Auckland on Saturday night. Key points: - Tonga to field team made up of NRL and English Super League players - A win for Tonga could result in more high-profile games in the South Pacific - Several dual nationals have switched from NZ or Australia for Tonga The two sides have never met before, but Tonga — with a team full of NRL and English Super League stars — are out to demonstrate that their tier-two ranking does not do them justice. Audio: Tonga: Mate Ma'a out to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>‘Untouched’ Pacific island forests could be destroyed within 20 years due to unsustainable logging - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/environment/forests-solomon-islands-pacific-logging-china-deforestation-global-witness-a8589036.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDb2L8vsNPq6fJKd5RknI2IqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 23:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/environment/forests-solomon-islands-pacific-logging-china-deforestation-global-witness-a8589036.html" target="_blank"&gt;‘Untouched’ Pacific island forests could be destroyed within 20 years due to unsustainable logging&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unsustainable and potentially illegal logging in remote Pacific islands could leave their natural resources decimated within 20 years, according to activists. The Solomon Islands are described by travel guides and the nation’s tourist board as “unspoiled”, but a new report by international NGO Global Witness has revealed this is far from the truth. One of the poorest nations in the Pacific region, the Solomon Islands have an economy that is highly reliant on its forestry sector. - Read more Alarming photos reveal scale of forest destruction in Papua New Guinea Despite this reliance, a repor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Harry and Meghan's overseas tour: The highlights - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/sunday-planning/2018/10/19/harry-and-meghan-overseas-tour-highlights-lon-orig.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENmZJ7IY6TXE8q7UGhFWwQEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 13:04:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/sunday-planning/2018/10/19/harry-and-meghan-overseas-tour-highlights-lon-orig.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Harry and Meghan's overseas tour: The highlights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Duke and Duchess of Sussex are on a 16-day tour of Australia, New Zealand, Fiji and the Kingdom of Tonga. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>China demand fuels Solomon Islands mass deforestation - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/china-demand-fuels-solomon-islands-mass-deforestation-181018032325122.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIgBoJEwswFMokaURm5n7GIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 06:25:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/china-demand-fuels-solomon-islands-mass-deforestation-181018032325122.html" target="_blank"&gt;China demand fuels Solomon Islands mass deforestation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forest is being felled at an unsustainable rate in the Solomon Islands to meet surging demand from China, according to a new investigation by environmental group Global Witness. A combination of detailed research, satellite imagery, trade data, and on-the-ground and drone photography showed "the shocking pace and extent of the growing degradation of the Solomon Islands’ tropical forests", Global Witness said in its report into logging in the South Pacific country. The trade volume of its single largest export commodity surged more than 20 percent to just over three million cubic metres in 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Magnitude 6.5 earthquake recorded east of New Caledonia: USGS - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-newcaledonia-quake/magnitude-6-5-earthquake-recorded-east-of-new-caledonia-usgs-idUSKCN1MQ01Q</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN5SR6PEtqrIciPXdfm8uu8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 00:50:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-newcaledonia-quake/magnitude-6-5-earthquake-recorded-east-of-new-caledonia-usgs-idUSKCN1MQ01Q" target="_blank"&gt;Magnitude 6.5 earthquake recorded east of New Caledonia: USGS&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An earthquake with a preliminary magnitude of 6.5 was recorded east of New Caledonia in the South Pacific on Tuesday, the U.S. Geological Survey said. The epicenter of the quake was 190 km (120 miles) east of Tadine in the Loyalty Islands at a depth of 33 km (20 miles), the USGS said. There was no immediate threat of a tsunami, according to the Pacific Tsunami Warning Center in Hawaii. (Reporting by Paul Tait; editing by Richard Pullin)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>UNHCR: Australia Must Evacuate 1,400 Refugees for Medical Care - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/unhcr-australia-papua-new-guinea-nauru-refugees-medical-care/4611339.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOtuBCFJ4Ryqf4EkD7t6f1cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 19:15:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/unhcr-australia-papua-new-guinea-nauru-refugees-medical-care/4611339.html" target="_blank"&gt;UNHCR: Australia Must Evacuate 1,400 Refugees for Medical Care&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N. refugee agency says the health of more than 1,400 refugees and asylum seekers held at offshore processing facilities in Papua New Guinea and Nauru has seriously deteriorated. It says they must be moved immediately to Australia, where they can get medical care. Australia set up offshore processing centers in Papua New Guinea and Nauru in 2013 to deter refugees arriving by sea from landing on its shores. Over the past five years, 12 people have died, half of them confirmed or suspected suicides. UNHCR spokeswoman Catherine Stubberfield says under international law, Australia is respo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Farewell to Fariborz: Australian burial for refugee who killed himself on Nauru - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/10/farewell-to-fariborz-australian-burial-for-refugee-who-killed-himself-on-nauru</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHKCkfJwGvfxQEVvKfZHMsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 07:24:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/10/farewell-to-fariborz-australian-burial-for-refugee-who-killed-himself-on-nauru" target="_blank"&gt;Farewell to Fariborz: Australian burial for refugee who killed himself on Nauru&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last Friday relatives of Fariborz Karami finally said goodbye to the 26-year-old, an athletic and intelligent dentistry student who had married just a short time before taking his life inside a tent on Nauru. It had been more than three months since he died, and many years since doctors first raised concerns about his mental health with immigration detention authorities. At Mount Gravatt cemetery in Brisbane, friends and relatives ofKarami gathered under a small marquee, taking turns to kiss and embrace a white coffin adorned with silver handles, red roses resting on its lid. “I never thoug...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>We all know what is going on in Nauru, even if we pretend it isn't happening - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/12/we-all-know-what-is-going-on-in-nauru-even-if-we-pretend-it-is-not-happening</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPzq45Ozq8RO47HBn3zw-zkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 05:36:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/12/we-all-know-what-is-going-on-in-nauru-even-if-we-pretend-it-is-not-happening" target="_blank"&gt;We all know what is going on in Nauru, even if we pretend it isn't happening&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;First Dog on ... #kidsoffnauru&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Sun, sea and sand: Which Pacific paradise is right for you? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/oceania/articles/best-pacific-island-paradise/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIHW8LB1ZEQPd6tD4QewePIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/oceania/articles/best-pacific-island-paradise/" target="_blank"&gt;Sun, sea and sand: Which Pacific paradise is right for you?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a region that is never entirely out of focus – even if the mind’s eye seems to view it in a swirl of heat haze, shimmering far beyond the horizon. The South Pacific is a destination which crops up in travel fantasies, palm trees whispering above beaches of a fine powder; the sea sighing as a barely plausible shade of perfect blue. But now is a moment when, for all its considerable distance from these shores (it is a full 9,563 miles by plane from London to Tahiti) the South Pacific is particularly in focus for would-be British visitors. This summer witnessed the 250th anniversary (Aug...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Nauru orders MSF to stop mental health work on island - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/06/nauru-orders-msf-to-stop-mental-health-work-on-island</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECmbwe2FhzffJduDtB1Jn_oqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 10:24:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/06/nauru-orders-msf-to-stop-mental-health-work-on-island" target="_blank"&gt;Nauru orders MSF to stop mental health work on island&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nauru’s government has ordered Médecins Sans Frontières (MSF) to stop work there immediately, despite a physical and mental health crisis in the country. The medical NGO has been providing psychological and psychiatric services to residents, asylum seekers and refugees on the island since late 2017. MSF staff wrote to its clients on Saturday to tell them it could no longer offer them treatment because of an order from Nauru’s health minister, who said the its services were “no longer required on the island”. MSF said in its letter that the order meant its “mental health activities in Nauru ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>To truly fight climate change, we need to set our sights higher - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/03/opinions/climate-change-marshall-islands-fiji-bainimarama-heine/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChJH282MSqmBn7SEWs6eB0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 21:04:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/03/opinions/climate-change-marshall-islands-fiji-bainimarama-heine/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;To truly fight climate change, we need to set our sights higher&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kids on the street in Majuro, Marshall Islands, in the remote Pacific, can tell you anything you want to know about climate change. They know the seas are rising. This basketball court is next to the foundation of a house destroyed in a recent flood. John D. Sutter/CNN Marshallese people are known as master canoe builders and navigators. Including the ocean, the nation is three times the size of Texas. But it only has as much land as Washington, D.C. "We are not a small island country," said Tony de Brum, the foreign minister. "We are a big ocean country." John D. Sutter/CNN Rositha Anwel, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>#BeingMicronesian: online hatred spurs positive fightback - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/06/beingmicronesian-online-hatred-spurs-positive-fightback</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEgbR0lYCe7Yoc8_P-YehMwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 03:07:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/06/beingmicronesian-online-hatred-spurs-positive-fightback" target="_blank"&gt;#BeingMicronesian: online hatred spurs positive fightback&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the case of one offensive Facebook post too many. Sha Ongelungel, a Palauan-American woman, was looking at Facebook when she saw yet another derogatory post directed at Micronesians – people from the western sub-region of the Pacific, including the countries of Federated States of Micronesia, Palau, Kiribati, Marshall Islands and Nauru, as well as three US territories. She decided she had had enough. Ongelungel, a writer and activist now living in Hawaii, began sharing examples of online abuse directed toward Micronesians, that she had been collating over the past three years, in wha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Nauru 19: at least three members denied passports despite court throwing out case - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/04/nauru-19-at-least-three-members-denied-passports-despite-court-throwing-out-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO9mjUU6FSjIOOcgEh48He0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/04/nauru-19-at-least-three-members-denied-passports-despite-court-throwing-out-case" target="_blank"&gt;Nauru 19: at least three members denied passports despite court throwing out case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nauruan government has refused passports to at least three members of the so-called Nauru 19, who were charged over attending a political rally in 2015, despite the court throwing out a criminal case against them. The three people, including a former Nauruan government minister, were all told their applications were rejected on the grounds of “potential for harmful conduct” legislation. The trio wrote to the minister on Wednesday, asking him to explain the decision and detail the concerns he held about them. “We believe the minister needs to give us clarification on what his concerns ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>How to visit the world's most beautiful islands - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/oceania/articles/travel-guide-to-oceania-french-polynesia-tahiti-fiji-tonga-samoa-hawaii/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEc6ZlKW9Cg6ur3Eh6WOHCQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/oceania/articles/travel-guide-to-oceania-french-polynesia-tahiti-fiji-tonga-samoa-hawaii/" target="_blank"&gt;How to visit the world's most beautiful islands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a region which is never entirely out of focus - even if the mind's eye seems to view it in a swirl of heat haze, shimmering far, far beyond the horizon. The South Pacific is a destination which crops up in travel fantasies - palm trees whispering above beaches of a fine powder; the sea sighing and swaying as a barely plausible shade of perfect blue. But now - the early stages of the autumn of 2018 - are a moment when, for all its considerable distance from these shores (it is a full 9,563 miles by plane from London to Tahiti) the South Pacific is particularly in focus for would-be Bri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Watch US Navy attempt rescue as plane sinks - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/09/30/us-navy-plane-water-rescue-video-micronesia-nr-bpr-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELAdEVIbU9qKrXq5i-Tya8oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 08:12:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/09/30/us-navy-plane-water-rescue-video-micronesia-nr-bpr-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Watch US Navy attempt rescue as plane sinks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US Navy Sailors assisted in the rescue of several passengers and crew members after a plane crashed into a lagoon near Chuuk, Federated States of Micronesia, according to a statement from the US 7th fleet. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Passenger Jet Crashes off Micronesia; Everybody Survives - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/passenger-jet-crashes-off-micronesia-everybody-survives/4590980.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEcQk10GxbqCBA75Q0Zo4mEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 04:28:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/passenger-jet-crashes-off-micronesia-everybody-survives/4590980.html" target="_blank"&gt;Passenger Jet Crashes off Micronesia; Everybody Survives&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All 47 passengers and crew survived a plane’s crash landing in a Pacific lagoon Friday morning, wading through waist-deep water to the emergency exits and escaping on local boats that came to the rescue in the Micronesia archipelago. Seven people were taken to a hospital, according to officials, including one described as being in a critical but stable condition. Passenger Bill Jaynes said the plane came in very low as it was attempting to land at the Chuuk Island airport. “I thought we landed hard,” he said. “Until I looked over and saw a hole in the side of the plane and water was coming ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Trevor the 'world's loneliest duck' puts tiny Niue on the map - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-21/trevor-the-worlds-loneliest-duck-puts-tiny-niue-on-the-map/10287508</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKLo67-zyHsGAsV2H32lInIqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 21:00:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-21/trevor-the-worlds-loneliest-duck-puts-tiny-niue-on-the-map/10287508" target="_blank"&gt;Trevor the 'world's loneliest duck' puts tiny Niue on the map&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Catherine Graue When the results came up you may have quickly found yourself dreaming about a tropical island getaway, to a place with glittering turquoise waters and palm trees swaying in the wind. A cynic would say the mysterious story of how a mallard duck made its way to a coral atoll in the Pacific ocean, without wetlands or ponds, is in fact a stroke of marketing brilliance. "I think Trevor is an excellent ambassador for Niue and the reason I say that, is that he has raised the profile of people globally who may or may not have been aware of Niue's existence beforehand," Felicity B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>'Kill me, I can't cope': Refugee women on Nauru robbed of their dignity speak out - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/18/kill-me-i-cant-cope-anymore-nauru-women-robbed-of-their-dignity-speak-out</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOkH4Nk1Uctfn2VGrEJDRY4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 02:54:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/18/kill-me-i-cant-cope-anymore-nauru-women-robbed-of-their-dignity-speak-out" target="_blank"&gt;'Kill me, I can't cope': Refugee women on Nauru robbed of their dignity speak out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fascists kill. But for those damaged survivors who flee persecution, and face a new authoritarianism, sustaining themselves can be a monumental personal undertaking. Before I discuss four stages of redistributive justice, I’ll record examples of threat and intimidation which make the struggle for justice so necessary. Related: Australia is reported to UN human rights council over illegal detention of asylum seekers “Kill me, I can’t cope anymore. Only death can rescue me” is one of the most common phrases that I heard from women and children on death row in Iran and women and children facin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item></channel></rss>