<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Asif Ghafoor - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZrWkhkMGVEVnNjUklDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-PK&amp;gl=PK&amp;ceid=PK:en</link><language>en-PK</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:13:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Army backs US peace talks with Taliban - The Express Tribune</title><link>https://tribune.com.pk/story/1861478/1-army-focused-improving-relations-india-dg-ispr/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780128258380</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:33:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://tribune.com.pk/story/1861478/1-army-focused-improving-relations-india-dg-ispr/" target="_blank"&gt;Army backs US peace talks with Taliban&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Express Tribune&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thenews.com.pk/print/402614-moment-is-watershed-time-ahead-may-be-very-good-or-bad-paint-pakistan-positive-for-six-months-says-dg-ispr" target="_blank"&gt;Moment is watershed; time ahead may be very good or bad: Paint Pakistan positive for six months, says DG ISPR&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The News International&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://nation.com.pk/07-Dec-2018/-we-stand-at-watershed-beyond-which-is-prosperity" target="_blank"&gt;We stand at watershed, beyond which is prosperity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Nation&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pakistantoday.com.pk/2018/12/06/mna-mohsin-dawar-chides-ispr-dg-over-ptm-remarks/" target="_blank"&gt;MNA Mohsin Dawar chides ISPR DG over PTM remarks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Pakistan Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://tribune.com.pk/story/1861589/1-will-reconstruct-pakistan-brick-brick-gen-qamar/" target="_blank"&gt;Will reconstruct Pakistan brick-by-brick: Gen Qamar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Express Tribune&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpNa3EtbWpZQU1FY05aNklLaERZSlNLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://tribune.com.pk">The Express Tribune</source></item><item><title>SP Dawar’s murder in Afghanistan raises many questions: ISPR - The Express Tribune</title><link>https://tribune.com.pk/story/1847947/1-sp-dawars-murder-afghanistan-raises-many-questions-ispr/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vdHJpYnVuZS5jb20ucGsvc3RvcnkvMTg0Nzk0Ny8xLXNwLWRhd2Fycy1tdXJkZXItYWZnaGFuaXN0YW4tcmFpc2VzLW1hbnktcXVlc3Rpb25zLWlzcHIv0gGsAWh0dHBzOi8vdHJpYnVuZS1jb20tcGsuY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy90cmlidW5lLmNvbS5way9zdG9yeS8xODQ3OTQ3LzEtc3AtZGF3YXJzLW11cmRlci1hZmdoYW5pc3Rhbi1yYWlzZXMtbWFueS1xdWVzdGlvbnMtaXNwci8_YW1wPTEmYW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 07:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://tribune.com.pk/story/1847947/1-sp-dawars-murder-afghanistan-raises-many-questions-ispr/" target="_blank"&gt;SP Dawar’s murder in Afghanistan raises many questions: ISPR&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Express Tribune&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The abduction and brutal murder of a senior Pakistani police officer in Afghanistan and the follow-up behaviour of Afghan authorities indicate involvement of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://tribune.com.pk">The Express Tribune</source></item><item><title>Pakistan's army says it backs U.S. peace talks with Afghan Taliban - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-usa-afghanistan-idUSKBN1O51H7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIfbPWxo0wmAI9n1Ne-QbvgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:31:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-usa-afghanistan-idUSKBN1O51H7" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan's army says it backs U.S. peace talks with Afghan Taliban&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan's army on Thursday threw its support behind the latest U.S. efforts for a political settlement with the Afghan Taliban to end a 17-year-old war, urging Washington to leave Kabul as a friend of the region rather than a "failure". The comments by Pakistan's army spokesman, Major-General Asif Ghafoor, came just after the U.S. special representative for Afghanistan, Zalmay Khalilzad, concluded a visit to the Pakistani capital of Islamabad. "As much as we can, we will facilitate," Ghafoor told a news conference in the garrison city of Rawalpindi, replying to a query about what Pakistan ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan summons U.S. envoy as Trump doubles down on criticism - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-usa/pakistan-summons-u-s-envoy-to-protest-trumps-criticism-idUSKCN1NP0R2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBL84-2qCW2TffqFvrM5lNMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 12:54:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-usa/pakistan-summons-u-s-envoy-to-protest-trumps-criticism-idUSKCN1NP0R2" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan summons U.S. envoy as Trump doubles down on criticism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan summoned the U.S. Chargé d'Affaires in Islamabad on Tuesday to protest President Donald Trump's criticism of Pakistan's role in fighting terrorism and the killing of Osama bin Laden. Trump's comments over the last few days have angered Pakistan, including Prime Minister Imran Khan, who on Monday hit back by saying on Twitter that few allies had sacrificed or helped the United States as much as Pakistan in its war on terror, suffering 75,000 casualties. The friction threatens to worsen already fragile relations between Islamabad and Washington, on-off allies which have repeatedly cl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Builds Fence on Afghan Border - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3813260.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBaZZdMp49wk7CLSC1JehPQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 14:50:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3813260.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Builds Fence on Afghan Border&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s military announced Monday that its plan to fence the entire 2,611-kilometer largely porous border with Afghanistan is underway and scores of new outposts are also being built to prevent terrorist infiltration. Army spokesman Major-General Asif Ghafoor told reporters in Rawalpindi that a total of 338 security posts and forts will be constructed along the frontier by the end of 2019. He said 42 such installations have been built while work on another 63 is under way. Pakistan announced last month that was starting to build the fence in "high threat zones" of its shared border with ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan denies allegations of supporting armed groups - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/pakistan-denies-allegations-supporting-armed-groups-171005170120696.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFMJDwOyXcKnaMCfFhpk8_sqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 17:45:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/pakistan-denies-allegations-supporting-armed-groups-171005170120696.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan denies allegations of supporting armed groups&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamabad, Pakistan - The Pakistani military has responded to a charge of having links to armed groups in South Asia, arguing that it is the job of intelligence agencies to maintain such connections, but rejected the notion that Pakistan supported groups such as the Afghan Taliban. "Please understand, 'having links' and 'supporting' [armed groups] are two different things," said Major General Asif Ghafoor, the military's spokesperson, at a press conference in the northern garrison city of Rawalpindi. "Name an intelligence agency of any country that does not have links [to armed groups]. Eve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Unleashes New Anti-IS Military Operation Near Afghan Border - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-military-operation-afghan-border/3946340.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKweJA5ep6hlDRQG2Ct2890qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 15:52:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-military-operation-afghan-border/3946340.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Unleashes New Anti-IS Military Operation Near Afghan Border&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s military launched a major ground offensive Sunday to clear an isolated militant-infested border valley that Islamic State loyalists are using to export terrorism into the country from its bases in neighboring Afghanistan, where the group is "gaining strength", said an army spokesman. Major-General Asif Ghafoor told reporters that the operation dubbed Khyber-4 has been tasked with eliminating militant hideouts from an area of about 250-square kilometers in the Rajgal valley. He said militants linked to pro-IS groups, Jamaatul Ahrar and Lashkar-e-Jhangvi, as well as the Pakistani T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Army Chief to Visit Afghanistan Sunday - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-army-chief-to-visit-afghanistan-saturday/4049902.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIb8uYHvMVDodfpn1P_1sNwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 17:18:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-army-chief-to-visit-afghanistan-saturday/4049902.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Army Chief to Visit Afghanistan Sunday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s military chief, General Qamar Javed Bajwa, will undertake a crucial visit to Afghanistan on Sunday where his delegation is to discuss with Afghan counterparts ways to strengthen bilateral security cooperation and border management efforts. Relations between Islamabad and Kabul have been marred by mistrust and suspicion, with both sides routinely accusing each other’s security institutions of backing fugitive anti-state militants to plot terrorist attacks against the other. While no official details of Bajwa’s expected engagements in Kabul have been announced, he is scheduled to m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>6 Dead in Cross Border Shooting in Kashmir - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kashmir-cross-border-shooting/4039770.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPLwBwvBpUEwdpTqEgSm6hcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 07:54:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kashmir-cross-border-shooting/4039770.html" target="_blank"&gt;6 Dead in Cross Border Shooting in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan's military says the death toll from the overnight cross-border shooting by India in the disputed Kashmir region has risen to six. In a statement Friday army spokesman Major General Asif Ghafoor said 26 people, including women and children, were also wounded in what he called “unprovoked'' Indian shelling across the boundary in the Charwa and Harpal villages, on the Pakistani side. The latest incident in the disputed Himalayan region comes as Pakistani Prime Minister Shahid Khaqan Abbasi said in his speech at the U.N. General Assembly that India has committed a number of human right...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indian Army Says it Hit Pakistan Posts in Kashmir; Pakistan Denies it - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3867481.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKIy1-7y7ZfBUnD99Zmqw6oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 17:27:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3867481.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian Army Says it Hit Pakistan Posts in Kashmir; Pakistan Denies it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Indian army said Tuesday it has hit army posts in Pakistani Kashmir that were providing cover for militants planning to cross into the Indian side of the disputed Himalayan territory. Pakistan denies that any such action took place. Major General Ashok Narula did not specify when the military operation was carried out, but he said it happened “recently, very recently.” Narula called it part of counter-insurgency operations in Kashmir. “The recent action by our troops in Nowshera sector has caused some damage to Pak army force, which are supporting infiltration,” he told reporters in New...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Warns Afghanistan 'Blame Game' Hurting Peace Efforts - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-warns-afghanistan-blame-game-hurting-peace-talks/3677218.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMZYh6gJkv-ORS28b4b6DNAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 19:39:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-warns-afghanistan-blame-game-hurting-peace-talks/3677218.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Warns Afghanistan 'Blame Game' Hurting Peace Efforts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s military chief told Afghan President Ashraf Ghani on Sunday that his troops have eliminated "all safe havens” of terrorists on Pakistani soil, and he emphasized the need for security cooperation between the two countries to deter cross-border terrorist infiltration. General Qamar Javed Bajwa contacted Ghani by phone following Tuesday’s almost simultaneous bombings in different Afghan cities, including the capital city Kabul. The violence left more than 50 people and wounded scores of others. Five diplomats of the United Arab Emirates also were among the dead. Bajwa spoke to the A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistani army says it has acted against militants including Haqqani network - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-usa-idUSKCN1B11YF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDLoP1YwfQvzh6MJ2uGGJ3gqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 16:38:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-usa-idUSKCN1B11YF" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani army says it has acted against militants including Haqqani network&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Asif Shahzad ISLAMABAD (Reuters) - Pakistan has taken action against all Islamist militants including the Haqqani network, the army spokesman said on Monday hours ahead of a U.S. announcement on Afghan policy that could herald a tougher stance towards Islamabad. "There are no terrorist hideouts in Pakistan. We have operated against all terrorists, including (the) Haqqani network," spokesman Major General Asif Ghafoor told a media briefing in Islamabad. He said evidence to that effect was shared with General Joseph Votel, chief of the U.S. Central Command, who visited Pakistan over the we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Army Backs off After Questioning PM's Authority - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3846084.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOqBu71MPa-jXyE9X088ysYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 15:01:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3846084.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Army Backs off After Questioning PM's Authority&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s military backed off on Wednesday after publicly questioning the prime minister’s decision to sack an adviser over an explosive newspaper article alleging a rift between the country’s civilian government and the military. Government-military relations are a sensitive topic in Pakistan, which has had a history of military coups since gaining independence from Britain in 1947. Two weeks ago, Prime Minister Nawaz Sharif fired a senior adviser over a front-page article last year in the Dawn newspaper alleging the rift. Maj. Gen. Asif Ghafoor, a military spokesman, subsequently questio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan army says plan in place to integrate militant-linked groups - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-politics-militants/pakistan-army-says-plan-in-place-to-integrate-militant-linked-groups-idUSKBN1CA2CP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHkocoRTZwM2_gGG7HRGa3AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 18:14:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-politics-militants/pakistan-army-says-plan-in-place-to-integrate-militant-linked-groups-idUSKBN1CA2CP" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan army says plan in place to integrate militant-linked groups&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Asif Shahzad ISLAMABAD (Reuters) - The Pakistani army on Thursday confirmed that a plan was in place to try to integrate militant-linked groups into the mainstream of the country's politics. Milli Muslim League (MML), a new militant party controlled by Islamist Hafiz Saeed, backed a candidate in the September by-election for a seat vacated by ousted Prime Minister Nawaz Sharif in the eastern city of Lahore. The United States has offered a $10 million bounty for Saeed's capture. Reuters reported last month that the foray into politics by MML and other Islamists groups followed the integra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Sentences Suspected Indian Spy to Death - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3803756.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAXwJtX81VBRXJCVQgdWu2EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 12:50:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3803756.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Sentences Suspected Indian Spy to Death&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A military court in Pakistan has sentenced an alleged Indian spy to death on charges of “espionage and sabotage” activities against the country, a rare move likely to fuel bilateral tensions. An army spokesman, while announcing details of the decision Monday, identified the man as Kulbushan Sudhir Jadhav of India’s primary foreign intelligence agency, Research and Analysis Wing (RAW). Jadhav was arrested through a “counterintelligence operation” in Pakistan’s violence-hit southwestern Baluchistan province in March 2016, and the military court found him guilty of all charges, said Major-Gene...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Hardens Stance to Trump’s Afghan Strategy - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-hardens-stance-to-trump-afghan-strategy/4003894.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF-HxZh_J7kcvzIyCmE8-h0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 18:30:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-hardens-stance-to-trump-afghan-strategy/4003894.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Hardens Stance to Trump’s Afghan Strategy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan appears to have hardened its stance to U.S. President Donald Trump’s recently announced Afghan and South Asia strategy; but, officials dismiss suggestions Islamabad is seeking “confrontation” or a “rupture” in its decades-old relations with Washington. While announcing his long-awaited policy last week, Trump accused Pakistan of housing “agents of chaos” and “the very terrorists” the U.S. military has been battling in Afghanistan. The policy also attempts to give Pakistan’s archival, India, a major role in security-related regional efforts. Pakistani leaders responded by saying the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan launches military operation in tribal areas targeting Islamic State - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-militants-idUSKBN1A10NH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKZLnG6kCU1NVFxh5ICuY50qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 14:51:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-militants-idUSKBN1A10NH" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan launches military operation in tribal areas targeting Islamic State&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Saad Sayeed ISLAMABAD (Reuters) - Pakistan's military has launched a major operation in its volatile tribal areas to stop the Islamic State making inroads into areas bordering Afghanistan, the military's spokesman said on Sunday. Pakistan has long denied Islamic State has a foothold inside the nuclear-armed nation despite a series of attacks claimed by the group over the past two years, including a bombing in the northern town of Parachinar last month that killed 75. Military spokesman Lieutenant General Asif Ghafoor said Islamic State - also known as Daesh - was growing in strength insi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Probes Detained IS Female Suicide Bomber Who Planned to Assault Christians - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-detained-islamic-state-female-suicide-bomber-planned-assault-christians/3814085.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGsMS-jh-mU-k3jNFYvEr-oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 20:07:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-detained-islamic-state-female-suicide-bomber-planned-assault-christians/3814085.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Probes Detained IS Female Suicide Bomber Who Planned to Assault Christians&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Military officials in Pakistan say a would-be Islamic State female suicide bomber had planned to assault a church during Easter celebrations Sunday in Lahore before a counterterrorism raid captured her this past Friday. Army spokesman General Asif Ghafoor at a news conference Monday identified the suspect as Naureen Leghari, saying she is still under investigation. The young woman, officials say, has told investigators she was contacted and radicalized by IS operatives through social media. Ghafoor also dismissed reported claims that Leghari had traveled to Syria and received training at IS...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan works to stop Asia Bibi leaving after blasphemy protests - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/02/outrage-as-pakistani-government-vows-to-stop-asia-bibi-leaving</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFi_rlV33bB8ZrhiMNhsfvsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 19:41:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/02/outrage-as-pakistani-government-vows-to-stop-asia-bibi-leaving" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan works to stop Asia Bibi leaving after blasphemy protests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s government has been accused of signing the “death warrant” of Asia Bibi after it said it would begin the process of preventing her leaving the country. Bibi, a Christian farm labourer, was acquitted of blasphemy on Wednesday. She had spent eight years on death row after she drank from the same cup as a Muslim, prompting false allegations that she insulted the prophet Muhammad. Bibi’s lawyer, Saif-ul-Mulook, has reportedly since fled the country amid fears for his life, telling AFP: “I need to stay alive as I still have to fight the legal battle for Asia Bibi.” The ruling Pakistan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Pakistan, Russia Begin Joint Anti-Terror Military Drills - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-russia-begin-joint-anti-terror-military-drills/4624012.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDVc9SkDWH-wIOgqWA_skbwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 14:53:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-russia-begin-joint-anti-terror-military-drills/4624012.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan, Russia Begin Joint Anti-Terror Military Drills&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan and Russia have begun annual joint military drills to boost counterterrorism cooperation to tackle the growing threat of Islamic State stemming from neighboring Afghanistan. Officials said the "Druzhba-III" (Friendship-III) drills went into action Monday at the National Counter-Terrorist Center in the mountain town of Pabbi, where the Pakistan army's commando unit, the Special Services Group, is headquartered. Chief army spokesman Major-General Asif Ghafoor said this is the third exercise of the Pakistan-Russia bilateral training cooperation. Russian military officials said during ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan's army chief visits Beijing after 'Silk Road' tension - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-china-military/pakistans-army-chief-visits-beijing-after-silk-road-tension-idUSKCN1LW0PR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB5F5YWZQQDaoPGb1ppvmF4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 14:31:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-china-military/pakistans-army-chief-visits-beijing-after-silk-road-tension-idUSKCN1LW0PR" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan's army chief visits Beijing after 'Silk Road' tension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan's army chief General Qamar Javed Bajwa began a three-day visit to China on Sunday, Pakistan's military said, days after a Pakistani minister stirred unease about Chinese Silk Road projects in the South Asian nation. Bajwa is the most senior Pakistani figure to visit staunch ally China since the new government of Prime Minister Imran Khan took office in August, and his trip comes a week after China's top diplomat visited Islamabad. Pakistan has deepened ties with China in recent years as relations with the United States have frayed. Bajwa may be hoping in Beijing to smooth out any C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan: Engagements With US Over Afghanistan to 'Yield More Positive Results' - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-engagements-with-us-over-afghanistan-to-yield-more-positive-results-/4491490.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH4Ij8W_2tkekx2r1XoctcYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 18:45:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-engagements-with-us-over-afghanistan-to-yield-more-positive-results-/4491490.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan: Engagements With US Over Afghanistan to 'Yield More Positive Results'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following years of an acrimonious blame game, the Pakistan and U.S. militaries appear to be engaged again in tactical counterterrorism cooperation for promoting a negotiated settlement to the war in Afghanistan. American and Pakistani military officials have acknowledged the positive trend in mutual ties, with both sides underscoring the need for continued engagements. “Pakistan looks forward to peace in Afghanistan. Pakistan has been doing its bit in this regard with other stakeholders,” army spokesman Major-General Asif Ghafoor told VOA on Friday. Ghafoor was responding to comments made b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>More than 370,000 troops to guard Pakistan election as army denies meddling - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/10/370000-troops-guard-pakistan-election-army-denies-meddling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8UM2wxVgq9ruS9YtvSv3EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:25:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/10/370000-troops-guard-pakistan-election-army-denies-meddling/" target="_blank"&gt;More than 370,000 troops to guard Pakistan election as army denies meddling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan's military said it would deploy more than 370,000 troops to guard the general election later this month, but said it was not meddling in the democratic process. Major General Asif Ghafoor told a news conference that more than three times as many troops would be deployed than in the 2013 elections, and they would be stationed inside and outside polling stations. Campaigning has so far been dominated by allegations the military has run a multi-pronged campaign to undermine the Pakistan Muslim League (PML-N) party of ousted former Prime Minister, Nawaz Sharif, and muzzled the media. S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Two British climbers rescued from Pakistan mountain - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/01/two-british-climbers-rescued-from-pakistan-mountain</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIYzCT_WbI2FhC7T0IYVV2kqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 13:38:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/01/two-british-climbers-rescued-from-pakistan-mountain" target="_blank"&gt;Two British climbers rescued from Pakistan mountain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s air force has rescued two British climbers after an avalanche crushed their tent near the top of a mountain in northern Pakistan, killing the third member of the party. Bruce Normand and Timothy Miller raised the alarm on Saturday night after tumbling snow and ice trapped them 5,900 metres (19,400 ft) up Ultar Sar, a mid-size mountain in the Karakoram range that includes K2, the second-tallest mountain in the world, and spans the border of China, India and Pakistan. On Sunday, an army helicopter pilot flew the two men down to Gilgit heliport along with the body of Austrian Christ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>British mountaineers rescued from deadly Pakistan avalanche at 19,000ft - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/01/british-mountaineers-rescued-deadly-pakistan-avalanche-19000ft/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ86AA-JDSJ91huQZJIKvhsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 13:07:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/01/british-mountaineers-rescued-deadly-pakistan-avalanche-19000ft/" target="_blank"&gt;British mountaineers rescued from deadly Pakistan avalanche at 19,000ft&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two British mountaineers have been rescued by helicopter from a remote peak in Pakistan after their Austrian climbing partner was killed when an avalanche hit the trio. Bruce Normand and Timothy Miller were fetched to safety by the army after being stranded by bad weather at more than 19,000ft. Their companion, Christian Huber, died when the avalanche hit their tent during a storm on Ultar Sar near Hunza in north east Pakistan. Mr Normand and Mr Miller were reported to be safe and uninjured. Both were photographed standing alongside their rescuers soon after they were brought down. Photogra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Taliban Announces Limited Cease-Fire - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/taliban-limited-cease-fire/4431503.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJeTS6euK9mhr2-lWo8D74IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 05:27:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/taliban-limited-cease-fire/4431503.html" target="_blank"&gt;Taliban Announces Limited Cease-Fire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Taliban announced Saturday it will halt offensive operations against government security forces across Afghanistan during three days of Eid al-Fitr festivities, which mark the end of the Muslim fasting month of Ramadan. The cease-fire coincides with the unilateral, weeklong stoppage of anti-Taliban operations by Afghan President Ashraf Ghani starting Tuesday (June 12). An insurgent statement said the Taliban leadership has also ordered his fighters not to hold meetings in civilian areas during the holiday period to enable their countrymen to peacefully celebrate the festival. But it vow...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>US Asks Pakistan to Facilitate Afghan-Taliban Peace Talks - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-asks-pakistan-to-facilitate-afghan-taliban-peace-talks/4430302.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaGhI1hW18aI_KObstm1-IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 15:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-asks-pakistan-to-facilitate-afghan-taliban-peace-talks/4430302.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Asks Pakistan to Facilitate Afghan-Taliban Peace Talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States has confirmed it is asking Pakistan for help in facilitating the Afghan government's direct peace talks with the Taliban insurgency. After months of strained relations and disruption in high-level mutual contacts, U.S. Vice President Mike Pence and Secretary of State Mike Pompeo this week spoke to Pakistani civilian and military leaders to push Afghan political reconciliation efforts. The flurry of high-level contacts came as Washington suspended all military assistance to Islamabad and both countries imposed travel restrictions on each other's diplomats. Lisa Curtis, a de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistani activist abduction sparks fear of crackdown on dissent - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/06/pakistani-activist-abduction-sparks-fear-crackdown-dissent-180606122635686.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENbSNvi_VP6XPK-SKLBdRUsqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 16:20:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/06/pakistani-activist-abduction-sparks-fear-crackdown-dissent-180606122635686.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani activist abduction sparks fear of crackdown on dissent&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brief abduction of a prominent Pakistani social activist and newspaper columnist known for her strident criticism of the country's powerful military has raised fears of a renewed crackdown on dissent in the South Asian country. Gul Bukhari, 52, was abducted by several unidentified men while she was on her way to a television news studio in the eastern city of Lahore on Tuesday night, a family member told Al Jazeera. Several hours later, she was released, they confirmed, although they did not provide any details regarding the attack. The abduction has heightened fears among activists and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistani military says 'no space for war' with India - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/06/pakistani-military-space-war-india-180605081226956.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDbBrA54rSUFg7m9sTA0yX0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 09:22:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/06/pakistani-military-space-war-india-180605081226956.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani military says 'no space for war' with India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamabad, Pakistan - Pakistan's military says there is "no space for war" with its eastern neighbour India, calling upon its regional rival to respect a reiterated commitment to a ceasefire in the disputed region of Kashmir made last week. Speaking at a press briefing on Monday, Pakistani military spokesperson Major-General Asif Ghafoor said he wished for all issues between the nuclear-armed neighbours to be resolved through dialogue. "War is a failure of diplomacy," he said. "We are two nuclear states, there is no space for war. So dialogue continues. India has always been the one to back...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan: Review set for ex-PM's remarks on Mumbai attacks - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/006d7e6c07da4b9f938d2e49e11c1b9b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOYAafD33fFo5NIQTDYtvLgqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 17:06:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/006d7e6c07da4b9f938d2e49e11c1b9b" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan: Review set for ex-PM's remarks on Mumbai attacks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISLAMABAD (AP) — Pakistan's army says the country's National Security Committee is set to discuss "recent misleading media statements" by the former prime minister regarding the 2008 Mumbai attacks. Army spokesman Maj. Gen. Asif Ghafoor says Sunday that a review on Monday was suggested to Prime Minister Shahid Khaqan Abbasi, who belongs to disqualified premier Nawaz Sharif's Pakistan Muslim League party. In an affront to the army, Sharif had implied in a recent interview that militants in Pakistan had crossed the border into India to carry out the Mumbai attacks. The Lashker-e-Taiba militan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Clashes Erupt Between Afghan and Pakistani Border Forces - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/violene-at-pakistan-afghan-border/4348823.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOR00lLXFRUPVs2h_zONW50qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 09:36:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/violene-at-pakistan-afghan-border/4348823.html" target="_blank"&gt;Clashes Erupt Between Afghan and Pakistani Border Forces&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan says cross-border fire from Afghanistan Sunday killed two Pakistani paramilitary soldiers and wounded five others. A military spokesman said its personnel were conducting routine "surveillance" in the remote Kurram region “to plug gaps and make necessary preparations to start fencing” the border when they came under attack from the other side. FILE - Pakistan army spokesman Maj. Gen. Asif Ghafoor. Army spokesman Major-General Asif Ghafoor said an “engagement” between military officials of the two countries “is underway to defuse [the] situation.” Pakistani troops, he added, are “e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Tests Sub-Launched Nuclear-Capable Cruise Missile - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-tests-sub-launched-nuclear-capable-cruise-missile/4322928.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENtfzG5y0ciTaFQhcC_UT_YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 21:06:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-tests-sub-launched-nuclear-capable-cruise-missile/4322928.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Tests Sub-Launched Nuclear-Capable Cruise Missile&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan announced Thursday that it had successfully conducted another test-firing of a nuclear-capable, submarine-launched cruise missile (SLCM), which has a range of 450 kilometers. The indigenously developed Babur missile was fired from an underwater platform and "engaged its target with precise accuracy," a military statement said. The rocket is capable of delivering "various types of payloads" and provides Pakistan a "credible" second-strike capability. Military spokesman Major-General Asif Ghafoor, while referring to the country's archrival India, said the development of Babur was a r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan tests submarine-launched, nuclear-capable missile - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/422760-pakistan-cruise-missile-test/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELE6CcTJRUY8AJcR4ePre_AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 09:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/422760-pakistan-cruise-missile-test/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan tests submarine-launched, nuclear-capable missile&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan has announced a successful test of its state-of-the-art Babur-III, which is a submarine-launched, nuclear-capable cruise missile. The Babur missile family has been in service since 2010. The third modification of the cruise missile was developed for the Pakistan’s navy to provide a second-strike capability in case of a war. Babur-III is submarine-launched, capable of carrying a nuclear payload weighing up to 500kg, and has a range of 450km, according to the Pakistani military. On Thursday, Islamabad announced that its navy has successfully test-fired a Babur-III missile from an und...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>US Rejects Claim Drone Hit Refugee Camp in Pakistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-rejects-claim-drone-hit-refugee-camp-in-pakistan/4224888.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE9NPNkT9WKOgwe4HCGlWicqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 18:09:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-rejects-claim-drone-hit-refugee-camp-in-pakistan/4224888.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Rejects Claim Drone Hit Refugee Camp in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States has denied Pakistan's claim that an American drone strike targeted an Afghan refugee camp in the country, in a war of words between the uneasy allies. The denial Thursday came a day after missiles fired from an unmanned aircraft struck a militant hideout located between Pakistan's semiautonomous Kurram region and the Hango district, both in the country's northwest. The pre-dawn Wednesday attack killed a commander of the Haqqani militant network and his two aides. The Pakistani Foreign Ministry denounced the "unilateral action," saying a compound being used by Afghan refuge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistani Army Chief Says Nation Felt 'Betrayed' by US - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistani-armyc-hief-says-nation-felt-betrayed-us/4205340.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGIoK968wCllaUADlC4outIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 18:50:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistani-armyc-hief-says-nation-felt-betrayed-us/4205340.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani Army Chief Says Nation Felt 'Betrayed' by US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A top American general has told Pakistan's army chief the U.S. military does not intend to conduct any unilateral strikes inside the country and both sides emphasized the need for continued cooperation to fight terrorism, an official announcement said Friday. U.S. Central Command General Joseph Votel telephoned General Qamar Javed Bajwa this week and offered the assurance, said army spokesman Major-General Asif Ghafoor, while releasing details of the conversation. He did not say when it occurred. The high-level contact came after U.S. President Donald Trump, in a New Year Day's tweet, accus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Slams India for 'Invitation for Nuclear Encounter' - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-slams-india-inviting-nuclear-encounter/4206639.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELGysq9KRhMzO82QCXHPbLoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 23:49:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-slams-india-inviting-nuclear-encounter/4206639.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Slams India for 'Invitation for Nuclear Encounter'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan denounced Saturday as "irresponsible" remarks by rival India's army chief in which he vowed to expose "Pakistan's nuclear bogey" in the event of a war between the countries. Islamabad's reaction came a day after Indian General Bipin Rawat dismissed assertions that Pakistani "tactical" nuclear weapons had effectively countered India's ability to impose a conventional military war on the neighboring country. "We will call their bluff. If given the task, we will not say we cannot cross the border because they have nuclear weapons," Rawat said while speaking to reporters in New Delhi. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Mulls NATO Offer to Ship Afghan Supplies Through Gwadar Port - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-mulls-natio-offer-to-ship-afghan-supplies-through-gwadar-port/4201473.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOut96cSLFhbvohyLzUr8gYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 14:59:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-mulls-natio-offer-to-ship-afghan-supplies-through-gwadar-port/4201473.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Mulls NATO Offer to Ship Afghan Supplies Through Gwadar Port&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistani officials say the U.S.-led NATO military coalition in Afghanistan has offered to import vital supplies through the southwestern port of Gwadar, calling it a much shorter and economically viable route into landlocked Afghanistan. The federal minister for maritime affairs, Hasil Bizenjo, says NATO representatives proposed the idea at a recent meeting he convened with local and international business leaders. “They (NATO) are very interested and we are working on it,” Bizenjo told VOA in an interview. The coalition of about 16,000 troops, known as Resolute Support, mostly consists of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>War of Words Rattles Pakistan’s Ties With US - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/war-of-words-rattles-pakistans-ties-with-us-/4193993.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECYMYIEsh3USxAhE8aRIjDcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2018 17:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/war-of-words-rattles-pakistans-ties-with-us-/4193993.html" target="_blank"&gt;War of Words Rattles Pakistan’s Ties With US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s military said Friday the suspension of U.S. assistance will undermine bilateral security cooperation and regional peace efforts but will not deter the Pakistan's counterterrorism resolve. “Pakistan never fought for money but for peace,” army spokesman Major-General Asif Ghafoor told VOA. The Trump administration announced Thursday it was suspending hundreds of millions of dollars in military assistance to Pakistan until the latter takes "decisive action" against the Afghan Taliban and the Haqqani network. The militant groups allegedly operate out of Pakistani territory and conduc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Warns US to Avoid 'Collision Course - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-warns-us-to-avoid-collision-course-/4191820.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKKpjmVPOqaUolobj8IQjcsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 11:45:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-warns-us-to-avoid-collision-course-/4191820.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Warns US to Avoid 'Collision Course&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan is rife with uncertainty and speculation on steps the United States may possibly take in the wake of President Donald Trump’s New Year’s Day tweet about slashing the country’s aid for treating U.S. leaders “as fools” and giving safe haven to the terrorists battling American forces in Afghanistan. Islamabad denounced the comments as “completely incomprehensible” and has reiterated its resolve to work together with Washington to fight terrorism and stabilize Afghanistan. Pakistani leaders insist the United States is scapegoating their country for its Afghan “failures.” However, Trump...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Planned Pakistan-Afghanistan Border Fence Moves Ahead Despite Objections - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-afghanistan-border-fence/4185735.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDfVQqYy3QIQAGmpDfmdLf8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 17:33:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-afghanistan-border-fence/4185735.html" target="_blank"&gt;Planned Pakistan-Afghanistan Border Fence Moves Ahead Despite Objections&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan says that almost 92 percent of its 2,611-kilometer largely porous frontier with Afghanistan will be fenced by end of 2018, hoping the massive unilateral undertaking will effectively address mutual complaints of militant incursions. The military-led construction effort went into action earlier this year. It has already fenced off about a 150-kilometer portion of the border identified as “highly prone” to terrorist infiltration. The pair of nine-foot wire fences, with a six-foot gap, and topped with barbed wire, runs along rugged terrain and snow-capped mountains as high as 12,000 fe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Warns US Against Unilateral Military Action on Its Soil - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/paksitan-warns-us-against-unilateral-military-action/4182958.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENFr_1zzyDCuG4-O7LDdlHMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 18:54:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/paksitan-warns-us-against-unilateral-military-action/4182958.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Warns US Against Unilateral Military Action on Its Soil&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan has warned the United States against undertaking any "unilateral" military action on its soil and rejected as baseless accusations of "inaction" against the Haqqani Network plotting deadly attacks in neighboring Afghanistan. Chief military spokesman Major-General Asif Ghafoor reiterated Thursday that Pakistani forces have undertaken "indiscriminate operations" against terrorists, including Haqqanis," rendering U.S. charges of "inaction" as irrelevant and baseless. He went on to say the impact of Pakistan's counterterrorism actions "will be seen in subsequent years and months." "Unf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan warns US against unilateral military action - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/12/pakistan-warns-unilateral-military-action-171229063851063.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBXzueD1H-MlX6ViYxEd5T0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 07:02:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/12/pakistan-warns-unilateral-military-action-171229063851063.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan warns US against unilateral military action&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamabad, Pakistan - Pakistan's military has warned the United States against the possibility of taking unilateral action against armed groups on its soil, in its strongest response yet to tensions between the two allies. Speaking to journalists in the garrison city of Rawalpindi on Thursday, Pakistan military spokesman Major-General Asif Ghafoor rejected the notion that Pakistan is not doing enough to fight armed groups. "We have sacrificed a lot. We have paid a huge price both in blood and treasure," Ghafoor said. "We have done enough and we cannot do any more for anyone." He said Pakist...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan: 3 Troops Killed in Cross-border Raid - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-cross-border-raid/4175514.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ1LsVtp6x0oEFvLn-iqf40qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 18:08:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-cross-border-raid/4175514.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan: 3 Troops Killed in Cross-border Raid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan says "terrorists” from across the Afghan side of the border raided an outpost Friday, killing at least three soldiers. An army spokesman said personnel of the paramilitary Frontiers Corps were constructing a new border post in the Mohmand tribal region when they came under attack. Major-General Asif Ghafoor said Pakistani troops killed five of the assailants and wounded many more in retaliatory fire. "Fleeing terrorists were seen carrying back dead bodies and injured,” Ghafoor added. He said Pakistan is "paying the price" for Afghan forces’ lack of capacity and "ungoverned spaces” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Twelve killed by Islamist militants in Pakistan - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-12-01/gunmen-attack-agriculture-institute-in-pakistan-killing/9218802</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVS_2__hNmYlaypwffFN1YqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:15:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-12-01/gunmen-attack-agriculture-institute-in-pakistan-killing/9218802" target="_blank"&gt;Twelve killed by Islamist militants in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamist militants have stormed a government complex in northwest Pakistan, killing 12 people and wounding 35 others, police and rescue officials have said. Key points: - The attackers were clad in women's burqas - Security forces were able to evacuate residents rapidly, saving scores of lives - Military spokesman says attack was planned in Afghanistan Police and military troops killed three attackers during a firefight at the provincial government complex for agriculture research in Peshawar, they said. The main Taliban militant group, Tehrik-e-Taliban Pakistan, claimed responsibility. Pol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Militant Attack on Pakistan University Kills 9 - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-agriculture-university-gunmen/4144814.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHizck86jRwGhnktlyWSxKwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 06:22:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-agriculture-university-gunmen/4144814.html" target="_blank"&gt;Militant Attack on Pakistan University Kills 9&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A group of heavily armed suicide assailants stormed a government agriculture research center and adjoining university hostel in northwestern Pakistan Friday, killing at least 9 people and wounding more than 35 others. Pakistani police and counterterrorism units swiftly surrounded the complex in Peshawar and began a rescue operation. The gunfight with terrorists lasted several hours and killed three militants. Provincial police chief Salahuddin Mahsud later told reporters investigators were trying to determine whether a fourth body retrieved from the site was also that of a militant. He said...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Welcomes US Offer to Prevent Militant Raids from Afghanistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-welcomes-us-offer-to-prevent-militant-raids-from-afghanistan/4128569.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPFrk-G--tYwxhatfkWuvYQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 17:19:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-welcomes-us-offer-to-prevent-militant-raids-from-afghanistan/4128569.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Welcomes US Offer to Prevent Militant Raids from Afghanistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan is welcoming a U.S. military offer to take action against militants involved in cross-border raids against Pakistan from Afghan soil. Pakistani officials say the move "augurs well" for regional counterterrorism cooperation. General John Nicholson, commander of U.S. forces in Afghanistan, told reporters in Kabul on Monday his offer was meant to discourage Pakistan's army from shooting at civilians across the Afghan border while responding to border raids by militants. “We have also offered if they [Pakistan] have a concern about anything on this side of the Durand Line [the border] ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan, US Divided on How to Initiate Afghan Peace Talks - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-pakistan-afghan-peace-talks/4092104.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEELz-KtvYzBk0Z0Xo3NLg8oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 14:52:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-pakistan-afghan-peace-talks/4092104.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan, US Divided on How to Initiate Afghan Peace Talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan has cautioned the United States that "cooperation," not "coercion," is the way forward for the two countries to find a politically negotiated end to an increasingly deadly war in Afghanistan. The message was conveyed to U.S. Secretary of State Rex Tillerson when he undertook his inaugural visit to Islamabad last Tuesday for detailed talks, led by Prime Minister Shahid Khaqan Abbasi, with civilian and military leaders, say Pakistani officials. The discussions focused on regional counterterrorism efforts and promoting peace talks between the Afghan government and the Taliban. During ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan, US Upbeat About Future Ties After Hostage Rescue - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-united-states-upbeat-about-future-ties/4070576.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHLjfSNz-5f8aY_zrcNdC_wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 20:05:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-united-states-upbeat-about-future-ties/4070576.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan, US Upbeat About Future Ties After Hostage Rescue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan and the United States, uneasy allies in the war against terrorism, appear upbeat about better cooperation and relations after a joint effort freed a U.S.-Canadian family from Taliban captivity. Pakistani security forces, acting on a tip from U.S. intelligence, rescued American Caitlan Coleman; her Canadian husband, Joshua Boyle; and their three young children Wednesday, hours after kidnappers had transported them into Pakistan across the porous Afghan border. The family has since been repatriated to Canada, after enduring five years as captives of the Taliban-linked Haqqani network...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Canadian says child killed, wife raped in Afghanistan - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/canadian-hostage-child-killed-wife-raped-afghanistan-haqqani-171014061959694.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGbpNu2cSZOf5YgQLIjVlR8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 16:48:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/canadian-hostage-child-killed-wife-raped-afghanistan-haqqani-171014061959694.html" target="_blank"&gt;Canadian says child killed, wife raped in Afghanistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former hostage Joshua Boyle said upon arriving back in Canada that the Haqqani network in Afghanistan had killed his infant daughter and raped his wife during the years they were held in captivity. Boyle gave the statement shortly after landing in Canada late on Friday with his American wife, Caitlan Coleman, and three young children. The couple was rescued on Wednesday, five years after they had been abducted by the Taliban-linked network while in Afghanistan as part of a backpacking trip. Coleman was pregnant at the time and had four children in captivity. The birth of the fourth child ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Milli Muslim League registration rejected by ECP - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/milli-muslim-league-registration-rejected-ecp-171012072803257.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGIqJPqIZQkXtqo_dW5SBEIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 14:13:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/milli-muslim-league-registration-rejected-ecp-171012072803257.html" target="_blank"&gt;Milli Muslim League registration rejected by ECP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamabad, Pakistan - The Election Commission of Pakistan has rejected the registration application of a new political party due to its links to charities said to be fronts for the armed Lashkar-e-Taiba (LeT) group. Milli Muslim League's (MML) application for registration was rejected on Wednesday by a four-man panel headed by Chief Election Commissioner Sardar Muhammad Raza in the capital Islamabad, MML spokesperson Tabish Qayyum confirmed to Al Jazeera. "We have been told that we need to get clearance from the interior ministry," he said. "This is an unprecedented move." Qayyum said the M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan bars a militant-linked group from forming new political party - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-politics-militants/pakistan-bars-a-militant-linked-group-from-forming-new-political-party-idUSKBN1CG1VZ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3lBtPt4El2Jq-vJCLEHmwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 14:09:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-politics-militants/pakistan-bars-a-militant-linked-group-from-forming-new-political-party-idUSKBN1CG1VZ" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan bars a militant-linked group from forming new political party&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Asif Shahzad ISLAMABAD (Reuters) - Pakistan's electoral commission on Wednesday barred from contesting elections a new political party that is backed by an Islamist with a $10 million U.S. bounty on his head, a government official said. Haroon Khan, a spokesman for the commission, said a four-man panel rejected the registration of Milli Muslim League (MML) as an official political party. Khan said Muhammad Raza Khan, chief of the Election Commission of Pakistan (ECP), told MML's lawyer at the final hearing of the registration that the new party has links with militant groups and as such ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>US disputes Pakistan story of American hostage’s liberation from Taliban-linked group - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/406538-family-rescued-haqqani-pakistan-us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENvKlL81hh25tleobnwsK7oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 02:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/406538-family-rescued-haqqani-pakistan-us/" target="_blank"&gt;US disputes Pakistan story of American hostage’s liberation from Taliban-linked group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An American woman and her Canadian husband, along with their children, have been freed by Pakistani forces after five years of being held by the Taliban-linked Haqqani network. But conflicting stories have emerged as to how the rescue went down. Caitlan Coleman and Joshua Boyle were freed on Wednesday by Pakistani forces. The Pakistani government claims the family was rescued in a hostile takeover, while the US rejects those claims. Coleman and Boyle are currently in Pakistan awaiting transportation out of the country. So far Boyle has declined to board any aircraft, despite the family bein...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item></channel></rss>