<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Jammu and Kashmir - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNR1JxWjNRU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-PK&amp;gl=PK&amp;ceid=PK:en</link><language>en-PK</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:09:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Engaging for Kashmir - The News International</title><link>https://www.thenews.com.pk/print/403033-engaging-for-kashmir</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiPGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZW5ld3MuY29tLnBrL3ByaW50LzQwMzAzMy1lbmdhZ2luZy1mb3Ita2FzaG1pctIBhQFodHRwczovL3d3dy10aGVuZXdzLWNvbS1way5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy50aGVuZXdzLmNvbS5way9hbXAvNDAzMDMzLWVuZ2FnaW5nLWZvci1rYXNobWlyP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:16:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thenews.com.pk/print/403033-engaging-for-kashmir" target="_blank"&gt;Engaging for Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The News International&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prime Minister Imran Khan's recent reiteration of Pakistan's position that war was no solution to solve the festering Kashmir problem is quite timely and has ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thenews.com.pk">The News International</source></item><item><title>Indian forces martyr seven in held-Kashmir - Pakistan Today</title><link>https://www.pakistantoday.com.pk/2018/11/25/indian-troops-martyr-eight-kashmiris-in-shopian-district-of-iok/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnBha2lzdGFudG9kYXkuY29tLnBrLzIwMTgvMTEvMjUvaW5kaWFuLXRyb29wcy1tYXJ0eXItZWlnaHQta2FzaG1pcmlzLWluLXNob3BpYW4tZGlzdHJpY3Qtb2YtaW9rL9IBwQFodHRwczovL3d3dy1wYWtpc3RhbnRvZGF5LWNvbS1way5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy5wYWtpc3RhbnRvZGF5LmNvbS5way8yMDE4LzExLzI1L2luZGlhbi10cm9vcHMtbWFydHlyLWVpZ2h0LWthc2htaXJpcy1pbi1zaG9waWFuLWRpc3RyaWN0LW9mLWlvay9hbXAvP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.pakistantoday.com.pk/2018/11/25/indian-troops-martyr-eight-kashmiris-in-shopian-district-of-iok/" target="_blank"&gt;Indian forces martyr seven in held-Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Pakistan Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SRINAGAR: At least eight people, including a civilian and an Indian army soldier, were killed in Indian-administered Kashmir on Sunday, capping off one of the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.pakistantoday.com.pk">Pakistan Today</source></item><item><title>Kashmir's youngest pellet gun victim could lose complete sight - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/kashmir-youngest-pellet-gun-victim-lose-complete-sight-181206223840348.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK-RXWHCV17Y3xJ_MzZLHNAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:05:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/kashmir-youngest-pellet-gun-victim-lose-complete-sight-181206223840348.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kashmir's youngest pellet gun victim could lose complete sight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shopian, Indian-administered Kashmir - Hiba Nisar, a toddler, is determined to play with her tricycle as her mother, Mursala Jan, struggles to keep the child from racing out onto the lawn. Any contact with dust could cause an infection to her eye. She can't talk much yet, but regularly fusses and points her finger to where there is pain. Doctors have warned that she may have permanently lost vision in her right eye. On November 23, the 18-month-old's eye was ruptured by pellets fired by security forces inside her home at Kapran, a village in the Shopian district in Indian-administered Kashm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Fighter accused in Kashmir journalist's murder killed in gunfight - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/fighter-accused-kashmir-journalist-murder-killed-gunfight-181128101426651.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG7lmqcPf9c279-5r9bZ2SoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 13:08:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/fighter-accused-kashmir-journalist-murder-killed-gunfight-181128101426651.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fighter accused in Kashmir journalist's murder killed in gunfight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Security forces in Indian-administered Kashmir claim they have killed a senior fighter believed to be involved in the murder of a prominent Kashmiri journalist in June. Naveed Jatt, the fighter who was killed after a gun battle, was a member of the Pakistan-based armed Lashkar-e-Taiba (LeT) group, police said on Wednesday, adding that he was part of the group of assailants who killed journalist Shujaat Bukhari. Bukhari was killed in a daring attack inside Srinagar's high security press area on June 14, while he was getting into his car. Police said on Wednesday, Jatt and another fighter wer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Opposition seeks clarity on Norwegian 'mediation' in Kashmir - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/opposition-seeks-clarity-norwegian-mediation-kashmir-181127130555711.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMFLGHm1AuhLKVMnm9b3ww8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:56:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/opposition-seeks-clarity-norwegian-mediation-kashmir-181127130555711.html" target="_blank"&gt;Opposition seeks clarity on Norwegian 'mediation' in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent visit by former Norwegian prime minister to Indian-administered Kashmir, where he met separatist leaders, has sparked a controversy, with opposition parties questioning the government over the surprise trip. Omar Abdullah, the leader of the regional National Conference (NC) party, pointed fingers at the Hindu nationalist government of Prime Minister Narendra Modi to explain the closed-door meetings held in Srinagar, the main city in the region. "What are the Norwegians up to in Kashmir? Would either (External Affairs Minister) @SushmaSwaraj ji or (National Security Advisor Ajit) Do...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Nine killed as Kashmir reels from its deadliest year since 2009 - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/killed-kashmir-reels-deadliest-year-2009-181125132023234.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM8v8IzKWFxL7BZ8w50aw4QqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 14:54:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/killed-kashmir-reels-deadliest-year-2009-181125132023234.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nine killed as Kashmir reels from its deadliest year since 2009&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar, India-administered Kashmir - At least nine people have been killed in violence in India-administered Kashmir, capping off one of this year's deadliest weeks in the disputed region already suffering its worst bloodshed in a decade. At least six rebels were killed in an early morning gun battle on Sunday between fighters and security forces in Kapran village of Shopian district in southern Kashmir. The fighting later sparked clashes in the volatile district between locals and police, during which a 15-year-old civilian was killed by security forces, according to residents. A senior ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistanis 'on one page' in seeking friendship with India: PM Khan - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-pakistan-idUSKCN1NX17Z</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENOvjHDc_nLFUVB0TzVch2MqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 12:49:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-pakistan-idUSKCN1NX17Z" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistanis 'on one page' in seeking friendship with India: PM Khan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan Prime Minister Imran Khan said on Wednesday his government and the military want to mend ties with arch-foe India, in the latest bid to improve relations between the nuclear-armed neighbours. "I, the prime minister, my political party, the rest of our political parties, our army, all our institutions are all on one page. We want to move forward," Khan said in a speech to open a new border crossing with India in Punjab province. "If India takes one step forward then we will take two steps forward toward friendship," he said. Pakistan's chief of army staff, General Qamar Javed Bajwa,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Indian troops kill 6 in Kashmir as death toll hits record high - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/indian-troops-kill-6-kashmir-death-toll-hits-record-high-181123114305542.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM50X1Pk6rV1UTg-i6J-q60qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:18:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/indian-troops-kill-6-kashmir-death-toll-hits-record-high-181123114305542.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian troops kill 6 in Kashmir as death toll hits record high&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian troops killed six separatist fighters in a gun battle in the disputed region of Kashmir on Friday, the army said, taking the death toll for the year to the highest in nearly a decade. So far this year, 400 people have been killed in Kashmir, India's only Muslim majority state, and more than half of them were rebels fighting Indian rule. It is the highest toll since 2008 when 505 people were killed. The number of deaths in violence in Indian-administered Kashmir had dropped to 99 in 2012 but has been climbing since. The disputed region has witnessed spike in violence since Prime Minis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Turmoil in Kashmir as state assembly dissolved after 'faulty' fax machine prompts Twitter fight - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/22/turmoil-kashmiras-state-assembly-dissolved-faulty-fax-machine/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKBOVgWZdK9-lDdE9iFPWQUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 13:30:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/22/turmoil-kashmiras-state-assembly-dissolved-faulty-fax-machine/" target="_blank"&gt;Turmoil in Kashmir as state assembly dissolved after 'faulty' fax machine prompts Twitter fight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The volatile state of Jammu and Kashmir was plunged into chaos as its legislative assembly was dissolved amid claims of backroom deals, treason and a supposedly wonky fax machine. Two coalition groups claimed they had faxed the governor of Kashmir with their arguments for taking power, but that the machine at his office was malfunctioning. They both then took to Twitter and Whatsapp to try and make their cases, prompting the dissolution of the state assembly amid the confusion. The state has been in a political limbo since a coalition between the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP), of the prime m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>India dissolves Kashmir assembly, fresh polls likely - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/india-dissolves-kashmir-assembly-fresh-polls-181121161530575.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEITDM5aidD78e1wjoLqlVVoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 20:21:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/india-dissolves-kashmir-assembly-fresh-polls-181121161530575.html" target="_blank"&gt;India dissolves Kashmir assembly, fresh polls likely&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar, India-administered Kashmir - The legislative assembly in India-administered Kashmir has been dissolved, a move likely to lead to fresh elections in the troubled state that has seen violence escalate in the last few years. Jammu and Kashmir Governor Satya Pal Malik dissolved the assembly on Wednesday, shortly after former chief minister Mehbooba Mufti staked claim to form the government by forming a "grand alliance" with two rival parties. Mufti, whose People's Democratic Party (PDP) had 29 lawmakers in the 87-member assembly, claimed she had the support of the National Conference ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Q&amp;A: Hizbul Mujahideen leader: 'We will never surrender' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/qa-hizbul-mujahideen-leader-surrender-181109111719903.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBY1X5Y1shJWvB9RGQCoX5EqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 05:09:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/qa-hizbul-mujahideen-leader-surrender-181109111719903.html" target="_blank"&gt;Q&amp;A: Hizbul Mujahideen leader: 'We will never surrender'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Riyaz Naikoo is one of the most wanted armed Kashmiri fighters with a bounty of 12 lakh (approximately $170,00) on his head. The 31-year-old former mathematics teacher is the commander of Hizbul Mujahideen (HM), a pro-Pakistan armed separatist group that opposes Indian rule in Kashmir. The HM group, founded in 1989, is regarded as a terrorist organisation by India as well as the United States and the European Union. The Himalayan region is home to seven decades of conflict, with more than half a million Indian forces deployed to fight rebel groups demanding either independence or merger wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>JKCA painting 'misleading picture' - Vinod Rai - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/20680112/jkca-painting-misleading-picture-vinod-rai</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENKxveW1pNoEketekVl0yaoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 19:20:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/20680112/jkca-painting-misleading-picture-vinod-rai" target="_blank"&gt;JKCA painting 'misleading picture' - Vinod Rai&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Committee of Administrators (CoA) has told the Jammu &amp; Kashmir Cricket Association (JKCA) to stop painting a "misleading" picture about the BCCI's reasons for withholding funds to the association. The CoA has said such pressure tactics will not work, and that the JKCA's non-compliance in implementing the Lodha Committee's recommendations was the reason behind the BCCI not releasing the funds. Iqbal Ahmad Shah, the JKCA secretary, had said earlier this week that cricket in J&amp;K had been "severely hit" because all the funds were "exhausted" following the Supreme Court order last October di...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Pakistan: Indian Cross-Kashmir Border Fire Kills 4 Civilians - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-indian-kashmir-border-fire/4038742.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKpt0MQLdenw7-HLTOjGbsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 17:35:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-indian-kashmir-border-fire/4038742.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan: Indian Cross-Kashmir Border Fire Kills 4 Civilians&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan says Indian shelling across the disputed Kashmir frontier has killed at least four civilians, including two women. The deadly incident took place in a remote village in the Charwa sector, the military reported Thursday evening. Pakistani forces responded, targeting Indian posts from where fire on the civilian population originated, it added. New Delhi has not yet responded to Pakistan's allegations. The two nuclear-armed rival nations routinely engage in clashes along the Line of Control, or LoC, in Kashmir, with both sides blaming each other for firing the first shot in violation ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>J&amp;K players ask CoA to intervene with participation in doubt - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/20672037/jk-players-ask-coa-intervene-participation-doubt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGIqZp0WC1oWcYRDFyl49SkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 01:50:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/20672037/jk-players-ask-coa-intervene-participation-doubt" target="_blank"&gt;J&amp;K players ask CoA to intervene with participation in doubt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Virtually every domestic cricket season in the last five years has begun with controversy and crisis at the Jammu &amp; Kashmir Cricket Association (JKCA). With less than a month before the Ranji Trophy is scheduled to begin, the JKCA and players are waving the red flag as the state's participation in the tournament remains in severe danger if the BCCI fails to inject fresh funds. Both the JKCA and the players have communicated their plight to Vinod Rai, the chairman of the Committee of Administrators (CoA), seeking his urgent attention. Earlier this year, the CoA, at the behest of the Supreme ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Ten killed in Kashmir clashes as Indian forces regain control of police camp - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/aug/26/indian-forces-kill-two-militants-and-regain-control-of-police-camp</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDPoMAEqY2Fgb6rznALoe_AqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 17:08:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/aug/26/indian-forces-kill-two-militants-and-regain-control-of-police-camp" target="_blank"&gt;Ten killed in Kashmir clashes as Indian forces regain control of police camp&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian security forces in the Kashmir Valley shot dead two militants after an hours-long gun battle to regain control of a government compound in which eight policemen were also killed, the state’s top police official has said. The shootout started after the militants stormed into the police camp in Pulwama, a town in southern Kashmir, early on Saturday, SP Vaid, the director general of Jammu and Kashmir police, told reporters in Srinagar. A search of the camp was continuing, he said, with all the militants believed to have been killed. In a statement to local newspapers, Islamist group Jai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Sunset - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/221449757/sunset-by-suhail-khan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGMNfivKuReoOV2VCpNbg_kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:32:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/221449757/sunset-by-suhail-khan" target="_blank"&gt;Sunset&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunset at Manasbal lake, Kashmir, India.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>US Sanctions Kashmiri Militant Group Hizbul Mujahideen - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/united-states-sanctions-kashmiri-militant-group-hizbul-mujahideen/3988515.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPgEL5BhDOKMVKI7Q-2ylL4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 19:54:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/united-states-sanctions-kashmiri-militant-group-hizbul-mujahideen/3988515.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Sanctions Kashmiri Militant Group Hizbul Mujahideen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States on Wednesday said it had sanctioned Hizbul Mujahideen, the largest of the anti-Indian Kashmiri militant groups fighting in the Himalayan territory divided between Pakistan and India. The Treasury Department, in a statement on its website, said it had listed the Pakistan-based group as a counterdesignated group, freezing any assets it may hold in the Untied States and prohibiting Americans from dealings with it. "These designations seek to deny HM [Hizbul Mujahideen] the resources it needs to carry out terrorist attacks," the State Department said in a separate statement. I...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kashmiris cast doubt on Indian PM Modi's 'warm' words - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/kashmiris-cast-doubt-indian-pm-modi-warm-words-170815093114638.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDbLA1NIvr-3O-hnd8Mapm8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 21:39:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/kashmiris-cast-doubt-indian-pm-modi-warm-words-170815093114638.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kashmiris cast doubt on Indian PM Modi's 'warm' words&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Narendra Modi said force would not resolve the situation in Kashmir in a speech marking 70 years of Indian independence. The Indian prime minister's comments on Tuesday came amid an upturn in fighting between Indian soldiers and separatist fighters in the Himalayan region and angry protests against Indian rule. "Abuse and bullets will not solve the Kashmir issue," Modi said, adding "embracing Kashmiris will". Just two days earlier in south Kashmir's Shopian area, three local fighters, two soldiers, and two civilians were killed in a firefight that led to street protests that wounded more th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>6 Dead in Cross Border Shooting in Kashmir - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kashmir-cross-border-shooting/4039770.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPLwBwvBpUEwdpTqEgSm6hcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 07:54:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kashmir-cross-border-shooting/4039770.html" target="_blank"&gt;6 Dead in Cross Border Shooting in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan's military says the death toll from the overnight cross-border shooting by India in the disputed Kashmir region has risen to six. In a statement Friday army spokesman Major General Asif Ghafoor said 26 people, including women and children, were also wounded in what he called “unprovoked'' Indian shelling across the boundary in the Charwa and Harpal villages, on the Pakistani side. The latest incident in the disputed Himalayan region comes as Pakistani Prime Minister Shahid Khaqan Abbasi said in his speech at the U.N. General Assembly that India has committed a number of human right...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indian fire kills Pakistan girl in Kashmir: officials - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/indian-fire-kills-pakistan-girl-kashmir-officials-170902145524540.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDtQpG6LfnhJh9CdVJZsXowqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 15:02:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/indian-fire-kills-pakistan-girl-kashmir-officials-170902145524540.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian fire kills Pakistan girl in Kashmir: officials&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A five-year-old Pakistani girl was killed on Saturday after she was hit in the head by a bullet fired by Indian troops across the border in disputed Kashmir, officials said. The incident took place in Polas village at Abbaspur sector on the Line of Control, the de facto border dividing Kashmir between nuclear-armed rivals Pakistan and India. "A five-year-old girl was walking outside her house when a lone bullet fired by Indian troops pierced through her head," official Tahir Mumtaz told AFP news agency. The girl was rushed to hospital but died on the way, he said, adding villagers held a pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Fighters, Indian troops among latest killed in Kashmir - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/fighters-indian-troops-latest-killed-kashmir-170803075746543.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEx00GYNyCCVkSa7fUUuti0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 11:34:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/fighters-indian-troops-latest-killed-kashmir-170803075746543.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fighters, Indian troops among latest killed in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two Indian soldiers and two fighters were killed in clashes in Indian-administered Kashmir, where tensions are high following the killing of a prominent leader of the Lashkar-e-Taiba (LeT) group. Early on Tuesday, Indian troops ambushed the two fighters in Kulgam, south of the main city of Srinagar. "It was a deliberate and swift operation," an army officer told the AFP news agency. In a separate incident, two Indian troops were killed and another was injured in a shootout with rebels in Shopian district, the officer said, speaking on the condition of anonymity. "Three soldiers were evacuat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Raw beauty of Turtuk village side in Ladakh - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/224279427/raw-beauty-of-turtuk-village-side-in-ladakh-by-meens-photography</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMXgFfbJGJaSF4spxEvrqE8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 10:05:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/224279427/raw-beauty-of-turtuk-village-side-in-ladakh-by-meens-photography" target="_blank"&gt;Raw beauty of Turtuk village side in Ladakh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turtuk - Quaint little village side on the border of India-pak in Ladakh region.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Eight Indian security personnel killed in Kashmir - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/170826132256811.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJvMWZRybz9WbrGscf7jPAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 17:08:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/170826132256811.html" target="_blank"&gt;Eight Indian security personnel killed in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar, Indian-administered Kashmir - Four policemen and four paramilitary personnel were killed as rebels stormed a police installation in the southern part of this disputed territory. The attack began around 4am on Saturday when a group of rebels breached the highly guarded district police base in Pulwama, 35km from Kashmir's main city Srinagar. Local villagers said they were awoken in the early hours by an intense rattle of gunfire and explosions. "We were sleeping when we heard the gunshots and then there was sound of blasts. We thought it will end but it kept happening again and agai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>pangong lake,ladkah,india - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/229789303/pangong-lake-ladkah-india-by-tejas-soni</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENKJsbb5t0HqXbtgUDDqYbYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 20:28:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/229789303/pangong-lake-ladkah-india-by-tejas-soni" target="_blank"&gt;pangong lake,ladkah,india&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;pangong tso,ladakh&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>India-China tensions escalate as soldiers hurl stones at each other in Kashmir - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/india-china-tensions-kashmir-soldiers-throw-stones-at-each-other-a7897241.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA_f67Cfx2llKhvPvVRXdNUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 18:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/india-china-tensions-kashmir-soldiers-throw-stones-at-each-other-a7897241.html" target="_blank"&gt;India-China tensions escalate as soldiers hurl stones at each other in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials say Indian and Chinese soldiers hurled stones at one another during an altercation in the high Himalayas in Indian-controlled Kashmir, escalating the tensions between two nations already engaged in a lengthy border standoff elsewhere. Police and Indian army officials said Wednesday the Chinese soldiers hurled stones while attempting to enter Ladakh region near Pangong Lake on Tuesday but were confronted by Indian soldiers. They said Indian soldiers retaliated but neither side used guns. Soldiers from the two countries are already locked in a bitter but non-violent standoff in Dokl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>A Tale of Leh Mountains - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/227608649/a-tale-of-leh-mountains-by-phongsiri-kittikamhaeng</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECDA7uXeWFLOhYye8elrTh8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 13:15:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/227608649/a-tale-of-leh-mountains-by-phongsiri-kittikamhaeng" target="_blank"&gt;A Tale of Leh Mountains&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leh Ladakh, India&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>US Terror Label on Kashmiri Group Unlikely to Curb Violence - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-terror-label-on-kashmiri-group-unlikely-to-curb-violence/3998620.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFMVHPBs_3gqDBMYaFCY4t0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 09:14:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-terror-label-on-kashmiri-group-unlikely-to-curb-violence/3998620.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Terror Label on Kashmiri Group Unlikely to Curb Violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India scored a major diplomatic victory over Pakistan earlier this month when the United States designated the largest militant group fighting against Indian rule in the divided Kashmir region as a “foreign terrorist” organization. For India, the terror label on the banned Hizbul Mujahideen, or HM, is a strong affirmation of its argument that the violence in its only Muslim majority region is fueled by Islamic militant groups that operate from Pakistan, what India has long called “cross-border terrorism.” Islamabad denies the charges. HM was established in 1989 when the insurgency erupted i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Kashmir militant leader announced as head of new al-Qaida-linked cell - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jul/27/kashmir-militant-leader-announced-as-head-of-new-al-qaida-linked-cell-zakir-musa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPyygGchsKQZAi-t9HtgLcsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 09:35:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jul/27/kashmir-militant-leader-announced-as-head-of-new-al-qaida-linked-cell-zakir-musa" target="_blank"&gt;Kashmir militant leader announced as head of new al-Qaida-linked cell&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An al-Qaida-affiliated propaganda channel has announced one of Kashmir’s most popular militant leaders as the head of a newly created cell in the disputed Himalayan territory. The appointment of Zakir Musa as head of the new group represents the first time militants linked to al-Qaida have operated openly in Kashmir, site of a decades-long separatist insurgency and the only Muslim-majority region under Indian control. Related: Attack by militants kills at least seven Hindu pilgrims in Kashmir Musa, 23, is the leading figure among a new generation of militants who have exploited social media...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Kashmir victim: Life since India's pellets blinded me - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/09/kashmir-victim-life-india-pellets-blinded-170929102239932.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPv5Wl7UJLtKHmzHrmslEX8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 08:13:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/09/kashmir-victim-life-india-pellets-blinded-170929102239932.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kashmir victim: Life since India's pellets blinded me&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sedow, India-administered Kashmir – More than one year has passed since Insha Mushtaq got a good night's sleep. The teenager cannot forget the evening of July 11, 2016, when, aged 14, she had opened the window to look out at the protests raging against the killing of a popular rebel commander, Burhan Wani, in the village of Sedow in southern Kashmir. The next moment, the police would fire a volley of iron pellets indiscriminately, hitting Insha in the face, skull and her eyes. The pellets penetrated deep into her eyes. She was suddenly blinded. "I just peeped through the window and the pol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Protests erupt as India troops kill Kashmir fighters - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/protests-erupt-india-troops-kill-kashmir-rebels-170805075259981.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP3ygrkgUjgOBN2xUYnva94qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 16:42:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/protests-erupt-india-troops-kill-kashmir-rebels-170805075259981.html" target="_blank"&gt;Protests erupt as India troops kill Kashmir fighters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian troops have killed at least three suspected suspected fighters in a gun battle in Indian-administered Kashmir, officials say - an incident that has led to another round of protests. Fighting erupted in the divided Himalayan region after government forces raided a cluster of homes on a tip that the fighters were hiding in northwestern Sopore area, Muneer Ahmed Khan, police inspector-general, said on Saturday. He said that as the soldiers began searching homes, they came under gunfire from the fighters. A police statement said the men belonged to the Lashkar-e-Taiba group. Police on Tu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>India, at U.N., calls Pakistan 'pre-eminent export factory for terror' - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-un-assembly-india-pakistan/india-at-u-n-calls-pakistan-pre-eminent-export-factory-for-terror-idUSKCN1BY0S2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOW4Tn5iUf7WejxZNYt2TvoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 16:37:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-un-assembly-india-pakistan/india-at-u-n-calls-pakistan-pre-eminent-export-factory-for-terror-idUSKCN1BY0S2" target="_blank"&gt;India, at U.N., calls Pakistan 'pre-eminent export factory for terror'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By David Brunnstrom UNITED NATIONS (Reuters) - India responded with irritation on Saturday to Pakistani allegations of brutality in Kashmir, saying that while India had made substantial progress since independence, all Pakistan had achieved was a reputation as the "pre-eminent export factory for terror." Addressing the annual United Nations General Assembly, Indian Foreign Minister Sushma Swaraj rejected allegations by Pakistani Prime Minister Shahid Khaqan Abbasi at the world body earlier in the week in which he accused India of state-sponsored terrorism, and violating human rights. "Those...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Cross-Kashmir Border Clash Kills Pakistani Soldier, 2 Civilians - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/cross-kashmir-border-clash-kills-pakistani-soldier-two-civilians/4050417.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDGGdW1z7NUjI6ejKCXxIY8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 22:39:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/cross-kashmir-border-clash-kills-pakistani-soldier-two-civilians/4050417.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cross-Kashmir Border Clash Kills Pakistani Soldier, 2 Civilians&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan said that cross-border shooting by India late Friday left one soldier and two civilians dead in the disputed Kashmir region. Three soldiers and two civilians were wounded, according to a Pakistani military statement. The statement blamed Indian troops for initiating the fire and targeting the civilian population with heavy weapons in the Rakhchikri area near the Line of Control, which separates Pakistani and Indian portions of Kashmir. Soldiers dispatched to help evacuate injured civilians then also came under attack from Indian troops, the Pakistan army said. Pakistani forces retu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indian army kills Kashmir student mistaken for rebel - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/indian-army-kills-kashmir-student-mistaken-rebel-170824083746569.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENKzsk0-NQ9myhmbtZKIsMAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 11:00:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/indian-army-kills-kashmir-student-mistaken-rebel-170824083746569.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian army kills Kashmir student mistaken for rebel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar, Indian-administered Kashmir - The Indian army killed an unarmed 19-year-old student who they mistook for a rebel, said police in Indian-administered Kashmir. The fatal shooting on Tuesday of the teenager, Shahid Bashir Mir, led to protests on Thursday in Handwara, in the northern part of Indian-administered Kashmir. Residents of the Daril Tarthpora village clashed with police as they demanded a criminal investigation against the soldiers involved in killing Mir. Protesters carried Mir's body in a coffin but refused to bury the victim until such an investigation was launched. Kashm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Indian police kill militant commander in Kashmir; protests erupt - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir-idUSKBN1AH3JK</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJLVv4gwEQ46B32_Drk_KukqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 08:16:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir-idUSKBN1AH3JK" target="_blank"&gt;Indian police kill militant commander in Kashmir; protests erupt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Fayaz Bukhari SRINAGAR, India (Reuters) - The top commander of an Islamist group was killed in Indian-ruled Kashmir on Tuesday, a police official said, triggering protests and prompting the authorities to suspend internet and train services. Abu Dujana, of the Lashkar-e-Taiba militant group, was gunned down with an accomplice in Pulwama district to the south of the region's summer capital Srinagar, police spokesman Manoj Pandita said. Acting on a tipoff, police launched a search in the village of Hadripora in the early hours and killed the two in a fierce encounter, Pandita said. Dujana ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The innocent victims of India's 'indiscriminate' shotgun use in crowd control - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-14/amnesty-urges-india-to-end-indiscriminate-use-of-shotguns/8943738</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIIZjTiLw2pSKrPTAXnZp0sqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 21:43:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-14/amnesty-urges-india-to-end-indiscriminate-use-of-shotguns/8943738" target="_blank"&gt;The innocent victims of India's 'indiscriminate' shotgun use in crowd control&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Kashmir's capital Srinagar, former carpet weaver Ghulam Mohammed sits with three of his daughters. They all used to study, he said, but shotgun pellets have left him blind in one eye and jobless, meaning he can no longer afford their schooling. "Now my girls have taken to embroidery work," he said. "They earn 100 rupees [$2] a day, that is how my family is surviving these days." Shotguns have been used in Kashmir since 2010, and Government forces fired them widely last year during months of anti-India protests, which followed Indian forces' killing of a popular militant leader. Mr Mohamm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Searching for new spots - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/224755135/searching-for-new-spots-by-michal-prouza</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsw_kULDzDScniPuCYUWqUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 11:23:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/224755135/searching-for-new-spots-by-michal-prouza" target="_blank"&gt;Searching for new spots&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location check no 1&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Kashmir: Five-year-old girl shot in head by Indian troops on disputed border with Pakistan - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/kashmir-india-pakistan-five-year-old-girl-shot-dead-border-conflict-a7926571.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED9sHfsFL4ZoT3XifNjoeZ4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 22:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/kashmir-india-pakistan-five-year-old-girl-shot-dead-border-conflict-a7926571.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kashmir: Five-year-old girl shot in head by Indian troops on disputed border with Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A five-year-old girl has reportedly been killed after being shot by Indian troops on the Pakistani border. The child had been walking outside her home in Polas village in the disputed region of Kashmir when a stray bullet hit her in the head. The girl was rushed to hospital but died on the way from her injuries. Read more - India-China tensions escalate as soldiers hurl stones at each other in - The British Empire’s homophobic legacy could be overturned in India - Rains lash southern Pakistan after causing havoc in India - India and Pakistan must tread the long hard road to peace "A five-ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Al-Qaida Announces Establishment of Group in Indian Kashmir - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/al-qaida-group-indian-kashmir/3962660.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELDO3r4gOxJ8xfuuaJykTjUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 09:57:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/al-qaida-group-indian-kashmir/3962660.html" target="_blank"&gt;Al-Qaida Announces Establishment of Group in Indian Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian police say they are investigating a claim by al-Qaida that it has established a new group in Indian Kashmir. It is the first time a global terror outfit has claimed a presence in Kashmir, where local Islamic militant groups have led a violent, separatist insurgency. Al-Qaida announced the establishment of the Ansar Ghawzat-Ul-Hind, to be led by a local commander, Zakir Musa, on its online information network, the Global Islamic Media Front. Musa represents a new generation of young militants who Indian experts say are radicalizing young Kashmiris to revitalize an insurgency that had ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indian troops kill six militants in Kashmir - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir/indian-troops-kill-six-militants-in-kashmir-idUSKCN1NU0BG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEZiHQxPpdf4f-QLBeLTOZsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 09:46:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir/indian-troops-kill-six-militants-in-kashmir-idUSKCN1NU0BG" target="_blank"&gt;Indian troops kill six militants in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian troops on Sunday killed six separatist militants in a gun battle in the disputed region of Kashmir, the army said, as its forces stepped up operations in one of the bloodiest weeks of fighting this year during which 23 people have been killed. The six militants were shot dead by troops in a village south of Srinagar in an operation launched early on Sunday, Indian army spokesman in Kashmir, Colonel Rajesh Kalia, said. One soldier was also killed in the operation. The bodies of the militants and ammunition were recovered from the site of the operation, he said. Locals in the area clas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Indian-administered Kashmir: Militant leader's death sparks protests - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/02/asia/protests-indian-administered-kashmir/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPiaN-3H_nRrkUu6rmJfZ5gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 14:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/08/02/asia/protests-indian-administered-kashmir/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian-administered Kashmir: Militant leader's death sparks protests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Violent protests have erupted in Indian-administered Kashmir over the killing of a militant leader early Tuesday. According to Indian officials, Pakistani commander of banned terror group Lashkar-e-Taiba (LeT) Abu Dujana, along with his aide Arif Nabi Dar, were killed after engaging in a lengthy gun battle Tuesday morning with government troops in Kashmir's Pulwama district, 35 kilometers south of the capital Srinagar. "Abu Dujana was the Lashkar-e-Taiba chief for Kashmir ... a category A plus, plus, terrorist," said senior Indian army official JS Sandhu during a press conference. "This is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Two Indian soldiers, three militants killed in gunfight in Kashmir - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir-idUSKCN1AT08U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJK6Qvc4n6qcVOE_tMpIMm0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 08:59:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir-idUSKCN1AT08U" target="_blank"&gt;Two Indian soldiers, three militants killed in gunfight in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SRINAGAR, India (Reuters) - Two Indian soldiers and three militants were killed in a 12-hour gunfight in South Kashmir's Shopian district, a top police official said on Sunday. The gunfight began on Saturday night when militants hiding inside a village opened fire on security forces, who were conducting a search in the area following a tip-off about the presence of three members of Hizbul Mujahideen - the largest of the anti-Indian Kashmiri militant groups. The gun battle went on until Sunday morning. "Three terrorists were killed in the encounter," S.P. Vaid, director general of the state ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The endless wait for Kashmir's disappeared to return - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/endless-wait-kashmir-disappeared-return-170830094023374.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM29b0I_BrQlcAYxXeakxF0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 12:22:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/endless-wait-kashmir-disappeared-return-170830094023374.html" target="_blank"&gt;The endless wait for Kashmir's disappeared to return&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar, Kashmir - In a central park in Kashmir's Srinagar, relatives of the disappeared gather for a day of remembrance and mourning. Some burst into tears as they hold photographs of their lost loved ones, some of whom have been missing for years and whose fate remains unknown. It is the International Day of the Disappeared and these families have one simple question: are their loved ones dead or alive? They have waited years for any sign of them. They have visited graveyards, morgues, prisons and torture centres, but found no trace of their missing kin. The families were brought togethe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>India kills five militants in Kashmir: army spokesman - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir-idUSKBN1AN23U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENMFtcTrrO7BkfPEXbRaVZcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 17:16:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir-idUSKBN1AN23U" target="_blank"&gt;India kills five militants in Kashmir: army spokesman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Fayaz Bhukari SRINAGAR, India (Reuters) - The Indian Army killed five militants on Monday who were trying to enter from Pakistan across a disputed Kashmir frontier, an Indian defense official said. India and Pakistan have been in a confrontation for decades across the Line of Control (LoC), the de facto border separating parts of Kashmir held by both countries. "Five terrorists were killed today by the army in the Machil sector of the LoC, where a major infiltration attempt by terrorists has been foiled," Colonel Rajesh Kalia, a Defence Ministry spokesman, told Reuters. Kalia said weapon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Fighters and Indian soldiers killed in Kashmir clash - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/rebels-indian-soldiers-dead-kashmir-gun-battle-170813080642308.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdZzhlXqUicJobBGxkTin0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 13:46:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/rebels-indian-soldiers-dead-kashmir-gun-battle-170813080642308.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fighters and Indian soldiers killed in Kashmir clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two Indian soldiers and three separatist fighters have been killed in a fierce gun battle in Indian-administered Kashmir. Hundreds of Indian soldiers surrounded Awneera, a village about 50km south of the main city of Srinagar, on Saturday night following a tip-off about fighters in the area, AFP news agency reported. Kashmir has been divided between India and Pakistan since the end of British colonial rule in 1947. Both claim the territory in full. Muneer Khan, Kashmiri police chief, told Al Jazeera that fighting took place in the Shopian area. "We laid the cordon yesterday evening after we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Kung Fu Nuns Strike Back at Rising Sex Attacks on Women in India - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/kung-fu-nuns-strike-back-at-rising-sexx-attacks-on-women-india/4000160.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbBPgy085g7X7E1xftqGt8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 09:50:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/kung-fu-nuns-strike-back-at-rising-sexx-attacks-on-women-india/4000160.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kung Fu Nuns Strike Back at Rising Sex Attacks on Women in India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As dawn breaks, the sun edges over the expansive jagged mountains of Ladakh - a remote Buddhist ex-kingdom in the Indian Himalayas bordering Tibet - to reveal a world where time appears to have stood still. The chant of monks in a centuries-old monastery can be heard in the distance. Villagers slowly emerge from whitewashed stone cottages to tend to their wheat and barley fields, and ready their goats to search for pasture. Complete with its picture-perfect temples precariously perched atop rocky mountain outcrops, giant shrines and mantra-engraved walls, Ladakh's age-old Tibetan Buddhist w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>‘Indians have high threshold for tolerating stench’: Israeli stink bomb fails Kashmir tests - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/397724-israeli-stink-bombs-india/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEII40lK3CvTn7lFeU3gy3pQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 14:55:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/397724-israeli-stink-bombs-india/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Indians have high threshold for tolerating stench’: Israeli stink bomb fails Kashmir tests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Israeli crowd control stink bomb known as the Skunk, which smells like raw sewage and rotting bodies, destined for employment in the restive region of Kashmir, was rejected after it was found that Indians easily ignored its smell, local media report. High-level officials, who were not authorized to speak openly, told the Hindustan Times that the product, which is mixed with liquid and sprayed on crowds out of a water cannon, performed poorly in a test in New Delhi, despite its arrival being announced with much fanfare earlier. “The CRPF [Central Reserve Police Force] decided to test a fe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Gunmen kill a leader of India's ruling party in disputed Kashmir - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir/gunmen-kill-a-leader-of-indias-ruling-party-in-disputed-kashmir-idUSKCN1N7104</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIJq7oSTlzoGmArDmwuM27wqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 10:27:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-kashmir/gunmen-kill-a-leader-of-indias-ruling-party-in-disputed-kashmir-idUSKCN1N7104" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen kill a leader of India's ruling party in disputed Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unidentified gunmen killed a leader of India's ruling Hindu nationalist Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) in Jammu and Kashmir state late on Thursday, prompting authorities to impose a curfew in the area. Anil Parihar, 53, state secretary of the BJP, and his brother, Ajit, were shot dead in the predominantly Muslim town of Kishtwar, while they headed home after shutting their shop, police said. Police are investigating whether it was a militant attack or a criminal act, a senior police officer said. Anil Parihar was an influential leader in the region. He was considered a moderate and had a size...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Real Kashmir F.C.: Fairy-tale journey 'putting a smile' on the face of a troubled region - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/01/football/real-kashmir-fc-i-league-india-football-spt-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ7AnuN7NLkTPb9vvwxm_6oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 12:15:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/11/01/football/real-kashmir-fc-i-league-india-football-spt-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Real Kashmir F.C.: Fairy-tale journey 'putting a smile' on the face of a troubled region&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's the story of a how a football team in northern India has offered hope to a region struggling with economic and social problems. Now plying its trade in India's top-flight, Real Kashmir F.C. is gaining global recognition. TAUSEEF MUSTAFA/AFP/AFP/Getty Images Real Kashmir's journey started after floods devastated the region in 2014. Two local friends -- Sandeep Chattoo and Shamim Meraj -- saw the community struggling to cope and wanted to help. DIBYANGSHU SARKAR/AFP/AFP/Getty Images They were spurred on by seeing groups of youths congregating in the evenings causing social unrest. The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Last Light II - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/279896775/the-last-light-ii-by-mohammad-aehsan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENHhJpV3N8RoC-KrCfab_7QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:15:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/279896775/the-last-light-ii-by-mohammad-aehsan" target="_blank"&gt;The Last Light II&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a hiking trip in lower himalayas in Indian side of Kashmir.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>‘Stop glorifying terrorists’: New Delhi fires back at Pakistan PM over his tweet - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/442049-india-pakistan-terrorists-kashmir/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGqi8IcXrxn8PQ0sWwVWX5UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 15:58:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/442049-india-pakistan-terrorists-kashmir/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Stop glorifying terrorists’: New Delhi fires back at Pakistan PM over his tweet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India fired back at Pakistani PM Imran Khan, saying his country should stop “glorifying terrorists.” New Delhi’s reaction was triggered by Khan’s tweet, where he alleged that Indian troops killed “innocent” people in Kashmir. Indian Foreign Ministry spokesman Raveesh Kumar called on Islamabad to worry about its own internal affairs and “take credible action” to tackle terrorism in areas it controls rather than pointing the finger at others. The remarks came in response to Khan’s tweet on Sunday saying he “strongly condemns the new cycle of killings of innocent Kashmiris” at the hands of Ind...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Fresh clashes in Kashmir after four killed in gunfight - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/fresh-clashes-kashmir-killed-gunfight-181017105144129.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDlcGdFx4ibmEgDzlRjTi_gqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 11:58:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/fresh-clashes-kashmir-killed-gunfight-181017105144129.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fresh clashes in Kashmir after four killed in gunfight&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar, Indian-administered Kashmir - Massive clashes have erupted in India-administered Kashmir following the killing of two rebels and a civilian in an early morning gun battle with Indian forces in the main city of Srinagar. The police officials said a police was also killed in the violent clashes that broke out in the busy Fateh Kadal locality of Srinagar on the wee hours of Wednesday. "On a specific information, cordon and search operation was launched at Fateh Kadal in Srinagar which turned into an encounter. Three militants were killed in the encounter. One policeman was also marty...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Fighting in Kashmir city leaves 3 combatants, civilian dead - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/6f3e96b4fef24a14960aeceed79d4304</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOqiqthUXkk7K3fjl8CeTkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 14:39:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/6f3e96b4fef24a14960aeceed79d4304" target="_blank"&gt;Fighting in Kashmir city leaves 3 combatants, civilian dead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SRINAGAR, India (AP) — Anti-India protests and clashes erupted in the main city in disputed Kashmir on Wednesday after a gunbattle between militants and government forces killed at least two rebels, a civilian and a counterinsurgency police official, residents and police said. At least a dozen journalists covering the fighting were beaten by counterinsurgency policemen well after the fighting ended, media groups and reporters said. The gunbattle began early Wednesday after troops cordoned off a neighborhood in Srinagar on a tip that some rebels were in a civilian home, police said. The exch...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Indian troops fire shots at Pakistani helicopter in Kashmir - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/indian-troops-fire-shots-pakistani-helicopter-kashmir-180930172137493.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFayRekL80yiUrmNUqxXdngqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 07:23:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/indian-troops-fire-shots-pakistani-helicopter-kashmir-180930172137493.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian troops fire shots at Pakistani helicopter in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leader of the Pakistan-administered Kashmir region has accused Indian troops of shooting at his helicopter while it was flying close to the highly militarised Line of Control (LoC), the de facto border dividing the region. The incident happened in Havaily district in Poonch sector in the India-administered Kashmir when Raja Farooq Haider Khan, prime minister of Pakistan-administered Kashmir region, was on his way to a nearby village to give condolences to the family of a local politician who had died. "My helicopter had not even committed any violation and was flying well within our side of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Chief of Pakistani Kashmir region says Indian army shot at his helicopter - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-india-kashmir/chief-of-pakistani-kashmir-region-says-indian-army-shot-at-his-helicopter-idUSKCN1MA0RN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG3keuYlFKgeMt6wY5zqP5IqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 15:55:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-india-kashmir/chief-of-pakistani-kashmir-region-says-indian-army-shot-at-his-helicopter-idUSKCN1MA0RN" target="_blank"&gt;Chief of Pakistani Kashmir region says Indian army shot at his helicopter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The leader of Pakistani-administered Kashmir region said on Sunday Indian troops shot at his helicopter near the disputed frontier, a move likely to further fray ties between the two countries. Muslim-majority Kashmir is divided between nuclear-armed neighbors, who both claim the mountainous region in full and have fought two of their three wars over it since their separation in 1947. Farooq Haider Khan, the prime minister of the Azad Kashmir region controlled by Pakistan, said his civilian helicopter was fired upon by Indian army from across the "Line of Control", which acts as a de facto ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>India, Pakistan trade barbs at UN over failed bid for talks - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/india-pakistan-trade-barbs-failed-bid-talks-180929202643933.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFLTJ89WgSBrmlHdvB21KlwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 20:52:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/india-pakistan-trade-barbs-failed-bid-talks-180929202643933.html" target="_blank"&gt;India, Pakistan trade barbs at UN over failed bid for talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India and Pakistan exchanged barbs at the United Nations on Saturday after plans for a rare meeting between the foreign ministers in New York fell through. India cancelled the talks offered by Pakistan's new Prime Minister Imran Khan following an attack that foreign minister Sushma Swaraj said had killed three Indian soldiers. Addressing the United Nations General Assembly, the Indian foreign minister denied that her government had sought a pretext to derail the offer to sit down with her Pakistani counterpart Shah Mehmood Qureshi. Swaraj also said Hafiz Saeed, the alleged mastermind of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Why Kashmir's local policemen have become rebels' new targets - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/kashmir-local-policemen-rebels-targets-180922092913063.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL2kAHJnqhcyYTllJBTFmzwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 09:51:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/kashmir-local-policemen-rebels-targets-180922092913063.html" target="_blank"&gt;Why Kashmir's local policemen have become rebels' new targets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shopian, Indian-administered Kashmir - The killing of three more local policemen in Indian-administered Kashmir has underlined growing tensions between rebels and police. At least 37 policemen have been killed by rebels so far this year, according to official figures, compared with 32 in all of 2017. Relatives of 38-year-old Nisar Ahmad Dhobi, 28-year-old Firdous Ahmad Kuchay, and Kulwant Singh, 35, said they were taken from their homes and shot dead in the early hours of Friday by suspected members of two armed groups, in the villages of Kapran and Batgund in southern Kashmir's Shopian reg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Khan disappointed by 'arrogant' India after talks cancellation - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/khan-disappointed-arrogant-india-talks-cancellation-180922101232815.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJZsnpmWF7_9rufAjtQbUp8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 12:17:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/khan-disappointed-arrogant-india-talks-cancellation-180922101232815.html" target="_blank"&gt;Khan disappointed by 'arrogant' India after talks cancellation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan Prime Minister Imran Khan has lashed out at India's decision to cancel talks between the two countries at next week's United Nations General Assembly, calling the reversal "arrogant" and "negative". Officials from the two countries were scheduled to meet in New York. However, India backed out of the talks on Friday, blaming "latest brutal killings of our security personnel by Pakistan-based entities and the recent release of a series of twenty postage stamps by Pakistan glorifying a terrorist and terrorism". On Saturday, Khan took to Twitter to express his disappointment. "Disappoi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Outrage after photo shows soldiers dragging Kashmir rebel's body - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/outrage-photo-shows-soldiers-dragging-kashmir-rebel-body-180916145546197.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDpJfF5RTGnENHrct2cF5W8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 19:17:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/outrage-photo-shows-soldiers-dragging-kashmir-rebel-body-180916145546197.html" target="_blank"&gt;Outrage after photo shows soldiers dragging Kashmir rebel's body&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar, Indian-administered Kashmir - A photograph showing Indian soldiers dragging the bloodied, half-naked body of a rebel has triggered outrage in and outside Indian-administered Kashmir, with rights activists calling it a "barbaric" act which violates international humanitarian laws. The incident took place on September 13 in the Kakriyal forests in Reasi area of Jammu in the southern part of the disputed territory after a seven-hour gun battle, in which the army killed three rebel fighters. Soon after the fighting was over, the image of Indian soldiers dragging the dead fighter with ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>India and Pakistan foreign ministers to meet in sign of thaw - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/da7acba2-bcc2-11e8-8274-55b72926558f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKWoMQW-XtdHHcNqz3d1aT4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 14:47:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/da7acba2-bcc2-11e8-8274-55b72926558f" target="_blank"&gt;India and Pakistan foreign ministers to meet in sign of thaw&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The foreign ministers of India and Pakistan will meet on the sidelines of the UN General Assembly in New York this month, New Delhi has confirmed, in the first signs of a significant thaw in tensions since Imran Khan came to power in Pakistan. India’s foreign ministry said on Thursday that Sushma Swaraj, the country’s foreign minister, would meet Shah Mehmood Qureshi, her Pakistani counterpart, following a request from Mr Khan to Narendra Modi, the Indian prime minister. Raveesh Kumar, Indian foreign ministry spokesman, stressed the session would be “a meeting and not a dialogue” and did no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>India and Pakistan engage in war of words at UN over Kashmir - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/india-pakistan-kashmir-un-united-nations-border-violence-a8516131.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH04sgnSwuiPc1rAAfBn7A8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 09:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/india-pakistan-kashmir-un-united-nations-border-violence-a8516131.html" target="_blank"&gt;India and Pakistan engage in war of words at UN over Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diplomats from India and Pakistan aired their differences over the disputed region of Kashmir at the UN this week, in what was supposed to be a general session on the merits of mediation at the organisation’s headquarters in New York. UN secretary general Antonio Guterres opened the Security Council debate by saying that mediating peace had become “increasingly complex” in the modern world - and so it proved, as bitter rivals India and Pakistan used the session to trade barbs. Nestled in the Himalayas, the broader region of Kashmir is split by the line of control between India and Pakistan,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>India: Six people killed after 'infiltration bid' in Kashmir - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/08/india-people-killed-infiltration-bid-kashmir-180807151253104.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGhAqaa5edXxF7opxxtGaIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 17:05:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/08/india-people-killed-infiltration-bid-kashmir-180807151253104.html" target="_blank"&gt;India: Six people killed after 'infiltration bid' in Kashmir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least four Indian soldiers and two fighters have been killed in a gunfight at the de facto border dividing the disputed region of Kashmir, according to the Indian army. The armed confrontation erupted on Tuesday after a group of rebels crossed from the Pakistan-controlled part of Kashmir into the Indian-held portion in Gurez valley, Colonel Rajesh Kalia, spokesman for the Indian defence ministry in Kashmir, said in a statement. He said the "infiltration bid" was foiled and two rebels were killed in the clash. "They were confronted when they were seen attempting to infiltrate into our sid...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Kashmir: Tension rises as citizenship rights law under threat - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/08/kashmir-tension-rises-citizenship-rights-law-threat-180804092715362.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHcLC9ANnKErKANe6glnNjcqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 11:33:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/08/kashmir-tension-rises-citizenship-rights-law-threat-180804092715362.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kashmir: Tension rises as citizenship rights law under threat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar, Indian-administered Kashmir - Tension is growing in Indian-administered Kashmir amid fears India's top court will revoke a law on Monday protecting exclusive citizenship rights. Article 35-A empowers the Jammu and Kashmir state's legislature to define "permanent residents" and provide them with special rights and privileges. It also bars non-state subjects from purchasing property and having government jobs in the disputed state. In the event India's Supreme Court repeals the law, there are concerns of a demographic change in the Muslim-majority state. Politicians, traders, civil ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Sun Bathing - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/267195637/sun-bathing-by-atul-singh</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMeOMbP0t1-qlm7stmxa9w0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 03:52:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/267195637/sun-bathing-by-atul-singh" target="_blank"&gt;Sun Bathing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sun bathing of the horse, after a long trek around Lake Karzok. A lake across two northern states of India in the Himalayan Region.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Unprecedented security at Kashmir's annual Hindu pilgrimage - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/unprecedented-security-kashmir-annual-hindu-pilgrimage-180716230226877.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJt4B-GAhACW2vB_ovyr8akqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 13:02:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/unprecedented-security-kashmir-annual-hindu-pilgrimage-180716230226877.html" target="_blank"&gt;Unprecedented security at Kashmir's annual Hindu pilgrimage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar, Indian-administered Kashmir - The Srinagar-Jammu highway in Indian-administered Kashmir is lined with bunkers and checkpoints. Security arrangements for the annual Amarnath Yatra, which takes place in the lap of Himalayas every summer, are high this year. Hundreds and thousands of devotees will make the days-long pilgrimage to the Amarnath cave, one of Hinduism's holiest sites, at 12,700 feet above sea level. Festivities last for two months, ending late August. As temperatures rise in the cave, an ice stalagmite forms. It is known as Shiv Linga, an iconic representation of Hindu d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Sarchu, Leh-Manali Highway,J&amp;K, India - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/266040561/sarchu-leh-manali-highway-j-k-india-by-dilip-khant</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMCdA3HpXzj1AgoQc2hBcEAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 13:12:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/266040561/sarchu-leh-manali-highway-j-k-india-by-dilip-khant" target="_blank"&gt;Sarchu, Leh-Manali Highway,J&amp;K, India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sarchu, Leh-Manali Highway,J&amp;K, India&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Three civilians killed in fresh wave of Kashmir violence - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/civilians-killed-fresh-wave-violence-kashmir-180707165615140.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO29Z7uCJ2sH4nD2bbuVaSwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 18:49:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/civilians-killed-fresh-wave-violence-kashmir-180707165615140.html" target="_blank"&gt;Three civilians killed in fresh wave of Kashmir violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Srinagar, Indian-administered Kashmir - Three civilians, including a 15-year-old female student, have been killed after Indian paramilitary forces fired on protesters in Indian-administered Kashmir, officials said. A top police official told Al Jazeera that the clashes on Saturday erupted after demonstrators threw rocks at an army patrol in Hawoora Mishipora village of the southern Kulgam district. "In a very unfortunate incident, three civilians were killed during the clashes in Kulgam. We are investigating the incident," the official said on condition of anonymity. The official said two ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item></channel></rss>