<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Papua - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRE40Y25FU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-PK&amp;gl=PK&amp;ceid=PK:en</link><language>en-PK</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:44:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>16 bodies found after attack in Indonesia’s Papua - The Express Tribune</title><link>https://tribune.com.pk/story/1861358/3-16-bodies-found-attack-indonesias-papua/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780128569578</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:58:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://tribune.com.pk/story/1861358/3-16-bodies-found-attack-indonesias-papua/" target="_blank"&gt;16 bodies found after attack in Indonesia’s Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Express Tribune&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/army-vows-hunt-killers-31-labourers-indonesias-papua-province/" target="_blank"&gt;Army vows to hunt killers of 31 labourers in Indonesia's Papua province&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpxa2NLbWpZQU1FWW9kVGtYLVFmOG5LQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://tribune.com.pk">The Express Tribune</source></item><item><title>Indonesia probes mass shooting reports in Papua - The Nation</title><link>https://nation.com.pk/05-Dec-2018/indonesia-probes-mass-shooting-reports-in-papua</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780125183989</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:25:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://nation.com.pk/05-Dec-2018/indonesia-probes-mass-shooting-reports-in-papua" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia probes mass shooting reports in Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Nation&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/indonesia-hunts-suspects-papua-mass-killings-181205084835789.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia hunts suspects after Papua mass killings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWoxdl9Pa2pZQU1FVkpxbjN0UEpxa2FLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://nation.com.pk">The Nation</source></item><item><title>West Papua independence leader urges calm after killings - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/06/west-papua-independence-leader-urges-calm-after-killings</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKtIvCxem8UT6KLuySQngUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/06/west-papua-independence-leader-urges-calm-after-killings" target="_blank"&gt;West Papua independence leader urges calm after killings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sixteen bodies retrieved as leader Benny Wenda calls for diplomacy and transparency on what happened in Nduga.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Rebels demand Indonesia negotiate on Papua independence - Washington Post</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/rebels-demand-indonesia-negotiate-on-papua-independence/2018/12/07/36d0f930-fa85-11e8-8642-c9718a256cbd_story.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMipAFodHRwczovL3d3dy53YXNoaW5ndG9ucG9zdC5jb20vd29ybGQvYXNpYV9wYWNpZmljL3JlYmVscy1kZW1hbmQtaW5kb25lc2lhLW5lZ290aWF0ZS1vbi1wYXB1YS1pbmRlcGVuZGVuY2UvMjAxOC8xMi8wNy8zNmQwZjkzMC1mYTg1LTExZTgtODY0Mi1jOTcxOGEyNTZjYmRfc3RvcnkuaHRtbNIB-wFodHRwczovL3d3dy13YXNoaW5ndG9ucG9zdC1jb20uY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy93d3cud2FzaGluZ3RvbnBvc3QuY29tL2FtcGh0bWwvd29ybGQvYXNpYV9wYWNpZmljL3JlYmVscy1kZW1hbmQtaW5kb25lc2lhLW5lZ290aWF0ZS1vbi1wYXB1YS1pbmRlcGVuZGVuY2UvMjAxOC8xMi8wNy8zNmQwZjkzMC1mYTg1LTExZTgtODY0Mi1jOTcxOGEyNTZjYmRfc3RvcnkuaHRtbD9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:04:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/rebels-demand-indonesia-negotiate-on-papua-independence/2018/12/07/36d0f930-fa85-11e8-8642-c9718a256cbd_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rebels demand Indonesia negotiate on Papua independence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA, Indonesia — Rebels in Indonesia's Papua province demanded that the government hold negotiations on their territory's self-determination and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.washingtonpost.com">Washington Post</source></item><item><title>Rebels Demand Indonesia Negotiate on Papua Independence - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/rebels-demand-indonesia-negotiate-on-papua-independence/4690843.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_xJ5OOo03iGAveBBjRBhwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:12:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/rebels-demand-indonesia-negotiate-on-papua-independence/4690843.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rebels Demand Indonesia Negotiate on Papua Independence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rebels in Indonesia's troubled Papua province demanded Friday that the government hold negotiations on self-determination for the province and warned of more attacks. Sebby Sambom, spokesman for the West Papua National Liberation Army, the military wing of the Free Papua Movement, said in a telephone interview they attacked a government construction site last weekend because they believe the project is conducted by the military. "Trans-Papua road projects are being carried out by Indonesian military and that is a risk they must bear," Sambom said. "We want them to know that we don't need de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indonesia halts search for Papua dead after clash with separatists - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua/indonesia-halts-search-for-papua-dead-after-clash-with-separatists-idUSKBN1O516M</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEW0V90YsH_kgKRzOuok-38qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:32:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua/indonesia-halts-search-for-papua-dead-after-clash-with-separatists-idUSKBN1O516M" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia halts search for Papua dead after clash with separatists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesian soldiers on Thursday retrieved the bodies of nine construction workers killed by separatists in the province of Papua, where fresh fighting halted a search for the remaining dead, a military spokesman said. Colonel Muhammad Aidi said efforts to retrieve more bodies from the weekend attack on a Papua construction site were halted after soldiers clashed with fighters from the separatist Free Papua Movement (OPM). "We still haven't been able to recover another seven because there was a shootout between the military and the separatist group," Aidi said, adding that the bodies of 16 o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>West Papua: conflicting reports surround attack that killed up to 31 - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/west-papua-fears-of-spiralling-violence-after-attack-leaves-up-to-31-dead</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECweYT8MW0wpwrGGF59XSD4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:44:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/west-papua-fears-of-spiralling-violence-after-attack-leaves-up-to-31-dead" target="_blank"&gt;West Papua: conflicting reports surround attack that killed up to 31&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deadly violence has escalated in West Papua following the shooting deaths of up to 31 construction workers in a central district of the region and the reported killing of an Indonesian investigator. The West Papuan liberation army has claimed responsibility for the attack – the deadliest in many years in the ongoing independence conflict – but there are otherwise differing versions of events from Indonesian authorities. There are fears of reprisals and violent crackdowns. There were mass arrests of hundreds of West Papuan protesters across the region who were marking the 1 December “indepen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Indonesia probes mass suspected killings in Papua - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/indonesia-probes-mass-suspected-killings-papua-181204234322758.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFhE3Q44yNVClwcY9zYQMzQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:09:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/indonesia-probes-mass-suspected-killings-papua-181204234322758.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia probes mass suspected killings in Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indonesian soldier has been killed while investigating reports that more than two dozen construction workers were shot dead by separatist rebels in the far-east province of Papua, officials said Tuesday. If confirmed, the killings would mark the deadliest bout of violence in years to hit a resource-rich but impoverished region wracked for decades by a low-key armed battle for independence. Citing local police, Indonesian media reported late on Monday that the workers were shot dead on Sunday in Nduga, a district in the centre of the region on the western half of New Guinea island, just n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Indonesian Public and Human Rights Groups Decry West Papuan Arrests - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/west-papuan-arrests/4687497.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIkFUhwZVaNhil2UJAmUc4IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:24:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/west-papuan-arrests/4687497.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian Public and Human Rights Groups Decry West Papuan Arrests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesian human rights groups decried the arrests made of West Papuan students and pro-independence activists after they staged peaceful rallies across Indonesian cities on Saturday. Benny Wenda, chairman of the United Liberation Movement for West Papua (ULMWP), demanded accountability from the Indonesian law enforcers, writing, “in the strongest possible terms, the ULMWP condemns the Indonesian government for the arrest and brutal treatment of over 500 West Papuan people and Indonesians in solidarity, who were targeted on 1st December simply for peaceful commemorating West Papua National ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Separatist gunmen kill 31 workers in Papua region: Indonesian officials - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/west-papua-separatists-allegedly-kill-workers-indonesia/10582480</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFMuskDrqkda1zYA0GcBjL8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 08:03:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/west-papua-separatists-allegedly-kill-workers-indonesia/10582480" target="_blank"&gt;Separatist gunmen kill 31 workers in Papua region: Indonesian officials&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesian authorities say independence supporters in the restive province of Papua have slaughtered up to 31 people who were working at a state-owned construction company. Key points: - The alleged separatist attack is the worst for many years in Indonesia's Papua region - The violence reportedly flared after migrant workers photographers a pro-independence rally - A low-level insurgency has plagued the mineral-rich but impoverished region for decades Papua police spokesman Suryadi Diaz said 24 workers were killed when gunmen stormed a government bridge construction project in a remote mou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Britain has the chance to bring a brutal colonial occupation to an end - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/21/britain-west-papua-colonial-occupation-geoge-monbiot</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENvlhmzCwE7gkWTjQSQTTg4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 06:00:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/21/britain-west-papua-colonial-occupation-geoge-monbiot" target="_blank"&gt;Britain has the chance to bring a brutal colonial occupation to an end&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every colonial enterprise pretends to be inspired by something other than theft. The General Act of the Berlin Conference in 1885, under which the European powers carved Africa into formal colonial possessions, claimed that their purpose was “furthering the moral and material wellbeing of the native populations … and bringing home to them the blessings of civilisation”. Similar rhetoric has attended all such seizures. To save native people from their enslavement to the Devil, or the Arabs, or each other, they had to be forced into general servitude, while their land and natural wealth were ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Freeport Indonesia mine workers extend strike for fourth month - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-freeport-mcmoran-indonesia-strike-idUSKBN1A61VJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrxLA020uF_WpUEmSMKPzoqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 14:39:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-freeport-mcmoran-indonesia-strike-idUSKBN1A61VJ" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport Indonesia mine workers extend strike for fourth month&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Wilda Asmarini and Susan Taylor JAKARTA/TORONTO (Reuters) - An estimated 5,000 workers at the giant Grasberg copper mine operated by Freeport-McMoRan Inc's (FCX.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Indonesian unit will extend their strike for a fourth month, a union official said on Friday, in an ongoing dispute over layoffs and employment terms. The escalating labor issue comes as Freeport, the world's largest publicly traded copper miner, is snarled in a lengthy and costly dispute with Indonesia's government over rights to the Grasberg copper and gold mine. Freeport resumed copper ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Banned West Papua independence petition handed to UN - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/sep/27/banned-west-papua-independence-petition-un</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK1_28cPuLjUTu0OtSniuEIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 05:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/sep/27/banned-west-papua-independence-petition-un" target="_blank"&gt;Banned West Papua independence petition handed to UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A petition banned by the Indonesian government, but bearing the signatures of 1.8 million West Papuans – more than 70% of the contested province’s population – has been presented to the United Nations, with a demand for a free vote on independence. Exiled West Papuan independence campaigner Benny Wenda presented the bound petition to the UN’s decolonisation committee, the body that monitors the progress of former colonies – known as non-self-governing territories – towards independence. Related: Melanesian leaders condemn UN for turning 'a deaf ear' to West Papua atrocities The petition was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Magnitude 7.9 quake strikes off Papua New Guinea - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/01/22/asia/papua-new-guinea-quake/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJzCdxYOTIAEZyYf20SwjOsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 07:52:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/01/22/asia/papua-new-guinea-quake/" target="_blank"&gt;Magnitude 7.9 quake strikes off Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A magnitude 7.9 earthquake has struck west of Papua New Guinea. The quake was 153 kilometers (95.5 miles) deep and centered 40 kilometers (24 miles) west of the town of Panguna, according to the US Geological Survey. The Pacific Tsunami Warning Center has advised that tsunami waves of up to a meter above the tide level are possible for some coasts of Papua New Guinea and nearby Solomon Islands. Preliminary reports said the earthquake, which occurred at 2:30 p.m. local time Sunday (11:30 p.m. Saturday ET) measured 8.0 but USGS later downgraded its magnitude. The USGS estimates that 72,000 pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Showdown in Indonesia Brings World’s Biggest Gold Mine to Standstill - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/showdown-in-indonesia-brings-gold-mine-to-standstill/3741401.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIms2EAGZQYPyj1-U_JV3zEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 12:57:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/showdown-in-indonesia-brings-gold-mine-to-standstill/3741401.html" target="_blank"&gt;Showdown in Indonesia Brings World’s Biggest Gold Mine to Standstill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American mining company Freeport-McMoRan has brought the world's biggest gold mine, in the Indonesian province of West Papua, to a standstill. The corporation is butting heads with the Indonesian government over protectionist mining regulations. And now that Freeport has started to dismiss tens of thousands of workers, the local economy is poised to take a huge hit. In Mimika Regency, the West Papua province containing the Grasberg gold mine, 91 percent of the Gross Domestic Product (GDP) is attributed to Freeport. Freeport Indonesia abruptly stopped production on February 10 and lai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indonesia strikes deal with Freeport over copper mine - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8441a589-616b-3684-b9cc-0cfe0243a0f0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECwLCL5qNhu4WjeIP-jey7oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 08:42:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8441a589-616b-3684-b9cc-0cfe0243a0f0" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia strikes deal with Freeport over copper mine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia has reached an agreement with US copper miner Freeport-McMoran to allow the company to keep operating its giant Grasberg mine in the country. Phoenix-based Freeport has agreed to give a 51 per cent ownership in the mine to Indonesia and build smelters in the country, according to a statement by the Ministry of Energy and Mineral Resources. It will be allowed to operate the mine until 2041 under a special licence, it said. Freeport had been embroiled in a bitter dispute with the government in Jakarta over its contract to operate Grasberg, the world’s second-largest copper mine. Tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>England beats Samoa, rugby league world is still three countries - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-05-06/england-samoa-fiji-tonga-papua-new-guinea-cook-islands-rl-tests/8503562</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDTCD8HWAqAeskj47iWygOkqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 11:43:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-05-06/england-samoa-fiji-tonga-papua-new-guinea-cook-islands-rl-tests/8503562" target="_blank"&gt;England beats Samoa, rugby league world is still three countries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rugby league world remains, for all intents and purposes, just three countries wide after England beat Samoa in Campbelltown. After the Kangaroos' dominant performance against the Kiwis on Friday night, the international league scene could have used a shake-up, but none was forthcoming. A Samoan side brimming with NRL talent could not match it with the Englishmen, who ran out 30-10 victors. The win wrapped up a three-Test Saturday, during which Papua New Guinea beat the Cook Islands 32-22 and Tonga scored a last-gasp 26-24 victory over Fiji. Ultimately, Samoa ran out of puff in the last...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Plane tips over on runway after cooking oil spill makes cargo slip to its tail - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/indonesia/articles/plane-tips-onto-its-tail-after-cooking-oil-spillage-slump/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED4wku-Q5nYUF3-PDKaB568qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/indonesia/articles/plane-tips-onto-its-tail-after-cooking-oil-spillage-slump/" target="_blank"&gt;Plane tips over on runway after cooking oil spill makes cargo slip to its tail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A plane ended up sat on its haunches after a cooking oil spillage in the hold meant that all its cargo slipped to the back of the aircraft, raising its nose into the air. The mishap took place at Wamena Airport in Papua, Indonesia, as the Tri-MG plane that had arrived from Timika was being unloaded. Among its cargo was a shipment of Indonesian Bimoli oil which was somehow breached, allowing its contents to grease the floor of the fuselage. Thanks to the shifting balance of weight, the aircraft see-sawed on its wheels, only coming to a stop when its tail was touching the tarmac. A post share...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>West Papuans Protest Against Indonesian Rule - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/ap-west-papuans-protest-against-indonesian-rule/3618542.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEXdm3SBYVtn3fladcbZJ7cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 04:49:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/ap-west-papuans-protest-against-indonesian-rule/3618542.html" target="_blank"&gt;West Papuans Protest Against Indonesian Rule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;West Papuan protesters faced off with police in the Indonesian capital on Thursday in a demonstration calling for the remote region's independence. Organizers had promised protests in other cities and said police had denied them permission to march in central Jakarta. The dozens of demonstrators were blocked from marching onto a busy traffic circle in the capital by several hundred police who fired water cannons and dragged men from the crowd into waiting police vans. “Don't hinder our right to voice our aspirations. Papuans are demanding the truth of our history,” a speaker standing atop a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>13 people killed when Indonesian C-130 cargo plane hits mountain (PHOTOS) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/370654-indonesian-hercules-plane-crash/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKa--DEQPwlMc5B-Ifp3ufQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 05:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/370654-indonesian-hercules-plane-crash/" target="_blank"&gt;13 people killed when Indonesian C-130 cargo plane hits mountain (PHOTOS)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All 13 people on board a Hercules C-130 plane owned by the Indonesian Air Force died after it crashed into a mountain near the town of Wamena in the eastern Papua province not far from the airport on Sunday. The US-made transport plane departed from the city of Timika at 22:35 GMT and was set to arrive at Wamena airport at 23:13 GMT. However, contact with the aircraft was lost some ten minutes before the scheduled landing, and search and rescue crews were dispatched to the area. Puing puing Pesawat Hercules C-130 HS milik TNI AU yang jatuh di Pegunungan Wamena pagi ini, 3 Pilot dan 10 Awak ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Freeport cuts copper production targets after Indonesia spat - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/612cb890-41c5-3501-8917-a06e430f6713</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK72j0tOe3ID9ULkvylFz_oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 12:57:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/612cb890-41c5-3501-8917-a06e430f6713" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport cuts copper production targets after Indonesia spat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freeport-McMoRan, the world’s largest publicly traded copper company, has cut its production forecasts following a stand-off with the Indonesian government stop exports from its Grasberg mine banned. The Arizona-based miner company had previously expected to sell 4.1bn pounds of copper this year, a figure it has now revised to 3.9bn after Jakarta banned shipments from Grasberg, the world’s second biggest copper mine. The new guidance was revealed in a trading update that saw Freeport report net income of $228m for the three months to the end of March, against a loss of $4.2bn a year ago whe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Indonesia takes majority stake in Freeport-McMoRan copper mine - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9c6614d4-8c94-11e7-a352-e46f43c5825d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJL1vMv5vw7GP5zJKML_QcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 13:40:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9c6614d4-8c94-11e7-a352-e46f43c5825d" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia takes majority stake in Freeport-McMoRan copper mine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia will take a majority stake in US miner Freeport-McMoran’s group Grasberg copper and gold mine as part of an agreement that will allow the mine to keep operating after months of bitter dispute. Phoenix-based Freeport has agreed to give a 51 per cent ownership in the mine to Indonesia and build a smelter in the country within five years, according to the country’s Ministry of Energy and Mineral Resources. The company will be allowed to operate the mine until 2041 under a special licence, it said. Freeport had been embroiled in a dispute with the government in Jakarta over its contra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Freeport-McMoRan boosted by higher copper price - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/feb60078-7154-11e7-aca6-c6bd07df1a3c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC1dgMWC9uOT8s3jTFlvBv4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 17:51:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/feb60078-7154-11e7-aca6-c6bd07df1a3c" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport-McMoRan boosted by higher copper price&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Freeport-McMoRan, the world’s biggest listed copper company, jumped by the most in 16 months on Tuesday as a higher copper price and news of constructive discussions with the Indonesian government over its operating licence helped offset the sting of a guidance cut. The stock rose as much as 13.4 per cent to a five-month high of $14.70 after Freeport’s chief executive Richard Adkerson said he was optimistic of reaching an agreement with Jakarta over its contract to operate in the country and run the giant Grasberg copper deposit. The move is the stock’s biggest one-day rise since ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>How I ended up in the jungle with deadly hornets in my hair - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/dec/28/giant-hornets-antidote-west-papua-vicks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK4OwvAqwtgWnFQyBmVdbmgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 07:30:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/dec/28/giant-hornets-antidote-west-papua-vicks" target="_blank"&gt;How I ended up in the jungle with deadly hornets in my hair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story has no message or purpose. It is one of the winter’s tales – accounts of the many bizarre incidents that have marked my life – that I tell at this time of year. For once, I am not trying to make a point. In 1987, I was working with the photographer Adrian Arbib in the occupied territory of West Papua. Annexed by Indonesia in 1963, it was being governed with characteristic brutality by the Suharto regime. The indigenous people were being forced off their land and replaced, in a programme sponsored by the World Bank, by migrants from Java and Bali. Many had been tortured and killed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Indonesian provincial government says Freeport loses $188 million tax appeal - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-freeport-tax-idUSKBN1591SI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMgObayER4Wd9K2k4cKDIlwqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 15:03:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-freeport-tax-idUSKBN1591SI" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian provincial government says Freeport loses $188 million tax appeal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - Indonesia's Papua province, home of the giant Grasberg copper mine operated by the local unit of Freeport McMoRan Inc (FCX.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), said it has won a court battle in a claim against the company for 2.51 trillion rupiah ($188 million) in outstanding surface water taxes. According to Papua's local government Indonesia's Tax Court has rejected a lawsuit lodged by PT Freeport Indonesia over the claim for taxes on water the company used from the Aghawagon and Otomona rivers between 2011 and mid-2015. Freeport, which used the water to suspend i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Freeport-McMoRan threatens to sue Indonesia over mine dispute - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9ba0b210-f776-11e6-9516-2d969e0d3b65</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELj9o6_oZQfUtiI_I7gfhCUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 17:23:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9ba0b210-f776-11e6-9516-2d969e0d3b65" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport-McMoRan threatens to sue Indonesia over mine dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freeport-McMoRan on Monday warned the Indonesian government it was prepared to sue Jakarta if it could not resolve an increasingly bitter dispute that has slashed production at its flagship copper deposit in the country. Richard Adkerson, chief executive of the US mining company, said Jakarta had been notified of what he characterised as violations of its contract to mine copper at the giant Grasberg deposit in the eastern province of Papua. The two sides have 120 days to resolve the issues, which was triggered by changes to Indonesia’s mining laws — otherwise Freeport will launch arbitrati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Freeport shares jump after CEO signals progress on Indonesia mine talks - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e568ae24-fec9-3e63-a133-6b8268ec9e01</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIXuweQSSWnlWWDU6aBIIS4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 15:19:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e568ae24-fec9-3e63-a133-6b8268ec9e01" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport shares jump after CEO signals progress on Indonesia mine talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Freeport-McMoran, the world’s biggest listed copper company, jumped in morning trading in New York as a higher copper price and news of constructive discussions with the Indonesian government over its operating license offset revised sales guidance. The stock rose as much as 12.5 per cent to a five-month high of $14.58 after Freeport’s chief executive Richard Adkerson said he was optimistic of reaching an agreement with Jakarta over its contract to operate in the country and run the giant Grasberg copper deposit. “We are now approaching a stage where both parties have expressed an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Dingo relative rediscovered in New Guinea Highlands - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-30/dingo-relative-rediscovered-in-papua-new-guinea-highlands/8463208</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPCrNNqwPS54OoZbRYSPpEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 23:57:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-30/dingo-relative-rediscovered-in-papua-new-guinea-highlands/8463208" target="_blank"&gt;Dingo relative rediscovered in New Guinea Highlands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have confirmed the existence of an ancient dog species in one of the world's most remote places — the mountains of Papua New Guinea and Indonesia's Papua provinces. Key points: - The discovery is the first sighting of the dogs in more than 40 years - They are among the oldest and most primitive canines in the world - Analysis of the species could help explain dog and human co-evolution The international team led by scientists from Indonesia's University of Papua captured evidence of the New Guinea highland wild dog during a 2016 expedition to an austere, high-altitude region near...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>British cruise ship crashes into one of world's most spectacular coral reefs - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/british-cruise-ship-crashes-coral-reef-indonesia-papua-raja-ampat-a7629061.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG0IYbTR7El2D4YRs-bPQbgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 14:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/british-cruise-ship-crashes-coral-reef-indonesia-papua-raja-ampat-a7629061.html" target="_blank"&gt;British cruise ship crashes into one of world's most spectacular coral reefs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A British-owned cruise ship carrying hundreds of tourists has crashed into one of the world’s most spectacular coral reefs, sparking outrage from locals. The 4,290-tonne Caledonian Sky caused "irreparable damage" in Raja Ampat, an idyllic island chain in the west of Indonesia’s Papua province. The ship, owned by British company Noble Caledonia, was hosting a bird-watching trip on earlier this month when it veered off course, running aground during low tide and ploughing into the coral. Roughly 1,600 square meters of the “underwater Amazon” is thought to have been damaged in the incident. Re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Swimming with jellyfish: a Pacific paradise in the Raja Ampat islands - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/jan/26/indonesia-pacific-misool-island-new-guinea-raja-ampat</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKcvGXqti6YmtwWXrKHSUlsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCw3Gc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 10:38:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/jan/26/indonesia-pacific-misool-island-new-guinea-raja-ampat" target="_blank"&gt;Swimming with jellyfish: a Pacific paradise in the Raja Ampat islands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Raja Ampat archipelago, off the Indonesian province of West Papua, is famed for its whale sharks, manta rays and diverse coral. But I’m here to witness another natural phenomenon – a lake that’s home to thousands of giant golden medusa jellyfish. And, what’s more, I’m going for a swim. Some jellyfish can kill people, but the species here are unarmed. Bobbing around in the lake, gelatinous blobs collide with me, tentacles wrap gently around my legs and torso, their bulbous bodies pulse like beating hearts in an oddly therapeutic dance of the deep. Misool island. Photograph: Alamy There a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Papua New Guinea Parliament Re-elects Prime Minister - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/papua-new-guinea-parliament-re-elects-prime-minister/3969132.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHFAnJ5V8GiCs4FZVkgojYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 15:07:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/papua-new-guinea-parliament-re-elects-prime-minister/3969132.html" target="_blank"&gt;Papua New Guinea Parliament Re-elects Prime Minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incumbent Peter O'Neill has been re-elected as prime minister of Papua New Guinea, following a chaotic, violence-plagued campaign marred by allegations of voting irregularities. O'Neill was sworn in Wednesday to a second five-year term to lead the South Pacific island nation after his People's National Congress formed a coalition government with other minor parties, giving O'Neill 60 votes with 46 votes against him. The weeks-long election process struggled because of poor organization and accusations by opposition candidates of vote rigging. Papua New Guinea has been plagued for decades by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indonesian Military Plane Crashes, Killing All 13 Aboard - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/indonesia-plane-crash/3640781.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPzzRGOpqcnIvZrJzefGjcIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 04:38:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/indonesia-plane-crash/3640781.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian Military Plane Crashes, Killing All 13 Aboard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indonesian military plane crashed into a mountain near Wamena, Papua, Sunday, killing all 13 people on board. The statement from the Indonesian Air Force sent to VOA said that the Hercules C-130 plane was carrying 12 tons of food supplies from Timika to Wamena, a distance of about 200 kilometers (125 miles), and some other areas (Jayapura, Merauke, Biak) when it crashed. The plane left Timika around 5:45 a.m. local time and was to arrive in Wamena around 6:15 a.m. local time. Just before it landed, the control tower lost contact with the plane. The plane was carrying three pilots and 10 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indonesia rights body urges end to abuses in Papua after police shooting - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua-idUSKBN1AJ1F2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELCDNoMn_Z36mCwU4ERV8eMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 10:41:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua-idUSKBN1AJ1F2" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia rights body urges end to abuses in Papua after police shooting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - Indonesia's human rights commission on Thursday urged President Joko Widodo to end rights violations in the easternmost province of Papua after police were alleged to have killed one person and wounded 16 others while trying to quell a protest. The incident started on Tuesday when workers at a construction site in the province's Deiyai district refused to transport a man who had nearly drowned in a river to a hospital, according to local media Tabloid Jubi. Residents were angry when the man eventually died and attacked the workers' camp and assaulted police officers who ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Indonesian air force plane crashes in Papua killing 13, official says - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-airplane-crash-idUSKBN14702U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJlAjstUSbz0pUWQPE0Bbf8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 03:04:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-airplane-crash-idUSKBN14702U" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian air force plane crashes in Papua killing 13, official says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - An Indonesian air force transport plane has crashed into a mountain, killing all 13 people board, during a training exercise in the remote region of Papua, a search and rescue agency official said on Sunday. The Hercules C130 plane had taken off from the city of Timika before crashing near its destination of Wamena at around 6.15 a.m. local time (2315 GMT), said Ivan Ahmad Riski Titus, operational director of Indonesia's Search and Rescue Agency. The crash site on Lisuwa mountain had been found and the bodies of the victims were being brought back to Wamena, he said. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Marathon Election Starts in Papua New Guinea - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/marathon-election-starts-in-papua-new-guinea/3915885.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGY2iWOkz3G0xJg1HD3vZl0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 09:09:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/marathon-election-starts-in-papua-new-guinea/3915885.html" target="_blank"&gt;Marathon Election Starts in Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voting has begun in Papua New Guinea's marathon national elections as the Prime Minister faces an arrest warrant for corruption. Peter O’Neill’s People’s National Congress won the last poll in 2012, but critics are accusing him of “burying” the economy in debt. Papua New Guinea, or PNG, is a South Pacific nation of almost 7 million and lies to the north of Australia. About 5 million voters will elect members of Papua New Guinea’s 111-seat parliament. Occupying the eastern half of the island of New Guinea and numerous islands, PNG is a land of rugged terrain and voting will last for two we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Copper concentrate supply hit by disputes in Chile and Indonesia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/5db10156-0713-11e7-97d1-5e720a26771b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHoRfegtZ98PoAs55HUnLWAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 02:34:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5db10156-0713-11e7-97d1-5e720a26771b" target="_blank"&gt;Copper concentrate supply hit by disputes in Chile and Indonesia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supply disruptions at two large mines in Chile and Indonesia are spurring a global shortfall in copper concentrate according to the chairman of China’s second-largest copper refiner. Disputes at the Escondida and Grasberg mines were having “a big effect on global supplies of copper concentrate”, Jiangxi Copper chairman Li Baomin told the Financial Times in Beijing, adding: “It’s the first time in 15 years that copper concentrate is not overproduced.” Copper concentrate — a dry grey powder — is a feedstock used by smelters to create molten copper that is cast into anodes. Annual production i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Outlawed West Papua independence petition presented to the UN - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-27/west-papua-independence-petition-handed-to-un/8994400</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHL1L-HB-wDsj6FP9dg--FwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 10:12:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-27/west-papua-independence-petition-handed-to-un/8994400" target="_blank"&gt;Outlawed West Papua independence petition presented to the UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A secret petition demanding a new independence referendum for West Papua has been presented to the United Nations. The Indonesian Government banned the petition in the provinces of West Papua and Papua, threatening that those who signed it will be arrested and face jail. But the document was smuggled between villages where it has been signed by 1.8 million West Papuans, more than 70 per cent of the province's population. Advocates argue that West Papuans have been denied a legitimate self-determination process, since it was incorporated into Indonesia in 1969. The petition demands a free vo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Freeport-McMoran lowers sales guidance after industrial action - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/90b50edb-6673-31a1-a559-2b8c9a9a0497</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIEoTs9yQeBJ9E_Ixhjnd-cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 12:44:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/90b50edb-6673-31a1-a559-2b8c9a9a0497" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport-McMoran lowers sales guidance after industrial action&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freeport-McMoran, the world’s biggest publicly listed copper miner, has lowered it sales guidance because of industrial action at its giant Grasberg pit in Indonesia. The New-York-listed company now expects to produce 3.7bn pounds (1.68m tonnes) of copper this year, down 150m pounds on its previous forecast. Freeport blamed the the shortfall on lower mining rates and reduced “manpower levels” at the Grasberg open pit and the slower development of a nearby underground expansion project. “These shortfalls are expected to be recovered in future periods,” the company said. The revised guidance ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>UN rejects reports of petition for West Papua independence vote - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-29/west-papua-independence-petition-reports-false-say-un/9001538</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOB74puQeKCsKX9owcsWusUqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-29/west-papua-independence-petition-reports-false-say-un/9001538" target="_blank"&gt;UN rejects reports of petition for West Papua independence vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The head of the United Nation's decolonisation committee has rejected reports of a secret petition demanding a free vote for independence in West Papua. Exiled West Papuan independence campaigner Benny Wenda had told the press 1.8 million West Papuans had signed the secret petition that was passed between homes and villages across provinces. In the reports, Mr Wenda said he presented the petition to the UN Special Committee on Decolonisation. But from New York, the chairman of the committee said no petition had been received and the report, which first appeared in The Guardian newspaper, wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Freeport fights for future of Grasberg mine - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9ab702a4-30b1-11e7-9555-23ef563ecf9a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOYGhXp9Pccw3AZjsm1duYAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 04:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9ab702a4-30b1-11e7-9555-23ef563ecf9a" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport fights for future of Grasberg mine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richard Adkerson, chief executive of Freeport-McMoRan, has six months to thrash out a deal with Indonesia to assure the future of Grasberg, the world’s second-biggest copper deposit. The main open pit at Grasberg sits more than 4,000 metres above sea level among snow capped mountains in a remote and restless part of Indonesia. Continually shrouded in fog and soaked by heavy rains, conditions at the pit are among the toughest in the mining industry. But government interference in the lucrative mine has proven more difficult to deal with than even the harshest of conditions. Freeport, the Pho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Global union heads to Indonesia to defend Freeport workers - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-08-11/global-union-heads-to-indonesia-to-defend-freeport-workers/8795584</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK4Jife81A0-FtRFuLKAt70qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 21:48:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-08-11/global-union-heads-to-indonesia-to-defend-freeport-workers/8795584" target="_blank"&gt;Global union heads to Indonesia to defend Freeport workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fight between West Papuan workers and mining giant Freeport-McMoRan has intensified with the US-owned company accused of denying health care for striking workers and education for their children. Key points: - Workers have been on strike for over four months - The unions say the workers were sacked for taking part in legal strike action - Australia's CFMEu says "a very tragic set of circumstances… occurring as a result of this labour dispute" A global trade union is in Jakarta to lobby the Indonesian Government to help solve the ongoing dispute between Freeport and an estimated 4,000 wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>US, Allies to ‘Transform’ Papua New Guinea With Electricity - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-allies-to-transform-papua-new-guinea-with-electricity/4663416.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ-926ByS0JTl5pjNk3yZLQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 04:01:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-allies-to-transform-papua-new-guinea-with-electricity/4663416.html" target="_blank"&gt;US, Allies to ‘Transform’ Papua New Guinea With Electricity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S., Japan, New Zealand and Australia said they’ll bring electricity to 70 percent of Papua New Guinea’s people by 2030, boosting the West’s response to growing Chinese influence in the South Pacific. The four countries and Papua New Guinea signed the electrification agreement Sunday at the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation meeting behind held in the capital Port Moresby. U.S. Vice President Mike Pence said it shows how strongly the U.S. and its allies are committed to the region. “The commitment of the United States of America to this region of the world has never been stronger,” he s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>APEC is being held by the member country that can least afford it - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/13/asia/papua-new-guinea-apec-summit-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJjAuiebOw82Jx3AJXskxEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:27:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/13/asia/papua-new-guinea-apec-summit-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;APEC is being held by the member country that can least afford it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Port Moresby doesn't know what's about to hit it. The Papua New Guinean capital, a tiny cluster of high rise and residential buildings housing some 300,000 people on the Pacific nation's southern coast, has been preparing all year for the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) summit, which begins on November 17. But for months, experts have been warning the city isn't ready, and concerns remain over costs, infrastructure and security. This is the first time Papua New Guinea (PNG), the poorest of the 21 countries in APEC, has hosted the summit. PNG ranks 110th worldwide for GDP, with an e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>'Can they really pull it off?': the Apec summit comes to Papua New Guinea - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/12/can-they-really-pull-it-off-the-apec-summit-comes-to-papua-new-guinea</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0AaMhH_MBSJ4dc4epPF78qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 23:44:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/12/can-they-really-pull-it-off-the-apec-summit-comes-to-papua-new-guinea" target="_blank"&gt;'Can they really pull it off?': the Apec summit comes to Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is likely to end, as all Apec leaders summits do, with world leaders, including Xi Jinping, Mike Pence, Shinzo Abe, Justin Trudeau and Australian prime minister Scott Morrison, donning matching shirts and posing awkwardly for a photo op. But this week world leaders will arrive in Port Moresby, the capital of Papua New Guinea, for an Apec unlike any other. This is the first time Papua New Guinea, the poorest country among the 21 countries of the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation (Apec) bloc, has hosted the summit. PNG ranks around 130th worldwide for GDP and 135th in the corruption percep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>First Maseratis, now Bentleys for Apec in Papua New Guinea - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/16/first-maseratis-now-bentleys-for-apec-in-papua-new-guinea</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIAZwBjFFh8cxLzFg-BiDbsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 06:03:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/16/first-maseratis-now-bentleys-for-apec-in-papua-new-guinea" target="_blank"&gt;First Maseratis, now Bentleys for Apec in Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Papua New Guinea has reportedly added three Bentleys to its controversial fleet of luxury cars purchased for the upcoming Apec leaders’ summit in November. Papua New Guineans reacted with outrage to the news that the PNG government had bought 40 Maseratis for the summit despite the country struggling with a nationwide polio outbreak, increased rates of tuberculosis and chronic funding shortages for health, education and other services. Opposition MPs called for a nationwide strike over the purchase, which cost millions of dollars, calling it “blatant fraud”. The anger looks set to continue ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Papua New Guinea imports 40 Maseratis to transport Apec delegates - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/12/papua-new-guinea-imports-40-maseratis-to-transport-apec-delegates</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAOWboSDTDwt4_bxRg-G1bEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 03:33:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/12/papua-new-guinea-imports-40-maseratis-to-transport-apec-delegates" target="_blank"&gt;Papua New Guinea imports 40 Maseratis to transport Apec delegates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Papua New Guineans have reacted with anger at its government importing a fleet of Maseratis to drive international delegates around the Apec conference next month, amid a health and poverty crisis, struggling economy, and ongoing efforts after a devastating earthquake. The PNG government has defended its decision, expressing confidence that all 40 luxury cars will be bought by the “private sector” after the two-day event, leaving the government with no financial burden. The cars, which cost between $200,000 and $350,000 each in Australia, were flown in from Milan on two Boeing 747-8F charte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Papua New Guinea hit by 7 magnitude earthquake - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/11/papua-new-guinea-hit-by-7-magnitude-earthquake</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPY6dMmOZMt6i5RdXSXWdIIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 22:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/11/papua-new-guinea-hit-by-7-magnitude-earthquake" target="_blank"&gt;Papua New Guinea hit by 7 magnitude earthquake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A magnitude 7.0 earthquake has struck remote New Britain island in Papua New Guinea, the United States Geological Survey said, though there were no immediate reports of damage. The quake hit about 200km (125 miles) south-west of the town of Rabaul at a depth of almost 40km, just before 7am local time (2100 GMT Wednesday). “We felt the earthquake a bit, but it was not too strong,” constable Roy Michael told Reuters by phone from Rabaul police station. Related: 'A lurking beast': polio casts shadow over Papua New Guinea independence day He said there was no damage in the town, but officers ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Indonesia accuses Vanuatu of 'inexcusable' support for West Papua - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/03/indonesia-accuses-vanuatu-of-inexcusable-support-for-west-papua</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDLKryRudNcx3ONtQWzMdwgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 18:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/03/indonesia-accuses-vanuatu-of-inexcusable-support-for-west-papua" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia accuses Vanuatu of 'inexcusable' support for West Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia has accused Vanuatu of challenging “friendly relations” between the two countries and supporting separatist movements, after it offered support to West Papua at the United Nations. Vanuatu has long been a supporter of the rights of West Papuans in their movement for independence from Indonesia. On Monday Indonesia used its second right of reply at the 73rd UN general assembly to mount an excoriating attack on Vanuatu over its support for West Papuan self-determination, calling it “clueless”. “Although being disguised with flowery human rights concern, Vanuatu’s sole intention and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Polish globe-trotter blunders into Indonesia-Papua conflict - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/2361971b0e0a474386e6047d3ab0cd58</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHSZWfJyzh_im4aPbGe1VEMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 02:16:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/2361971b0e0a474386e6047d3ab0cd58" target="_blank"&gt;Polish globe-trotter blunders into Indonesia-Papua conflict&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA, Indonesia (AP) — To the Indonesian government, the 39-year-old factory worker and globe-trotting Polish traveler is a danger to the state, a man who plotted with shadowy gunmen to foment revolt in isolated eastern jungles. But to his supporters, Jakub Skrzypski is just an idealistic tourist with no money to his name, a man with an oddball combination of sympathies for right-wing and liberation causes. Even Indonesian police say it's unlikely Skrzypski could have arranged the arms deal they say he promised to make with rebels. But Skrzypski, who is charged with treason, still faces ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>U.S. to counter Chinese internet bid in Papua New Guinea: diplomat - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pacific-debt-huawei-tech/u-s-to-counter-chinese-internet-bid-in-papua-new-guinea-diplomat-idUSKCN1M800X</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDgGHQGmfRIvGW1SR-KlVEUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMNT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 08:57:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pacific-debt-huawei-tech/u-s-to-counter-chinese-internet-bid-in-papua-new-guinea-diplomat-idUSKCN1M800X" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. to counter Chinese internet bid in Papua New Guinea: diplomat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States is working on a counter-offer to stop Chinese telecom giant Huawei Technologies Co Ltd [HWT.UL] from building internet infrastructure in Papua New Guinea (PNG), its top diplomat to Australia said on Friday. The bid comes two years after Huawei first agreed to build a network there, and as the United States and its allies mount a vigorous campaign to check China's rising influence in the region by deepening their own diplomatic ties and boosting aid. It also follows Australia shutting Huawei out of contracts to build a national mobile network on security grounds, and blocki...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Heavy metal fans communicate like remote Papua New Guinea tribes, study finds - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/20/heavy-metal-fanscommunicate-like-remote-papua-new-guinea-tribes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL3mMd2cmIZ91VXvjBnJvhsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/20/heavy-metal-fanscommunicate-like-remote-papua-new-guinea-tribes/" target="_blank"&gt;Heavy metal fans communicate like remote Papua New Guinea tribes, study finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heavy metal fans have evolved to communicate with each other like remote tribes in Papua New Guinea, a study by UCL anthropologists has found. They have rules for behaviour in the front-of-stage “mosh pit” that are passed down by “elders”, there are gift-sharing rituals at concerts and dark cathartic music, which mirror rites among Papuan tribes that have changed little in 40,000 years. Lindsay Bishop, a researcher, has spent 10 years studying heavy metal, the loud, pounding style of music that has grown from early followers of the band Black Sabbath in Birmingham into a worldwide culture w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Indonesia charges Pole suspected in Papua arms smuggling plot - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua/indonesia-charges-pole-suspected-in-papua-arms-smuggling-plot-idUSKCN1LQ1MG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJiee2YHpMrFE0tIRX8lM5UqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 13:01:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua/indonesia-charges-pole-suspected-in-papua-arms-smuggling-plot-idUSKCN1LQ1MG" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia charges Pole suspected in Papua arms smuggling plot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Pole detained in Indonesia late last month could face life imprisonment having been charged with plotting against the state after being named as a suspect in a conspiracy to smuggle arms to separatists in Papua, a police spokesman said on Monday. Jakub Fabian Skrzypski was detained on Aug. 26 and is being held at police headquarters in the eastern province of Papua where he has been charged along with three Papuans under the law governing treason, which carries a maximum sentence of life in jail. "He has been charged with treason," Papua police spokesman Ahmad Musthofa Kamal said. Police ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>On Blue 14 - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/273910687/on-blue-14-by-anton-raharja</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKuV1VtIcCryfXHS6ZsaGPAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 12:07:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/273910687/on-blue-14-by-anton-raharja" target="_blank"&gt;On Blue 14&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wayag Islands from the top karst hill, Raja Ampat, West Papua Province, Indonesia.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Indonesia to deport Australian graduate student traveling to Papua - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua-deportation/indonesia-to-deport-australian-graduate-student-traveling-to-papua-idUSKBN1KP05U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO8bumSqNSVo3CbKxbhJfCIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 06:21:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua-deportation/indonesia-to-deport-australian-graduate-student-traveling-to-papua-idUSKBN1KP05U" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia to deport Australian graduate student traveling to Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesian authorities have denied entry and will deport an Australian graduate student who was traveling via Bali to Indonesia's easternmost province of Papua on vacation. Belinda Lopez, a PhD candidate for Indonesian studies at Macquarie University in Australia, wrote on social media that she had been detained at Bali's Denpasar airport since midnight on Saturday and was told she was on a government blacklist. Papua has suffered a simmering separatist conflict since it was incorporated into Indonesia after a widely criticized U.N.-backed referendum in 1969 and remains one of its poorest r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Amnesty: Indonesian forces behind unlawful killings in Papua - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/010d496017f44051b0d4e8a783fba09f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDPWwK4LGwN6GrdQsNpoDpYqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 10:42:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/010d496017f44051b0d4e8a783fba09f" target="_blank"&gt;Amnesty: Indonesian forces behind unlawful killings in Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA, Indonesia (AP) — Indonesia's police and military are responsible for at least 95 unlawful killings in the easternmost Papua region since 2010, including targeted slayings of activists, Amnesty International said Monday, condemning a near-total absence of justice for the mainly indigenous victims. In a report based on two years of research, Amnesty said that more than half the victims were either political activists or people taking part in peaceful protests often unrelated to the Papuan independence movement. Security forces often explain their use of deadly force in Papua as a jus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Indonesia says talks completed on control of Freeport-McMoran mine - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/909d5bce-7da9-11e8-bc55-50daf11b720d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFNjYH5-1gvY44LwnNqiHkEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 04:41:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/909d5bce-7da9-11e8-bc55-50daf11b720d" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia says talks completed on control of Freeport-McMoran mine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Indonesian government said it could finalise as soon as this week a long-awaited deal in which a local company will take majority control of the country’s biggest copper mine from the world’s largest publicly traded copper company, Freeport-McMoran. An official from the Indonesian state-owned enterprises ministry told local media in Jakarta at the weekend that talks have been completed and an agreement could be signed this week for a transfer of control of the massive Grasberg mine from Freeport and its partner Rio Tinto to Indonesian state-owned resources group Inalum. Freeport was tol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Gunmen kill three in Papua as tensions grow before election - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/26/gunmen-kill-three-in-papua-as-tensions-grow-before-election</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELBFOBt2arZoEaPHUrygcW4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 04:15:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/26/gunmen-kill-three-in-papua-as-tensions-grow-before-election" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen kill three in Papua as tensions grow before election&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three people were killed and a child was wounded when separatist fighters in Indonesia’s Papua province opened fire on a small plane bringing in security personnel ahead of regional elections later this week, officials said on Monday. Colonel Muhammad Aidi, the army’s spokesman in Papua province, said three civilians were killed and two people, including the pilot, were injured in the attack, which occurred after the plane landed at Kenyam airport in remote Nduga district. “The plane was carrying 15 mobile brigade officers tasked with safeguarding the local election,” said Muhammad Aidi, a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Poll-related violence flares in Indonesia's Papua - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-elections-papua/poll-related-violence-flares-in-indonesias-papua-idUSKBN1JO0FP</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJsrjuXzRrx5RAREfEPJrV8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 04:45:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-elections-papua/poll-related-violence-flares-in-indonesias-papua-idUSKBN1JO0FP" target="_blank"&gt;Poll-related violence flares in Indonesia's Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - Three people, including two police officers, were killed in Indonesia's easternmost province of Papua after alleged separatists opened fire on boats carrying voters and officials who had just cast ballots in local elections, police said. Indonesia had been on high alert for violence with elections for 171 city mayors, regents, and provincial governors held across the world's biggest Muslim-majority country on Wednesday. Indonesia took control of Papua following a widely criticized U.N.-backed referendum in 1969, six years after the end of Dutch colonial rule. Alleged sep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Rio Tinto in talks over Grasberg exit - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/360d9182-5e65-11e8-9334-2218e7146b04</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENcKYpUq7l3n_yJfKmYl-jgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 12:55:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/360d9182-5e65-11e8-9334-2218e7146b04" target="_blank"&gt;Rio Tinto in talks over Grasberg exit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Indonesian government has moved a step closer to acquiring a controlling stake in Grasberg, the world’s second-biggest copper mine. Rio Tinto said on Wednesday that it was in talks to sell its interest in Grasberg to PT Indonesia Asahan Aluminium (Inalum), a state-backed mining group. The talks come ahead of a 2019 deadline set by Jakarta that requires local companies to control at least 51 per cent of its mining projects and are a key part of a plan by President Joko Widodo to boost local ownership of natural resources. Grasberg is 91 per cent owned by US company Freeport-McMoran, whic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Deep sea drone captures haunting footage of mysterious WWI submarine (VIDEO) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/424896-australian-navy-submarine-drone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECwOQ3QYuwH-TcqX3jW0U9sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 15:17:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/424896-australian-navy-submarine-drone/" target="_blank"&gt;Deep sea drone captures haunting footage of mysterious WWI submarine (VIDEO)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mission to uncover the secrets of a century-old Australian Navy submarine which was mysteriously lost at sea along with its entire crew has taken place off Papua New Guinea. The HMAS AE1, the first-ever submarine belonging to the Royal Australian Navy, went missing in September 1914 during the early stages of World War I. Commanded by Lieutenant Thomas Besant, the vessel left the Papua New Guinea township of Rabaul on the morning of September 14, 1914. The patrol was the submarine’s last, however, and the 35 crew onboard were never seen again. Now a joint US and Australian expedition has ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Freeport flags further problems in Indonesia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/742ddecc-47e0-11e8-8ee8-cae73aab7ccb</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB6fNhcy-CeiMO0nvAKKTB4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 17:04:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/742ddecc-47e0-11e8-8ee8-cae73aab7ccb" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport flags further problems in Indonesia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares of Freeport-McMoRan were down more than 14 per cent on Tuesday after the company flagged further problems at its giant Indonesian gold and copper deposit Freeport chief executive Richard Adkerson said Jakarta has imposed new environmental standards on its Grasberg mine, which he slammed as “shocking” and not “feasible”. For the past 20 years, Freeport has been able to dispose of waste material, or tailings, produced by the Grasberg mine on land as well as in a local river system. The government now wants the company to retain 95 per cent of the tailings on land, rather than 50 per ce...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Indonesian forces detain dozens at West Papua university - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/apr/04/indonesian-forces-detain-dozens-at-west-papua-university</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN7l4eIAtDQOokpETjHiX2wqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 07:31:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/apr/04/indonesian-forces-detain-dozens-at-west-papua-university" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian forces detain dozens at West Papua university&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dozens of students and activists have been detained by Indonesian security forces at a West Papua university. It comes amid fatal shootouts in the region and the release of a high-profile activist from prison. More than 40 people were taken into custody at the University of Cenderawasih campus in Jayapura on Wednesday morning, according to the National Committee for West Papua (KNPB), and were still being questioned on Wednesday afternoon. Related: West Papuan activist on trial for treason over independence petition The university is considered one of West Papua’s top institutions and has a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Indonesia says 1 Soldier Killed in Papua Clash - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/papua-indonesia-violence/4327366.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECR9kJgpENPDOfyGJD6Fi1AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 09:03:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/papua-indonesia-violence/4327366.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia says 1 Soldier Killed in Papua Clash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia's military said Monday that one solider has been killed in an ongoing clash between security forces and Papuan independence fighters near the U.S.-owned Grasberg copper mine in the country's east. Military spokesman Col. Muhammad Aidi said the soldier was shot in the head and died Sunday afternoon. He said that a joint military and police force was hunting an "armed separatist criminal group.'' Aidi denied a purported statement from the National Liberation Army of West Papua that numerous Indonesian soldiers were killed in the clashes and a 10-year-old boy had died in a fire cause...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Major quake cuts communications, halts oil and gas operations in Papua New Guinea - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-papua-quake/powerful-quake-hits-central-papua-new-guinea-disrupts-oil-and-gas-operations-idUSKCN1G90UR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEZXx2bv3yVvO9XIQWBoOn0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 06:23:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-papua-quake/powerful-quake-hits-central-papua-new-guinea-disrupts-oil-and-gas-operations-idUSKCN1G90UR" target="_blank"&gt;Major quake cuts communications, halts oil and gas operations in Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Charlotte Greenfield and Sonali Paul WELLINGTON/MELBOURNE (Reuters) - At least one company began evacuating non-essential personnel after a powerful 7.5 magnitude earthquake hit Papua New Guinea's energy-rich interior on Monday, causing landslides, damaging buildings and closing oil and gas operations. The tremor hit in the rugged, heavily forested Southern Highlands about 560 km (350 miles) northwest of the capital, Port Moresby, at around 3.45 a.m. local time (1545 GMT Sunday), according to the U.S. Geological Survey (USGS). A spokesman at Papua New Guinea's National Disaster Center sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Kri Island sunset - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/246010963/kri-island-sunset-by-fred-singer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHnaO3QOapK3rS9--gcMEp4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 20:16:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/246010963/kri-island-sunset-by-fred-singer" target="_blank"&gt;Kri Island sunset&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia, Papoua, Kri island at sunset january 2018&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Papua Health Crisis Prompts International Scrutiny, Internal Review - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/papua-new-guinea-health-crisis/4242728.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBdQaibc3GuxN0atscRQKqoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 13:48:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/papua-new-guinea-health-crisis/4242728.html" target="_blank"&gt;Papua Health Crisis Prompts International Scrutiny, Internal Review&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twin crises of measles and malnutrition have recently afflicted Indonesia’s easternmost province, Papua, inciting foreign and media scrutiny as well as internal review from the Indonesian government. Papua is an impoverished but mineral-rich province with a history of separatist struggle, which has been quashed for decades by the Indonesian military. This week, the nation’s health ministry declared both crises to be under control, but 72 people have already died in Asmat regency. In wake of the outbreaks, finance minister Sri Mulyani said that special autonomy funding for the province would...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Going off grid on Indonesia's forgotten islands - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/indonesia/articles/going-off-grid-in-raja-ampat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF3jI0lZmRXvdUZE70j6hTAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 13:10:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/indonesia/articles/going-off-grid-in-raja-ampat/" target="_blank"&gt;Going off grid on Indonesia's forgotten islands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am sitting in a small, weather-beaten motorboat, an inch of salt water lapping at my feet. My suitcase is wrapped in an old tarpaulin. My only companion is Frendy, the boatman. He doesn’t speak English. We met an hour ago at a ferry port. After 30 hours of travelling, three planes and a boat, I was relieved when he approached me on the dock and said my name. Somebody was expecting me. Frendy’s boat is the last leg of my journey. He knows the route well and weaves his way between coral beds. When I look into the clear blue I see shoals of glittering fish and – aaah! – a single sleek silver...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Indonesia declares Papua health crisis under control - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua/indonesia-declares-papua-health-crisis-under-control-idUSKBN1FQ0Q1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPRJs2fEY4Iab4qiD_j0C7MqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMIT6lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 06:57:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua/indonesia-declares-papua-health-crisis-under-control-idUSKBN1FQ0Q1" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia declares Papua health crisis under control&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - A measles and malnutrition crisis that killed dozens of children in Indonesia's impoverished province of Papua over the past few months is under control, the health ministry said on Tuesday. At least 72 people, mostly children, died from complications of malnutrition and measles in Asmat, a remote area of the country's easternmost province. The outbreak prompted health authorities to send in military paramedics and aid and declare an "extraordinary outbreak" on Jan. 15. "We have withdrawn the 'extraordinary outbreak' status because the trend of affected people is declini...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>BBC journalist ordered to leave Indonesia's Papua over tweets - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-rights/bbc-journalist-ordered-to-leave-indonesias-papua-over-tweets-idUSKBN1FN0EQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIGupFW03EN9GbVQPeSwCBwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 14:35:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-rights/bbc-journalist-ordered-to-leave-indonesias-papua-over-tweets-idUSKBN1FN0EQ" target="_blank"&gt;BBC journalist ordered to leave Indonesia's Papua over tweets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Ed Davies and Agustinus Beo Da Costa JAKARTA (Reuters) - A BBC journalist on a reporting trip to cover a health and malnutrition crisis in Indonesia's easternmost area of Papua was forced to leave the province after the country's military said tweets she sent on her trip had "hurt soldiers' feelings". Papua is one of Indonesia's poorest areas and President Joko Widodo after coming to power in 2014 pledged to speed up its development and ease media restrictions in the area, where there has been a simmering secessionist movement. But while investment has risen and efforts made to address s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>BBC journalist ordered out of Papua over tweets that 'hurt soldiers' feelings' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/feb/04/bbc-journalist-rebecca-henschke-papua-tweets-hurt-soldiers-feelings</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVIenD45ESe0FI03Of_bL4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 02:12:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/feb/04/bbc-journalist-rebecca-henschke-papua-tweets-hurt-soldiers-feelings" target="_blank"&gt;BBC journalist ordered out of Papua over tweets that 'hurt soldiers' feelings'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A BBC journalist reporting on a health and malnutrition crisis in Indonesia’s easternmost area of Papua has been forced to leave the province after the military said tweets she sent during her trip had “hurt soldiers’ feelings”. Rebecca Henschke, the BBC’s Indonesia editor, had tweeted a photo of supplies on her personal Twitter account, adding: “This is the aid coming in for severely malnourished children in Papua – instant noodles, super sweet soft drinks and biscuits.” Indonesia’s military said the post about the type of food being sent to the district of Asmat had “hurt the feelings of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item></channel></rss>