<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Khyber Pakhtunkhwa - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFZvZDI0U0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-PK&amp;gl=PK&amp;ceid=PK:en</link><language>en-PK</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:57:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Momina Basit elected Chairperson KPK Standing Committee on Zakat, Ushar, Social Welfare - The News International</title><link>https://www.thenews.com.pk/latest/402579-momina-basit-elected-chairperson-kpk-standing-committee-on-zakat-ushar-social-welfare</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMifmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZW5ld3MuY29tLnBrL2xhdGVzdC80MDI1NzktbW9taW5hLWJhc2l0LWVsZWN0ZWQtY2hhaXJwZXJzb24ta3BrLXN0YW5kaW5nLWNvbW1pdHRlZS1vbi16YWthdC11c2hhci1zb2NpYWwtd2VsZmFyZdIBxgFodHRwczovL3d3dy10aGVuZXdzLWNvbS1way5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy50aGVuZXdzLmNvbS5way9hbXAvNDAyNTc5LW1vbWluYS1iYXNpdC1lbGVjdGVkLWNoYWlycGVyc29uLWtway1zdGFuZGluZy1jb21taXR0ZWUtb24temFrYXQtdXNoYXItc29jaWFsLXdlbGZhcmU_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:23:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thenews.com.pk/latest/402579-momina-basit-elected-chairperson-kpk-standing-committee-on-zakat-ushar-social-welfare" target="_blank"&gt;Momina Basit elected Chairperson KPK Standing Committee on Zakat, Ushar, Social Welfare&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The News International&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MPA Abdul Ghaffar, Aisha Naeem, Rabia Basri, Zeenat Bibi, Sitara Afreeen, Rehana Ismail, Shagufta Malik, and Nighat Yasmeen have been elected the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thenews.com.pk">The News International</source></item><item><title>KPK musical night pull big crowds to Lok Virsa - Business Recorder</title><link>https://www.brecorder.com/2018/11/09/451771/kpk-musical-night-pull-big-crowds-to-lok-virsa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiW2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmJyZWNvcmRlci5jb20vMjAxOC8xMS8wOS80NTE3NzEva3BrLW11c2ljYWwtbmlnaHQtcHVsbC1iaWctY3Jvd2RzLXRvLWxvay12aXJzYS_SAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.brecorder.com/2018/11/09/451771/kpk-musical-night-pull-big-crowds-to-lok-virsa/" target="_blank"&gt;KPK musical night pull big crowds to Lok Virsa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Business Recorder&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISLAMABAD: The Khyber Pakhtunkhwa (KPK) pavilion at ongoing Lok Mela hosted a cultural night here late Friday mesmerizing audience in large number. The.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.brecorder.com">Business Recorder</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/pt0HVpg1kaUXBMzuwywpt7tyC6R1PKLoF7JcOOqIhTJU8_cj4Pw6VcisRe-6SEG2VCNCTx_yuTmqbuSw9mW7Povv7LVFIw6Zy56qOObX6iVR3pDMNIjmoziW=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Blast at market in northwest Pakistan kills at least 25 - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-blast-market/blast-at-market-in-northwest-pakistan-kills-at-least-25-idUSKCN1NS0JF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDCO29QAcZqif0R5Jvo31WQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 15:20:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-blast-market/blast-at-market-in-northwest-pakistan-kills-at-least-25-idUSKCN1NS0JF" target="_blank"&gt;Blast at market in northwest Pakistan kills at least 25&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A suicide bomb attack on a crowded festival and market in northwest Pakistan's northwest killed at least 25 people on Friday and wounded 20, a government official said. The blast occurred at around the same time that three attackers tried to storm the Chinese consulate in the southern city of Karachi. Two policemen and the three attackers were killed. The Karachi attack was claimed by a separatist insurgent group called the Balochistan Liberation Army, and did not appear to be connected to the attack on the market in the northwestern region of Orakzai. In Orakzai, a suicide bomber drove a m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan: Deadly blast hits market in Orakzai district - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/pakistan-deadly-blast-hits-market-orakzai-district-181123072104727.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKQ65_hdvkFyQ4-ZnqEH8IYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:54:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/pakistan-deadly-blast-hits-market-orakzai-district-181123072104727.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan: Deadly blast hits market in Orakzai district&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An explosion has ripped through a busy marketplace in the northwestern Pakistani town of Kalaya, killing at least 26 people, officials say. More than 55 people were wounded when the blast occurred on Friday morning, health official Adnan Tahir told Al Jazeera by telephone from the provincial capital, Peshawar. It was unclear whether the explosion was caused by a suicide bomber or an improvised explosive device, local government official Mudassir Bangash told Al Jazeera. "Reports are still coming in, nothing is confirmed yet," Bangash told Al Jazeera by telephone. Abbas Khan, the assistant c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Blast targets bazaar in Pakistan, at least 31 killed - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/asia/pakistan-orakzai-market-blast-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDqcB7_gPEQKGNJR6YAaFWAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 15:02:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/asia/pakistan-orakzai-market-blast-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Blast targets bazaar in Pakistan, at least 31 killed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bomb smuggled into a market inside a carton killed as many as 31 people in northern Pakistan Friday, according to officials. The explosion, in Kalya in Orakzai Agency, took place just before 9 a.m. local time (10.30 p.m. ET Wednesday), according to Khalid Iqbal, police deputy commissioner in Orakzai. The majority of the dead were Shia, he added. The blast took place in the vegetable section of the market, Iqbal said. At least 51 people were injured, 17 critically, according to Amin Ullah, the District Administrator for Kalaya. They have been moved to the larger towns of Kohat and Peshawar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Avalanches kill at least 59 in Afghanistan and Pakistan - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/05/world/pakistan-avalanche-khyber-pakhtunkhwa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHPCJv5gl2v72u6Smef-LDkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 18:01:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/05/world/pakistan-avalanche-khyber-pakhtunkhwa/" target="_blank"&gt;Avalanches kill at least 59 in Afghanistan and Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heavy snowfall triggered a series of avalanches along the Afghan-Pakistani border on Sunday, killing at least 59 people in the two countries, officials say. 45 died and 11 were injured in northeastern Afghanistan's Barg-e-Matal district. Nuristan Province Governor Hafiz Abdul Qayum said the death toll may rise as more victims are discovered. The area is about 150 miles northeast of Afghanistan's capital, Kabul. Across the border in northwest Pakistan, a mass of snow, ice and rocks plummeted upon five houses in the mountainous Sher Shal village in the district of Chitral. The village's 14 de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Suspected Suicide Blast Kills District Police Chief in Pakistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/suspected-suicide-blast-police-chief-pakistan/3935529.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO6LXAv4kiLB7h3_NNM7wf0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 11:27:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/suspected-suicide-blast-police-chief-pakistan/3935529.html" target="_blank"&gt;Suspected Suicide Blast Kills District Police Chief in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A suspected suicide blast in southwestern Pakistan Monday killed a district police chief along with his security guard and a civilian passerby. The Pakistani Taliban swiftly claimed responsibly for the attack in the town of Chaman near the Afghan border, saying the bomber was one of its members. The slain police chief, Sajid Khan Mohmand, was traveling to his office and a traffic jam had slowed his vehicle on a busy narrow road when a suicide bomber riding a motorbike struck it, said eyewitnesses. Authorities have retrieved body parts of the suspected attacker from the site but have not yet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Report: Considerable Drop in Militancy in Pakistan’s Restive Tribal Areas - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/report-finds-drop-in-militancy-in-pakistan-tribal-areas/3986905.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBSwJzaH41P6vr3hHl2memsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 19:40:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/report-finds-drop-in-militancy-in-pakistan-tribal-areas/3986905.html" target="_blank"&gt;Report: Considerable Drop in Militancy in Pakistan’s Restive Tribal Areas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s northwestern tribal region, beleaguered for years by terrorism and lawlessness, has seen a decline in militant activities during the past few months as the result of government counterinsurgency operations, a recent security report says. FATA Research Center (FRC), a non-governmental organization based in the capital of Pakistan, observed a decline of 19 percent in violent incidents during the second quarter of 2017 in the semi-autonomous Federally Administered Tribal Areas (FATA) along the border with Afghanistan. The report also indicated, however, that banned terror outfits su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Suspected U.S. drone strike kills two in Pakistan near Afghan border: village elder - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-drones-idUSKBN16914P</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED5ByPq0At2qzbSrH8EoWZEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 13:10:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-drones-idUSKBN16914P" target="_blank"&gt;Suspected U.S. drone strike kills two in Pakistan near Afghan border: village elder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KURRAM AGENCY, Pakistan (Reuters) - A suspected U.S. drone strike killed two men on Thursday in a Pakistani village near the Afghanistan border, a local government official and a village elder said. U.S. drone attacks inside Pakistan have become rare over the past few years and the latest strike, if confirmed, would be the first such attack inside the nuclear-armed nation since U.S. President Donald Trump took office in January. The missile struck two men riding a motorcycle in Pakistan's northern Kurram Agency, part of the country's lawless tribal areas said to be home to militants from bo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>BlackForestBlue II - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/214777493/blackforestblue-ii-by-kpk-</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELD8_d9gSAULzypVt8_BNkcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 04:43:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/214777493/blackforestblue-ii-by-kpk-" target="_blank"&gt;BlackForestBlue II&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black Forest 2017 Website Facebook Fotocommunity ArtLimited Instagram&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Pakistani Taliban suicide bomber targets judges in Peshawar - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-attack-idUSKBN15U140</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKSjdNzL7ltdK0LK7WQjUZwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 17:13:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-attack-idUSKBN15U140" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani Taliban suicide bomber targets judges in Peshawar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Mehreen Zahra-Malik ISLAMABAD (Reuters) - A suicide bomber from the Pakistani Taliban militant group attacked a van carrying judges in northwestern city of Peshawar on Wednesday, wounding several judges and killing the driver, police said. It was the region's second attack of the day in a new surge in militant violence. In the Mohmand agency area north of Peshawar, a suicide bomber blew himself up outside a government office, killing five people. Security has improved in Pakistan over the past few years but a spate of attacks in recent days, and a threat by hardline militants to unleash ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Deadly blast rocks market in Pakistan's northwest - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/01/deadly-blast-rocks-market-pakistan-northwest-170121050027278.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIoZjfc30MON0NBurwy_G4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 12:27:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/01/deadly-blast-rocks-market-pakistan-northwest-170121050027278.html" target="_blank"&gt;Deadly blast rocks market in Pakistan's northwest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bomb blast ripped through a vegetable market in Pakistan's northwestern region in a predominantly Shia area, killing at least 22 people and wounding about 90 others. The explosion occurred Saturday morning at the Eidgah Market in Parachinar city, the capital of Kurram Agency, where a large number of people had gathered to buy fresh produce. Ashiq Hussain, who was lightly wounded, was being treated in Parachinar hospital. He said he was among the people purchasing fruit and vegetables loaded on a van when the explosion took place. "There was a big bang and I saw a dark cloud of smoke and d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Morning - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/196722515/morning-by-hafiz-naveed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENEgstM-zr57nLXBGAn2kJgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 17:36:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/196722515/morning-by-hafiz-naveed" target="_blank"&gt;Morning&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beautiful Morning at River Panjkora Kumrat Valley Pakistan&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Pakistan's beautiful but dangerous tribal areas may finally open for tourism again - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-11-22/pakistans-dangerous-tribal-areas-may-open-for-tourism-again/8043210</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECDnNo6lmM622worjs4CVqIqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 19:15:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-11-22/pakistans-dangerous-tribal-areas-may-open-for-tourism-again/8043210" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan's beautiful but dangerous tribal areas may finally open for tourism again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a land of striking beauty, ancient cultures, and fierce warriors, Haji Ibrahim Khan is all set to go back to his home after languishing in a refugee camp for almost seven years. Once called "the most dangerous place in the world" by US President Barack Obama, Pakistan's Government is now contemplating opening the area to international tourism. Though the family is excited, while packing their few possessions, Mr Khan says he has reservations about their safety. "I can only hope against hope," he says. Photo: Ibrahim Khan is all set to go back to his home in Malakdin Khel, Khyber Agency. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan's First Female Police Chief Breaking Cultural Taboos - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistans-first-female-police-chief-breaking-taboos/3978519.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGafpo5q8U9hW19thv-NPfgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 14:18:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistans-first-female-police-chief-breaking-taboos/3978519.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan's First Female Police Chief Breaking Cultural Taboos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rizwana Hameed made history a month ago when she became the first female head of a male police station in Pakistan’s Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province, or KPK, where conservative cultural and religious traditions often discourage women from leaving home. Hameed has been a member of the provincial police force for the past 15 years and has participated in numerous crime investigations as well as daring raids against suspected criminal terrorist hideouts. But after becoming the first officer to supervise a male police station in a predominantly conservative male society, she is feeling the pressure...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan hate speech investigation against clerics after student killed for alleged blasphemy - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-blasphemy-idUSKBN17I0AK</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOCPmBe6tLbefRurxzWP6jgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 15:59:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-blasphemy-idUSKBN17I0AK" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan hate speech investigation against clerics after student killed for alleged blasphemy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Jibran Ahmed PESHAWAR, Pakistan, (Reuters) - Pakistani police opened a hate speech investigation involving two Muslim clerics on Sunday after the killing of a university student over allegations he committed blasphemy. The clerics are accused of attempting to disrupt the funeral of student Mashal Khan, who was beaten to death by fellow students after a dormitory debate was followed by accusations of blasphemy being spread across a university campus in the northern city of Maradan. University officials had issued a public notification hours before the murder naming three students being in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>At least 22 killed and dozens injured after explosion at Pakistan market - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/pakistan-explosion-market-shia-sunni-bombing-a7539276.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGmEHMe3A0nzsWsqEnBz0GgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 15:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/pakistan-explosion-market-shia-sunni-bombing-a7539276.html" target="_blank"&gt;At least 22 killed and dozens injured after explosion at Pakistan market&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 22 people died and dozens of others were injured after a bomb exploded at a busy vegetable market in north-west Pakistan. More than 50 people were said to have been wounded in the attack in the Kurram area agency's regional capital Parachinar as locals crowded into the market to buy fruit and vegetables. Some of the wounded were taken to hospital in Parachinar, while others were airlifted to hospitals in Peshawar, the capital of north-western Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province, reportedly due to the local hospitals' lack of capacity to deal with such emergencies. The explosion has been cl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pakistan scrambles to protect China's 'Silk Road' pioneers - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-china-islamic-state-idUSKBN1920KL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBw5FkKrhK1FAgcUalsw_0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 11:10:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-china-islamic-state-idUSKBN1920KL" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan scrambles to protect China's 'Silk Road' pioneers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Drazen Jorgic and Jibran Ahmad ISLAMABAD/PESHAWAR, Pakistan (Reuters) - Chastened by the Islamic State's claim to have killed two kidnapped Chinese teachers, Pakistan is beefing up security around Chinese citizens streaming into the country on the back of Beijing's "Belt and Road" infrastructure splurge. China has often urged Pakistan to improve security after pledging around $57 billion to build power plants, railways, and roads that will cross the Himalayas to connect western China with Pakistan's Arabian Sea port of Gwadar. Pakistani officials have outlined to Reuters extensive securi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Many killed in Pakistan market bomb blast - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jan/21/many-killed-in-pakistan-market-bomb-blast</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP7ssvDpelsG6ADE3GLAG5UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 08:45:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jan/21/many-killed-in-pakistan-market-bomb-blast" target="_blank"&gt;Many killed in Pakistan market bomb blast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 18 people have been killed and 51 wounded after a bomb exploded in a busy market town close to Pakistan’s border with Afghanistan. Sabir Hussain, a doctor at the main hospital in Parachinar, said 11 critically wounded people who were brought in from blast site died while being treated. He said several of the wounded were in serious condition and were being transferred to other hospitals for better care. Shahid Khan, an assistant tribal administrator, said the explosion took place when the market was crowded with retailers buying fruits and vegetables from a wholesale shop. He said ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Millions of Children in Restive Pakistani Province Lack Access to Education - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/millionis-of-children-in-restive-pakistani-province-lack-access-to-education/3823408.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECzgtAnx95p0NzsJc5LgQfQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 17:27:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/millionis-of-children-in-restive-pakistani-province-lack-access-to-education/3823408.html" target="_blank"&gt;Millions of Children in Restive Pakistani Province Lack Access to Education&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nine-year-old Fahad works at a tailor shop in Peshawar with his brother to provide for their family of 11, including his six brothers, two sisters and his parents. Making just $20 a month, his job hinders him from going to school. “Every day on my way to work, I see students who go to school and it is very hard for me to ignore them,” Fahad told VOA. “My parents are poor and I have to work to be able to make ends meet.” Fahad is not alone on having to trade off school for work. An estimated 3 million children have no access to formal education in the restive Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province of P...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>NGOs: Pakistan Government Restrictions Hamper Campaigns to Curb Militancy - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-ngos-red-tape/3733512.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENxyqtyc5T1Lx5zK8BhayMYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 15:21:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-ngos-red-tape/3733512.html" target="_blank"&gt;NGOs: Pakistan Government Restrictions Hamper Campaigns to Curb Militancy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aid agencies in Pakistan’s restive northwestern region are struggling to provide services to help curb militancy and deliver aid because they lack government permission to operate, according to humanitarian organizations. The aid groups say the government is creating obstacles for them to obtain a "No Objection Certificate" (NOC) in northwestern Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province, which has been hard-hit by militancy and terrorism. The certificate is a requirement for an organization to work in the area. “Getting an NOC is almost impossible in the areas where military operations are currently ong...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Charsaddah government office attacked by gunmen - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/charsaddah-government-office-attacked-gunmen-170223062629898.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG7G9dOkeUIVq6dQMz7qv64qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 06:52:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/charsaddah-government-office-attacked-gunmen-170223062629898.html" target="_blank"&gt;Charsaddah government office attacked by gunmen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least three gunmen attacked the National Database and Registration Authority (NADRA) in Pakistan's northwest Charsadda district. Local media reports said the attack was foiled when police returned fire and the attackers fled, prompting a search operation. "All schools near the area are shut under further notice," a resident and an eye witness, Shoukat Iqbal, told Al Jazeera. It was not immediately clear if there were any casualties. On Tuesday, Pakistan TalibanJamaat-ur-Ahrar faction claimed responsibility for the attack in town of Tangi in the district of Charsadda where suicide bombers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Sets Up Unique Helpline for Women in Need - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-sets-up-unique-helpline-for-women-in-need/3792827.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEATzrIHa8BNwikM_6iL93W0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 12:12:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-sets-up-unique-helpline-for-women-in-need/3792827.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Sets Up Unique Helpline for Women in Need&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Durdana married for a second time and to a man of her own choosing, her parents threatened to kill her if she tried to see her new husband. They imprisoned her in their home, but she still had her mobile phone and had learned that a helpline for women had been set up. She noted the number and then one day when she was alone in the house, she called. Nayab Hassan was on the other end. She had been trained how to answer the call. "Be gentle. Listen. Let them speak. Let them tell you what they want. Sometimes they are very emotional," she said at the helpline center — located in the spraw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Suspect Raising Money for IS Granted Bail in Pakistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/suspect-raising-money-for-is-granted-bail-in-pakistan/3993340.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF3X4-uWZ9R1_1YGw5J9veIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 18:52:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/suspect-raising-money-for-is-granted-bail-in-pakistan/3993340.html" target="_blank"&gt;Suspect Raising Money for IS Granted Bail in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An anti-terrorism court in Peshawar has granted bail to a suspect allegedly involved in generating funds for the so-called Islamic State in Pakistan’s northwestern region. Earlier this month security forces arrested Zahid Ullah, a resident of Peshawar on suspicion of raising money and recruiting for Islamic State. The security forces also retrieved a notebook from the suspect that had details of people who donated to the IS, Pakistani media reported. Political analyst A. Z. Hilali said this case is another example of how people hesitate to become a witness and testify against the terror cul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>One Billion Trees Planted in Pakistan’s NW Province - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/one-billion-trees-planted-in-pakistan-nw-province/3983609.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEESPVitfBfnU3KGNFibTwgYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 09:10:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/one-billion-trees-planted-in-pakistan-nw-province/3983609.html" target="_blank"&gt;One Billion Trees Planted in Pakistan’s NW Province&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s northwestern province, Khyber Pakhtunkhaw (KPK), has planted an unprecedented 1 billion trees in just more than two years and surpassed an international commitment of restoring 350,000 hectares of forests and degraded land. The massive effort aims to turn the tide on land degradation and loss in the mountainous, formerly forested KPK, which lies in the Hindu Kush mountain range. Imran Khan, head of the Pakistan Tehreek-e-Insaf (PTI) party governing the province, launched the reforestation campaign, dubbed “Billion Tree Tsunami,” in 2015. Pictures of a river bank before and after ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>UN cuts cash incentive to Afghan refugees in Pakistan - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/cuts-cash-incentive-afghan-refugees-pakistan-170402061355610.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBdmkSbRCtBJyKQdml9wPIQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 10:48:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/cuts-cash-incentive-afghan-refugees-pakistan-170402061355610.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN cuts cash incentive to Afghan refugees in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voluntary repatriation of Afghan refugees from Pakistan is set resume on Monday with a cut in the cash incentive for returnees, a UNHCR official said. The repatriation grant for registered Afghan refugees this year has been set to $200 from the previous amount of $400. Pakistan hosts 1.3 million registered Afghan refugees, in addition to nearly a million unregistered Afghans, of which 600,000 live in Khyber-Pakhtunkhwa province, bordering Afghanistan. "The amount before [the cut] at least helped us with our basic needs during our return to Afghanistan, but something is at least better than ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>InfiniteEnlightment II - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/206772429/infiniteenlightment-ii-by-kpk-</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTPRWiGUKxLnOUUCfzclVEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 05:22:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/206772429/infiniteenlightment-ii-by-kpk-" target="_blank"&gt;InfiniteEnlightment II&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Berlin 2016 Website Facebook Fotocommunity ArtLimited&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Pakistan's Northwest Region Continues its Struggle Against Terror Financing - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-terror-financing/3965056.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFf6DcvfaNEvHgMXgLH93J0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 16:09:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-terror-financing/3965056.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan's Northwest Region Continues its Struggle Against Terror Financing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan’s restive northwest province Khyber Pakhtunkhwa has issued directives to its administrative and security departments to make serious efforts to cut off the money supply of banned terror groups. The provincial departments have been instructed to devise a strategy to crack down and to closely monitor the proscribed groups and individuals involved in raising funds illegally for welfare or religious purposes, Pakistani media reported. Punjab, Sindh, Khyber-Pakhtunkhwa and Balochistan provinces, Pakistan Despite its continued efforts against terrorism, terror financing remains a challen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Explosions rock district courts in Charsadda - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/explosions-rocks-district-courts-charsadda-170221070524712.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLVDpcZnpSsGXdikUYVfM8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 08:13:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/02/explosions-rocks-district-courts-charsadda-170221070524712.html" target="_blank"&gt;Explosions rock district courts in Charsadda&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suicide bombers attacked a court complex in northwestern Pakistan, killing at least three people, police said. A spokesperson for the Pakistan Taliban Jamaat-ur-Ahrar faction claimed responsibility for the attack in town of Tangi in the district of Charsadda. "At least three [were] people killed and more than 10 [were] wounded in the attack," district police chief, Sohail Khalid, told Al Jazeera. Three suicide attackers attempted to attack the court but as they exploded their vests, they were shot dead at the gate, another police official, Sabz Ali, told Al Jazeera. Police sources said a se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Tribesmen Displaced in Pakistan's Anti-militant Operations Demand Repatriation - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3850777.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO0gi-a3R4MG3vpEhF_KMEoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 20:10:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3850777.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tribesmen Displaced in Pakistan's Anti-militant Operations Demand Repatriation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of displaced Pashtu tribesmen in northwestern Pakistan have asked the government to ensure their return to their homes before the Muslim holy period of Ramadan begins this month. About 2,400 tribal families from the Dande Darpakhel village in North Waziristan, which is part of a semiautonomous tribal region known as the Federally Administered Tribal Areas (FATA), are living in temporary shelters with inadequate facilities. More than 1 million people have been displaced by Pakistani military operations against militant groups in the tribal region since 2014. North Waziristan until ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistani opposition retracts claim two supporters killed in clashes with police - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-politics-claim-idUSKBN12W4RW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDqnl_OHlXPJWvrRzqxcW1EqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 18:22:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-politics-claim-idUSKBN12W4RW" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani opposition retracts claim two supporters killed in clashes with police&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISLAMABAD (Reuters) - Pakistani opposition figure Imran Khan and his party late on Tuesday retracted earlier claims that two supporters had been killed in clashes with police in the run-up to a planned "shutdown" of the national capital. A spokeswoman for Khan's Pakistan Tehreek-e-Insaf (PTI) blamed the error on conflicting reports on the ground and an over-reliance on local media. "Our party after scrutinizing the events is confirming that no human life was lost in the conflict," the spokeswoman said in a statement. Khan himself tweeted late on Tuesday night "Glad to learn no PTI KP worker...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Kicks Out Medical Charity MSF From Country's Tribal Region - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-kicks-out-msf-from-tribal-region/4027729.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGfSm4v83pBQzBat6Ce5z7YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 21:17:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-kicks-out-msf-from-tribal-region/4027729.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Kicks Out Medical Charity MSF From Country's Tribal Region&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan on Wednesday told medical charity Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF) to stop work and leave its impoverished tribal areas that border Afghanistan, the health organization said, ending its 14-year stay in the volatile region. MSF works out of two health facilities in the Kurram district of Pakistan's Federally Administered Tribal Areas (FATA) region, which has been plagued by militancy over the past decade and was the location of many U.S. drone strikes targeting commanders from al-Qaida and other militant groups. Though security has improved in FATA in recent years, sectarian militant ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Electoral Reform Plans Aim to Boost Women's Participation in Politics - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-electoral-reform-hopes-to-boost-women-participation-in-politics/3710710.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAJMmMhHMIatUfrI8TqyZboqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 03:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-electoral-reform-hopes-to-boost-women-participation-in-politics/3710710.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Electoral Reform Plans Aim to Boost Women's Participation in Politics&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reforms to Pakistan's electoral laws making it mandatory for political parties to allot five percent of their tickets to women candidates were approved on Tuesday by the federal cabinet, the country's highest decision-making body. Under Pakistan's constitution, women are guaranteed seats through a quota system in the national parliament and regional assemblies in Punjab, Sindh, Khyber-Pakhtunkhwa and Balochistan provinces. At present, 60 out of 342 seats in the National Assembly, or lower house of parliament, are reserved for women with a further 137 seats reserved for women in the four pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Afghanistan Criticizes Pakistan's Anti-IS Operations - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/afghanistan-criticizes-pakistan-anti-islamic-state-operations/3963604.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDNax0bOdN78_ImdK5kA_I0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 22:30:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/afghanistan-criticizes-pakistan-anti-islamic-state-operations/3963604.html" target="_blank"&gt;Afghanistan Criticizes Pakistan's Anti-IS Operations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan and Afghanistan continue to carry out operations targeting Islamic State militants along their shared border, but there are signs that the two countries are not communicating, making the effort less effective. This week, Pakistan said that it just completed the first phase of its Khyber 4 operation against IS militants in the country's Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province. "Terrorist hideouts were dismantled, and caches of IEDs [improvised explosive devices], arms and ammunition were seized," Pakistan Army's media wing (ISPR) said a statement. But Afghan defense officials told VOA that Afgh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistanis protest against increasing power cuts during Ramadan - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-electricity-idUSKBN18Q17N</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDZZ53ECnI6OKIFFGl1HYHsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 11:48:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-electricity-idUSKBN18Q17N" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistanis protest against increasing power cuts during Ramadan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Syed Raza Hassan and Jibran Ahmad KARACHI/PESHAWAR, Pakistan (Reuters) - Protesters in Pakistan's largest city set tires ablaze on Tuesday after power cuts disrupted a traditional pre-dawn meal during the holy month of Ramadan, police said, a day after two protesters in another city were shot dead. Prime Minister Nawaz Sharif came to power four years ago promising to end scheduled blackouts - known as "load shedding" - that have plagued daily life for years, hobbling the economy and deterring foreign investment. Higher power generation has helped ease load shedding in many areas in recen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistani Province Grows 750 Million Trees - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistani-province-grows-seven-hundred-fifty-million-trees/3746994.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEin-n5Iw69kb9pKNzD1HxkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 19:35:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistani-province-grows-seven-hundred-fifty-million-trees/3746994.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani Province Grows 750 Million Trees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials in Pakistan say a massive government-run reforestation campaign has grown 750 million trees across a northwestern province since 2015. The government of Khyber Pakhtunkhwa, or KP, launched the four-year project with a goal of planting 1 billion trees by the end of 2018, hoping it would "turn the tide on land degradation and loss" in a formerly forested province in the Hindu Kush mountain range. Officials and leaders of Pakistan Tehreek-e-Insaf, or PTI, party — which rules the province — gathered Thursday in the national capital of Islamabad to mark the progress in what is official...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Clashes hit Pakistan-Afghanistan border - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/03/clashes-pakistan-afghanistan-border-kill-170317061451793.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM6o6hbFWhj7Pj6qsWeJQDoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 09:43:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/03/clashes-pakistan-afghanistan-border-kill-170317061451793.html" target="_blank"&gt;Clashes hit Pakistan-Afghanistan border&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamabad, Pakistan - Eight people, including two soldiers, have been killed in a raid on a Pakistani military border post in the Khyber tribal area, according to the Pakistan military. The raid was launched from Afghan territory on Friday and resulted in the killing of six attackers and two Pakistani soldiers. The Tehreek-e-Taliban Pakistan's Jamaat-ur-Ahrar faction claimed responsibility for the attack in a statement issued via email to media, claiming it had attacked three border posts, capturing one. "One of the Pakistani forces' posts was defeated by the mujahideen and set on fire," sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Daral lake. - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/221393811/daral-lake-by-usman-saqib</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPAjnx4S_rM87M68kj8tIwkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 16:33:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/221393811/daral-lake-by-usman-saqib" target="_blank"&gt;Daral lake.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hindu Kush mountain range. Swat valley, KPK, Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Pakistan's 'father of Taliban' cleric killed in knife attack - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/7ea77c93fb774b76b671a0a9f6c2b58a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENbsdmPbc4vTQ10Ugi1Qnx0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 19:13:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/7ea77c93fb774b76b671a0a9f6c2b58a" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan's 'father of Taliban' cleric killed in knife attack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISLAMABAD (AP) — Prominent Pakistani cleric Maulana Samiul Haq, also known as the "father of the Taliban," was killed in a knife attack at his home in the garrison city of Rawalpindi on Friday, his family and police said. Haq's son, Hamidul Haq, said his father was alone in his bedroom when he was attacked by an assailant, who escaped undetected. "My father has been martyred. He was alone at his home. His guard had gone out minutes before the attack and upon his return he saw my father in critical condition," he told reporters. Police say Haq, 81, was taken to a nearby hospital, where he di...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>'Father of Taliban' killed in Pakistan attack - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-03/sami-ul-haq-father-of-taliban-dies-in-pakistan/10462676</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELhK4rQWWuyuKuGvC5NpFe0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 21:14:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-03/sami-ul-haq-father-of-taliban-dies-in-pakistan/10462676" target="_blank"&gt;'Father of Taliban' killed in Pakistan attack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Muslim cleric Sami ul-Haq, known as the "Father of the Taliban" for having taught some of the Afghan Islamist movement's leaders, has been killed in Pakistan. Key points: - Reports vary over exactly how Sami ul-Haq was killed and why his bodyguard and driver were apparently not there to defend him - He ran a seminary near the Afghan border in Pakistan for decades, with one of his students going on to found the Taliban - A Pakistan military spokesman condemns the "assassination" Unknown attackers killed the cleric, who ran an Islamic seminary in north-western Pakistan and was seen as a possi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Several killed as bus crashes into ravine in northern Pakistan - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/killed-bus-crashes-ravine-northern-pakistan-181029054429357.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4YDi5MH7o3Fjn9wxpcSsAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 06:55:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/killed-bus-crashes-ravine-northern-pakistan-181029054429357.html" target="_blank"&gt;Several killed as bus crashes into ravine in northern Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamabad, Pakistan - At least 17 people have been killed after a bus plunged into a deep ravine in northern Pakistan's district of Kohistan, officials say, with at least eight passengers still missing after the accident. The accident took place late on Sunday night on a remote road winding through steep mountains near the boundary between Kohistan and the Gilgit-Baltistan region, about 200km north of the capital Islamabad, senior police official Raja Abdul Saboor told Al Jazeera by telephone. "According to the lone survivor, a woman, she heard a loud sound, as if that of a tire bursting as...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>New premier Imran Khan pledges to restore Pakistan's economy - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/ba272f12044a4d67afa8fa1cbea71737</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJnK93X1Ypb5rkcVTPjc2NoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:39:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/ba272f12044a4d67afa8fa1cbea71737" target="_blank"&gt;New premier Imran Khan pledges to restore Pakistan's economy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISLAMABAD (AP) — Prime Minister Imran Khan said in his first televised speech in office that Pakistan is in the worst economic condition it has seen and pledged to cut government spending, end corruption and repatriate public funds. A day after he was sworn in, Khan promised reforms across all fields. "I want to see Pakistan a great country" with social services for the poor, Khan said. Khan pointed to the growing divide between the rich and poor and said he would adopt austerity measures to relieve the strain on the economy and tackle the country's foreign debt, over $95 billion. "The inte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Beautiful Pakistan - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/267207819/beautiful-pakistan-by-rizwan-saeed</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA6NDxJ37PQIzNahBWSqDCkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 06:27:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/267207819/beautiful-pakistan-by-rizwan-saeed" target="_blank"&gt;Beautiful Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swat valley, kpk, Pakistan&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>The determined transgender candidate from Khyber Pakhtunkhwa - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/determined-transgender-candidate-khyber-pakhtunkhwa-180718221322920.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDAHHJ12ffQLFNdlx365vjQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 18:27:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/determined-transgender-candidate-khyber-pakhtunkhwa-180718221322920.html" target="_blank"&gt;The determined transgender candidate from Khyber Pakhtunkhwa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maria Khan gives herself plenty of time in the morning to get ready before heading out for another day of door-to-door campaigning in Pakistan's northwest Khyber Pakhtunkhwa (KPK) province. She likes to wear a brightly coloured shalwar kameez, a slick of eyeliner and red lipstick. "I want to speak for the people of Pakistan, I want to represent them and help in ending their problems," she told Al Jazeera. Khan is a 38-year-old transgender woman from Mansehra, an eastern city surrounded by green mountains, and is running in Pakistan's July 25 election as an independent candidate. There will ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan secular party defiant after its leader killed in blast - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/pakistan-secular-party-defiant-leader-killed-blast-180711160102056.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMetdNGFvX81Eg4_pSE7iYQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 18:32:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/pakistan-secular-party-defiant-leader-killed-blast-180711160102056.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan secular party defiant after its leader killed in blast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan's Awami National Party (ANP) on Wednesday vowed to fight against armed groups after its senior leader Haroon Bilour was killed in a suicide attack a day ago in the Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province. The attack on Tuesday at an election campaign event organised by the ANP also killed at least 20 people. Their funerals were held in the KPK provincial capital Peshawar on Wednesday. The Pakistani Taliban claimed responsibility for the attack. Bilour was a provincial assembly candidate for the July 25 general elections. His father, Bashir Bilour, also a prominent ANP politician, was killed by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan's secular Pashtun party defiant after Taliban bomber kills 20 activists - Reuters</title><link>https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-politics-anp/pakistans-secular-pashtun-party-defiant-after-taliban-bomber-kills-20-activists-idUSKBN1K11U2?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO1xf7wUnVT-LiLcQ70i_rkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 23:40:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://internal.www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-politics-anp/pakistans-secular-pashtun-party-defiant-after-taliban-bomber-kills-20-activists-idUSKBN1K11U2?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan's secular Pashtun party defiant after Taliban bomber kills 20 activists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan's Awami National Party vowed on Wednesday not to be swayed from its resolve to face down terrorists, a day after a Taliban suicide bombing killed a score of its activists, including the son of a party leader assassinated in 2012. The secular party, drawn chiefly from the Pashtun ethnic group that also provides the Taliban with many recruits, has long competed with it and other Islamist groups in Pakistan's northwestern region bordering Afghanistan. "We want peace on our soil and will stand with our ‎people," said senior party leader Mian Iftikhar Hussain, who lost his only son in a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://internal.www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistani Taliban claim bombing at rally that killed 21 - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/acc6ce725cb54b98a4ff61f57723bdf9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBCS1EO4galwQSbnqIHZMcEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 15:48:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/acc6ce725cb54b98a4ff61f57723bdf9" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani Taliban claim bombing at rally that killed 21&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PESHAWAR, Pakistan (AP) — The Pakistani Taliban on Wednesday claimed responsibility for an overnight suicide bombing at a campaign rally that killed a secular politician and 20 others, two weeks before the country's nationwide elections. Mohammad Khurasani, a spokesman for the Pakistani Taliban, confirmed the militant group targeted a rally of the Awami National Party in the northwestern city of Peshawar. The bombing killed Haroon Ahmed Bilour, a candidate for a seat in the provincial legislature. Another 65 people were wounded. Islamic extremists grew to despise the Awami National Party wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Suicide blast kills ANP candidate, supporters at election rally - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/suicide-bomber-kills-anp-candidate-supporters-election-rally-180710201101463.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM7zT2p52mje0f9vTNkUSBkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 07:48:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/suicide-bomber-kills-anp-candidate-supporters-election-rally-180710201101463.html" target="_blank"&gt;Suicide blast kills ANP candidate, supporters at election rally&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A suicide bomb attack at an election rally in the northwestern city of Peshawar, Pakistan, has killed at least 20 people, including prominent local politician Haroon Bilour, police said. The attack on Tuesday at a campaign event organised by the Awami National Party (ANP) also wounded at least 69 people, according to the local police chief. Bilour was a provincial assembly candidate for the July 25 general elections. His father, Bashir Bilour, also a prominent ANP politician, was killed by a suicide bomber in 2012. Police said the bomber struck when Bilour was about to address some 200 supp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>'Green gold': Pakistan plants hundreds of millions of trees - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/06/gold-pakistan-plants-hundreds-millions-trees-180626095806407.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMi7cpsVNXYDvGtknje2xKYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 16:30:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/06/gold-pakistan-plants-hundreds-millions-trees-180626095806407.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Green gold': Pakistan plants hundreds of millions of trees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The change is drastic: around the region of Heroshah, previously arid hills are now covered with forest as far as the horizon. In northwestern Pakistan, hundreds of millions of trees have been planted to fight deforestation. In 2015 and 2016 some 16,000 labourers planted more than 900,000 fast-growing eucalyptus trees at regular, geometric intervals in Heroshah - and the titanic task is just a fraction of the effort across the province of Khyber Pakhtunkhwa. "Before it was completely burnt land. Now they have green gold in their hands," commented forest manager Pervaiz Manan as he displayed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan approves bill to merge tribal regions with country - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f5910c4403234010ac8f0d555548e743</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAhmVk2AcOIEV6K6wDQlmC4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 15:22:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f5910c4403234010ac8f0d555548e743" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan approves bill to merge tribal regions with country&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PESHAWAR, Pakistan (AP) — The assembly of northwestern Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province approved a bill Sunday to merge the tribal regions along the Afghan border with its territory, paving the way to granting equal rights to about 5 million people in the restive area. The milestone step comes after both houses of parliament had earlier approved granting equal rights to the tribes that have been governed by discriminatory laws since British colonial rule. The bill now goes to President Mamnoon Hussain to be signed into law. Haji Abdul Rehman, a tribal elder from the Mohmand tribal area and membe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Pakistan dismantles troubled tribal regions - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/05/25/asia/pakistan-tribal-areas-dismantled-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJRaQUn7XGRN9MY2xBPryyEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 14:58:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/05/25/asia/pakistan-tribal-areas-dismantled-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan dismantles troubled tribal regions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan has abolished its troubled northwest tribal areas in a historic parliamentary bill granting rights to millions of conflict-weary people and scrapping a draconian colonial-era regime. The Federally Administered Tribal Areas (FATA) were merged into the country's administrative mainstream, becoming part of the northern province of Khyber Pakhtunkhwa, by a parliamentary amendment approved by the senate on Friday. Taliban fighters have used the Pakistani tribal areas as a refuge from the US-led coaltion since the 2001 invasion of Afghanistan. STR/AFP/AFP/Getty Images Since Pakistan's cr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Pakistan parliament passes landmark tribal areas reform - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/05/pakistan-parliament-passes-landmark-tribal-areas-reform-180524111258832.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPFNAZy8Q1q4DO1MWIMT54AqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 11:56:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/05/pakistan-parliament-passes-landmark-tribal-areas-reform-180524111258832.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan parliament passes landmark tribal areas reform&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamabad, Pakistan – Pakistan's lower house of parliament has passed a landmark constitutional amendment extending widespread political, administrative and human rights reforms to the country's northwestern tribal areas, a region that had long been sanctuary to armed groups. The constitutional amendment, passed by the National Assembly in the capital, Islamabad, on Thursday, sees the Federally Administered Tribal Areas (FATA) merged into Khyber Pakhtunkhwa (KP) province. It effectively abolishes draconian colonial era regulations that the districts had been governed under for decades, maki...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan passes bill to bring law and order to former Taliban region - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/may/25/pakistan-passes-bill-to-bring-law-and-order-to-former-al-qaida-region</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKkB2_bn49vbueXzds4D7y4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 01:00:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/may/25/pakistan-passes-bill-to-bring-law-and-order-to-former-al-qaida-region" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan passes bill to bring law and order to former Taliban region&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For centuries the north-west corner of Pakistan known as the federally administered tribal areas (Fata) has been known as one of the world’s most lawless regions – a mountainous bolthole for terrorist groups. This week, however, Pakistan’s parliament passed a a landmark piece of legislation to abolish the semi-autonomous zone of Fata and bring a court system, police and modern governance to its long-suffering 5 million residents. Under the legislation passed on Thursday, the neighbouring province of Khyber Pakhtunkhwa will gradually absorb a region once dubbed the “most dangerous place in t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Paves Way to Mainstreaming Restive Tribal Areas - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-paves-way-mainstreaming-restive-tribal-areas/4408514.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDx3TgUhifXBisNTlf3Gq2kqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 19:12:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-paves-way-mainstreaming-restive-tribal-areas/4408514.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Paves Way to Mainstreaming Restive Tribal Areas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan's national assembly passed a historic constitutional amendment Thursday, paving the way to bringing the restive Federally Administered Tribal Areas, known as FATA, into the political mainstream, just a week before the end of its tenure. The bill will be taken up Friday in the Senate. Until now, the area bordering Afghanistan was treated as a separate administrative unit with limited interference from the Pakistani government. It was loosely governed by local tribal law and British-era regulations. It also lagged behind the rest of the country in terms of infrastructure and basic fa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Bombs, blood and bravery: Defusing IEDs in Pakistan - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/bombs-blood-brotherhood-defusing-ieds-pakistan-180322081147559.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEnUGHQH7ZnJFD0GRbPuGPsqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 07:46:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/bombs-blood-brotherhood-defusing-ieds-pakistan-180322081147559.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bombs, blood and bravery: Defusing IEDs in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every time the phone rings, it's bad news. An improvised explosive device (IED) has been found, or worse, it has already gone off. The crackled message is relayed on walkie-talkies across Pakistan's northwestern Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province (KPK) and the men of the KPK Bomb Disposal Unit (BDU) spring into action. {articleGUID} Braving booby-trapped devices and targeted attacks, the 34-man team risk their lives to make their region safer. The danger they face is exacerbated by underfunding and a lack of equipment, with the unit almost completely dependent on international donations. Borderin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Dancing in the hills: a journey to meet Pakistan’s Kalash people - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0bf722c8-2b6b-11e8-97ec-4bd3494d5f14</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOiU8QkZq844F-NTuj8BPs0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 11:57:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0bf722c8-2b6b-11e8-97ec-4bd3494d5f14" target="_blank"&gt;Dancing in the hills: a journey to meet Pakistan’s Kalash people&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We headed up the mountain in the moonlight, through a forest of holly oaks and walnuts, dotted with crudely carved wooden-box graves. Occasionally a life-sized weathered wooden effigy of some armoured and helmeted warrior reared out of the darkness, leaning at a crazy angle. Above us we could hear the beat of drums and the cries of dancers; from below us came the rush of a mountain torrent. The beat got louder and more driven the closer we came to the ceremonial platform at the top of the hill. We were in the mountains of the North-West Frontier of Pakistan, less than 20 miles from the Afgh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>plASTic - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/248008499/plastic-by-kpk-</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOUehFRc7e58f_C0Z8IEgPQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 06:45:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/248008499/plastic-by-kpk-" target="_blank"&gt;plASTic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Berlin KPK Photography Facebook Fotocommunity ArtLimited Instagram twitter&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Provincial Government in Pakistan Under Criticism for Aiding Controversial School - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/provincial-government-in-pakistan-under-criticism-for-aiding-controversial-school/4270068.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAYBazL2tA8nBLIHCouW31QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 23:49:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/provincial-government-in-pakistan-under-criticism-for-aiding-controversial-school/4270068.html" target="_blank"&gt;Provincial Government in Pakistan Under Criticism for Aiding Controversial School&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The provincial government of Pakistan's northwest Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province came under sharp criticism for giving an Islamic seminary $2.5 million (Rs.277 million) in aid. The government, led by Pakistan Tehreek-e-Insaf, used government funds to support Darul Uloom Haqqania, a religious seminary. Pakistani religious schools have long been blamed for producing extremists. "Government is supporting extremist elements — this will not help any move to curb militancy in the country. And if Pakistan is blamed for supporting militants, this proves it," Syed Alam Mehsud, presidentof nationalist p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan's Pashtuns march for justice - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/pakistan-pashtuns-march-justice-180224114356113.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEExFdwP1TLVZhveGdoNeDVYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 13:19:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/pakistan-pashtuns-march-justice-180224114356113.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan's Pashtuns march for justice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Naqeeb Mehsud, a 27-year-old aspiring Pashtun model residing in Karachi, was killed by the police, there was an outcry on social media by his family and friends, leading to a police investigation and the eventual sacking of Karachi's Malir district chief of police, Rao Anwar. While Anwar was found to be responsible for 400 other such murders, he has not shown up for court and remains at large. Mehsud's murder has sparked an unprecedented outcry among Pashtuns against the trend of extrajudicial killings and forced disappearances across Pakistan. Especially since 9/11, the term "missing ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>DirtyLanxx - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/247027961/dirtylanxx-by-kpk-</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJvgGtVYBIHGxwVG5dezM3gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 18:13:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/247027961/dirtylanxx-by-kpk-" target="_blank"&gt;DirtyLanxx&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cologne 2018 KPK Photography Facebook Fotocommunity ArtLimited Instagram twitter&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Plans to Reform Nation's Religious Seminaries - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-plans-to-reform-nation-religious-seminaries/4258297.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGX1mqm_eklCbZc_KfTgmqoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 23:12:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-plans-to-reform-nation-religious-seminaries/4258297.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Plans to Reform Nation's Religious Seminaries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an effort to control militancy and the alleged abuse of madrassas (religious seminaries) by some militant groups operating in the country, Pakistan’s government recently announced plans to bring all madrassas under the formal education structure of the country. Ahsan Iqbal, Pakistan’s interior minister, reportedly told a seminar last month the government already has allocated funds for initiating the reforms in the country’s education sector, and they include modernizing the educational curriculum and bringing traditional seminaries into the formal government structure. The new measures ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pashtuns End Protest in Islamabad, Vow to Reconvene if Demands Not Met - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pashtun-protest-islamabad/4248586.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGBRGkp9D7pXnoj1FD7gOiEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 02:42:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pashtun-protest-islamabad/4248586.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pashtuns End Protest in Islamabad, Vow to Reconvene if Demands Not Met&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pashtuns have felt neglected and wrongly targeted in Pakistan for some time. But the death of a shopkeeper, who died in an alleged extrajudicial killing, led to a protest by some Pashtuns. Naqeebullah Mehsud, 27, was killed January 13 in Karachi, the capital of Sindh province. Law enforcement authorities initially accused him of having ties with the Pakistani Taliban. The charge was later dropped following an internal inquiry, and amid growing anger among Pashtuns, who viewed his death as an extrajudicial killing — when someone is killed by government officials without a sanctioned judicial...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan court convicts 31 over campus lynching of student falsly accused of blasphemy - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/02/07/pakistan-court-convicts-31-campus-lynching-student-falsly-accused/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA4HNrD0dS6pbFVzsrvUm38qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 13:58:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/02/07/pakistan-court-convicts-31-campus-lynching-student-falsly-accused/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan court convicts 31 over campus lynching of student falsly accused of blasphemy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One person was sentenced to death and 30 others were imprisoned over the brutal campus lynching of a university student who was falsely accused of blasphemy in Pakistan. A court in the northwestern Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province acquitted 26 other suspects in the killing of Mashal Khan last year, which sparked outcry in the religiously conservative country. Mr Khan, 23, a communications student, was attacked and killed by a mob on the campus after a dormitory debate about religion. The 57 suspects indicted over the murder included students, teachers and some officials of Abdul Wali Khan Univer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Anti-US Cleric Released on Bail in Pakistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/anti-us-cleric-bail-pakistan/4209058.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMAe362o4C273W2Hiqy066cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 23:20:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/anti-us-cleric-bail-pakistan/4209058.html" target="_blank"&gt;Anti-US Cleric Released on Bail in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistani authorities on Monday released anti-U.S. and pro-Taliban cleric Maulana Sufi Muhammad after eight years in prison. He was facing sedition charges and was allegedly involved in attacks on police stations. While some in the country do not view Muhammad's release as a good sign, others support the move. "He is a 93-year-old person. He is seriously sick, almost paralyzed and could not be treated inside the jail," Latif Afridi, a lawyer and an expert of legal affairs, told VOA. "The Pakistani courts have the power to release the sick and people who are so old on bail." Muhammad is cons...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Authorities Investigate Cases of Forced Conversion of Sikh Minority in Pakistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-sikh-minority-forced-conversion/4177063.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEiSLurr4Xw2W7mXag8Utr8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 02:33:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-sikh-minority-forced-conversion/4177063.html" target="_blank"&gt;Authorities Investigate Cases of Forced Conversion of Sikh Minority in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistani authorities have initiated an inquiry into allegations that members of the Sikh religious minority have been forced to convert to Islam in the country’s northwestern Khyber Pakhtunkhwa province. The Sikh community in Hangu district last week filed a complaint, accusing a government official of forcing them to convert to Islam. The provincial government reportedly suspended Tehsil Tall Yaqoob Khan, assistant commissioner of Hangu, on suspicion of involvement in the case. Investigation underway The government confirmed that a high-level investigation is underway and measures have be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Twelve killed by Islamist militants in Pakistan - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-12-01/gunmen-attack-agriculture-institute-in-pakistan-killing/9218802</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVS_2__hNmYlaypwffFN1YqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:15:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-12-01/gunmen-attack-agriculture-institute-in-pakistan-killing/9218802" target="_blank"&gt;Twelve killed by Islamist militants in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamist militants have stormed a government complex in northwest Pakistan, killing 12 people and wounding 35 others, police and rescue officials have said. Key points: - The attackers were clad in women's burqas - Security forces were able to evacuate residents rapidly, saving scores of lives - Military spokesman says attack was planned in Afghanistan Police and military troops killed three attackers during a firefight at the provincial government complex for agriculture research in Peshawar, they said. The main Taliban militant group, Tehrik-e-Taliban Pakistan, claimed responsibility. Pol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item></channel></rss>