<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Nadia Murad - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZpZUdwcWMyWnVZeElDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-PK&amp;gl=PK&amp;ceid=PK:en</link><language>en-PK</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:11:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Nadia Murad: From jihadists´ captive to Nobel laureate - The News International</title><link>https://www.thenews.com.pk/latest/402943-nadia-murad-from-jihadists-captive-to-nobel-laureate</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780129275641</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:02:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thenews.com.pk/latest/402943-nadia-murad-from-jihadists-captive-to-nobel-laureate" target="_blank"&gt;Nadia Murad: From jihadists´ captive to Nobel laureate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The News International&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.geo.tv/latest/221021-nadia-murad-from-daesh-captive-to-nobel-laureate" target="_blank"&gt;Nadia Murad: from Daesh captive to Nobel laureate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Geo News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/news/audio/2018/dec/08/what-is-it-like-to-fear-your-own-child" target="_blank"&gt;What is it like to fear your own child?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWo1bmUybWpZQU1FU0I3c2xJYVZMelNLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thenews.com.pk">The News International</source></item><item><title>Nadia Murad: ‘I survived the Isis genocide, now I want to rebuild the Yazidi homeland’ - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/f28c4184-f823-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKSk_ohPuVTf4QcY8dUXm9YqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f28c4184-f823-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Nadia Murad: ‘I survived the Isis genocide, now I want to rebuild the Yazidi homeland’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Change can happen when one least expects it. I know this to be true because my life changed in an instant. One moment I was a farm girl, going to school in my village in northern Iraq and the next I was an Isis sex slave, “owned” by militants. My peaceful existence was shattered simply because my religious beliefs were deemed sub-human by a group of men who believed they were superior. Isis murdered my family and took me captive, exposing me to horrors which would be impossible to imagine had I not endured every moment and felt each brutal blow. My story is not unique. I am only one Yazidi ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>In Early 2019, UN Team to Begin Probe of IS Crimes in Iraq - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/in-early-2019-un-team-to-begin-probe-of-is-crimes-in-iraq/4687322.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA1OvVb-azGZIGPHfCN0HcAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:28:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/in-early-2019-un-team-to-begin-probe-of-is-crimes-in-iraq/4687322.html" target="_blank"&gt;In Early 2019, UN Team to Begin Probe of IS Crimes in Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A U.N. team authorized over a year ago to investigate the massacre of the Yazidi minority and other atrocities by jihadists in Iraq will finally begin work early next year, the head of the investigation said Tuesday. The U.N. Security Council adopted a resolution in September 2017 to bring those responsible for Islamic State group war crimes to justice — a cause championed by Nobel Peace Prize winner Nadia Murad and international human rights lawyer Amal Clooney. The team, led by British lawyer Karim Asad Ahmad Khan, was deployed to Baghdad in October, but has since focused on administrativ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The 2018 Nobel Peace Prize Raises Awareness Of The Use Of Sexual Violence In War - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewelinaochab/2018/12/01/the-2018-nobel-peace-prize-raises-awareness-of-the-use-of-sexual-violence-in-war/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBXmPmD_i6a2kEBV6W7Q_tQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 14:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewelinaochab/2018/12/01/the-2018-nobel-peace-prize-raises-awareness-of-the-use-of-sexual-violence-in-war/" target="_blank"&gt;The 2018 Nobel Peace Prize Raises Awareness Of The Use Of Sexual Violence In War&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nobel Peace Prize is an award that is meant for a person “who shall have done the most or the best work for fraternity between nations, for the abolition or reduction of standing armies and for the holding and promotion of peace congresses.” Over the years, it has been awarded to many extraordinary people who have spent their lives dedicated to achieving a state of peace. Recipients have included Malala, the International Committee of the Red Cross, Mother Teresa, the European Union, Shirin Ebadi, Kofi Annan, the United Nations, Médecins Sans Frontières and many more. Only a few weeks a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Former Isil sex slave's tearful return to home village - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/06/02/former-isil-sex-slaves-tearful-return-home-village/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELbMmE2Iv5L7oYxZiBJZISwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:04:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/06/02/former-isil-sex-slaves-tearful-return-home-village/" target="_blank"&gt;Former Isil sex slave's tearful return to home village&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nadia Murad, the Yazidi woman who was abducted into sex slavery by Islamic State, has made a emotional return to her home village of Kocho, in Iraq, earlier this week. Nadia had been kidnapped in August 2014 and escaped three months later. She then was able to go to Germany and became an advocate for the plight of the Yazidi minority in Iraq. Now, the UN Goodwill Ambassador has also been nominated for the Nobel Peace Prize. Video block text&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Put Some Respect on Amal Clooney’s Name - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2017/03/20/put-some-respect-on-amal-clooney-s-name.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJCQFZFYnMW8fS9N5w2bLLgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2017/03/20/put-some-respect-on-amal-clooney-s-name.html" target="_blank"&gt;Put Some Respect on Amal Clooney’s Name&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to famous women, entertainment reporting is all too often limited to the three w’s: who are you wearing, what do you weigh, and where is your boyfriend? Female celebrities are increasingly fed up with questions about their fitness regimens and relationship statuses. Prime examples include Scarlett Johansson getting pissed off when a reporter asked her what lingerie she wore under her Avengers costume, and Ariana Grande lecturing a radio interviewer who questioned whether she could last longer without her phone or her makeup. Although, knowing women, it was probably just these ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Amal Clooney to Iraq: Allow U.N. probe of Islamic State Yazidi crimes - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-clooney-idUSKBN16H07L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMBz8yKBRaltvvTclY53BXUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 05:42:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-clooney-idUSKBN16H07L" target="_blank"&gt;Amal Clooney to Iraq: Allow U.N. probe of Islamic State Yazidi crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Michelle Nichols UNITED NATIONS (Reuters) - International human rights lawyer Amal Clooney and a young Yazidi woman who was enslaved and raped by Islamic State fighters pushed Iraq on Thursday to allow a United Nations investigation into crimes by the militant group. Britain is drafting a United Nations Security Council resolution to establish a U.N. investigation, but Clooney said the Iraqi government needs to send a letter formally requesting the inquiry before the 15-member council can vote. Islamic State is committing genocide against the Yazidis in Syria and Iraq to destroy the mino...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>U.S.-Backed Battle For Mosul Could Mean Death For Yazidis Held As ISIS Sex Slaves - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/yazidi-hostages-isis-mosul_us_5801002ce4b0e8c198a7a6ad</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBxs2AiD0GSoFUpqNjMDZ6EqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMO2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 18:15:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/yazidi-hostages-isis-mosul_us_5801002ce4b0e8c198a7a6ad" target="_blank"&gt;U.S.-Backed Battle For Mosul Could Mean Death For Yazidis Held As ISIS Sex Slaves&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DOHUK, Iraq ― The thick black binder in front of Bahzad Farhan Murad is filled with images of children. In it, a 12-year-old girl in Raqqa makes a sexual gesture near her genitals. The men selling her want $15,000. A 13-year-old is sprawled out for the camera, stripped of her pants. A doe-eyed toddler boy stares blankly, wearing black eyeliner. And a 17-year-old named Zeina is for sale for $10,000 cash. The self-described Islamic State, also known as ISIS, is using these pictures to sell kids for rape. Murad is an activist and investigator who works to free Yazidis from the militant group,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Ex-captive of Islamic State Sheds Tears on Return to Village in Northern Iraq - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/3883230.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPpKEkJSqt_vsCp6cA4nj7AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 20:50:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/3883230.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-captive of Islamic State Sheds Tears on Return to Village in Northern Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nadia Murad made an emotional return on Thursday to the Yazidi village in northern Iraq where she was captured and sold as a slave by Islamic State, three years ago. She broke down in tears as she approached the school where the militants rounded up the population of Kojo and separated the men from the women, part of a series of crimes the United Nations described as a genocide against the Yazidi minority. “We hoped our fate would be to be killed like the men instead of being sold and raped by Syrians, Iraqis ... Tunisians and Europeans,” Murad said after composing herself, speaking from th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Iraq's Iran-backed Paramilitary Advances Towards Syria Border - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3874621.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO4mouVQJrhy7m0p5CFhgeEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 17:35:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3874621.html" target="_blank"&gt;Iraq's Iran-backed Paramilitary Advances Towards Syria Border&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iraq's Iran-backed Shi'ite paramilitary force said on Sunday it had dislodged Islamic State from a number of villages west of Mosul, scoring further progress towards the border with Syria. The villages taken by the Popular Mobilization paramilitary force include Kojo, where Islamic State fighters abducted hundreds of Yazidi women in 2014, including Nadia Murad and Lamiya Aji Bashar, recipients of the European Parliament's Sakharov Prize for freedom of thought. Kojo and the other villages of the Sinjar mountain region will be returned to the Yazidi community, a Popular Mobilization leader, A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Amal Clooney and her client on ISIS brutality - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2017/03/17/exp-gps-amal-clooney-nadia-murad-isis-legal.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFHWx3R-1zETH70qZ82UsUAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:11:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2017/03/17/exp-gps-amal-clooney-nadia-murad-isis-legal.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Amal Clooney and her client on ISIS brutality&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amal Clooney and her client Nadia Murad tell Fareed about the atrocities ISIS committed against Nadia and her Yazidi community. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>No, Amal Clooney Wasn't 'Showing Off Her Baby Bump' At The UN - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/amal-clooney-united-nations-tweet_us_58c2b10fe4b054a0ea6a101e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP5ENJhbQSS-HWz9ZtXy7ssqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMKOXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:40:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/amal-clooney-united-nations-tweet_us_58c2b10fe4b054a0ea6a101e" target="_blank"&gt;No, Amal Clooney Wasn't 'Showing Off Her Baby Bump' At The UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;International human rights lawyer Amal Clooney gave an emotional speech Thursday in New York City urging the United Nations to pursue a criminal investigation into acts committed by the self-titled Islamic State, including genocide, rape and kidnapping. However, some publications chose to focus on her “baby bump,” instead. Clooney, who is expecting twins with husband George Clooney, made headlines in multiple publications not for the urgent and harrowing situation involving the militant group or the young Yazidi victim she is representing, but rather for how her pregnant figure looked in a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>ISIS sex slave survivor demands recognition of Yazidi genocide in tearful homecoming - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/390662-nadia-murad-isis-yazidi-iraq/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBBp2ZHFDISDgbxAaYNjz-QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 18:35:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/390662-nadia-murad-isis-yazidi-iraq/" target="_blank"&gt;ISIS sex slave survivor demands recognition of Yazidi genocide in tearful homecoming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nadia Murad made an emotional return to her home village of Kocho in Iraq on Thursday for the first time since she was kidnapped by Islamic State militants (IS, formerly ISIS/ISIL) in 2014. "I am a daughter of this village," Murad, who wailed and shed tears, told Reuters upon her return. Surrounded by Yazidi fighters, who reclaimed the village from IS last week, the 24-year-old spoke from the roof of her old school. Yazidi survivor and United Nations Goodwill Ambassador for the Dignity of Survivors of Human trafficking Nadia Murad (C), Kojo, Iraq June 1, 2017. © Alkis Konstantinidis / Reute...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Iraq unsure if U.N. help needed to probe Islamic State crimes - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-un-idUSKBN16H2QN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENqGHyk10mB8J92afF-ASN8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 22:52:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-un-idUSKBN16H2QN" target="_blank"&gt;Iraq unsure if U.N. help needed to probe Islamic State crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Michelle Nichols UNITED NATIONS (Reuters) - Iraq is assessing what help it might need to collect and preserve evidence of Islamic State crimes, but has not yet decided whether it needs United Nations assistance, the country's U.N. Ambassador, Mohamed Ali Alhakim, said on Friday. Britain is drafting a U.N. Security Council resolution to establish a U.N. investigation to collect and preserve evidence for future prosecution, but would like Iraq to approve such a move by sending a letter formally requesting council action. International human rights lawyer Amal Clooney and Nadia Murad, a you...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Escaped Isis sex-slave Nadia Murad urges EU to recognise Yazidi genocide - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/people/nadia-murad-isis-sex-slave-yazidi-genocide-eu-call-recognition-syria-iraq-a7469791.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECCCYiL8R81bt61AhQmLXX0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 12:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/people/nadia-murad-isis-sex-slave-yazidi-genocide-eu-call-recognition-syria-iraq-a7469791.html" target="_blank"&gt;Escaped Isis sex-slave Nadia Murad urges EU to recognise Yazidi genocide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Escaped Isis sex slave Nadia Murad has called on the EU to recognise the Jihadi group's ongoing genocide against the Yazidi people. Ms Murad said the EU must work to prosecute members of Isis and establish a safe zone to protect vulnerable minorities. She has been awarded the Sakharov Prize for Freedom of Thought along with Lamya Haji Bashar, another Yazidi woman who was also captured by Isis when the group launched a major assault across northern Iraq in 2014. They escaped after several months of enslavement and now campaign for Yazidi women. Escaped Yazidi Isis sex slaves win Sakharov pri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Escaped Yazidi Isis sex slaves win Sakharov prize, Europe’s most prestigious human rights award - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/people/escaped-yazidi-isis-sex-slaves-sakharov-prize-nadia-murad-lamiya-aji-bashar-a7383196.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK_4FAfd6jYmRb6XeHo9aqsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 13:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/people/escaped-yazidi-isis-sex-slaves-sakharov-prize-nadia-murad-lamiya-aji-bashar-a7383196.html" target="_blank"&gt;Escaped Yazidi Isis sex slaves win Sakharov prize, Europe’s most prestigious human rights award&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two Yazidi women who were abducted by the Isis terror group as sex slaves and escaped have been awarded the most prestigious human rights award in Europe. Nadia Murad and Lamiya Aji Bashar were captured by Isis fighters after the group launched a major assault on northern Iraq in 2014. Both now campaign for Yazidi women and were jointly awarded the Sakharov prize on Wednesday. European Parliament President Martin Schulz said awarding the honour to both women is “a very symbolic and significant decision to support these two survivors who came to Europe as refugees”. Taken by Isis, trafficked...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Yazidi human rights activist bursts into tears on return to her village for the first time in three years - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/yazidi-human-rights-activist-nadia-muarad-kojo-northern-iraq-isis-first-time-three-years-a7768816.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKnPlRO9nPRtr0Xo5_OqwxYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 11:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/yazidi-human-rights-activist-nadia-muarad-kojo-northern-iraq-isis-first-time-three-years-a7768816.html" target="_blank"&gt;Yazidi human rights activist bursts into tears on return to her village for the first time in three years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nadia Murad, the Yazidi woman who so bravely told the world about the horrors inflicted on her people by Isis, has made an emotional return home to her village in northern Iraq for the first time since 2014. Ms Murad, now 24, broke down in tears hugging her brother, a fighter who alongside the Shia paramilitary Popular Mobilisation Forces (PMF) managed to liberate Kojo earlier this week. She also visited her old home, collecting clothing which belonged to her mother, who was killed by Isis because she was considered old to be enslaved. Read more - Inside Lalish, the heart of the Yazidi fait...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Amal Clooney Continues To Show Us What Great Style Looks Like - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/amal-clooney-outshines-her-husband-in-sequined-chanel-dress_us_587e408ee4b07b9dd704b660</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA3OOlVgtLdk2a4kYJ66KGUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 14:52:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/amal-clooney-outshines-her-husband-in-sequined-chanel-dress_us_587e408ee4b07b9dd704b660" target="_blank"&gt;Amal Clooney Continues To Show Us What Great Style Looks Like&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;International human rights lawyer Amal Clooney brought all the star power to Davos on Tuesday. The 38-year-old outshone her fellow attendees in a vintage, sequined Chanel gown with dark green pumps. Clooney wore the illusion waist, haute couture dress to the Women of Impact dinner. According to People, the lawyer was there as an honored guest, along with her client, activist and Nobel Peace Prize-nominee Nadia Murad. Vice President Joe Biden and Amal’s actor husband, George Clooney, also attended the dinner. #georgeclooney#vip#actor#work#stunning #colorful #travel #goodtimes #beautiful #rom...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Iraq seeks international help to investigate Islamic State crimes - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-un-idUSKCN1AW2E7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA9Nw_Q7PEBjvLHZNXBrwosqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 18:41:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-un-idUSKCN1AW2E7" target="_blank"&gt;Iraq seeks international help to investigate Islamic State crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Riham Alkousaa UNITED NATIONS (Reuters) - Iraq asked for international help on Wednesday to collect and preserve evidence of crimes by Islamic State militants and said it is working with Britain to draft a United Nations Security Council resolution to establish the investigation. Britain, international human rights lawyer Amal Clooney and Nadia Murad, a woman from the Yazidi religious minority who was enslaved and raped by Islamic State fighters in Mosul, have been pushing Iraq to allow a U.N. inquiry. The 15-member Security Council could have established an inquiry without Iraq's consen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Former ISIS sex slave demands justice for Yazidis - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/03/19/middleeast/nadia-murad-amal-clooney-cnntv/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgk4LR24xhca7jPVwvUDMgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 13:35:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/03/19/middleeast/nadia-murad-amal-clooney-cnntv/" target="_blank"&gt;Former ISIS sex slave demands justice for Yazidis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Yazidi woman who was kidnapped and taken as a sex slave by ISIS told CNN's Fareed Zakaria on Sunday that the Iraqi government and the UN should establish an investigation in order to bring members of the brutal regime to justice. Nadia Murad, along with her counsel, international human rights lawyer Amal Clooney, described her ordeal to Zakaria. It began in 2014 after ISIS militants arrived at her village in Sinjar, Kurdistan, she said. "Early morning on August 3, 2014, they attacked us," she recalled. "Nearly 6,500 women and children from the Yazidi were abducted and about 5,000 people f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Ex-captive of ISIL sheds tears on return to Iraq - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/captive-isil-sheds-tears-return-iraq-170602013818265.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEUzoTEJ6czGI15lk0NNHc0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 02:02:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/captive-isil-sheds-tears-return-iraq-170602013818265.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-captive of ISIL sheds tears on return to Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nadia Murad made an emotional return to the Yazidi village in northern Iraq where she was captured and sold as a slave by Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant (ISIL) three years ago. She broke down in tears on Thursday as she approached the school where the fighters rounded up the population of Kojo and separated the men from the women, part of a series of crimes the United Nations described as a genocide against the Yazidi minority. "I have been waiting for this day for nearly three years," Murad said on the rooftop of the school, where she had studied for 11 years. On her return, Murad we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>UNICEF USAVoice: Amal And George Clooney Team Up With UNICEF To Help Refugees - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2017/07/31/amal-and-george-clooney-team-up-with-unicef-to-help-refugees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKS8nc5G98_tbo1o8t6W4NkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 19:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2017/07/31/amal-and-george-clooney-team-up-with-unicef-to-help-refugees/" target="_blank"&gt;UNICEF USAVoice: Amal And George Clooney Team Up With UNICEF To Help Refugees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A strikingly effective defender of neglected and exploited groups around the world, international human rights lawyer Amal Clooney and her husband, actor George Clooney, are stepping up to make sure all the world’s children get the opportunities they deserve. The high-profile couple’s Clooney Foundation for Justice today announced a $2.25 million partnership with UNICEF, which includes a generous donation from Google.org and an additional $1 million technology grant from HP Inc. The partnership with UNICEF will fund seven schools in Lebanon to help 3,000 currently out-of-school Syrian refug...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Iraq's Iran-backed paramilitary advances toward Syria border - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-mosul-idUSKBN18O0M2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGL3RjC5ei-bNG-c2nmbZj8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 16:59:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-mosul-idUSKBN18O0M2" target="_blank"&gt;Iraq's Iran-backed paramilitary advances toward Syria border&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BAGHDAD (Reuters) - Iraq's Iran-backed Shi'ite paramilitary force said on Sunday it had dislodged Islamic State from a number of villages west of Mosul, scoring further progress toward the border with Syria. The villages taken by the Popular Mobilisation paramilitary force include Kojo, where Islamic State fighters abducted hundreds of Yazidi women in 2014, including Nadia Murad and Lamiya Aji Bashar, recipients of the European Parliament's Sakharov Prize for freedom of thought. Kojo and the other villages of the Sinjar mountain region will be returned to the Yazidi community, a Popular Mob...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>UN Team to Collect Evidence of Islamic State War Crimes in Iraq - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-team-evidence-islamic-state-war-crimes-iraq/4039160.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPBg7U02qbPgoA6X0xYc2NoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 22:45:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-team-evidence-islamic-state-war-crimes-iraq/4039160.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Team to Collect Evidence of Islamic State War Crimes in Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations Security Council has voted unanimously to establish an investigative team to help Iraq secure evidence of atrocities committed by Islamic State militants "that may amount to war crimes, crimes against humanity and genocide." Britain, which drafted the resolution, said the team would bring some justice to those who had experienced atrocities at the hands of IS, variously known as ISIS, ISIL and Daesh. The U.S. Ambassador to the U.N., Nikki Haley, called the resolution "a landmark" that would "provide an indispensable record of the scope and scale" of IS atrocities. "This m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Amal Clooney's £168,000 maternity wardrobe is her masterful ploy to raise awareness of human rights abuses - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/fashion/people/amal-clooneys-168000-maternity-wardrobe-masterful-ploy-raise/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEASwjJX1PZrtJYfbdZlaHTsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCq098D</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 14:57:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/fashion/people/amal-clooneys-168000-maternity-wardrobe-masterful-ploy-raise/" target="_blank"&gt;Amal Clooney's £168,000 maternity wardrobe is her masterful ploy to raise awareness of human rights abuses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amal Clooney gave an impassioned speech at the UN last week as part of her defence of Iraq's Yazidi people and ongoing campaign to stop ISIS from committing further brutality. "Justice is what the victims want," Clooney said, "but justice will be forever out of reach if we allow the evidence to disappear, if mass graves are not protected, if medical evidence is lost, if witnesses can no longer be traced." She happened to deliver this impassioned speech in a bright yellow dress and matching coat from Bottega Veneta - one of a series £20,000+ designer looks she wore during her trip to New Yo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Amal Clooney is fighting Isis – but thankfully we're discussing more important matters like her pregnancy - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/amal-clooney-pregnant-united-nations-speech-isis-dress-heels-lawyer-yazidi-women-nadia-murad-a7622446.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN51zqSMWplp0Ho8LlBb_d0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/amal-clooney-pregnant-united-nations-speech-isis-dress-heels-lawyer-yazidi-women-nadia-murad-a7622446.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amal Clooney is fighting Isis – but thankfully we're discussing more important matters like her pregnancy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amal Clooney is pregnant! Did you know that? Pregnant! Enriched with the Hollywood sperm of her husband George, Clooney is currently in the process of growing not one but two – two! – babies. And she is “blossoming”, says the Sun. Also, she wore yellow, which is a “brave colour” in which to “show off” her bump (the Mirror). Brave Amal Clooney. But also, oh dear, reckless Amal Clooney, because what has she got on her feet? Heels. Not one, not two, not three, but four inch heels. “Towering heels”, in fact, the Daily Mail reports. As we all know this is a very unwise thing for a pregnant woman...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Amal Clooney urges world to stop Islamic State's genocide in Iraq - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/03/10/amal-clooney-urges-world-stop-islamic-states-genocide-iraq/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK59U1PR0-m8wj-2lmdOh3cqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 05:27:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/03/10/amal-clooney-urges-world-stop-islamic-states-genocide-iraq/" target="_blank"&gt;Amal Clooney urges world to stop Islamic State's genocide in Iraq&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human rights lawyer Amal Clooney urged Iraq and the world's nations on Thursday not to let the Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant "get away with genocide". The wife of actor George Clooney, who represents victims of Isil rapes and kidnappings, told a UN meeting that what's "shocking" is not just the extremist group's brutality but the "passive" response by the world's nations to the campaign to investigate its crimes and bring the perpetrators to justice. She urged Haider al-Abadi, Iraq's Prime Minister, to send a letter to the UN Security Council so it can vote to set up an investigation...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Amal Clooney told the UN they did nothing to help Isis sex slaves. Now she's asking women to help instead - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/people/amal-clooney-nadia-murad-escaped-isis-yazidi-sex-slave-a7421576.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2I76cUwG4RNZnyCYhMtHIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 17:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/people/amal-clooney-nadia-murad-escaped-isis-yazidi-sex-slave-a7421576.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amal Clooney told the UN they did nothing to help Isis sex slaves. Now she's asking women to help instead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After appearing before the United Nations for the first time and telling delegates she was “ashamed” to stand before them while they did nothing to prevent the rape and abuse of Yazidi women, Amal Clooney stood before a conference of women and urged them to join the fight for women’s rights in countries where they are most under threat. The renowned human rights lawyer gave the keynote speech at the Texas Conference for Women on Tuesday, where more than 100 leading women from different sectors also delivered talks. In September, Clooney condemned world leaders for their inaction over the pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Yazidi Women Accept Sakharov Prize - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/yazidi-women-accept-sakharov-prize/3634170.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJedHG8oMd6hS1JrnabVveUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 12:30:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/yazidi-women-accept-sakharov-prize/3634170.html" target="_blank"&gt;Yazidi Women Accept Sakharov Prize&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two Yazidi women who were abducted by Islamic State militants in 2014 and used as sex slaves have accepted the European Parliament's Sakharov Prize for freedom of thought and expression. Nadia Murad and Lamiya Aji Bashar were announced as the recipients in October and were given the prize Tuesday during a ceremony in Strasbourg, France. The two women are among as many as 7,000 thousand Yazidi women and girls who have been kidnapped and sold as sex slaves under Islamic State rule. Another 5,000 people were killed in an attempt to wipe out the religious sect. They were taken from their villag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>UNICEF USA BrandVoice: Nadia Murad Is Speaking Up Victims of Sexual War Crimes - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2018/11/16/nadia-murad-is-speaking-up-victims-of-sexual-war-crimes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOWkk4DHkJptyNqwDWc1zVkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 23:11:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2018/11/16/nadia-murad-is-speaking-up-victims-of-sexual-war-crimes/" target="_blank"&gt;UNICEF USA BrandVoice: Nadia Murad Is Speaking Up Victims of Sexual War Crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On November 10th, “On Her Shoulders” premiered at America’s largest documentary festival, DOC NYC. Following 23-year-old Nadia Murad’s journey from a survivor of the 2014 Yazidi genocide by ISIS to a harrowing global voice against human rights violations, “On Her Shoulders” puts a face to the atrocities of war crimes. [id=0] Since 2015, Murad has been on a mission to bring ISIS before the International Criminal Court on charges of genocide and crimes against humanity. Her activism has brought her to global acclaim. In 2016, she was named the UN’s first Goodwill Ambassador for the Dignity of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sexual violence is a widespread weapon of war – it's time international law caught up - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/politics/sexual-violence-women-war-feminism-gender-isis-yazidi-boko-haram-nobel-peace-prize-a8595736.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMCMGQGnWIly80l4SxmI4mIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 15:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/politics/sexual-violence-women-war-feminism-gender-isis-yazidi-boko-haram-nobel-peace-prize-a8595736.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sexual violence is a widespread weapon of war – it's time international law caught up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decision to award the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize to Nadia Murad and Denis Mukwege – two campaigners against sexual violence in war – has rightly been hailed as a much-needed signal that the international community recognises the severity of this problem in an increasingly conflict-ridden world. Violence against women has been a topic engaging feminist legal scholars and international lawyers for a long time. A sustained feminist advocacy emerged around widespread reports of sexual violence experienced by women during the armed conflicts in the former Yugoslavia and Rwanda in the early 1990s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>France pledges to take in 100 Yazidi women after appeal from Nobel-winning activist Nadia Murad - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/france-yazidi-women-iraq-asylum-isis-macron-nadia-murad-nobel-prize-a8602571.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFDBG7ozmvQj6NN0uL4uR8kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 11:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/france-yazidi-women-iraq-asylum-isis-macron-nadia-murad-nobel-prize-a8602571.html" target="_blank"&gt;France pledges to take in 100 Yazidi women after appeal from Nobel-winning activist Nadia Murad&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France has pledged to take in 100 Yazidi women who have suffered at the hands of Isis and are living in Internally Displaced Persons camps in Iraq. French President Emmanuel Macron agreed to accept the women after meeting with 2018 Nobel Peace Prize winner Nadia Murad, a Yazidi human trafficking victim who campaigns to end sexual violence as a weapon of war. Ms Murad presented the premier with a report by the International Federation for Human Rights (FIDH) that said the campaign of violence against the Yazidi people in Iraq, which involved the mass enslavement of women and children, amount...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Report: Foreign fighters led IS atrocities against Yazidis - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/87a9984614c94627a0784ff9fae4389a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI7_WwZ0ztMckKyPMxU5ISwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 11:23:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/87a9984614c94627a0784ff9fae4389a" target="_blank"&gt;Report: Foreign fighters led IS atrocities against Yazidis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PARIS (AP) — Foreign fighters, including many Europeans, took a leading role in carrying out the Islamic State group's atrocities against minority Yazidis, an international human rights group said Thursday, citing testimony and documentation from survivors of an organized system of killing and enslavement. In a report, the Paris-based International Federation for Human Rights emphasized how foreign fighters led organized rape and slavery devised by the Islamic State group's Iraqi hierarchy. It said the actions amounted to genocide and crimes against humanity, and called for the extremist gr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>France to Take in 100 Yazidi Women Stranded in Iraqi Kurdistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/france-to-take-in-100-yazidi-women-stranded-in-iraqi-kurdistan/4629397.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKmYzXPvdpmll3pbomR7WnsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 20:23:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/france-to-take-in-100-yazidi-women-stranded-in-iraqi-kurdistan/4629397.html" target="_blank"&gt;France to Take in 100 Yazidi Women Stranded in Iraqi Kurdistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron has pledged to bring to France 100 Yazidi women who were victims of assault by Islamic State fighters in northern Iraq beginning in 2014, his office said Thursday. Macron's offer came after a meeting in Paris with Nadia Murad, who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize this month for her campaign to end sexual violence as a weapon of war. Murad was one of thousands of Yazidi women captured by IS jihadists before they were driven out of Sinjar and other parts of Iraq, starting with campaigns by Kurdish forces backed by US-led coalition forces. Macron said that in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Iraqi minority shuns children born of IS rape, enslavement - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/7b9a8ff33b8c40c38deb9f210408608d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDhS2kwct0FRE6QxGOo3xkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 20:38:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/7b9a8ff33b8c40c38deb9f210408608d" target="_blank"&gt;Iraqi minority shuns children born of IS rape, enslavement&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAHUK, Iraq (AP) — The 26-year-old Yazidi mother faces a heartbreaking choice. Her family is preparing to emigrate from Iraq to Australia and start a new life after the suffering the Islamic State group wreaked on their small religious minority. She is desperate to go with them, but there is also someone she can't bear to leave behind: Her 2-year-old daughter, Maria, fathered by the IS fighter who enslaved her. She knows her family will never allow her to bring Maria. They don't even know the girl exists. The only relative who knows is an uncle who took the girl from her mother and put her ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Nobel Peace Prize Winner Wants IS Jihadists to Face Trial - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/nobel-peace-prize-winner-wants-islamic-state-jihadists-to-face-trial/4605390.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECjifmMeSBA73Q2-ZbAtc_wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:42:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/nobel-peace-prize-winner-wants-islamic-state-jihadists-to-face-trial/4605390.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nobel Peace Prize Winner Wants IS Jihadists to Face Trial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobel Peace Prize winner Nadia Murad wants to see members of the Islamic State jihadist group face justice — not death, but trial in a courtroom, she said Monday. Murad was one of thousands of young women from the Yazidi religious minority who were kidnapped by IS in Iraq four years ago and held in sexual slavery, but was able to escape. Older women and men faced summary execution during the IS assault on the Yazidis, which the United Nations has described as a genocide. "For me, justice doesn't mean killing all of the Daesh members who committed these crimes against us," she said at the Na...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Nobel Peace winner Murad urges global fight against genocide - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/79e6964e52b34b17805a1a1222b4068e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8tUxx5KHqjQtOXvpAFaCEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 18:57:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/79e6964e52b34b17805a1a1222b4068e" target="_blank"&gt;Nobel Peace winner Murad urges global fight against genocide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A co-winner of this year's Nobel Peace Prize called Monday for a global fight against genocide and sexual violence, pledging to be a voice for victims around the world. Iraqi Nadia Murad said in her first news conference since accepting the award that she feels obligated to use her voice to defend the rights of persecuted people around the world. "We must work together to put an end to genocide, hold accountable those who commit these crimes and achieve justice for the victims," Murad told a packed room at the National Press Club. The 25-year-old Murad was among thousands ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>I was an Isis sex slave. I tell my story because it is the best weapon I have - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/06/nadia-murad-isis-sex-slave-nobel-peace-prize</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEfUKg_s5G3UV3YJrNYGu4YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 06:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/oct/06/nadia-murad-isis-sex-slave-nobel-peace-prize" target="_blank"&gt;I was an Isis sex slave. I tell my story because it is the best weapon I have&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The slave market opened at night. We could hear the commotion downstairs where militants were registering and organising, and when the first man entered the room, all the girls started screaming. It was like the scene of an explosion. We moaned as though wounded, doubling over and vomiting on the floor, but none of it stopped the militants. They paced around the room, staring at us, while we screamed and begged. They gravitated toward the most beautiful girls first, asking, “How old are you?” and examining their hair and mouths. “They are virgins, right?” they asked a guard, who nodded and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Yazidi Community Reacts to Nadia Murad's Nobel Prize - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/yazidi-community-reacts-to-nadia-murad-s-nobel-prize-/4601853.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDipAan4yz0ALbA6Wa44j2AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 21:07:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/yazidi-community-reacts-to-nadia-murad-s-nobel-prize-/4601853.html" target="_blank"&gt;Yazidi Community Reacts to Nadia Murad's Nobel Prize&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Yazidi community in Iraq and around the world expressed joy and hope after the Norwegian Nobel Committee awarded its 2018 Peace Prize to Nadia Murad, a Yazidi activist and survivor of sexual slavery by the Islamic State (IS) in Iraq. Murad will be sharing the prize with Dr. Denis Mukwege, a Congolese gynecologist who treated thousands of women victims of rape and sexual violence. The Nobel Peace Committee praised Murad's courage because she did not accept the social codes that require women to remain silent and shamed after abuse. "She has shown uncommon courage in recounting her own s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Nadia Murad, from ISIS sex slave to global human rights campaigner - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/05/middleeast/nadia-murad-nobel-peace-prize-2018-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELU68eyMUKVHtQZLKVb0Z9IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 13:09:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/05/middleeast/nadia-murad-nobel-peace-prize-2018-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nadia Murad, from ISIS sex slave to global human rights campaigner&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nadia Murad, joint winner of the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize, is a Yazidi human rights activist and survivor of sexual slavery at the hands of ISIS in Iraq. She has used her traumatic experience -- kidnapped, enslaved and raped by ISIS fighters in Mosul in 2014 -- to become an advocate for the Yazidi minority in Iraq and for the wider issues of refugees' and women's rights. Her ordeal began in 2014 after ISIS militants arrived at her village of Kocho in Iraqi Kurdistan. Her mother and six of her nine brothers and step-brothers were executed, while many of the unmarried women in the village were ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Nadia Murad carries the fight for traumatised Yazidis - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/05/nadia-murad-carries-the-fight-for-traumatised-yazidis-nobel-prize</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEByOqlanLiVL3MCCqHj5T0sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 11:15:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/05/nadia-murad-carries-the-fight-for-traumatised-yazidis-nobel-prize" target="_blank"&gt;Nadia Murad carries the fight for traumatised Yazidis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a child, Nadia Murad Basee wanted to be a teacher or open a beauty salon, but as she reached the cusp of adulthood Isis swept into her small Iraqi village, and destroyed her world, her family and her dreams. She was captured in August 2014 and sold into sexual slavery, targeted because her family belonged to the minority Yazidi religion. Repeatedly raped and repeatedly sold on, she endured months of torture until one captor left a door unlocked. She gambled her life on an escape bid, and made it to safety. Related: Nobel peace prize 2018 won by Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad - live update...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Nadia Murad: Nobel Peace Prize-winning sex slavery survivor who took on Isis - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/nadia-murad-nobel-peace-prize-winners-sex-slave-isis-amal-clooney-islam-a8570661.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOGN9b1RAqSMW5_VtZFeti0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/nadia-murad-nobel-peace-prize-winners-sex-slave-isis-amal-clooney-islam-a8570661.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nadia Murad: Nobel Peace Prize-winning sex slavery survivor who took on Isis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nadia Murad never had any ambitions to become a global rights campaigner, nor to work with Amal Clooney, let alone win a Nobel prize. But, growing up, she was not to know how her life would be terrifyingly turned upside down in 2014, as Isis terrorists would take her and other Yazidi women and imprison them as sex slaves. Four years ago, when she was 21, she lived with her mother, her brothers, their wives and children in Kocho, northern Iraq. She worked on a farm and went to school, where she had just passed the eleventh grade. And then Isis fighters arrived. Murad and other young women we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Lawyer Clooney says client's Nobel sends message - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f6d1084cd6e0420f853aab7031be5ab6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPLRZ6xsxy3HRBedZ3ElDCcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 20:34:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f6d1084cd6e0420f853aab7031be5ab6" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Lawyer Clooney says client's Nobel sends message&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OSLO, Norway (AP) — The Latest on the awarding of the Nobel Prizes (all times local): 10:15 p.m. Human rights lawyer Amal Clooney says the Nobel Peace Prize awarded to her client Nadia Murad "sends a message that survivors of sexual violence must not be ignored, and that their abusers must be held to account." Clooney said in a statement after Murad was named co-winner of the prestigious prize Friday that "at a time when so many women's voices are still silenced, Nadia's has been heard around the world." The 25-year-old Murad was recognized for her activism on behalf of fellow Yazidi women ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Denis Mukwege, Nadia Murad awarded 2018 Nobel Peace Prize - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/denis-mukwege-nadia-murad-awarded-2018-nobel-peace-prize-181005065640760.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENFPQSwxQeBKAEf0I6vrFLoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 16:50:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/denis-mukwege-nadia-murad-awarded-2018-nobel-peace-prize-181005065640760.html" target="_blank"&gt;Denis Mukwege, Nadia Murad awarded 2018 Nobel Peace Prize&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denis Mukwege, a gynaecologist treating victims of sexual violence in the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC), and Yazidi human rights activist Nadia Murad have been awarded the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize. The pair received the award for their "effort to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war and armed conflict", Berit Reiss-Andersen, chair of the Nobel Committee, announced at a press conference in the Norwegian capital, Oslo, on Friday. "Both laureates have made a crucial contribution to focusing attention on and combatting such war crimes," said Reiss-Andersen. "Denis Mukwege is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>2018 Nobel Peace Prize Recognizes Warriors Against Sexual Violence - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/congolese-mukwege-iraq-s-murad-win-2018-nobel-peace-prize/4600914.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEALW3mACih34UhiOv6Xhf9cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 09:14:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/congolese-mukwege-iraq-s-murad-win-2018-nobel-peace-prize/4600914.html" target="_blank"&gt;2018 Nobel Peace Prize Recognizes Warriors Against Sexual Violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2018 Nobel Peace Prize has been awarded to Nadia Murad, a Yazidi human rights activist and survivor of sexual slavery by Islamic State in Iraq, and Denis Mukwege, a gynecologist treating victims of sexual violence in the Democratic Republic of Congo. The Norwegian Nobel Committee said in a statement Friday that the award recognizes "their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war and armed conflict.'' Murad, 25, is the founder of Nadia's Initiative, an organization devoted to helping women victimized by genocide and other atrocities. FILE - Former Islamic State captiv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Nobel Peace Prize awarded to anti-sexual violence campaigners Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nobel-peace-prize-awarded-to-anti-sexual-violence-campaigners-denis-mukwege-and-nadia-murad-2018-10-05-61031726</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELe1j6Ei7Ojlj5v4EAuMBu8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 10:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nobel-peace-prize-awarded-to-anti-sexual-violence-campaigners-denis-mukwege-and-nadia-murad-2018-10-05-61031726" target="_blank"&gt;Nobel Peace Prize awarded to anti-sexual violence campaigners Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WALL STREET JOURNAL By Isabel Coles, Gabriele Steinhauser Congolese gynaecologist Denis Mukwege, left, and Nadia Murad, who were awarded the Nobel Peace Prize on Friday. Reuters The Nobel Peace Prize was awarded Friday to Congolese doctor Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad, a former captive of Islamic State, for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence in war. Nadia Murad has campaigned for justice for Iraq’s Yazidi minority, which was subjected to a genocidal campaign, including the use of rape as a military strategy by Islamic State militants. Murad was kidnapped and enslaved by Isl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Nobel peace prize goes to campaigners against sexual violence - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/05/denis-mukwege-nadia-murad-nobel-peace-prize-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFIJJuzRJaiY5JDI284bvasqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 11:09:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/05/denis-mukwege-nadia-murad-nobel-peace-prize-2018" target="_blank"&gt;Nobel peace prize goes to campaigners against sexual violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two leaders of the struggle against sexual violence in war have won this year’s Nobel peace prize, a choice that will hearten campaigners fighting for greater recognition of a grave but long-neglected problem, and may also bring hope to victims worldwide that their suffering has at last been recognised. The Norwegian Nobel committee said that Denis Mukwege, a doctor in the Democratic Republic of the Congo, and Nadia Murad, a 25-year-old Yazidi activist, had been awarded the prize “for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war and armed conflict”. Mukwege, 63, has sp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Murad says sexual violence victims should be heard - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/10/08/murad-says-sexual-violence-victims-shoul?videoId=471495398</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECJwN6mOGSwtYffeEpp883EqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 16:39:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/10/08/murad-says-sexual-violence-victims-shoul?videoId=471495398" target="_blank"&gt;Murad says sexual violence victims should be heard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobel Peace Prize winner Nadia Murad says she hopes the #MeToo movement will provide all victims of sexual violence a platform to be heard. Rough Cut (no reporter narration).&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nobel Peace laureates demand end to sexual violence in war - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/5b21d8cde03c4ac9a7c40e728d51724b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0PcniyiVe-VE15TJ5Wf6cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 21:28:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/5b21d8cde03c4ac9a7c40e728d51724b" target="_blank"&gt;Nobel Peace laureates demand end to sexual violence in war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OSLO, Norway (AP) — Raped after being forced into sexual slavery by the Islamic State group, Nadia Murad did not succumb to shame or despair — the young Iraqi woman spoke out. Surgeon Denis Mukwege treated countless victims of sexual violence in war-torn Congo and told the world of their suffering. Together, they were awarded the Nobel Peace Prize on Friday for their campaigns to end rape and sexual abuse as weapons of war. The award "is partly to highlight the awareness of sexual violence. But the further purpose of this is that nations take responsibility, that communities take responsibi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Yazidi activist Nadia Murad on receiving the Nobel Peace Prize - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nobel-prize-peace-murad-statement/yazidi-activist-nadia-murad-on-receiving-the-nobel-peace-prize-idUSKCN1MF1XE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPg2qX2NRQXfZDsCEgWE5s0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 15:08:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nobel-prize-peace-murad-statement/yazidi-activist-nadia-murad-on-receiving-the-nobel-peace-prize-idUSKCN1MF1XE" target="_blank"&gt;Yazidi activist Nadia Murad on receiving the Nobel Peace Prize&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following is the statement by Nobel Peace Prize laureate Nadia Murad on receiving the award. This morning the Nobel Committee informed me that I was selected as a co-recipient of the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize. I am incredibly honored and humbled by their support and I share this award with all Yazidis with all the Iraqis, Kurds and all the minorities and all survivors of sexual violence around the world. As a survivor, I am grateful for this opportunity to draw international attention to the plight of the Yazidi people who have suffered unimaginable crimes since the genocide by Daesh, which be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nobel Peace Prize award to Congolese Mukwege, Iraq's Murad - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nobel-prize-peace-fulltext/nobel-peace-prize-award-to-congolese-mukwege-iraqs-murad-idUSKCN1MF13D</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGDC_1okRrwT5qY3cMkHoX8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 12:11:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nobel-prize-peace-fulltext/nobel-peace-prize-award-to-congolese-mukwege-iraqs-murad-idUSKCN1MF13D" target="_blank"&gt;Nobel Peace Prize award to Congolese Mukwege, Iraq's Murad&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following is the text of the Nobel Peace Prize award for 2018 on Friday to Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad: The Norwegian Nobel Committee has decided to award the Nobel Peace Prize for 2018 to Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war and armed conflict. Both laureates have made a crucial contribution to focusing attention on, and combating, such war crimes. Denis Mukwege is the helper who has devoted his life to defending these victims. Nadia Murad is the witness who tells of the abuses perpetrated against herself and others. Each of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nobel Peace Prize: Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad win 2018 award beating Donald Trump and Kim Jong-un - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/politics/nobel-peace-prize-2018-win-denis-mukwege-nadia-murad-winner-yazidi-congo-sexual-violence-trump-kim-a8569766.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChSjqcVFxsFvtm9wJy9jcAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 08:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/politics/nobel-peace-prize-2018-win-denis-mukwege-nadia-murad-winner-yazidi-congo-sexual-violence-trump-kim-a8569766.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nobel Peace Prize: Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad win 2018 award beating Donald Trump and Kim Jong-un&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congolese doctor Denis Mukwege and Yazidi campaigner Nadia Murad have won the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize. The pair were awarded the honour "for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war and armed conflict." Dr Mukwege, a gynaecologist, has treated thousands of victims of sexual assault in Congo despite threats to his life. Ms Murad, 25, was kidnapped and taken as a sex slave by Islamic State militants in 2014 and two years later became the first UN goodwill ambassador for survivors of human trafficking. Her fight to bring the terror group to account for war crimes is su...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Reactions to Nobel Peace Prize award for combating sexual violence - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nobel-prize-peace-reaction/reactions-to-nobel-peace-prize-award-for-combating-sexual-violence-idUSKCN1MF1HK</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHiCg8VgZ7kzTAScssegQtkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 12:49:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nobel-prize-peace-reaction/reactions-to-nobel-peace-prize-award-for-combating-sexual-violence-idUSKCN1MF1HK" target="_blank"&gt;Reactions to Nobel Peace Prize award for combating sexual violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following are reactions to Friday's award of the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize to Congolese doctor Denis Mukwege and Yazidi rights activist Nadia Murad for their work to end the use of sexual violence in war. UNITED NATIONS HIGH COMMISSIONER FOR HUMAN RIGHTS MICHELLE BACHELET: "It is hard to imagine two more worthy winners of the Nobel Peace Prize than Nadia Murad and Denis Mukwege. This is richly deserved recognition of these two extraordinarily brave, persistent and effective campaigners against the scourge of sexual violence, and the use of rape as a weapon of war. Nadia and Denis, I'm sure I s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nobel Peace Prize awarded for efforts to end sexual violence in war - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-05/nobel-peace-prize-awarded-for-efforts-to-end-sexual-violence-war/10344706</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGnOrRwzH6910F2_g5ePbVQqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 09:03:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-05/nobel-peace-prize-awarded-for-efforts-to-end-sexual-violence-war/10344706" target="_blank"&gt;Nobel Peace Prize awarded for efforts to end sexual violence in war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physician Denis Mukwege and former captive of the Islamic State (IS) group Nadia Murad have won the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war. Gynaecologist Dr Mukwege has spent large parts of his adult life helping thousands of victims of such violence in the Democratic Republic of Congo, which the United Nations has called "the rape capital of the world". "The importance of Dr Mukwege's enduring, dedicated and selfless efforts in this field cannot be overstated," the Nobel committee said. "He has repeatedly condemned impunity for mass ra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Nobel Peace Prize 2018 goes to Yazidi activist and Congolese gynaecologist - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/05/yazidi-activist-congolese-gynecologist-awarded-nobel-peace-prize/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBkgtII8yGOSOVys2LGLEa0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 09:27:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/05/yazidi-activist-congolese-gynecologist-awarded-nobel-peace-prize/" target="_blank"&gt;Nobel Peace Prize 2018 goes to Yazidi activist and Congolese gynaecologist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nadia Murad, a Yazidi human rights activist and survivor of sexual slavery by Islamic State in Iraq, and Denis Mukwege, a gynaecologist treating victims of sexual violence in the Democratic Republic of Congo, have jointly won the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize. The Norwegian Nobel Committee said it had awarded them the prize for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war. "Both laureates have made a crucial contribution to focusing attention on, and combating, such war crimes," it said in its citation. Ms Murad is an advocate for the Yazidi minority in Iraq and for refugee a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad win Nobel Peace Prize for fight against sexual violence - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/10/05/europe/nobel-peace-prize-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJcI1Mo8t1tiIvFp8QAqiLQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 19:47:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/10/05/europe/nobel-peace-prize-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad win Nobel Peace Prize for fight against sexual violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2018 Nobel Peace Prize has been awarded to Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war and armed conflict. Mukwege, a gynecologist and surgeon, has long worked to treat thousands of women and girls affected by rape and sexual violence in the Democratic Republic of Congo. Murad is a Yazidi woman from the northern Iraqi town of Sinjar, who was held as a sex slave by ISIS, she told CNN in an interview last year. In 2016, at age 23, she was made a UN goodwill ambassador for the dignity of survivors of human trafficking. "Both laureate...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Congolese doctor, Yazidi activist, champions in fight against rape in war, win Nobel Peace Prize - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nobel-prize-peace/congolese-doctor-yazidi-activist-win-nobel-peace-prize-for-combating-sexual-violence-idUSKCN1MF0YB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP4XPy0UFiZzrIAxwzZzcOcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:15:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nobel-prize-peace/congolese-doctor-yazidi-activist-win-nobel-peace-prize-for-combating-sexual-violence-idUSKCN1MF0YB" target="_blank"&gt;Congolese doctor, Yazidi activist, champions in fight against rape in war, win Nobel Peace Prize&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denis Mukwege, a doctor who helps victims of sexual violence in the Democratic Republic of Congo, and Nadia Murad, a Yazidi rights activist and survivor of sexual slavery by Islamic State, won the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize on Friday. They were honored for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war, the Norwegian Nobel Committee said. "Denis Mukwege is the helper who has devoted his life to defending these victims. Nadia Murad is the witness who tells of the abuses perpetrated against herself and others," the Committee said in its citation. "Each of them in their own way...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Nobel academy does not always get it right – but this year’s peace prize recipients should be celebrated - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/editorials/nobel-peace-price-nadia-murad-denis-mukwege-a8570751.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEkawdiyrFO0q9z4PAmmj2MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 15:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/editorials/nobel-peace-price-nadia-murad-denis-mukwege-a8570751.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Nobel academy does not always get it right – but this year’s peace prize recipients should be celebrated&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There could be no more worthy winners of the Nobel Peace Prize than Nadia Murad and Denis Mukwege. In an age when rape has been used a systematic weapon of war, it is especially fitting that the honour has gone to two such indefatigable campaigners against rape in warfare. Ms Murad is herself a victim of such barbarity, having been tortured as a sex slave by Isis for three months before she managed to escape, probably saving her life in the process. Such is her bravery and singular spirit that she volunteered to tell her story to the BBC without the cover of anonymity. She has nothing to be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>2018 Nobel Peace Prize goes to duo for their work against sexual violence - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90247111/2018-nobel-peace-prize-goes-to-duo-for-their-work-against-sexual-violence</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOMmUbihWMB1wqUuZluyPocqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 06:06:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90247111/2018-nobel-peace-prize-goes-to-duo-for-their-work-against-sexual-violence" target="_blank"&gt;2018 Nobel Peace Prize goes to duo for their work against sexual violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Norwegian Nobel Committee has announced that the Nobel Peace Prize for 2018 has been awarded to Nadia Murad and Denis Mukwege “for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war and armed conflict.” BREAKING NEWS: The Norwegian Nobel Committee has decided to award the Nobel Peace Prize for 2018 to Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war and armed conflict. #NobelPrize #NobelPeacePrize pic.twitter.com/LaICSbQXWM — The Nobel Prize (@NobelPrize) October 5, 2018 Watch the moment the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize is an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Ceaseless persecution marks the Yazidis' history - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/53268dc1b43f48cbb18a29e8e0cad081</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHWnEqB1mFxSJBbrb2IaVzwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 16:14:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/53268dc1b43f48cbb18a29e8e0cad081" target="_blank"&gt;Ceaseless persecution marks the Yazidis' history&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Over the past centuries, the Yazidi community, one of Iraq's oldest religious minorities, has repeatedly been subjected to brutal attacks leaving thousands of its members dead. One of their worst subjugations occurred four years ago with the rise of the extremist Islamic State group. IS committed genocide and other crimes against the Yazidi minority in Iraq as their power in the country peaked in the summer of 2014. Hundreds of Yazidi women were captured, taken as sex slaves and subjected to horrific abuse by the extremists. Some managed to flee, including newly laurelled Nobe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Anti-sexual violence activists win Nobel prize - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/10/05/nobel-peace-prize-mukwege-murad-winner-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECx9Bu8mwgmalRF7HoXoGOUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 09:48:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/10/05/nobel-peace-prize-mukwege-murad-winner-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Anti-sexual violence activists win Nobel prize&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2018 Nobel Peace Prize has been awarded to Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad for their efforts to end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war and armed conflict. CNN's David McKenzie reports ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Peace Prize goes to duo battling sexual violence - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/10/05/peace-prize-goes-to-duo-battling-sexual?videoId=470488244</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDrfbrlDXBb6ujKw0VSrLgkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 13:09:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/10/05/peace-prize-goes-to-duo-battling-sexual?videoId=470488244" target="_blank"&gt;Peace Prize goes to duo battling sexual violence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denis Mukwege, a gynecologist treating victims of sexual violence in the Democratic Republic of Congo, and Nadia Murad, a Yazidi human rights activist and survivor of sexual slavery by Islamic State in Iraq, won the 2018 Nobel Peace Prize&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Nobel Peace Prize: Sexual Violence Activists Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad Win Award - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/denis-mukwege-and-nadia-murad-win-nobel-peace-prize</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_IF1a-ZX6gR2YGlo-LREMqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 09:02:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/denis-mukwege-and-nadia-murad-win-nobel-peace-prize" target="_blank"&gt;Nobel Peace Prize: Sexual Violence Activists Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad Win Award&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobel Prize, Wartime sexual violence activists Denis Mukwege and Nadia Murad have been named winners of the Nobel Peace Prize. The announcement was made at the Norwegian Nobel Institute in Oslo, Norway early Friday. The Nobel Committee said they'd chosen the winners for their efforts to “end the use of sexual violence as a weapon of war and armed conflict.” Dr. Mukwege has spent large parts of his life helping the victims of sexual violence in the Democratic Republic of Congo, treating thousands of patients who have been victims of sexual assault. Murad is one of an estimated 3,000 Yazidi g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>With a nod to #MeToo, Nobel's 2018 choice captures moment in history - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/10/05/europe/nobel-peace-prize-metoo-analysis-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPIzjPaZGM78w-QhGJ9Ws_8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 15:33:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/10/05/europe/nobel-peace-prize-metoo-analysis-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;With a nod to #MeToo, Nobel's 2018 choice captures moment in history&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The announcement of who will receive the Nobel Peace Prize is always most powerful when it taps into the global conversation of the moment. In that sense, the 2018 decision to recognize two people -- Congolese surgeon Denis Mukwege and Yazidi campaigner Nadia Murad -- for their efforts to end sexual violence as a weapon of war could not have been more apt, or better timed. The announcement landed one year to the day since the New York Times published a report on Harvey Weinstein that blew open the #MeToo movement. It also came hours after hundreds of Americans were arrested during protests ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>For Daesh Survivors The Worst Fear Becomes Reality Yet Again - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewelinaochab/2018/09/04/for-daesh-survivors-the-worst-fear-becomes-reality-yet-again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ7rxkdtvyEHaepUB383_FwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 05:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewelinaochab/2018/09/04/for-daesh-survivors-the-worst-fear-becomes-reality-yet-again/" target="_blank"&gt;For Daesh Survivors The Worst Fear Becomes Reality Yet Again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only two years ago, Nadia Murad, UN Goodwill Ambassador, expressed her deepest fear after surviving the Daesh atrocities “that once Daesh is defeated, Daesh militants will just shave off their beards and walk the streets of their cities as if nothing has happened.” Nadia Murad, UN Goodwill Ambassador and public advocate for the Yazidi community in Iraq and survivors of sexual enslavement by Daesh fighters was awarded the 2016 Sakharov Human Rights Prize, on December 13, 2016, at the European Parliament in Strasbourg. (Photo credit: FREDERICK FLORIN/AFP/Getty Images) Two years ago, this fear...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>