<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Wasim Khan - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNR05tTjNsM0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-PK&amp;gl=PK&amp;ceid=PK:en</link><language>en-PK</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:25:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>PCB appoints Wasim Khan as managing director - DAWN.com</title><link>https://www.dawn.com/news/1449836</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiIWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhd24uY29tL25ld3MvMTQ0OTgzNtIBamh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LWRhd24tY29tLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L3Mvd3d3LmRhd24uY29tL25ld3MvYW1wLzE0NDk4MzY_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:11:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.dawn.com/news/1449836" target="_blank"&gt;PCB appoints Wasim Khan as managing director&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;DAWN.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) on Thursday confirmed the appointment of Wasim Khan as its managing director. Wasim Khan, an MBA from Warwick ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWo2OUxtbWpZQU1FZTVmN1VTamJYY3FLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.dawn.com">DAWN.com</source></item><item><title>Leicestershire CEO Wasim Khan frontrunner for PCB MD role - ESPNcricinfo - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25429885/leicestershire-ceo-wasim-khan-frontrunner-pcb-md-role</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEANkPT8JLtrDoekVEAZ5fwgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 07:52:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25429885/leicestershire-ceo-wasim-khan-frontrunner-pcb-md-role" target="_blank"&gt;Leicestershire CEO Wasim Khan frontrunner for PCB MD role - ESPNcricinfo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wasim Khan has emerged as a strong candidate for the new role of Managing Director of the PCB. Wasim, currently chief executive at Leicestershire County ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Pakistan news Wasim Khan announced as PCB Managing Director 06 Dec 18 - International Cricket Council</title><link>https://www.icc-cricket.com/news/935099</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiJ2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmljYy1jcmlja2V0LmNvbS9uZXdzLzkzNTA5OdIBAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:22:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.icc-cricket.com/news/935099" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan news Wasim Khan announced as PCB Managing Director 06 Dec 18&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;International Cricket Council&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) have appointed Wasim Khan as their Managing Director.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.icc-cricket.com">International Cricket Council</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/t4llLuLI3lE4it9Ipt2ma4oCdMyNWSDZ0XZceKyTkyK_JcT72xwii6KZ_ppDt7-IwyxKvtxxo5fTFH-cCmNjBB-pqz5Mu87M8iK9hftO_MKiukPvh1XbVt0NGJQPgpGj7gBK0Ry4Z-8IL0BfI9uSjXHXY7D21KKROTlUxsFJvWr6XibXHDZLHJ0wfTTBTKFS=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Wasim Khan unveiled as PCB's new managing director - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25468383/wasim-khan-unveiled-pcb-new-managing-director</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFR9KLmsJAaERzaI8MbRQvcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:53:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25468383/wasim-khan-unveiled-pcb-new-managing-director" target="_blank"&gt;Wasim Khan unveiled as PCB's new managing director&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wasim Khan, Leicestershire's chief executive, has been unveiled as the new managing director of the Pakistan Cricket Board. Wasim, who has been one of the leading lights of the ECB's drive to engage British Asians in English cricket, forged his career as CEO of the schools' cricket charity, Chance to Shine, before taking over at Grace Road in 2014. He has been appointed to the PCB on a three-year contract, starting on February 1, following a comprehensive two-phase selection process featuring over 350 candidates. Wasim was sounded out for the role by Ehsan Mani, the former ICC chairman who ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Leicestershire turn to Ackermann - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/county-cricket-2016/content/story/1062400.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELE1yrQe3LCnfP-gbRYLnzcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 06:53:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/county-cricket-2016/content/story/1062400.html" target="_blank"&gt;Leicestershire turn to Ackermann&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leicestershire have turned to South Africa to bolster their batting strength, signing batsman Colin Ackermann on a two-year contract. The signing will encourage the belief that English counties are eager to raid South Africa for players who suspect their chances of progression may be limited in their own country because of stiffened transformation policies. Ackermann, a former South Africa U-19 international, will qualify as a non-overseas player. He has a first-class record approaching 40, the latest of seven hundreds coming for Warriors against Titans last week. He also has 10 half-centur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Leicestershire calm the financial storm - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/county-cricket-2017/content/story/1080267.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOzQh7wvNZ7VFlVh-YhcoTMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 14:10:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/county-cricket-2017/content/story/1080267.html" target="_blank"&gt;Leicestershire calm the financial storm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leicestershire have emerged from a troubled financial period to announce a net profit for the second year in a row. They returned a net profit of £8,813 for the year ended September 30, 2016, following another small profit of £4,315 the previous year. This follows cumulative losses of more than £500,000 in the previous three years. Total income reached a record £4.2m in 2016, with commercial revenue streams increasing overall by 35% to £1.465m - almost double the commercial return three years ago. Leicestershire hosted a profitable Elton John concert and an exclusive evening with Lord Mervy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Carberry in, McKay out at Leicestershire - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/20781924/michael-carberry-clint-mckay-leicestershire</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIk3ugSoqOxyiwXeNe4_aMgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 16:46:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/20781924/michael-carberry-clint-mckay-leicestershire" target="_blank"&gt;Carberry in, McKay out at Leicestershire&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carberry, the former England opener, joined the club from Hampshire on loan in August, with a brief return to the Hampshire side on T20 Finals Day. While he has not enjoyed an especially prolific start to life with Leicestershire - he has scored 42 runs in six innings with five single-figures scores and a high of 18 - he is seen as the experienced figure the side requires at the top of the order as they once again seek to rebuild after a disappointing season. "We have been looking to add an experienced opener to our squad and Michael fits the bill for us," Wasim Khan, the Leicestershire chi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Leicestershire welcome cricketer jail term after assault case is reopened - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/ci/content/story/1090146.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOEeBOkzlEXw-KL2P7uwRAUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 22:31:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/ci/content/story/1090146.html" target="_blank"&gt;Leicestershire welcome cricketer jail term after assault case is reopened&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A club cricketer has been jailed for 18 months for assault, following a review of his original sentence, after Leicestershire intervened to stress that he was not negotiating a contract with the county. Mustafa Bashir, 34, a local league cricketer from Oldham, received a suspended sentence at Manchester Crown Court in March for assault against his wife. The judge, Richard Mansell QC, did not impose a custodial term after hearing that he would lose a professional cricket contract if he were jailed. After the hearing, Leicestershire CCC accused Bashir of "inventing" the job offer "in order, i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Wife-beater spared jail as he 'would lose cricket contract' faces sentence review after club said claim was 'false' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/05/wife-beater-spared-jail-would-losecricket-contract-faces-sentence/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFJ1hg3NTtfBv9lgh9fnj-sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 10:49:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/05/wife-beater-spared-jail-would-losecricket-contract-faces-sentence/" target="_blank"&gt;Wife-beater spared jail as he 'would lose cricket contract' faces sentence review after club said claim was 'false'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man spared jail for beating his wife after telling a court he would lose an offer to play professional cricket is to have his sentence reviewed. Mustafa Bashir, 34, was given a suspended sentence at Manchester Crown Court for assaulting Fakhara Karim. Judge Richard Mansell QC has been heavily criticised by domestic abuse campaigners after he reportedly said Miss Karim was not vulnerable because she was a graduate. And the judge was told that if Bashir was spared custody he would be employed as a professional player by Leicestershire County Cricket Club. But the club later said this claim ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>De Bruyn quits as Leicestershire coach amid unrest - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/county-cricket-2017/content/story/1119281.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECEERkcnYIgGS_GEjYW_ZhQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 21:40:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/county-cricket-2017/content/story/1119281.html" target="_blank"&gt;De Bruyn quits as Leicestershire coach amid unrest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pierre de Bruyn has left his role as Leicestershire's head coach with immediate effect after tensions in the dressing became too much to resolve. He had been named in the role a year ago and began last October as Andrew McDonald's replacement. Leicestershire reached the quarter-finals of the NatWest T20 Blast this season but are currently bottom of Division Two in the County Championship without a victory and did not make it out of the group stage of the Royal London Cup. Graeme Welch and John Sadler will take charge of the first team until the end of the season. Welch might also be in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>England assistant Paul Farbrace linked with Hampshire vacancy - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25193136/england-assistant-paul-farbrace-linked-hampshire-vacancy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtp9kSmDUh1GMnzAXRT5ygqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 18:52:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25193136/england-assistant-paul-farbrace-linked-hampshire-vacancy" target="_blank"&gt;England assistant Paul Farbrace linked with Hampshire vacancy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;England could face upheaval ahead of the World Cup with news that Paul Farbrace is a candidate for another coaching job. Farbrace, England's assistant coach and a key figure in their limited-overs revival, is understood to have had talks with Hampshire in connection with the role recently vacated by Craig White. While Farbrace is far from certain to be offered, or to accept, the role, the fact that he is considering other opportunities at this stage underlines the uncertainty around the England camp. With Trevor Bayliss, England's head coach, stepping down from his role at the end of the 20...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>ECB announce domestic season rejig for 2020 onwards - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25133680/ecb-announce-domestic-season-rejig-2020-onwards</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJArem5B2P4zrOs2sJggbUYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 21:06:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/25133680/ecb-announce-domestic-season-rejig-2020-onwards" target="_blank"&gt;ECB announce domestic season rejig for 2020 onwards&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ECB's new city-based competition will take place at the same time as county cricket's existing 50-over tournament, after a review of the domestic schedule from 2020 onwards was ratified by the 18 first-class counties. In addition, three counties will be promoted to Division One of the County Championship in 2019, with one relegated, ahead of a new-look first-class structure which will feature ten teams in the top flight, eight in Division Two, and a new "seeding system" to enable a limit of 14 matches per season. The Men's Domestic Playing Programme group (MDPP), chaired by Leicestershi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>County Championship to be restructured with 10-team first division from 2020 - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/10/31/county-championship-restructured-10-team-first-division-2020/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFnz3VNXAdl7yFZiBJzCcEQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCe8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 16:48:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/cricket/2018/10/31/county-championship-restructured-10-team-first-division-2020/" target="_blank"&gt;County Championship to be restructured with 10-team first division from 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;County cricket will revert to a first division of ten teams from 2020 in a bid to stop short-term decision making by coaches fearing the sack. The changes announced on Wednesday will see three teams promoted to division one next season and only one relegated to enable the switch to a ten team first division and eight in the second. The championship schedule will continue to feature 14 matches and a seeding system will be introduced to decide who plays who twice in a season given ten teams will play 14 matches. The summer of 2020 will include the biggest shake up of domestic cricket in this ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Two-divisional Championship promotes 'short-termism' - Wasim Khan - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/23547061/two-divisional-championship-promotes-short-termism-wasim-khan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMLbRK3XFIDgLqKymQbB3H4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 00:23:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/23547061/two-divisional-championship-promotes-short-termism-wasim-khan" target="_blank"&gt;Two-divisional Championship promotes 'short-termism' - Wasim Khan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wasim Khan, Leicestershire's chief executive, has provided the clearest hint yet that the days of promotion and relegation in the County Championship could be coming to an end. While Wasim, chairman of the working party looking into the future shape of domestic cricket, was at pains to say no decisions had yet been made, he makes no secret of his fear that two divisions "promotes short-termism" and feels the county season starts too early to encourage good quality cricket. Wasim, who also feels counties should be better rewarded for producing England-qualified players and that it should be ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>English cricket coaching needs more diversity - Wasim Khan - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/22604703/english-cricket-coaching-needs-more-diversity-wasim-khan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPnfwWGpgfLk1zEJ2g14J38qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 05:52:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/22604703/english-cricket-coaching-needs-more-diversity-wasim-khan" target="_blank"&gt;English cricket coaching needs more diversity - Wasim Khan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wasim Khan, the chief executive of Leicestershire, has questioned whether the game in England and Wales can do more to encourage coaches and administrators from South Asian and Afro-Caribbean backgrounds. While Wasim has welcomed the appointment of Vikram Solanki and Dimitri Mascarenhas as assistant head coaches at Surrey and Essex respectively, he raised the possibility of "unconscious bias" inhibiting the progress of more non-white coaches and suggested a concerted effort should be made to improve the situation. His comments follow those of Roland Butcher, who recently described himself a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Leicestershire sign Abbas, Sohail as overseas players - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/22151393/leicestershire-sign-mohammad-abbas-sohail-khan-overseas-players</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKIZmt53hSmRATuUBsfccnYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 21:19:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/22151393/leicestershire-sign-mohammad-abbas-sohail-khan-overseas-players" target="_blank"&gt;Leicestershire sign Abbas, Sohail as overseas players&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leicestershire have made a double Pakistan pace bowler signing for the 2018 season, with Paul Nixon beginning his tenure as head coach by bringing in Mohammad Abbas and Sohail Khan to share overseas player duties. Abbas, 27, has made a good impression since his Test debut last year, taking 23 wickets at 21.34 in five matches. He will be available for Leicestershire's first Championship match, starting on April 20, and then again from mid-June - given his likely involvement with Pakistan's tour of England and Ireland during the first half of the season. Sohail, an experienced seamer who has ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item><item><title>Nixon returns to Leicestershire as head coach - ESPNCricinfo</title><link>http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/21039340/nixon-returns-leicestershire-head-coach</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDICdkqO29jeZJ473AwjOIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow7qimATDOxAowov85</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 15:04:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.espncricinfo.com/story/_/id/21039340/nixon-returns-leicestershire-head-coach" target="_blank"&gt;Nixon returns to Leicestershire as head coach&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ESPNCricinfo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nixon, twice the winning coach with Jamaica Tallawahs in the Caribbean Premier League, enjoyed a long and successful playing career with the club. He played in the County Championship winning sides of 1996 and 1998 and the T20 winning sides of 2004, 2006 and 2011. He made his Leicestershire debut in 1989 and was captain 2007 and 2008. He faces a tough task at Leicestershire, however. The club finished bottom of Division Two in the County Championship without a win with his predecessor, Pierre de Bruyn, sacked after barely a year in the role. "We are delighted that Paul has agreed to rejoin ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.espncricinfo.com">ESPNCricinfo</source></item></channel></rss>