<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Reindeer - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREV5Tm1kakVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-PK&amp;gl=PK&amp;ceid=PK:en</link><language>en-PK</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:12:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Christmas: From Scrooge to George Bailey and the Grinch, the inspiration behind our favourite festive stories - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/features/christmas-stories-scrooge-the-grinch-rudolph-reindeer-george-bailey-a8668936.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF0o1kcmMvlhfJ6NblX8U0IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/features/christmas-stories-scrooge-the-grinch-rudolph-reindeer-george-bailey-a8668936.html" target="_blank"&gt;Christmas: From Scrooge to George Bailey and the Grinch, the inspiration behind our favourite festive stories&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We cherish our favourite Christmas stories and revisit them every year, but rarely do we take a moment to consider their origins. The likes of Ebeneezer Scrooge, Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer and the Grinch are fixtures of the festive season, and the circumstances surrounding their conception are frequently fascinating. Here’s how some of our most-loved Yuletide tales were spun. ‘A Visit from St Nicholas’ (1823) More popularly known as “Twas the Night Before Christmas”, this poem by Clement Clarke Moore, a professor of Oriental and Greek Literature and Divinity in New York, did much to est...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Viewers Noticed Some Very Disturbing Details In ‘Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer’ - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer-disturbing-details_us_5bfe058fe4b0f43bf2661c7f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM69D5koKGS5F8Bb0LrAE2EqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:06:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer-disturbing-details_us_5bfe058fe4b0f43bf2661c7f" target="_blank"&gt;Viewers Noticed Some Very Disturbing Details In ‘Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer” aired Tuesday night on CBS, and Twitter users gathered around the digital fireplace to share the moment. And what a moment it was. Some people joked that they noticed a few things in the Christmas classic that they didn’t always spot ― or simply ignored ― when they saw it years ago. Here are some of those humorous observations: Every year the elf throws the bird out of the sleigh without an umbrella, even though earlier the bird said it CAN'T FLY. Every. Damn. Year. #RudolphTheRedNosedReindeer — Sarah B (@SarahB1863) November 28, 2018 Trivia Fact! Yukon Corn...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump is making the warming of Alaska even worse - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/opinions/climate-change-report-trump-administration-alaska-demientieff/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOGJJkOhMsHiNQOSSeGYnZsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:05:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/opinions/climate-change-report-trump-administration-alaska-demientieff/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump is making the warming of Alaska even worse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bernadette Demientieff is the Executive Director of the Gwich'in Steering Committee, which is dedicated to defending the coastal plain of the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge. The views expressed here are solely the author's. View more opinion articles on CNN. The latest National Climate Assessment report, released earlier this month, makes it clear how dangerous climate change is for the people of Alaska. The report highlights impacts like record-high temperatures, reduced ice cover, and threats to wildlife. Many of our Native communities already knew this, because we're living that reality...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>We went to Lapland for Father Christmas - but what unfolded proved even more magical - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/finland/articles/lapland-father-christmas-family-rovaniemi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIrKqut9IkOCgyOkR3D3LUEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/finland/articles/lapland-father-christmas-family-rovaniemi/" target="_blank"&gt;We went to Lapland for Father Christmas - but what unfolded proved even more magical&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lapland may not have featured on your own personal list of ultimates, but let me tell you – if there are small people in your life, it will feature in theirs. Just maybe not in the way you’d originally planned… It first became a “thing” in our house with the arrival of some very special post. Elf post, no less. An invitation, from the man himself. Yes, Mr Father Christmas Esq. Down the chimney (artfully singed by a match for authenticity), and personally addressed to each of the two children, Amelie, eight, and Charley, five. There was not the faintest whiff of suspicion that this might be ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The ultimate slow TV: a 168-hour show on reindeer migration - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/apr/26/slow-tv-reindeer-migration-norway-nrk-reinflytting-minutt-for-minutt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKC9oE9zUkjxO9u_SuBOK0UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 10:32:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/apr/26/slow-tv-reindeer-migration-norway-nrk-reinflytting-minutt-for-minutt" target="_blank"&gt;The ultimate slow TV: a 168-hour show on reindeer migration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;High up on a mountain plateau in Lapland there has been a tense silence for some days. A crew from the Norwegian Broadcasting Corporation (NRK) has been stuck with a herd of reindeer who are not intending to move. But move they must. Food is getting scarce and besides, their annual spring migration, towards new grazing land down at the coast 200km away, is going live on TV. Minute by minute. The transmission started on Monday night, but as the reindeer scraped through snow searching for more food, the lead female deer looked on unconcerned and immobile. The crew, less so. “We were waiting f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Santa's Shrinking Reindeer Blamed On Arctic Climate Change - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/smaller-reindeer-global-warming_us_584f4fa4e4b0bd9c3dfe70cd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEArT6_R3lqca84FhuyBVVQAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 04:44:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/smaller-reindeer-global-warming_us_584f4fa4e4b0bd9c3dfe70cd" target="_blank"&gt;Santa's Shrinking Reindeer Blamed On Arctic Climate Change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Climate change is so powerfully affecting reindeer habitat that the animals are shrinking from hunger, scientists have discovered. Over the past 20 years, reindeer in the Norwegian archipelago of Svalbard, north of the Arctic Circle, have grown smaller and lighter, researchers found. The reindeers’ average weight dropped by 12 percent — from 121 pounds for animals born in 1994 to just 106 pounds for those born in 2010, according to a study. That change may not seem like very much, “but given how important body weight is to reproduction and survival, it’s potentially huge,” lead researcher S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Herding Reindeer Isn't Just Child's Play For One Little Girl - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/reindeer-herders-mongolia_us_5852f800e4b08debb78818ca</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFj51ui8cCFBRSFD-I223doqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 22:31:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/reindeer-herders-mongolia_us_5852f800e4b08debb78818ca" target="_blank"&gt;Herding Reindeer Isn't Just Child's Play For One Little Girl&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Santa’s reindeer may work only once a year, but in real life, reindeer herding is a never-ending task. Filmmaker Joel Santos saw that firsthand when he went deep into Northern Mongolia to visit a tiny Tsaatan community, one of the few left who still pursue the ancient tradition of nomadic reindeer herding. The people of Zyyn Taiga depend on reindeer for meat, milk and cheese, as well as transportation and clothing. Reindeer hides also serve as the covering for teepees, which are heated by burning the animal’s dung, according to Barcroft TV. Zyyn Taiga’s people have access to horses, but pre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Beloved Harlem deer dies of stress after bureaucratic spat between New York City and state officials - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/harlem-deer-new-york-city-state-bill-de-blasio-andrew-cuomo-a7483076.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJe5AVhFxKakgz_k0Xai4l0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/harlem-deer-new-york-city-state-bill-de-blasio-andrew-cuomo-a7483076.html" target="_blank"&gt;Beloved Harlem deer dies of stress after bureaucratic spat between New York City and state officials&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A deer which captured the hearts of local residents has died of “stress” after a bureaucratic tussle between two branches of local government. The white tailed deer, which likely swam across New York’s East River in search of a mate, was seen for two weeks at the Jackie Robinson Park in the city. After the animal - dubbed ‘JR’ and ‘Lefty’ because of his missing antler - jumped a fence into a housing complex, he was tranquilised, captured and held in an animal sanctuary. The affair led to a spat between New York City officials and New York State’s Department of Environmental Conservation (DE...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pet deer named after Bambi character shot dead in front of US family in their driveway - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/pet-deer-shot-dead-driveway-family-faline-disney-bambi-kansas-warden-a7513606.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJI4NTwfuzfhsUMQQ2uHoOcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 20:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/pet-deer-shot-dead-driveway-family-faline-disney-bambi-kansas-warden-a7513606.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pet deer named after Bambi character shot dead in front of US family in their driveway&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A family are inconsolable after a wildlife warden came onto their land and shot their pet deer five times. A warden, flanked by two colleagues, entered the Mcgaugheys’ Kansas farm and killed the deer, called Faline, apparently just 10 minutes after handing them a warning notice stating the animal was an illegal pet. The family had looked after Faline, named after the Disney Bambi character, ever since it followed Kim Mcgaughey home. “I couldn’t believe it,” said Kim’s daughter Taryn, speaking to The Independent. “One shot to the head would have been enough but then he shot her in the leg an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>How disappearing sea ice has put Arctic ecosystem under threat - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/mar/04/arctic-ecosystem-ice-disappear-ecosystem-polar-bears-fish</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI4lPjv7YozjsG4j-TGNpKIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 15:29:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/mar/04/arctic-ecosystem-ice-disappear-ecosystem-polar-bears-fish" target="_blank"&gt;How disappearing sea ice has put Arctic ecosystem under threat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a few days the Arctic’s beleaguered sea ice cover is likely to set another grim record. Its coverage is on course to be the lowest winter maximum extent ever observed since satellite records began. These show that more than 2 million square kilometres of midwinter sea ice have disappeared from the Arctic in less than 40 years. The ice’s disappearance – triggered by global warming caused by rising carbon emissions from cars and factories – is likely to have profound implications for the planet. A loss of sea ice means a loss of reflectivity of solar rays and further rises in global temper...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Norway plans mass reindeer cull to halt spread of wasting disease - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/02/norway-plans-mass-reindeer-cull-halt-spread-wasting-disease/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOavNofAzaL1id3WJ6Vs00IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 04:08:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/02/norway-plans-mass-reindeer-cull-halt-spread-wasting-disease/" target="_blank"&gt;Norway plans mass reindeer cull to halt spread of wasting disease&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Norway is planning a mass cull of reindeer to stop the spread of Chronic Wasting Disease. Experts have said an entire herd must be killed off to prevent the disease devastating the country’s reindeer population, the Local reported. The cull which could involve several thousand animals is scheduled to take place in a mountainous region northwest of Oslo. Europe’s first case of the disease was discovered in April last year on a young caribou. Then three reindeer were found to have been suffering from the disease. Around 2,200 animals are in the Nordfjella region where the three diseased reind...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Domino's trains reindeer to deliver pizza - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/11/27/dominos-trains-reindeer-deliver-pizza/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKXGw61M-AIf-T9T548_RKIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 11:42:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/11/27/dominos-trains-reindeer-deliver-pizza/" target="_blank"&gt;Domino's trains reindeer to deliver pizza&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In possibly the most bizarre festive publicity stunt of the season, Domino's pizza is training reindeer to make deliveries. In Japan's northernmost island Hokkaido this Christmas, reindeer will be battling the cold to get pizzas to Domino's customers. Although the story sounds strange, a Domino's Japan press release given out earlier this month says the pizza company is working with reindeer breeders at the Hokkaido Delivery Integrated Research Center to train them how to deliver pizza. A full-scale rollout of reindeer will be implemented in December, according to the press release. On Thur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Domino's Is Training GPS-Equipped Reindeer To Deliver Pizza In Japan - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/dominos-pizza-reindeer-japan_us_583bd572e4b01ba68ac5074a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbxcOKKyHleBeGPCfU6VboqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 09:22:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/dominos-pizza-reindeer-japan_us_583bd572e4b01ba68ac5074a" target="_blank"&gt;Domino's Is Training GPS-Equipped Reindeer To Deliver Pizza In Japan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What if Santa brought pizza instead of toys? Domino’s seems to be trying to find out, at least in Japan, as a video released online shows the company training reindeer to deliver fresh, hot pizzas in snowy Hokkaido. The reindeer are equipped with GPS units so customers can track their pizzas ― but the footage indicates the system still needs a little more work: Domino’s said in a news release working with reindeer poses “unique challenges” but they are hoping to have the system up and running in early December. That means eventually, this could become a true Christmas miracle: The company s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Russia With Simon Reeve review – reindeer herders, endangered tigers ... and spies - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/sep/29/russia-with-simon-reeve-screw-police-we-are-doing-something-amazing</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB5-ynRICNO7ZWFmbgokuQ0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 05:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/sep/29/russia-with-simon-reeve-screw-police-we-are-doing-something-amazing" target="_blank"&gt;Russia With Simon Reeve review – reindeer herders, endangered tigers ... and spies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nice Simon Reeve is travelling across Russia. From east to west, like the sun, though that hardly makes an appearance above the horizon here in Kamchatka in early spring. Russia With Simon Reeve (BBC2) it’s called, though perhaps Russia With Simon Reeve and the FSB might have been a better title, the FSB being what used to be to be the KGB, of course. We’ll come to them. But first a spot of glamping for Simon. He’s staying in a yurt – that’s glamping, isn’t it? Except that his reindeer herder hosts, Alexei and Galina, live here, forever, and it’s -30C outside. That’s not so glam, nor much o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>World's most extreme wildlife encounters - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/travel-play/gallery/wildlife-encounters-tours/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELvCZDu0_1Y-YSJp7E0nH04qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 09:44:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/travel-play/gallery/wildlife-encounters-tours/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;World's most extreme wildlife encounters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Best wildlife encounters: Watching forest elephants up close while paddling in the wilderness of Ivindo National Park in Gabon is one of the world's most awe-inspiring wildlife encounters. Secret Compass Gabon: Floating amid dripping towering forests, deep dark braided rivers and equatorial Africa's highest waterfall in a tiny rubber paddleboat feels out-of-this-world. Reindeers in Russia: The indigenous Nenets, nomadic reindeer-herders, have started welcoming Intrepid travelers to live with them and their reindeer. The Nenets live at the edge of the Siberian Arctic, where temperatures can ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Of Course There’s An A Cappella Rudolph-Themed ‘Hamilton’ Parody - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/of-course-theres-an-a-cappella-rudolph-themed-hamilton-parody_us_58538f4ee4b039044707ff41</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBll0NIIrf7qtvKwd-G01JAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 07:36:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/of-course-theres-an-a-cappella-rudolph-themed-hamilton-parody_us_58538f4ee4b039044707ff41" target="_blank"&gt;Of Course There’s An A Cappella Rudolph-Themed ‘Hamilton’ Parody&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well this was probably inevitable, folks. An a cappella “Hamilton” parody set to the tale of “Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer” is here, just in time for Christmas. In the surprisingly clever adaptation, Rudolph is the story’s Alexander Hamilton, while Santa Claus appears as George Washington. Santa is, of course, “in dire need of assistance.” (There’s a thick fog threatening to ruin Christmas, for those who don’t remember the tale.) And Rudolph? Rudolph is not giving up his shot. Watch the rendition in the video above. You could spread some holiday cheer by sending it around to all the “Hami...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Rear ends of pantomime horses are kicking up - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/12/17/rear-ends-pantomime-horses-kicking/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKFl-E42nFsVP6cXNHxPwAEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/12/17/rear-ends-pantomime-horses-kicking/" target="_blank"&gt;Rear ends of pantomime horses are kicking up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is turning out to be the restive season. Everywhere we look there are strikes or threats of strikes. Right now, efforts are being made to resolve the dispute which has been disrupting one-horse open sleigh rides, as the Amalgamated Society of Jinglers (ASJ) resists plans to allow sleigh drivers to take on the task of jingling the bells. They say it is a safety issue, that drivers should not be distracted by jingling duties while dashing through the snow. “You wouldn’t say 'oh what fun’ if a sleigh overturned,” an ASJ spokesman told me. There is unrest among Santa’s elves. They all have...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Reindeer may ditch presents, deliver pizza - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2016/11/29/pizza-by-reindeer-pkg-moos-erin.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL7nG1rKha3-q1MJJboJTkIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 01:37:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/us/2016/11/29/pizza-by-reindeer-pkg-moos-erin.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Reindeer may ditch presents, deliver pizza&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Domino's Japan is testing a new delivery system: pizza by reindeer. CNN's Jeanne Moos reports. ©2016 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>2017 Travel Trends: Lapland With Added Thrills And Frills - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/sarahturner/2017/01/20/2017-travel-trends-lapland-with-added-thrills-and-frills/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3i_5QjYDzi9TT8TeE_HfkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/sarahturner/2017/01/20/2017-travel-trends-lapland-with-added-thrills-and-frills/" target="_blank"&gt;2017 Travel Trends: Lapland With Added Thrills And Frills&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Sapmi Nature Club Credit: Lennart Pittja Lapland is Europe’s Wild North; an experiential centre of excellence with ice driving, snowmobiles, huskies and drysuit dips within the Arctic Circle. In recent years Lapland has taken on a self-appointed role of making sub-zero temperatures serious fun. Yes, there is the draw of the Northern Lights; Prince Harry is thought to have taken girlfriend Meghan Markle to see them in Norway in January but while the aurora borealis has bucket list appeal, increasingly, it’s the accommodation options that keep people returning. The newest suite at the Tr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Polar bear numbers seen declining a third from Arctic sea ice melt - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-environment-climate-arctic-idUSKBN14205I</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJb3-iSUMpqNMJjIVxfIde4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 02:22:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-environment-climate-arctic-idUSKBN14205I" target="_blank"&gt;Polar bear numbers seen declining a third from Arctic sea ice melt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Laura Zuckerman (Reuters) - Rising temperatures that melt sea ice in the Arctic will probably reduce the polar bear population by a third over the next few decades, and the same warming trend is likely to worsen the decline of wild reindeer, scientists said on Monday. The new findings by university and government researchers were presented as part of a panel discussion about climate impacts on wildlife during a meeting of the American Geophysical Union in San Francisco. The presentation was streamed live on the internet. The polar bear research is drawn from new satellite data documentin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Appy Christmas! Jogger creates festive shapes using GPS running app - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/12/22/appy-christmas-joggercreates-festive-shapes-using-gps-running/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEB-CzfUyOTGrsvjolcXkNgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 13:47:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/12/22/appy-christmas-joggercreates-festive-shapes-using-gps-running/" target="_blank"&gt;Appy Christmas! Jogger creates festive shapes using GPS running app&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A keen jogger has used an activity-tracking app to create festive art while keeping fit by running in Christmas shapes. Owen Delaney has mapped out Father Christmas, a snowflake and a Christmas tree using running app Strava, which maps out shareable routes using GPS technology. Owen Delaney with son TomCredit: Owen Delaney / SWNS.com He first started making the images on the app when he realised the Diana Fountain in Bushy Park, near his home in Teddington, south west London, would make a good nose for Rudolph the reindeer. Mr Delaney, 40, has spent hours planning each run, some of which ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Last Look: Russia's Arctic expansion - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2017/02/05/exp-gps-0205-last-look-russia-arctic.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMtrN6l9DTwINHzyg5uKeUAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 15:47:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2017/02/05/exp-gps-0205-last-look-russia-arctic.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Last Look: Russia's Arctic expansion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fareed takes a look at a Russian military drill, complete with reindeer and huskies. What's behind their moves in the Arctic? ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Should there be stricter laws to protect Rudolph's relatives? - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-12-24/should-there-be-stricter-laws-to-protect-rudolphs-relatives/8143902</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENr27bRAbxrryWXr_Ws6lLoqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 00:26:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-12-24/should-there-be-stricter-laws-to-protect-rudolphs-relatives/8143902" target="_blank"&gt;Should there be stricter laws to protect Rudolph's relatives?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At a shopping centre in Essex in eastern England, Scrabble, Saxon, Strudel and Nok are being attached to Santa's sleigh. Dozens of children have come from around the area to watch these Scottish reindeer strut their stuff at the annual Christmas parade. "They don't mind the attention," handler Alex Smith from the Cairngorm Reindeer Centre said as he harnesses the animals. "They're domesticated, they're used to it and they're very friendly." External Link: A reindeer pulls Santa's sleigh Several animal welfare groups are opposed to this sort of festive event. The RSPCA has raised concerns in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>'Is it a reindeer crash?' Photographers on their best winter shots - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2016/dec/26/is-it-a-reindeer-crash-photographers-on-their-best-winter-shots</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHMZj5oyKD7aIkwNmqdo3R0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 07:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2016/dec/26/is-it-a-reindeer-crash-photographers-on-their-best-winter-shots" target="_blank"&gt;'Is it a reindeer crash?' Photographers on their best winter shots&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matt Stuart ‘Don’t just photograph the obvious’ I got a phone call from a friend saying he had seen loads of Santa Clauses walking towards the law courts in London. I changed direction quickly, and ran across two or three hundred of them, which, on paper, sounds like a photographer’s dream. They were demonstrating for Fathers for Justice, but I realised – after taking a roll or two – that it just looked like a bunch of guys dressed up as Santa Claus. One of the things I have always been told in photography is to look the other way – don’t just photograph the obvious. Sometimes it is better ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Prestholtseter - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/227680891/prestholtseter-by-thrasivoulos-griparis</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJtMsG7G75zinOX8KVyujuEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 22:28:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/227680891/prestholtseter-by-thrasivoulos-griparis" target="_blank"&gt;Prestholtseter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hiking Hardangervidda plateau is outmost satisfactory. the tundra and the open spaces have something magical. I will simply add the following sentences from lonely planet: "The desolate and beautiful Hardangervidda plateau, part of the 3430-sq-km Hardangervidda National Park (Norway's largest), ranges across an otherworldly tundra landscape that's the southernmost refuge of the Arctic fox (the natural population of which has increased through reintroduction programs) and home to Norway's largest herd of wild reindeer. Long a trade and travel route connecting eastern and western Norway, it's...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>How Reindeer Could Help Combat Climate Change - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/reindeer-grazing-climate-change_us_586f3d62e4b099cdb0fc8690</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJlLwFkWFMHOxdSrht8BpikqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 14:51:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/reindeer-grazing-climate-change_us_586f3d62e4b099cdb0fc8690" target="_blank"&gt;How Reindeer Could Help Combat Climate Change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Climate change poses a serious threat to reindeer. Over the past decade, at least 80,000 of them have starved to death in Siberia because of melting sea ice. In the North Pole, warmer temperatures have caused reindeers to shrink in size. But it turns out that reindeer may themselves be a useful weapon in the fight against global warming, a study published in the journal Environmental Research Letters last month finds. And their own appetites could help ensure their continued survival. Researchers visited the Arctic county of Troms, Norway, and discovered that reindeers’ grazing could help s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Watch the new trailer for Frozen short film, Olaf's Frozen Adventure - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/0/anna-elsa-return-first-trailer-olafs-frozen-adventure/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGLbwGpAoVKCdfvE6RsZmH4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDf2rcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 10:08:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/films/0/anna-elsa-return-first-trailer-olafs-frozen-adventure/" target="_blank"&gt;Watch the new trailer for Frozen short film, Olaf's Frozen Adventure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fans frothing at the mouth for Frozen 2 should be momentarily satisfied by this first glimpse of brand new Frozen content, with Disney debuting the trailer for the upcoming short film Olaf's Frozen Adventure. The 21-minute short acts as a sort-of mini-sequel to the 2013 blockbuster, with Anna and Elsa realising their family have no Christmas traditions (their parents being horribly drowned and all), inspiring Olaf to essentially roam Arendelle in the hopes of acquiring everyone else's. The short film was initially announced as a made-for-TV special, to be screened this Christmas, but a rele...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Reindeer herders kept going under the Nazis - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/mar/22/reindeer-herders-kept-going-under-the-nazis</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENIO5h8PGd45SIcJm-JloT0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 18:15:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/mar/22/reindeer-herders-kept-going-under-the-nazis" target="_blank"&gt;Reindeer herders kept going under the Nazis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patrick Barkham (Why the Cornish 500 matter, 21 March) criticises the government for withdrawing funding for the Cornish language and reports the Council of Europe’s disapproval of the BBC ignoring programming in Cornish. In this Nottingham radical bookshop, we have on our counter Deryvadow Party an Gemynwer, gans Karl Marx ha Frederick Engels in case any passing Cornish readers (or linguists) might be interested in challenging the nature of capitalist society. Ross Bradshaw Five Leaves Bookshop, Nottingham • Apropos John Palmer’s letter (15 March), it is my understanding that Sami reindeer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Reindeer shrink as climate change in Arctic puts their food on ice - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/dec/12/reindeer-shrink-as-climate-change-in-arctic-puts-their-food-on-ice</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKAbHWqWYOl3uKMueh7kN3sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 00:46:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/dec/12/reindeer-shrink-as-climate-change-in-arctic-puts-their-food-on-ice" target="_blank"&gt;Reindeer shrink as climate change in Arctic puts their food on ice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reindeer are shrinking on an Arctic island near the north pole as a result of climate change that has curbed the amount of winter food available to the animals, scientists said on Monday. The average weight of adult reindeer on Svalbard, a chain of islands north of Norway, fell from 55kg (121lb) to 48kg (106lb) in the 1990s as part of sweeping changes to Arctic life while temperatures rose, they said. “Warmer summers are great for reindeer but winters are getting increasingly tough,” Professor Steve Albon, an ecologist at the James Hutton Institute in Scotland who led the study with Norwegi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Mongolia's reindeer herders defend their way of life - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/03/mongolia-reindeer-herders-defend-life-170315082203586.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPr4QXR5TMdsLMINJxoXI0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 08:16:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/03/mongolia-reindeer-herders-defend-life-170315082203586.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mongolia's reindeer herders defend their way of life&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsagaannuur, Mongolia - Seated in a white teepee perched on a cliff that overlooks a snow-covered coniferous forest, Delger Gorshik talks about how his life as a Dukha, one of the world's smallest ethnic minorities, has changed over the years. "When I was a child, the only thing we could use for a light was a candle. Today, we have electric lamps and solar panels. This teepee used to be covered with animal skin; today, we use cloth canvas," the 55-year-old says. "And now," he adds, gesturing downhill to where his daughter and son-in-law live. "As you can see, we even have wooden houses." Wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Little Girl Inadvertently Draws NSFW Version Of Santa's Reindeer - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/reindeer-drawing-nsfw_us_585e46c4e4b0d9a5945876f3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKK-GiOsquvuzKm3jSyPwBIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 10:37:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/reindeer-drawing-nsfw_us_585e46c4e4b0d9a5945876f3" target="_blank"&gt;Little Girl Inadvertently Draws NSFW Version Of Santa's Reindeer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A six-year-old girl’s drawing of Santa Claus’ reindeer is going viral, after she inadvertently made it NSFW. Connie Bennett says her daughter was trying to depict Dasher, Dancer, Prancer et al. inside Kris Kringle’s stable, but the animals ended up bearing a striking resemblance to male genitalia: @TheUnmumsyMum I know how you appreciate a misunderstood child's drawing. Today my 6yr old drew Santa's reindeer in their stable pic.twitter.com/WdZETPObyn — Connie Bennett (@Connie_b88) December 22, 2016 Scotland-based Bennett posted the amusing picture to Twitter on Thursday, prompting a flurry ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Reindeer shrinking in size due to warmer Arctic temperatures - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/reindeer-shrinking-size-warmer-arctic-temperatures-global-warming-a7469351.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBoqA_Zbd5Ze2Cb20FVXDwkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 15:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/reindeer-shrinking-size-warmer-arctic-temperatures-global-warming-a7469351.html" target="_blank"&gt;Reindeer shrinking in size due to warmer Arctic temperatures&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reindeer could be shrinking because of warmer temperatures in the Arctic. A increase in temperature in Norway, the home of Svalbard reindeer, causes rain to fall on existing snow cover and freeze solid for eight months of the year - meaning the animals cannot brush it aside to get to the grass and moss they eat. Over the course of the past two decades, the size of the average reindeer has fallen from 55kg to 48kg, Science reported. Could big cats be facing extinction? - 5 show all Could big cats be facing extinction? - 1/5 Beverly Joubert - 2/5 Beverly Joubert - 3/5 Beverly Joubert - 4/5 Be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>How Santa Claus makes money (but still ends the year in the red) - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2016/12/22/santa-claus-makes-money-still-ends-year-red/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcdNtUnoWNbUw0sWYp8yngqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCtrhU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 10:34:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2016/12/22/santa-claus-makes-money-still-ends-year-red/" target="_blank"&gt;How Santa Claus makes money (but still ends the year in the red)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just when everything finally starts to slow down in the City, it all kicks off for the most suited and booted boss of them all: Santa. There are 1,860,463,578 people in the world between the ages of zero and 14 – about 10m more than there were in 2014 – according to the CIA. Making sure all those children get their Christmas presents is quite the corporate operation: staff wages, production costs and vehicle maintenance. Expert Market, the business-to-business marketplace, got its hands on Claus Inc's balance sheet. Here's what it looks like. Total costs: £9.9bn Product manufacturing: Santa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Lapland in Finland -- it's a lot more than a Christmas fantasy land - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/travel/article/finland-lapland/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMf_kJzkVExGIErWgpsUFmYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 15:42:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/travel/article/finland-lapland/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lapland in Finland -- it's a lot more than a Christmas fantasy land&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A trip to Finnish Lapland to see Santa Claus, his reindeer and the elves is the stuff of childhood dreams. The funny thing is you'll probably enjoy it even more as an adult. When the Yuletide bubbly has fizzled out and those rich, childish imaginings fade, this Arctic region that caps the northern part of the Scandinavian Peninsula offers a wintry, European experience that'll provide enough tales for many a future Christmas dinner. Here are 10 reasons you'll want to put Lapland on your list -- be the Christmas or travel variety: 1. Gold There's gold in them there Lapland river valleys. It w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Norway plans mass reindeer cull to prevent spread of wasting disease - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/norway-reindeer-cull-chronic-wasting-disease-nordfjella-a7663491.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFBg7tXd4jnaUA36A2YO9jgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 17:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/norway-reindeer-cull-chronic-wasting-disease-nordfjella-a7663491.html" target="_blank"&gt;Norway plans mass reindeer cull to prevent spread of wasting disease&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Norway is preparing to cull thousands of reindeer to stop the spread of Chronic Wasting Disease. Experts said an entire herd of wild reindeer must be exterminated in order to work towards eradicating the disease, The Local reported. The disease, which leads to chronic weight loss before the death of the animal, was first discovered in Europe last year. In April, a young caribou was found to be affected, followed by three reindeer and an elk. Around 2,000 reindeer are estimated to live in Nordfjella, the area the diseased reindeer were found. World news in pictures - 29 show all World news i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Toe pie and the five-second food rule - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2017/mar/16/toe-pie-and-the-five-second-food-rule</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEByaKbiBZEdH-irWdSPEqo8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 18:41:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2017/mar/16/toe-pie-and-the-five-second-food-rule" target="_blank"&gt;Toe pie and the five-second food rule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reading Joan Bakewell’s reminiscences about the Didcot cooling towers (National gallery, G2, 16 March) reminded me of the delighted observation by a little girl who, on seeing the billowing columns of steam rising from the towers, exclaimed: “Look, Mummy, a cloud factory!” Sadly, even cloud factories can’t withstand the advance of progress. John Hunter Bristol • John Palmer should have known the gaps in fencing on the Norway/Soviet border would never have been a viable crossing route for spies posing as indigenous reindeer herders during the cold war (Letters, 15 March). James Bond would ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>US skiing champion talks about her unusual pets - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/sports/2017/03/28/mikaela-shiffrin-u-s-skiing-slalom-champion-reindeer-sot-riddel-sports-cnni.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPI3VnJjaTqX9R92YInqUPEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 23:37:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/sports/2017/03/28/mikaela-shiffrin-u-s-skiing-slalom-champion-reindeer-sot-riddel-sports-cnni.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;US skiing champion talks about her unusual pets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Did you hear the one about the best female skier in the world and her two reindeer? Don Riddell asks Mikaela Shiffrin about her unusual pets. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>50 fabulous festive knits to celebrate Christmas jumper day in - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/fashion/shopping/best-christmas-jumpers2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEUkYLf04bUlsiy2GRJb_RsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCq098D</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 09:15:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/fashion/shopping/best-christmas-jumpers2/" target="_blank"&gt;50 fabulous festive knits to celebrate Christmas jumper day in&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;16 Dec 2016 50 fabulous festive knits to celebrate Christmas jumper day in Previous slideNext slide1 of 51View AllSkip Ad Whether you're planning on playing it safe with a whimsical star print or a touch of embellishment, are looking forward to pulling a chunky Fair Isle jumper on over everything, are partial to a simple cable knit, or are going the whole hog and wheeling out a reindeer-adorned sweater; here's our pick of the best festive jumpers. Click through our gallery of celebrities wearing festive jumpers in years gone past for some festive inspiration. Back to image&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>80,000 Reindeer Have Starved To Death In Siberia Because Of Melting Sea Ice - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/reindeer-dead-climate-change_us_5832bda6e4b058ce7aabe78e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE1LDQZutnA36bxy6SML0UEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 13:37:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/reindeer-dead-climate-change_us_5832bda6e4b058ce7aabe78e" target="_blank"&gt;80,000 Reindeer Have Starved To Death In Siberia Because Of Melting Sea Ice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to climate change iconography, there’s perhaps no image more recognizable than that of a lone polar bear marooned on a melting sheet of ice. But as the impacts of a continually warming Earth are felt by more species, new emblematic images are emerging: that of emaciated puffins washing up dead on Alaska’s shores; American pikas climbing high into the mountains in search of colder climes; snow-loving wolverines looking lost amidst greenery; and now dead reindeer, starved to death and buried deep in frozen Siberian snow. Russia’s Yamal Peninsula, located in northwestern Siberia,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>The Guardian view on climate change: bad for the Arctic - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/dec/27/the-guardian-view-on-climate-change-bad-for-the-arctic</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKcw_slsjH6-EIiXa72lcd8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 18:20:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/dec/27/the-guardian-view-on-climate-change-bad-for-the-arctic" target="_blank"&gt;The Guardian view on climate change: bad for the Arctic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not even donkeys get a worse deal in popular culture than the reindeer. Rabbits, mice, cats and even bears all have their distorted images in cartoons, but all of them show some sympathetic qualities of intelligence or kindness. Only the reindeer is forced in songs and cartoons to live down to the mangy and dispirited creatures chained up and sweating in rainy British theme parks. Even rats make cartoon heroes. Only reindeer are always caricatured as drunken, stupid and quarrelsome beasts of burden. In real life the partnership of the reindeer with the Sami peoples of northern Scandinavia i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The reindeer derby: a race across the Arctic Circle - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2016/dec/19/reindeer-race-finland-inari-bbc-world-service</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJZLykc9R90OlMHULfKmuTYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCw3Gc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 11:00:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2016/dec/19/reindeer-race-finland-inari-bbc-world-service" target="_blank"&gt;The reindeer derby: a race across the Arctic Circle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m in the far north of Finland. The sky is a perfect blue; beneath it, a few feet of ice lie between me and the black depths of Lake Inari. I’m part of a crowd, a thousand or so strong. We watch. We wait. Whoosh! Huff! Crunch! Half-a-dozen panting reindeer fly by, each pulling a jockey, crouched low over cross-country skis. I’m here to make a Christmas radio documentary for the BBC World Service about reindeer racing, a big thing in the Arctic Circle. Every spring, communities get together in forest clearings to watch reindeer haul riders around 1km circuits. The gathering on Lake Inari is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Take A Chilling Peak At Life In The Coldest Permanently Inhabited Town On Earth - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/coldest-place-on-earth_us_5887aee3e4b0441a8f7159ef</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEApdWcj1mL6sGXnsAjkK5KMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 21:19:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/coldest-place-on-earth_us_5887aee3e4b0441a8f7159ef" target="_blank"&gt;Take A Chilling Peak At Life In The Coldest Permanently Inhabited Town On Earth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hate tropical vacations? There’s always Oymyakon. This remote Russian village holds the world record for lowest temperature in a permanently inhabited place, at -90 degrees Fahrenheit. Forecasts for February 2017 hover in the -20s and -30s, and at some points in winter, the sun only shines for a mere three hours each day. Locals here use outhouses because indoor plumbing often freezes, and cars are rendered almost useless by the cold, Wired reports. BoredPanda recently dug up images from photographer Amos Chapple’s visit to Oymyakon a few years ago. They offer a chilling look at everyday li...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Arctic oil rush: Nenets' livelihood and habitat at risk from oil spills - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2016/dec/23/arctic-oil-rush-nenets-livelihood-and-habitat-at-risk-from-oil-spills</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPYC7MnW2TwDi2q9t_47nIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 07:00:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2016/dec/23/arctic-oil-rush-nenets-livelihood-and-habitat-at-risk-from-oil-spills" target="_blank"&gt;Arctic oil rush: Nenets' livelihood and habitat at risk from oil spills&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The livelihood of the Nenets people who live along the northern stretches of the Yenisei, Russia’s longest river, depends on two pursuits: fishing and reindeer herding. But locals have said both of those activities are under threat from an oil terminal due to be built on the Tanalau cape, near where the river empties into the Arctic Ocean. Greenpeace and the World Wildlife Fund (WWF) have protested against the high risk of an oil spill in difficult Arctic conditions. More than 40 people have signed a letter of protest to the company building the terminal, the Independent Petroleum Company (...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Drunk Grinch Sees Error Of His Ways After Stealing Light-Up Reindeer - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/thief-reindeer-apologize-note_us_58451a12e4b0c68e048195ab</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELumb38C2KqbLcSnY26GteQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 08:27:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/thief-reindeer-apologize-note_us_58451a12e4b0c68e048195ab" target="_blank"&gt;Drunk Grinch Sees Error Of His Ways After Stealing Light-Up Reindeer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A veritable Grinch has anonymously apologized with a handwritten note to the little girl whose Christmas lights he stole while drunk. Chiara Velardi, 9, was left in tears after unidentified men pulled up in a car outside her Sydney home on Thursday night and swiped her two light-up reindeer. A surveillance camera captured the theft of the display which, while only worth around $55 U.S., was of huge sentimental value to her family. See the video below: Middleton Grange: Thieves caught stealing Christmas light display from front lawn. @DamienSmith_7 #7News https://t.co/g7HcZkm7ie?ncid=NEWSST...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>'Reindeers don’t like people' – and other things we learned on a family holiday to Finnish Lapland - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/family-holidays/finland-lapland-for-families/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEELLR3Z4fn508hqej6LBQPsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/family-holidays/finland-lapland-for-families/" target="_blank"&gt;'Reindeers don’t like people' – and other things we learned on a family holiday to Finnish Lapland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t get me wrong, I’m a big fan of Father Christmas. Defying the laws of physics by being simultaneously everywhere for one night of the year is a pretty awesome super-power, after all. A grown man squeezing down my chimney? Brilliant, and in no way a security risk. Reindeer-powered flight? The future of aviation, almost certainly. Stuffing socks with gifts, asking whether I’ve been a “good little boy”, the white beard, the ho-ho-hos: all part of the wonder of growing up. The idea of going to visit him, though, has never particularly appealed. Plenty of families do it each year; he’s the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Lawmakers Renew Push for Drilling in Alaska Wildlife Refuge - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/lawmakers-renew-push-drilling-alaska-wildlife-refuge/3737389.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI8_6dbngwN-DK0Kl3qSc9gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 22:08:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/lawmakers-renew-push-drilling-alaska-wildlife-refuge/3737389.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lawmakers Renew Push for Drilling in Alaska Wildlife Refuge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former U.S. Sen. Frank Murkowski in 2001 gave a speech urging colleagues to approve oil drilling in America's largest wildlife refuge. The Alaska Republican held up a blank sheet of paper to illustrate his point. The field of white, he said, was all you could see each winter on the coastal plain of the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, implying that such a barren landscape would not be harmed by oil rigs. Sixteen years later, Murkowski's daughter is trying again. U.S. Sen. Lisa Murkowski is sponsoring legislation to open the refuge that takes up Alaska's northeast corner and is larger than W...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Northern Highlights &amp; the Arctic Circle - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/tours/partners/cosmos/northern-highlights-arctic-circle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENXXYRmogDSrHPu2thg3g9QqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 13:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/tours/partners/cosmos/northern-highlights-arctic-circle/" target="_blank"&gt;Northern Highlights &amp; the Arctic Circle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overview Experience the fragile and ethereal beauty of northern Scandinavia and the Arctic landscape. Visit the land of the reindeer, sail through the Norwegian fjords and weave around the striking coastline of the Atlantic Road. Price Includes - Fifteen nights accommodation - Return flights from a selection of regional UK airports - Transfers - Fifteen breakfasts and seven dinners - Services of a tour director - Porterage - Individual audio system - All local and airport taxes/service charges - Single share optionChoose your bookingSelected departure dates from 14 Aug 2017 - £2003pp, 30 Ap...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Russia with Simon Reeve - episode one feels like a Cold War spy thriller - review - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/tv/2017/09/28/russia-simon-reeve-episode-one-feels-like-cold-war-spy-thriller/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMv9nKgtUu2iSsY_u6n30UIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTD51N8D</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/tv/2017/09/28/russia-simon-reeve-episode-one-feels-like-cold-war-spy-thriller/" target="_blank"&gt;Russia with Simon Reeve - episode one feels like a Cold War spy thriller - review&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia with Simon Reeve (BBC Two) was billed as a travelogue but frequently felt more like a Cold War spy thriller. The camera crew were tailed by Federal Security Service (FSB) officers in unmarked cars. They were subjected to interrogations, drug tests and detained in police stations for no reason. Welcome to Putin’s police state. On the 100th anniversary of the Russian Revolution, this three-parter found adventurer Reeve journeying 4,000 miles across the world’s biggest country, from the snow-capped volcanoes of the east to the great cities of the west. Reeve’s very much from the Profess...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Dreaming of winter? Now is the time to book these 10 trips to Lapland - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/tours/how-visit-lapland-finland-sweden-tours-winter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwaNa8j3YaYQxs-EdVygGUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 14:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/tours/how-visit-lapland-finland-sweden-tours-winter/" target="_blank"&gt;Dreaming of winter? Now is the time to book these 10 trips to Lapland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Europe’s last true wildernesses and still home to the indigenous Sami nomads famous for their reindeer herds, Lapland is two different places depending on when you visit. A land of lakes and enchanting birch forest between May and September, it is the place to savour endless summer days, packing them with outdoor pursuits such as hiking wild mountain trails, floating down river on a raft made of logs, fishing on pristine lakes, foraging for the fabled cloudberry or simply taking in the colours of late August as the days shorten and rumour of winter grows. When winter has taken its lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Norway to ban the use of oil for heating buildings by 2020 - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/norway-ban-oil-use-heating-2020-a7819571.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBTl7ydBk1ymWN8Q0ThEzQAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 15:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/norway-ban-oil-use-heating-2020-a7819571.html" target="_blank"&gt;Norway to ban the use of oil for heating buildings by 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Norway is set to become the first country in the entire world to ban the use of gas to heat buildings. The Scandinavian country, which is the world's largest producer of oil and natural gas outside the Middle East, will wholly stop the use of both oil and paraffin to warm buildings from 2020 onwards. The country, which hopes to ban the sale of all fossil fuel-based cars by 2025, has made a concerted effort to introduce policies which shrink domestic emission of greenhouse gases. Vidar Helgesenlaid, the nation’s Environment Minister, laid out the plans in a statement, saying: “Those using fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Sleigh Ride: The BBC are repeating its hypnotic two-hour 'slow TV' Christmas classic - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/the-bbc-are-repeating-that-hypnotic-all-aboard-sleigh-ride-on-christmas-eve-a7486636.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGuK0WGppEI2tb04VUnG5T8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTD-yBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 12:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/the-bbc-are-repeating-that-hypnotic-all-aboard-sleigh-ride-on-christmas-eve-a7486636.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sleigh Ride: The BBC are repeating its hypnotic two-hour 'slow TV' Christmas classic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Christmas Eve 2015, BBC Four aired a two-hour long Sleigh Ride through the eyes of a reindeer herder in the frozen wilderness of the Arctic. Its striking presence in the TV schedules, so crammed with miserable episodes of EastEnders and Shrek sequels, hypnotised viewers who praised the channel for showing something that shunned the usual norm - there is no talking or presenter guiding the action; just the calming sounds of reindeer bells and crunching snow. The episode was a further experiment in the channel's 'BBC Four goes slow' movement - it paid off. If you missed Sleigh Ride last ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Reindeer kicked, abused and underfed away from bright lights of Christmas events - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/reindeer-santa-grotto-uk-christmas-lights-switch-on-sleigh-abuse-kent-blithbury-lodge-a8603751.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENMArf4vXu9UrBYTeozfuMYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 12:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/reindeer-santa-grotto-uk-christmas-lights-switch-on-sleigh-abuse-kent-blithbury-lodge-a8603751.html" target="_blank"&gt;Reindeer kicked, abused and underfed away from bright lights of Christmas events&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reindeer were kicked, abused and suffered health problems at centres that supply animals for Christmas grottos and markets, according to undercover investigators who secretly filmed scenes that have been condemned by a vet as “inexcusable and disturbing”. At centres around the country, footage was taken of workers kicking animals, and reindeer that appeared unwell, with diarrhoea or underweight, and others with raw, exposed skin. Others were kept in “desolate, unnatural” conditions including bright lights and being frightened by visitors banging on fences. Some were so malnourished that the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>10 of the best festive family holidays in Lapland - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/family-holidays/christmas-family-holidays-lapland/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKvlKw9wkVvWcUPVlDmq5NgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 12:42:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/family-holidays/christmas-family-holidays-lapland/" target="_blank"&gt;10 of the best festive family holidays in Lapland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nick Trend guides you to a meeting with Father Christmas himself amid the frozen landscapes of Lapland. 1. Log cabins and saunas For picture-perfect log cabins with open fires and in-house saunas, with snow-covered roofs hidden in forests where reindeer roam, head for the scenic fell of Yllas, Finland. This is the largest ski resort in the country with plenty of non-skiing winter activities to choose from, too, alongside the usual Santa packages of elf workshops and games. Four-night Santa Breaks from £1,320 per person, self-catering, at Villa Armas Cabins in Yllas, departing Bristol on Dec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Portrait of a Stag on Black - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/280616623/portrait-of-a-stag-on-black-by-haydn-bartlett</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAao1jXbNCOngyWwmgMKUKcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:20:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/280616623/portrait-of-a-stag-on-black-by-haydn-bartlett" target="_blank"&gt;Portrait of a Stag on Black&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer Ruminant Mammal Deer are the hoofed ruminant mammals forming the family Cervidae. The two main groups are the Cervinae, including the muntjac, the elk, the fallow deer and the chital, and the Capreolinae, including the reindeer, the roe deer and the moose. Female reindeer, and male deer of all species except the Chinese water deer, grow and shed new antlers each year. In this they differ from permanently horned antelope, which are part of a different family within the same order of even-toed ungulates.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>Dream Job Alert: Get Paid To Watch The Northern Lights - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jordilippemcgraw/2018/09/14/finland-dream-job/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMyDsBTiBMwySbQl1eevB3QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jordilippemcgraw/2018/09/14/finland-dream-job/" target="_blank"&gt;Dream Job Alert: Get Paid To Watch The Northern Lights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This could be your office. Finland really wants you to visit and has been on a non-stop campaign to attract travelers. Back in 2016, the country’s tourism board launched the “FinRelax” program encouraging visitors to chill out through a five-step, natured-focused process. Then, in 2017, Off the Map Travel launched a new experience called the Aurora Floating Experience where you float on a frozen lake in the country under the Northern Lights. And now they’re hoping to lure you there by offering up dream jobs. Dozens of companies in Northern Finland announced recently that they’re looking for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Siberia's forgotten women – a photo essay - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2018/sep/03/siberias-forgotten-women-a-photo-essay</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF5fDBtPhHBfPycoKV0SRGYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 06:00:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2018/sep/03/siberias-forgotten-women-a-photo-essay" target="_blank"&gt;Siberia's forgotten women – a photo essay&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a remote peninsula in northern Siberia lives a group of elderly women. They were once part of a migrating community of reindeer herders but today, in their old age, they spend most of their days in the village of Yar-Sale, cut off from their nomadic relatives and friends. Though the men are encouraged to stay within the wandering community as they grow older, the women often find themselves facing the struggles of ageing in isolation. Life in the village might seem more comfortable than life as a migrating elder in the wild tundra, but it comes at the cost of great loneliness and a loss ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Fence On Top Of A Fjell - 500px</title><link>https://500px.com/photo/272279985/fence-on-top-of-a-fjell-by-jukka-heinovirta</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMAF9So_PwyC7qcq5ejFTMEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow26UBMPBEMMD7CQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 08:33:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://500px.com/photo/272279985/fence-on-top-of-a-fjell-by-jukka-heinovirta" target="_blank"&gt;Fence On Top Of A Fjell&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;500px&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fence goes down the slope of the Yllas Fjell in the Finnish Lapland. The fence could be for the reindeer or for the downhill skiers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://500px.com">500px</source></item><item><title>How to find the best trip to see Father Christmas in Lapland - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/finland/articles/Visiting-Father-Christmas-in-Lapland/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMy5iRl-46aihiWcCMAjLkgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/finland/articles/Visiting-Father-Christmas-in-Lapland/" target="_blank"&gt;How to find the best trip to see Father Christmas in Lapland&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take the festive trip of your child’s dreams – from Santa to snow, our experts have it covered. These extraordinary trips are a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity, but they are not cheap (expect to pay an average of £1,000 per person for a three-night trip), so you want to be sure that you book the right option for your family. Father Christmas makes an appearance in all, but trips vary in their emphasis on ski, huskies, reindeer or elves. Sophie Butler, our consumer expert, explains the range of Father Christmas trips on the market, giving practical advice on everything from location to accomm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Sweden's reindeer at risk of starvation after summer drought - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/22/sweden-reindeer-herders-risk-starvation-climate-change-arctic</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF3YO_s4au03PHRSjCuGNqMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 11:05:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/22/sweden-reindeer-herders-risk-starvation-climate-change-arctic" target="_blank"&gt;Sweden's reindeer at risk of starvation after summer drought&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sweden’s indigenous Sami reindeer herders are demanding state aid to help them cope with the impact of this summer’s unprecedented drought and wildfires, saying their future is at risk as global warming changes the environment in the far north. The Swedish government this week announced five major investigations aimed at preparing the country for the kind of extreme heatwave it experienced in July, when temperatures exceeded 30C (86F) and forest fires raged inside the Arctic circle. But it has yet to come up with any concrete measures for the country’s 4,600 Sami reindeer owners – the only ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Mongolia: Riding Reindeer And Hunting With Eagles In East Asia's Most Fascinating Destination - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/breannawilson/2018/08/28/mongolia-riding-reindeer-and-hunting-with-eagles-in-east-asias-most-fascinating-destination/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGEb7nU0KHmgzUr45y-Mc8MqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/breannawilson/2018/08/28/mongolia-riding-reindeer-and-hunting-with-eagles-in-east-asias-most-fascinating-destination/" target="_blank"&gt;Mongolia: Riding Reindeer And Hunting With Eagles In East Asia's Most Fascinating Destination&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visiting the Tsaatan Tribe in Mongolia’s Khövsgöl Province. Let’s start with getting there. Which is no easy feat. (Pro tip: book your flight through Hong Kong and take advantage of the great lounges there. Hello, Cathay Pacific’s six lounges.). Once you’ve finally arrived in Ulaanbaatar, the country’s capital and the starting point for pretty much all the best adventures, get your last fill of life’s little luxuries – maybe hit the spa, or indulge on Korean barbeque, because life outside of the city is much simpler, but that’s exactly what you’re there for. And while it’s common that Mongo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>It's so hot in Finland's north reindeer can be seen on the beach - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-08-01/finland-heatwave-forces-reindeer-to-cool-off-at-the-beach/10063092</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGJLlSTsyOdg0nVYM94oEA0qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 12:13:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-08-01/finland-heatwave-forces-reindeer-to-cool-off-at-the-beach/10063092" target="_blank"&gt;It's so hot in Finland's north reindeer can be seen on the beach&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As beachgoers in Finland's north sought relief from sweltering temperatures with a dip in the ocean, they noticed three reindeer doing exactly the same thing. Some parts of Europe have been crippled with heat for weeks, and Spain is on alert after the country's weather agency warns temperatures could surpass 40 degrees Celsius. But while southern Europe is used to temperatures in the high-30s, for the countries near the Arctic Circle the heat is unexpected. Pekka Niinivaara from Vantaa, near Helsinki, took the photo of three reindeer drinking at the beach — a shot that has received more tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Polar bear shot dead after attacking cruise ship guard in Norway - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/29/polar-bear-shot-dead-after-attacking-cruise-ship-guard-in-norway</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA3WBnOgP14q1_GP425Go84qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 16:10:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/29/polar-bear-shot-dead-after-attacking-cruise-ship-guard-in-norway" target="_blank"&gt;Polar bear shot dead after attacking cruise ship guard in Norway&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A polar bear has been shot dead after attacking and injuring a guard who was leading tourists off a cruise ship on an Arctic archipelago in Norway. The bear was shot dead by another employee, the cruise company said after the attack on Saturday. The Joint Rescue Coordination for Northern Norway said on Twitter that the attack had occurred when tourists from the MS Bremen cruise ship landed on the northernmost island of the Svalbard archipelago, a region between mainland Norway and the North Pole known for its remote terrain, glaciers, reindeer and polar bears. A spokeswoman for the German H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Polar bear killed after attack on Arctic cruise ship guard - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-07-30/polar-bear-killed-after-attack-on-cruise-ship-guard-in-norway/10050534</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEyq5m_lkDq1G9nZ7PWEkzUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 22:47:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-07-30/polar-bear-killed-after-attack-on-cruise-ship-guard-in-norway/10050534" target="_blank"&gt;Polar bear killed after attack on Arctic cruise ship guard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A polar bear has been shot dead after attacking a guard who was leading tourists off a cruise ship on an Arctic archipelago. The Joint Rescue Coordination for Northern Norway tweeted that the attack happened when tourists from the MS Bremen cruise ship landed on the most northern island of the Svalbard archipelago, a region between mainland Norway and the North Pole that is known for its remote terrain, glaciers, reindeer and polar bears. The German Hapag Lloyd Cruises company, which operates the MS Bremen, said two polar bear guards from their ship went onto the island and one of them "was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item></channel></rss>