<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Nintendo Switch - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV6TUhCNVoyWVNBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-ZW&amp;gl=ZW&amp;ceid=ZW:en</link><language>en-ZW</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:54:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate' DLC: 'Persona 5' Character Coming In First Challenge Pack - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/12/07/super-smash-bros-ultimate-dlc-persona-5-character-coming-in-first-challenge-pack/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ5TCH6jSYl1JVOLA3Smd1kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/12/07/super-smash-bros-ultimate-dlc-persona-5-character-coming-in-first-challenge-pack/" target="_blank"&gt;'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate' DLC: 'Persona 5' Character Coming In First Challenge Pack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super Smash Bros. Ultimate just released on December 7 for the Nintendo Switch, but we’ve already learned about the first piece of DLC. As a part of the Challenger 1 Pack, Joker from the Persona 5 franchise will be added to the game. Joker in SSBU This announcement was made and revealed at the 2018 Video Game Awards in Los Angeles on Thursday night. Here is a look at the trailer: clearly, we wish there was a snippet of gameplay with Joker and/or on his stage, but based on the early reviews of SSBU, we’d be inclined to expect a solid and imaginative rendering. This is a significant add for S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Game Awards 2018 announcements: Dragon Age 4 and Far Cry: New Dawn headline new game reveals - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-announcements-dragon-age-4-far-cry-new-dawn/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOe9WHf9XKnjO0C_nfPE33MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:54:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-announcements-dragon-age-4-far-cry-new-dawn/" target="_blank"&gt;The Game Awards 2018 announcements: Dragon Age 4 and Far Cry: New Dawn headline new game reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BioWare has announced that RPG Dragon Age 4 is coming at The Game Awards ceremony. The long-awaited fantasy RPG is reportedly still early in development, but BioWare has teased its fans with a short video and the phrase The Dread Wolf Rises; a reference to elven apostate Solas. Far Cry: New Dawn, a direct post-apocalyptic sequel to Ubisoft's open-world shooter Far Cry 5, was unveiled for 15 February 2019. The game is set 17 years after Far Cry 5, with a 'super-bloom' transforming the setting of Hope County into a vivid, colourful post-nuclear land. And staying with pink post-apocalyptia, Ra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Super Smash Bros. Ultimate review | A riotous fighter and gloriously bonkers video game celebration - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/super-smash-bros-ultimate-review-riotous-fighter-gloriously/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEJen89qiL29lxmOhozmyvkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:00:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/reviews/super-smash-bros-ultimate-review-riotous-fighter-gloriously/" target="_blank"&gt;Super Smash Bros. Ultimate review | A riotous fighter and gloriously bonkers video game celebration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly twenty years after the first Super Smash Bros, the core appeal of Nintendo’s raucous fighter remains the same: being able to give Pikachu a good shoeing. Or using Donkey Kong to ground Fox McCloud by headbutting him into the dirt. Or allowing Princess Peach her ultimate revenge, belting Bowser into the stratosphere using a baseball bat. But in contrast to the ability for Nintendo characters to impart cartoonish violence on one another, Super Smash Bros. is also a celebration. A party to which anyone or anything that has graced a Nintendo console is invited, and the entertainment is a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate' Release Date And 10 Things You Should Know Before You Buy The Game - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/12/06/super-smash-bros-ultimate-release-date-and-10-things-you-should-know-before-you-buy-the-game/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEiaI5YlCnzmYVNKmqUCqIkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/12/06/super-smash-bros-ultimate-release-date-and-10-things-you-should-know-before-you-buy-the-game/" target="_blank"&gt;'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate' Release Date And 10 Things You Should Know Before You Buy The Game&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Nintendo Switch exclusives go, there aren’t many that are more valuable than the upcoming Super Smash Bros. Ultimate. SSBU for Nintendo Switch This iconic series has rarely produced a dud and with more characters than ever, expectations are high for yet another noteworthy achievement. SSBU releases on December 7 and here are the 10 things you should know about the final major video game release of 2018. Special Edition Info The Standard Edition will cost $59.99 and just comes with the game. MyBestBuy and Amazon Prime members are getting $10 reward certificate for buying the game. There’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled' Powerslides Onto Switch, PS4 and Xbox One Next Year - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mitchwallace/2018/12/06/crash-team-racing-nitro-fueled-powerslides-onto-switch-ps4-and-xbox-one-next-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH7uaxffEPvZUR5C04jSIiQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mitchwallace/2018/12/06/crash-team-racing-nitro-fueled-powerslides-onto-switch-ps4-and-xbox-one-next-year/" target="_blank"&gt;'Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled' Powerslides Onto Switch, PS4 and Xbox One Next Year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled First came Crash Bandicoot N. Sane Trilogy, followed recently by the amazing Spyro Reignited Trilogy, and now we have yet another retro-inspired remake on our hands. Even though it feels like Activision is just mining our childhoods for gold at this point, I’m not complaining, because what we’re getting in return is just too damn good. Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled After much speculation and a strange furry delivery earlier this week, Activision has officially confirmed and announced a high definition reboot of Naughty Dog’s excellent PS1 go-karting romp. Dub...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Lower Pre-Owned Video Game Products Sales Will Likely Weigh On GameStop's Near Term Earnings - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/12/06/lower-pre-owned-video-game-products-sales-will-likely-weigh-on-gamestops-near-term-earnings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPhfLZWYl2UZCocZe8dMz38qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/12/06/lower-pre-owned-video-game-products-sales-will-likely-weigh-on-gamestops-near-term-earnings/" target="_blank"&gt;Lower Pre-Owned Video Game Products Sales Will Likely Weigh On GameStop's Near Term Earnings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nintendo Co. Wii video games are displayed for sale inside a GameStop Corp. store in Louisville, Kentucky, on Thursday, March 15, 2018. G(Photographer: Luke Sharrett/Bloomberg) GameStop Inc (NYSE:GME) recently posted its Q3 FY 2018 results, which were below the street estimates. The company incurred a $587.5 million asset impairment charge primarily related to goodwill in Q3. It also lowered its fiscal 2018 guidance, which led to a sell off in the share price, following the earnings release. Looking forward, we forecast a mid-single digit decline in the company’s overall revenues for the f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate' Release Date And Special Edition Info: Which Version Should You Buy? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/12/03/super-smash-bros-ultimate-release-date-and-special-edition-info-which-version-should-you-buy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECezWTuCaTyzUywFgm2c7IAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/12/03/super-smash-bros-ultimate-release-date-and-special-edition-info-which-version-should-you-buy/" target="_blank"&gt;'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate' Release Date And Special Edition Info: Which Version Should You Buy?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most iconic Nintendo titles and most-anticipated games of the year on the Switch is almost here. Super Smash Bros. Ultimate is set to release on December 7. SSBU for Nintendo Switch It boasts a massive roster of characters–74 to be exact. I’ll break down the 10 things you need to know about the game later in the week, but for now, let’s look at the different versions available and find out which one is right for you. The Super Smash Bros. Ultimate Standard Edition is the most basic. It just includes the game and costs $59.99. Standard Edition On the pre-order side, My Best Buy an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Technology: is it game over for consoles? - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0a46b2ac-f70a-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO9YaoUBjxgIIggsdvhkLtkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0a46b2ac-f70a-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Technology: is it game over for consoles?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Home entertainment has always been a ruthless business, but games consoles’ 50-year territorial war for the living room has been endlessly brutal. On screen, it is fought with chainsaws, battleaxes, plasma rifles or the Poltergust 3000 spectral vacuum cleaner. Behind the scenes, though, is an even bloodier conflict fought with long-term bets on technology, balance sheets, exclusivity agreements and games so intricate that they require 1,000-strong armies of staff to produce. The casualties are frequent. Who remembers the Casio PV-1000, the Timlex Mega Duck and the Bandai Playdia? Each may h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Nintendo Switch Software Sales Will Likely See Strong Double-Digit Growth In The Near Term - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/30/nintendo-switch-software-sales-will-likely-see-strong-double-digit-growth-in-the-near-term/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENWLsoWZxP7WrfkhGxMjxdgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/30/nintendo-switch-software-sales-will-likely-see-strong-double-digit-growth-in-the-near-term/" target="_blank"&gt;Nintendo Switch Software Sales Will Likely See Strong Double-Digit Growth In The Near Term&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this Nov. 15, 2018, photo, shoppers standing on an escalator passes by the logo of Nintendo at an electronics store in Tokyo.(AP Photo/Koji Sasahara) photocredit: ASSOCIATED PRESS Nintendo (OTCMKTS:NTDOY) has seen stellar growth since the launch of the Switch console, both in hardware and software sales. Since its launch the company has sold close to 23 million consoles and over 100 million software titles. The company expects to ship 20 million consoles and 100 million software titles in fiscal 2019. We have created an interactive dashboard ~ How Much Can Nintendo Switch Software Sales ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Game Awards 2018: What will we see at annual celebration turned game announcement hotbed? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-new-games-will-see-announcement-hotbed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAH3LYht9cY2krWZ_0pEMTQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 09:33:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/news/game-awards-2018-new-games-will-see-announcement-hotbed/" target="_blank"&gt;The Game Awards 2018: What will we see at annual celebration turned game announcement hotbed?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite its overly corporate sheen, the annual Game Awards show has slowly become one of the key dates on the gaming calendar. Taking over from Spike TV’s long-running Video Game Awards show in 2014, The Game Awards began life as a celebration of the year’s best games, but is now more anticipated as a glimpse into the next. With most of the year’s games on shelves by the time the December show rolls around, The Game Awards has become the venue of choice for publishers to announce new titles and shed more light on upcoming ones. Away from the throng and pressure of E3, The Game Awards has se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Cyber Monday 2018: The Best Deals On Nintendo Switch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/26/cyber-monday-2018-the-best-deals-on-nintendo-switch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH-CPDb3dvG5V2tNdgeG2LkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/26/cyber-monday-2018-the-best-deals-on-nintendo-switch/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyber Monday 2018: The Best Deals On Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Legend of Zelda: The Breath of the Wild. The Nintendo Switch is a hit, but Nintendo has set some high expectations for its new-ish hybrid console. The company wants to sell 20 million of the things this fiscal year, and that means its pushing hard into this current holiday season. Whether or not it will meet those goals remains a question, but for those looking to buy, rest assured that you have an enthusiastic manufacturer to contend with. That means that the Switch has some good deals here on Cyber Monday 2018, so you can still grab a discount if you missed it on Black Friday. Here’s ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best games of 2018 | Our guide to the top titles of the year so far - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/best-games-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBW4IyRNHjzrwDFN1Qpv4XwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 16:32:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/features/best-games-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Best games of 2018 | Our guide to the top titles of the year so far&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we reach the business end of 2018, we reflect on a year that has provided players with another formidable line-up of top games, packed with monster hunting hijinks, earnest indie love stories, god-thumping blockbusters and outlaws on the run. That is if you can tear yourself away from Fortnite, of course. We will be keeping an evolving list of the best games for Xbox One, PS4, Switch, PC and mobile across the year --with many of the best new and upcoming games sure to make the grade-- so check back regularly for updates and let us know in the comments if any of your favourites demand inc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Here Are Some Of The Early Cyber Monday Deals At Walmart - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/23/here-are-some-of-the-early-cyber-monday-deals-at-walmart/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENOD2COUNuDwj2KyaGJdOxYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 02:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/23/here-are-some-of-the-early-cyber-monday-deals-at-walmart/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are Some Of The Early Cyber Monday Deals At Walmart&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Did you miss some of Walmart’s Black Friday deals that caught your eye? No worries. Chances are the same sales, or something similar will be available for the gaming consoles, games and other electronics on Cyber Monday. HONG KONG – 2018/11/21: Japanese multinational video gaming brand created and owned Nintendo, Nintendo Switch, the logo is seen on an Android mobile device with a Christmas wrapped gifts in the background. (Photo by Miguel Candela/SOPA Images/LightRocket via Getty Images) photo credit: LightRocket via Getty Images Technically, Cyber Monday is on November 26, but most of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here Are The Best Deals On Nintendo Switch For Black Friday 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/22/here-are-the-best-deals-on-nintendo-switch-for-black-friday-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1BW4cQmstyRDnSVjIg3TYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/22/here-are-the-best-deals-on-nintendo-switch-for-black-friday-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are The Best Deals On Nintendo Switch For Black Friday 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;the Nintendo Switch If you’re looking to get a Nintendo Switch this Black Friday, be forewarned: you’ll likely end up spending a bunch of money on accessories on top of whatever deal price you’re actually paying. That doesn’t mean you shouldn’t get one, of course: Nintendo’s little hybrid console is a magical device, and it’s the only thing that will allow you to challenge strangers to Mario Kart on flights, which is how I passed my time on a recent trip to New Orleans. And Black Friday is a good time to pick one up, as a rule of thumb. Let’s take a look at the best deals on Nintendo Switc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>GameStop Q3 FY18 Preview: Expect New Video Game Software Sales To Drive Earnings - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/28/gamestop-q3-fy18-preview-expect-new-video-game-software-sales-to-drive-earnings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA11c890qo3rOfvf6R601FgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 19:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/greatspeculations/2018/11/28/gamestop-q3-fy18-preview-expect-new-video-game-software-sales-to-drive-earnings/" target="_blank"&gt;GameStop Q3 FY18 Preview: Expect New Video Game Software Sales To Drive Earnings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon.com Inc. gift cards are displayed for sale inside a GameStop Corp. store in Louisville, Kentucky, on Thursday, March 15, 2018. (Photographer: Luke Sharrett/Bloomberg) GameStop Inc. (NYSE:GME) is scheduled to post its Q3 FY18 results on November 29. We expect the company to post a low single digit decline in the top line, as growth in New Video Game Software, and Digital, Technology Brands, Collectibles &amp; Others will be more than offset by a decline in New Video Game Hardware, and Pre-Owned &amp; Value Video Game Products, in our view. However, we forecast strong earnings growth in the n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Pokémon: Let's Go' Has Topped The Japanese Charts And Boosted Switch Sales In The Process - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/11/21/pokemon-lets-go-has-topped-the-japanese-charts-and-boosted-switch-sales-in-the-process/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDVnEVwmcO4p608Jzwz6wlAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 02:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/11/21/pokemon-lets-go-has-topped-the-japanese-charts-and-boosted-switch-sales-in-the-process/" target="_blank"&gt;'Pokémon: Let's Go' Has Topped The Japanese Charts And Boosted Switch Sales In The Process&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Pokémon: Let’s Go’ has done very well in Japan. The recently released and entirely excellent Pokémon: Let’s Go on the Switch has been received very well in Japan and helped to boost sales of its host console. In the first few days of the game’s release in Japan, it managed to sell 661,240 copies. However, the really remarkable news is how Switch sales have reacted to this game. Put simply, since the game was released last week the Switch has shifted 200,850 units. To put that figure into perspective, the PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 4 Pro only sold 8,922 and 8,867 units respectively. In a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Zelda: Breath Of The Wild' May Not Be Part Of Any Timeline After All - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/11/25/zelda-breath-of-the-wild-may-not-be-part-of-any-timeline-after-all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPI-dQDB4oqqA_oPufOPCwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 10:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/11/25/zelda-breath-of-the-wild-may-not-be-part-of-any-timeline-after-all/" target="_blank"&gt;'Zelda: Breath Of The Wild' May Not Be Part Of Any Timeline After All&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Breath of the Wild’ is now no longer part of the main timeline for the series. A few days ago, another book for Breath of the Wild was released. Entitled Creating a Champion, it features some comments by Eiji Aonuma where he changes his mind on previous comments about the game being at the end of The Legend of Zelda timeline. Before we get onto Aonuma’s original comments on Breath of the Wild’s timeline placement from August, it’s worth hearing what he now has to say. In books like the recently released The Legend of Zelda Encyclopedia, we revealed where each Zelda game fell on a timeline ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sorry, but the Nintendo 64 Classic isn’t happening anytime soon - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90268925/sorry-but-the-nintendo-64-classic-isnt-happening-anytime-soon</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ0vnJyv6-NnCNpWwcnduNcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 19:29:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90268925/sorry-but-the-nintendo-64-classic-isnt-happening-anytime-soon" target="_blank"&gt;Sorry, but the Nintendo 64 Classic isn’t happening anytime soon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After Nintendo released the NES Classic Edition in 2016 and the Super NES Classic Edition last year, a Nintendo 64 Classic seemed like the next logical step. But speaking to Kotaku, Nintendo of America President Reggie Fils-Aime suggested that it’s not going to happen soon, if ever. “I would not ever rule something out,” he said, “but what I can tell you is certainly that’s not in our planning horizon.” Fils-Aime explained that Nintendo viewed the previous retro consoles as “limited time opportunities,” which gave the company some new hardware to sell as it wound down the Wii U and ramped u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Cyber Monday 2018: Kohl's Nasty Expensive Surprises - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/26/cyber-monday-2018-kohls-sale-nintendo-switch-xbox-one-x-tv-deals-iphone-galaxy-savings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWqh_dez1MgH18hnf_wwQgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 20:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/26/cyber-monday-2018-kohls-sale-nintendo-switch-xbox-one-x-tv-deals-iphone-galaxy-savings/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyber Monday 2018: Kohl's Nasty Expensive Surprises&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. I had already ranked my favourite Cyber Monday deals, but Kohl’s was the champion of Black Friday so can its Cyber Monday sale pull out any last minute must-have deals? Sadly not. The nasty surprise with Cyber Monday 2018 at Kohl’s is the store appears to have blown everything on Black Friday… This is the sixth in my Cyber Monday ‘Nasty Sur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What's the best video games console for Christmas 2018? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/19/best-video-games-console-christmas-2018-playstation-4-xbox-one-nintendo-switch</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEs1apSqSDI0s3VttGU1-IYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:30:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/19/best-video-games-console-christmas-2018-playstation-4-xbox-one-nintendo-switch" target="_blank"&gt;What's the best video games console for Christmas 2018?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A games console is the perfect Christmas present – it’s exciting, it’s cool and everyone can join in on the day (as long as you’ve had the foresight to sneak it out of its packaging on Christmas Eve to download the inevitable six hours of system updates). But selecting which machine to opt for is complicated and confusing, and if you get it wrong you may end up with yet another unloved gadget crammed in the cupboard where you keep the air fryer and mini candyfloss machine. Here are some tips for harassed parents or partners who have found the words “games console” on a loved one’s Christmas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Here Are The Best Deals On Xbox One X For Black Friday 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/22/here-are-the-best-deals-on-xbox-one-x-for-black-friday-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEmNVrGiFtUMFRyPsEi7wvEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 14:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/22/here-are-the-best-deals-on-xbox-one-x-for-black-friday-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are The Best Deals On Xbox One X For Black Friday 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xbox One X Console and Controller. Xbox One X is the console for the person that wants the best. Not necessarily in terms of exclusive software, mind you, where the PS4 still reigns supreme followed by the Nintendo Switch. But you can’t touch it when it comes to raw power, and that means that this is the machine you want if you’re looking to put that new 4K HDR TV through its paces. It’s the machine you want to get to see Red Dead Redemption 2 at its absolute best, which for some will be worth the price of admission alone. But the Xbox One X isn’t cheap, and so you might have been waiting u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate' And The 5 Biggest Video Game Releases In December 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/22/super-smash-bros-ultimate-and-the-5-biggest-video-game-releases-in-december-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENzY4FTxF_QtGEGK1so4w6wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/22/super-smash-bros-ultimate-and-the-5-biggest-video-game-releases-in-december-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;'Super Smash Bros. Ultimate' And The 5 Biggest Video Game Releases In December 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;December is never really a huge month for video game releases and 2018 is no exception. WASHINGTON, DC – OCTOBER 8: Super Smash Bros Ultimate by Nintendo is part of The Washington Post via Getty Images annual gift guide October 08, 2018 in Washington, DC. (Photo by Katherine Frey/The Washington Post via Getty Images) That said, there are a handful of games that might be worth a look. In fact, there are at least two that could register as must-haves for hardcore gamers. It starts with Super Smash Bros. Ultimate. The latest edition in the hit Nintendo series arrives in stores on December 7 an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Google Express Has Some Of The Best Deals On PS4, Xbox One And Switch For Black Friday 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/22/google-express-has-some-of-the-best-deals-on-ps4-xbox-one-and-switch-for-black-friday-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEItK3lAECkQ9ce-2jE2iZAIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 15:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/22/google-express-has-some-of-the-best-deals-on-ps4-xbox-one-and-switch-for-black-friday-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Google Express Has Some Of The Best Deals On PS4, Xbox One And Switch For Black Friday 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xbox One X bundle Here’s an interesting, late-breaking retailer that’s throwing its hat firmly into the Black Friday ring for 2018: Google Express. It’s a Google partnership with Wal-Mart, Target, Costco and other retailers that is working as a sort of large-scale Amazon competitor. It’s not something I’ve used extensively or heard a huge amount about, but there’s no arguing with some of the prices it’s offering on video game consoles this Black Friday. I had thought that most of the deals had already solidified when I received this email last night, but there are several prices on here tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best Black Friday Deals On Xbox One, PlayStation 4 &amp; Nintendo Switch Consoles - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/22/best-black-friday-deals-on-gaming-consoles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAb5bW5bc6LjbiFO-Kho3FcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 16:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/22/best-black-friday-deals-on-gaming-consoles/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Black Friday Deals On Xbox One, PlayStation 4 &amp; Nintendo Switch Consoles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Game consoles aren’t cheap. In addition to buying a console for hundreds of dollars, you often need to buy a second controller to play with friends. And if you want games, dropping $60 for the latest and greatest titles is nothing new. But every year, even as games remain expensive and consoles add more capabilities, Black Friday comes around. And every year, a variety of retailers offer outstanding deals on the Nintendo Switch, Sony PlayStation 4, and Microsoft Xbox One that take the sting out of buying a new game console. When you’re buying a new console on sale, there are often some othe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Why The Wii U Beats Black Friday Nintendo Switch Bargains - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyrobertson/2018/11/21/why-the-wii-u-beats-black-friday-nintendo-switch-bargains/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEGllA0kZ99KW5E4BcB_OQ0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/andyrobertson/2018/11/21/why-the-wii-u-beats-black-friday-nintendo-switch-bargains/" target="_blank"&gt;Why The Wii U Beats Black Friday Nintendo Switch Bargains&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nintendo Switch is a great system for families, but my recommendation for a Nintendo Black Friday deal is the Wii U. Not only is it almost half the price to play many of the same (or very similar) games, but it offers multiplayer experiences like Nintendo Land that are still unmatched by the Switch. The Wii U underperformed by most measures, and is now perceived as something of a failed — or at least ill-timed — video game system. This reputation has a hidden benefit for families as the system’s games and hardware have a really low second hand price. Wii U Second Hand Price Tumbles Norm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 10 Best Video Gaming Deals For Black Friday 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/23/the-10-best-video-gaming-deals-for-black-friday-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKU61JrKsqgIJWx-_1K_UXQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 15:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/23/the-10-best-video-gaming-deals-for-black-friday-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;The 10 Best Video Gaming Deals For Black Friday 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black Friday is in full swing, though in most ways it’s already been in full swing for weeks. The video game world is not exactly shy about the crush of the holiday season, and retailers, console manufacturers, developers and online store owners have been pushing a wild morass of discounts basically since the beginning of the month, and they’ll keep doing so for some time. And yet there are still special deals to be had only on Black Friday, and there’s also a pleasant ritual about the biggest day of spending that American society has to offer, everyone soaked in stuffing and red wine and t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Cyber Monday 2018 Sales Preview: Walmart's Biggest Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/23/walmart-cyber-monday-2018-sale-iphone-ipad-xbox-one-ps4-slim-nintendo-switch-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENKACr0nFRvpRuuqGmEXuFUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/23/walmart-cyber-monday-2018-sale-iphone-ipad-xbox-one-ps4-slim-nintendo-switch-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyber Monday 2018 Sales Preview: Walmart's Biggest Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. Following Amazon’s early Cyber Monday sales, Walmart is announcing its own Cyber Monday sale right now and has confirmed many of the hottest tech products, from smartphones to games consoles. What’s more, I know many of the secret deals Walmart has yet to announce… My Cyber Monday 2018 store guides are already live for Amazon, for Best Buy ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Walmart's Black Friday 2018 Ad Has A Serious Problem - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/17/walmarts-black-friday-2018-ad-sales-xbox-one-x-ps4-slim-nintendo-switch-deals-problem/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIOP5iZDHYr6OxkO4oqdA50qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/17/walmarts-black-friday-2018-ad-sales-xbox-one-x-ps4-slim-nintendo-switch-deals-problem/" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart's Black Friday 2018 Ad Has A Serious Problem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. With Black Friday 2018 fast approaching it looks like Walmart’s 32-page Black Friday ad puts it in the box seat and its iPhone and Galaxy deals are the best around. But look closely and you’ll see one major area where Walmart simply cannot compete… Working with my holiday season sales partner BestBlackFriday.com, my Serious Problem Series highlights stores which are ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Pokémon: Let’s Go Pikachu &amp; Eevee! review – a children’s classic, refreshed - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/20/pokemon-lets-go-pikachu-eevee-review-nintendo-switch</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKw9XDTmmFyxFAhiKk49NMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 13:21:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/20/pokemon-lets-go-pikachu-eevee-review-nintendo-switch" target="_blank"&gt;Pokémon: Let’s Go Pikachu &amp; Eevee! review – a children’s classic, refreshed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A beloved childhood film can easily be shared with the next generation, but the cherished video games of 1990s children can now look off-puttingly primitive, even if they’re as fun to play as ever. Super Mario and Sonic the Hedgehog’s early outings might have weathered the years well, but Pokémon: Red and Blue, a foundational text of the millennial generation, has not. The originals were, after all, played on a two-inch Game Boy screen. Pokémon: Let’s Go Eevee! and Let’s Go Pikachu! are transformational remakes of those 20-year-old games for the Nintendo Switch, with bright, beautiful carto...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The best Nintendo Switch games | Our essential guide to the best titles for at home or on the go - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/best-nintendo-switch-games-essential-guide-best-titles-home/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHyrbZFA6vPyj_Lf3KXhw4EqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDs0LcF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 17:23:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/gaming/guides/best-nintendo-switch-games-essential-guide-best-titles-home/" target="_blank"&gt;The best Nintendo Switch games | Our essential guide to the best titles for at home or on the go&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first 18 months of the Nintendo Switch has produced a tremendous line-up of games. The idiosyncratic home-and-handheld hybrid console is host to a slew of inventive Nintendo treats and a range of independent gems. Even the big third-party publishers are getting involved. So out of that impressive nascent library, we pick our the 25 best Nintendo Switch games below. If there are any we have missed, then let us know your favourite Nintendo Switch games in the comments. And be sure to check out our list of the best PS4 games and best Xbox One games. Pokemon: Let’s Go The perfect stepping s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Why GameStop Has Some Of The Better Black Friday Deals On Switch, Xbox One And PS4 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/20/why-gamestop-has-some-of-the-better-black-friday-deals-on-switch-xbox-one-and-ps4/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBG0vcUmHC25pzNGpja8lawqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 19:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/20/why-gamestop-has-some-of-the-better-black-friday-deals-on-switch-xbox-one-and-ps4/" target="_blank"&gt;Why GameStop Has Some Of The Better Black Friday Deals On Switch, Xbox One And PS4&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;credit: Getty Yesterday, we posted the big deals from GameStop’s Black Friday ad: the biggest retailer in gaming didn’t come up short, particularly when it comes to software, and it’s looking like it will be one of the better destinations on Black Friday whether you’ve already got a current generation system or not. This might not be immediately apparent by looking at the ad, however, because there’s a ton of information there and the eye is naturally drawn to price tags, for obvious reasons. But you shouldn’t miss this one little line that puts it up above some other retailers: “Free $50 g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Pokémon: Let's Go' Review: It's Time To Go Back To A Rather Different Kanto - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2018/11/18/pokemon-lets-go-review-its-time-to-go-back-to-a-rather-different-kanto/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSaJ8U-V-ehXxFZdOTKwf4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/games/2018/11/18/pokemon-lets-go-review-its-time-to-go-back-to-a-rather-different-kanto/" target="_blank"&gt;'Pokémon: Let's Go' Review: It's Time To Go Back To A Rather Different Kanto&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Pokémon: Let’s Go’ retains a lot from the classic mainline games in the series. Back when the Switch was launched last year, it was somewhat obvious that certain studios were taken aback by its massive popularity. So much so that developers like Game Freak realized they had to get in on the action and fast, and lo Pokémon: Let’s Go was born. For those that played Pokémon back during the Game Boy days, then the approach in Let’s Go will be very familiar. That’s because Pokémon: Let’s Go is based on Pokémon Yellow but by way of the newer mobile phenomenon Pokémon GO. This means we are back i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Gamestop's Best Cyber Monday 2018 Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/25/gamestops-best-cyber-monday-2018-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENQwpqIZKLiyn7sPi-P5jWsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 08:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2018/11/25/gamestops-best-cyber-monday-2018-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Gamestop's Best Cyber Monday 2018 Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gamestop is extending and improving upon many of its Black Friday deals for Cyber Monday. Remember, these deals are only available online. Detail of a Microsoft Xbox One X home console, taken on October January 19, 2018. (Photo by Neil Godwin/T3 Magazine via Getty Images) photo credit: 2018 Future Publishing The retailer has an excellent deal for all of the year’s top sports games. Madden 19, NBA 2K19, FIFA 19 and WWE 2K19 were slashed to just $27.00. If you or a sports gamer on your list were waiting until the holidays to grab up these titles, you’d be hardpressed to find a better deal on ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Cyber Monday 2018 Ad Sales: Here Are Walmart's Best Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/26/walmart-cyber-monday-2018-ad-sales-xbox-one-x-iphone-nintendo-switch-laptops-tv-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAdB5z2kByTRDwVNczakJdYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 18:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/26/walmart-cyber-monday-2018-ad-sales-xbox-one-x-iphone-nintendo-switch-laptops-tv-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyber Monday 2018 Ad Sales: Here Are Walmart's Best Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected. Only BestBlackFriday.com will receive compensation from them. Cyber Monday 2018 is running white hot with Amazon’s mega sales, Walmart’s updated deals, big Samsung discounts Best Buy and Target running site-wide extra savings, Thanks to store’s extensive Cyber Monday ad scan we know. And there are genuine Star Buys among them… My dedicated Cyber Monday 2018 store guides are now live for Amazon, for A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Pokémon GO': It's Basically Impossible To Evolve Meltan Without 'Pokémon Let's Go' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/18/melmetal-pokemon-go-its-basically-impossible-to-get-melmetal-without-pokemon-lets-go/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDtxPF-1GqAnxlhJQKfPQdkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/18/melmetal-pokemon-go-its-basically-impossible-to-get-melmetal-without-pokemon-lets-go/" target="_blank"&gt;'Pokémon GO': It's Basically Impossible To Evolve Meltan Without 'Pokémon Let's Go'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melmetal Pokémon GO introduces new creatures all the time, but these ones are different. Meltan and Melmetal, just introduced on Friday, are something different. They’re not just new Pokémon for Pokémon GO, they’re new Pokémon period: brand-new character designs meant as a cross-promotion for Pokemon Let’s Go Pikachu and Eevee, a set of new games just released for the Nintendo Switch. As far as cross-promotion goes, it’s a no-brainer: a unique Pokémon tied to a new Pokémon game just sort of makes sense. And yet the idea also raises the ever-present issue of “pay-to-win” for free-to-play gam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>A Warning To Anyone Looking For A Deal On PS4 Pro This Black Friday - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/20/a-warning-to-anyone-looking-for-a-deal-on-ps4-pro-this-black-friday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKQZEJR6XRhduziaoPci9kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 20:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/20/a-warning-to-anyone-looking-for-a-deal-on-ps4-pro-this-black-friday/" target="_blank"&gt;A Warning To Anyone Looking For A Deal On PS4 Pro This Black Friday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;God of War. By and large, Black Friday is a good time to buy video game hardware. It’s not subject to some of the same bait and switch that you see in a lot of other industries, mostly because there isn’t a lot of room to do so with so few products and fairly well-known price points. If you see a good price you can buy it with some confidence: there’s a chance you might see someone match the price in the coming months, but it’s very unlikely that anyone is going to go lower. So go nuts when it comes to the Xbox One S, the Xbox One X, the PS4 or the Nintendo Switch. There’s one major console...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>eBay Pre-Black Friday 2018: Best Deals On Gaming Consoles And Accessories - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/15/ebay-pre-black-friday-2018-best-deals-on-gaming-consoles-and-accessories/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOnReOg5UUujuvJwIcY8xQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbes-finds/2018/11/15/ebay-pre-black-friday-2018-best-deals-on-gaming-consoles-and-accessories/" target="_blank"&gt;eBay Pre-Black Friday 2018: Best Deals On Gaming Consoles And Accessories&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re ready to go shopping online and want to find some deals, eBay is an outstanding destination. Over the years, eBay has evolved into a desirable destination for online shoppers. The marketplace has a variety of products new and old, new and used, and offers some of the best prices on the market. Best of all, eBay has solidified itself as a place where you can find the products you desire at prices you’d be surprised to get. It’s against that backdrop that we recently evaluated eBay for deals on video game products. From the latest and greatest consoles to the best games, eBay has so...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fallout 76 review: Can feel more like a task than a glorious adventure - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/fallout-76-review-game-xbox-ps4-pc-bethesda-multiplayer-bugs-a8639871.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGUfRkIlSMqhWuM22s-dL3wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 15:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/gaming/fallout-76-review-game-xbox-ps4-pc-bethesda-multiplayer-bugs-a8639871.html" target="_blank"&gt;Fallout 76 review: Can feel more like a task than a glorious adventure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallout 76 is a lonely place. Emerging from your vault, two decades after nuclear war has devastated the Earth, your task to reclaim the ashes of what’s left is an inglorious one. There is no one to celebrate your toil, no one to commemorate you as a hero. Bethesda’s prequel to its Fallout series has taken the increasingly popular route of the online multiplayer – the irony is just how isolating an experience that can be. Each map hosts a maximum of 24 people, which means chance encounters with other settlers are a rarity. Even with several hours invested both into the game and its beta rel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Best Buy 'Cyber Monday' 2018 Sales: What We Know So Far - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/17/best-buy-cyber-monday-2018-sales-iphone-xbox-ps4-galaxy-phone-sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPGPgcDYRNflZM3f7WpvuFsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/17/best-buy-cyber-monday-2018-sales-iphone-xbox-ps4-galaxy-phone-sales/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy 'Cyber Monday' 2018 Sales: What We Know So Far&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. As Black Friday 2018 approaches, doubts emerge: Will there be a better deal on Cyber Monday? Since this sales holiday is growing even faster than Black Friday, that’s a valid question. So do you wait? When it comes to Best Buy (52-page Black Friday ad scan), we have a very good idea… This is the second in my Cyber Monday 2018 preview series, following my Walmart Cybe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nasdaq contains losses as Nvidia woes hit chipmakers - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/56b0e776-e999-11e8-885c-e64da4c0f981</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP_ar6JULswJGx40-UAz51QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 00:58:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/56b0e776-e999-11e8-885c-e64da4c0f981" target="_blank"&gt;Nasdaq contains losses as Nvidia woes hit chipmakers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another spate of gloomy outlook statements by computer chipmakers has cast renewed doubts on the strength of the electronics market, as shares in Nintendo and its Switch graphics unit supplier Nvidia both plunged. The technology-heavy Nasdaq Composite fell more than 1 per cent at the market’s open on Friday as unexpectedly weak sales guidance from Nvidia knocked the wider semiconductor sector and further fuelled concerns that chip demand could be set for a slowdown. By the end of the day the Nasdaq had recovered most of the losses but was 0.15 per cent lower at 7,247.87 points. Shares in Nv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>First Look At GameStop's 'Black Friday' 2018 Deals: Discounts On Xbox One X, PS4 And Games - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/13/first-look-at-gamestops-black-friday-2018-deals-discounts-on-xbox-one-x-ps4-and-games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6XgvtWkh5VRDVfuBTAfnsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 15:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/13/first-look-at-gamestops-black-friday-2018-deals-discounts-on-xbox-one-x-ps4-and-games/" target="_blank"&gt;First Look At GameStop's 'Black Friday' 2018 Deals: Discounts On Xbox One X, PS4 And Games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s the big one, as far as gaming is concerned. Places like Best Buy, Target and Walmart have plenty to offer the video gaming public when it comes to deals for Balck Friday 2018, but GameStop is by far the largest gaming-focused retailer in the United States, and as such it’s a good place to go if you know what you want for Black Friday, and if that thing is games. We still don’t have the company’s full ad yet, but last night we got a look at a sneak peek teasing its biggest deals. So let’s look at some of the best GameStop deals for Balck Friday 2018 on things like Xbox One X, Nintendo S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best Buy's Black Friday 2018 Ad Has Nasty Surprises - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/10/best-buy-black-friday-2018-ad-free-shipping-iphone-xbox-one-nintendo-switch-sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPopCwzHq4gavO-hxByF-mMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/10/best-buy-black-friday-2018-ad-free-shipping-iphone-xbox-one-nintendo-switch-sales/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy's Black Friday 2018 Ad Has Nasty Surprises&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. Black Friday 2018 is counting down fast and some of the most impressive deals come from Best Buy’s 52-page Black Friday ad. On the surface, it has tempting savings on iPhones, Galaxy phones, the PS4, Xbox One, HDTVs and much more. But dig deeper and you will find not everything is as it seems. Just like Walmart’s problematic deals, Best Buy’s ad is hiding a number of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Best Buy's Black Friday 2018 Gaming Deals: Big Discounts On Nintendo Switch, Xbox, PS4 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/09/best-buys-black-friday-2018-gaming-deals-big-discounts-on-nintendo-switch-xbox-ps4/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPAfH0FFxO328H3x3tgMevcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 15:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/09/best-buys-black-friday-2018-gaming-deals-big-discounts-on-nintendo-switch-xbox-ps4/" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy's Black Friday 2018 Gaming Deals: Big Discounts On Nintendo Switch, Xbox, PS4&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty The big Black Friday ads are starting to come in. Yesterday we heard from Walmart, always one of the biggest centers of Black Friday madness whether we’re talking about tech or not, and today we’re hearing from Best Buy, the most recognizable physical electronics retailer in the country and always a major destination for consoles and games, not to mention HDTVs, sound systems and more or less everything else with a microchip in it. Today we’re focusing on all those gaming deals you can get, and it’s a good time to buy a Nintendo Switch, an Xbox One S or X, a PS4 or any games to go wit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The 11 best Nintendo Switch games of all time - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/06/11-best-games-on-nintendo-switch-mario-zelda</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGhVijJtGHzQ90TV6vtp2YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:45:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/nov/06/11-best-games-on-nintendo-switch-mario-zelda" target="_blank"&gt;The 11 best Nintendo Switch games of all time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Splatoon 2 A novel and lively take on the shooter genre that has you splattering urban arenas with bright ink, switching between human and squid forms to swim around in the resultant sea of colour. The funky 90s street-style aesthetic perfectly complements the fun, frenetic play, and it’s had so many updates since its release that you are constantly getting more for your money. • Read the review Super Mario Odyssey Mario sets off to run and jump around little planets again, each a self-contained ecosystem of puzzles, challenges and weird inhabitants that Mario can temporarily possess with h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Black Friday 2018 Preview: GameStop Deals On Xbox One, Switch, PS4, And Games - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/07/black-friday-2018-preview-gamestop-deals-on-xbox-one-switch-ps4-and-games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBJZXsd8MTWwPv6mfQNMHk4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 15:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/07/black-friday-2018-preview-gamestop-deals-on-xbox-one-switch-ps4-and-games/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Friday 2018 Preview: GameStop Deals On Xbox One, Switch, PS4, And Games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gamestop store facade. If you’re looking to load up on games and gaming hardware, there are few better times to do it than Black Friday. Sure, there are some times that are as good, but gaming is one of those places where we actually do see some of the best deals of the year on the day after Thanksgiving, and so you can safely make purchases without wondering too much about whether or not better deals will come along int he next few weeks–not necessarily true about the trickier worlds of TVs and such. GameStop is usually one of your best bets, too: as the only large-scale gaming-focused ret...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Kirby Is Getting A Giant Head Devouring Plush Next Summer - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/11/07/kirby-is-getting-a-giant-head-devouring-plush-next-summer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED9qO4AgJWBQNUz4vPlnPRUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 06:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/11/07/kirby-is-getting-a-giant-head-devouring-plush-next-summer/" target="_blank"&gt;Kirby Is Getting A Giant Head Devouring Plush Next Summer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The upcoming Kirby plush. Following the recent shocking trailer for Super Smash Bros. Ultimate, we now at least have a giant head devouring plush of Kirby on the way. If you missed the epic World of Light trailer (shown below) it results in Kirby surviving the annihilation of his Super Smash Bros. allies and forced to fix the world alone. Considering that the series started back with HAL Laboratory in 1999 for the N64 and that Masahiro Sakurai has helmed the games in the series since, the fact Kirby has been singled out like this should not be all that surprising. Anyway, everyone loves Kir...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Developers Discuss 'Diablo: Immortal' And How It Fits In Blizzard's Plans - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/hnewman/2018/11/09/developers-discuss-diablo-immortal-and-how-it-fits-in-blizzards-plans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKDjd2kWQ_JeVfp9uOge7hsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 19:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/hnewman/2018/11/09/developers-discuss-diablo-immortal-and-how-it-fits-in-blizzards-plans/" target="_blank"&gt;Developers Discuss 'Diablo: Immortal' And How It Fits In Blizzard's Plans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diablo: Immortal Fans’ reaction to the announcement of the upcoming Blizzard Entertainment mobile title Diablo: Immortal at the BlizzCon convention last weekend was swift and vicious. We caught up with two leading developers at the show to discuss game’s design and that response. Team members were booed from the audience, fans posited during a Q&amp;A hour that this was some kind of early April Fool’s Day joke, and the buzz overall was so negative that parent company Activision Blizzard’s stock dropped, apparently in reaction. Developers on stage were quick to reassure players that there were o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>What To Expect From Nintendo Switch Deals For Black Friday 2018 - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/02/what-to-expect-from-nintendo-switch-deals-for-black-friday-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELrvvIcHrv_bfxPsg9tuo_EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/02/what-to-expect-from-nintendo-switch-deals-for-black-friday-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;What To Expect From Nintendo Switch Deals For Black Friday 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super Mario Odyssey. If you’re looking to buy a new console, you could do a whole lot worse than late November. In most cases, you could actually do a whole lot worse than early November or December, but Black Friday remains the best time to pick up the best deals. That means those magical hours when the Thanksgiving meal wears off and everyone storms into the world of retail to buy whatever it is they’ve been putting off buying. Historically speaking, that day has some of if not the best deals on most consoles for the year. So let’s say you’re looking to buy a Nintendo Switch this holiday ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>eBay's Early Black Friday 2018 Has Some Good Gaming Deals On Switch, Xbox One X, PS4, Red Dead - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/05/ebays-early-black-friday-2018-has-some-good-gaming-deals-on-switch-xbox-one-x-ps4-red-dead/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAfXPJ1xfKgsUAO-NoR-m5EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 14:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/05/ebays-early-black-friday-2018-has-some-good-gaming-deals-on-switch-xbox-one-x-ps4-red-dead/" target="_blank"&gt;eBay's Early Black Friday 2018 Has Some Good Gaming Deals On Switch, Xbox One X, PS4, Red Dead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red Dead Redemption 2 Black Friday has had a way of expanding over the last few years. We remember that this is a retailer focused holiday more than a consumer-focused one: it’s the day when these retailers make it into the black for the season, selling as much merchandise as they possibly can to holiday shoppers. With that in mind, it’s not shocking that retailers are doing their best to start the party early and keep it going. eBay currently has some early Black Friday deals going up, and there are some excellent options for gamers out there. eBay isn’t always the first place you look fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Big Sale Has $60 Off Nintendo Switch, Savings On Xbox One X And 'Red Dead Redemption 2' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/01/google-express-sale-has-60-off-nintendo-switch-savings-on-xbox-one-x-and-red-dead-redemption-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKVwQ-aVqGVrGHIzgm7EJvcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 16:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/01/google-express-sale-has-60-off-nintendo-switch-savings-on-xbox-one-x-and-red-dead-redemption-2/" target="_blank"&gt;Big Sale Has $60 Off Nintendo Switch, Savings On Xbox One X And 'Red Dead Redemption 2'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nintendo Switch. The Nintendo Switch is still a pretty new console, as far as these things go. It’s pretty hard to find anywhere below its MSRP of $299.99, and for a while, it was even hard to find at that price. We see bundles and other deals from time to time, but by and large you’re paying full price for this thing, at least now. Which makes today’s Google Express sale all the more remarkable: a wide-ranging code is giving 20% off a bunch of stuff, which means that you can take $60 off the price of a new Nintendo Switch. To get the discount, use promo code Wish20. With that extra mon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Walmart 'Black Friday' 2018 Ad Preview: Expected iPhone, Galaxy, Switch, Xbox One Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/04/walmart-black-friday-2018-ad-preview-sales-apple-iphone-samsung-galaxy-microsoft-xbox-one-x-nintendo-switch-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKFpKrll1NOb98MfEE4-AyMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 21:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gordonkelly/2018/11/04/walmart-black-friday-2018-ad-preview-sales-apple-iphone-samsung-galaxy-microsoft-xbox-one-x-nintendo-switch-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart 'Black Friday' 2018 Ad Preview: Expected iPhone, Galaxy, Switch, Xbox One Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This post was created by the Contributor in partnership with BestBlackFriday.com, which specializes in holiday season sales. The deals highlighted within this post were independently selected and do not contain affiliate links. Black Friday 2018 already seems to be breaking records and the most sought-after deals from Walmart’s big circular have yet to be revealed. But, now that we have seen the 13-page Dell Black Friday ad, the 77-page JCPenney Black Friday ad, the 20-page Sam’s Club One-Day Sale ad and the 47-page Target Black Friday ad all leak, the picture for Walmart’s hottest items is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Black Friday 2018: What To Expect From Xbox One X Deals - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/05/black-friday-2018-what-to-expect-from-xbox-one-x-deals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1yoIwGG0csCfSs6uKvZsQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 16:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/05/black-friday-2018-what-to-expect-from-xbox-one-x-deals/" target="_blank"&gt;Black Friday 2018: What To Expect From Xbox One X Deals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xbox One X. If you held off on buying Microsoft’s ultra-powerful Xbox One X at launch, I don’t blame you. The beastly console is one impressive piece of hardware, but at launch it was hard to tell exactly which games it was meant to show off: no third-party titles were out that truly showed off the machine’s full power, and Microsoft’s lagging first-party support meant that exclusive titles just weren’t up to par with what we were seeing from Sony. Now, however, things are looking brighter. Not only is Xbox One X the best place to play Red Dead Redemption 2, but there are also a few more mu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nintendo Reveals 3 New Fighters For 'Super Smash Bros.' On Switch, And One Is Bizzare - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/01/nintendo-reveals-3-new-fighters-for-super-smash-bros-on-switch-and-one-is-bizzare/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJBR0TPm2QbIuDeIAqkr8tsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 15:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/01/nintendo-reveals-3-new-fighters-for-super-smash-bros-on-switch-and-one-is-bizzare/" target="_blank"&gt;Nintendo Reveals 3 New Fighters For 'Super Smash Bros.' On Switch, And One Is Bizzare&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Super Smash Bros. for Nintendo Switch. And that’s all, folks: a series of Nintendo Directs that began at E3 ends today, and Nintendo has now revealed the complete roster of 74 fighters that will be available for the launch of Super Smash Bros. on Nintendo Switch, with the final 2 launch fighters coming in today as well as the game’s first post-launch fighter. That last one is very weird, so let’s dive in here. Ken: Smash bros Ryu has been available for a little while here, and so it makes sense that Ken is showing up now. Ken will be an “echo fighter” of Ryu, something we’ve seen with a few...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here Are Kohl's Black Friday 2018 Gaming Deals, Big Discounts On Xbox One X And Nintendo Switch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/03/here-are-kohls-black-friday-2018-gaming-deals-big-discounts-on-xbox-one-x-and-nintendo-switch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN98CHi1s9sFipeBXNeCWlQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/11/03/here-are-kohls-black-friday-2018-gaming-deals-big-discounts-on-xbox-one-x-and-nintendo-switch/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are Kohl's Black Friday 2018 Gaming Deals, Big Discounts On Xbox One X And Nintendo Switch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kohl’s Black Friday ad. Black Friday leaking season is rolling in earnest, with full ads from places like Target and Costco already in the mix. It’s looking like a good year for console deals, with the Xbox One S, PS4, Xbox One X, and PS4 Pro all mature enough to be pushing for some impressive bundles and discounts as we enter into the golden years of this hardware generation. Today, we’re going to look at the gaming deals from Kohl’s, which are always some of the best on offer. For Kohl’s full ad scan, head to BestBlackFriday.com. For other tech deals, check out Gordon Kelly. As in past y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Junichi Masuda Talks About How 'Pokémon GO' Inspired The Creation Of 'Pokémon: Let's Go!' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/11/01/junichi-masuda-talks-about-how-pokemon-go-inspired-the-creation-of-pokemon-lets-go/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFcPJZTSjbCLT22tfY5l4eIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/11/01/junichi-masuda-talks-about-how-pokemon-go-inspired-the-creation-of-pokemon-lets-go/" target="_blank"&gt;Junichi Masuda Talks About How 'Pokémon GO' Inspired The Creation Of 'Pokémon: Let's Go!'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Pokémon: Let’s Go!’ was in part inspired by ‘Pokémon GO’. Considering that we don’t have long until the release of Pokémon: Let’s Go! on the Switch, I spoke with the game’s director Junichi Masuda about the game and its inspirations. Since the launch of the Switch last March, I wanted to understand how Pokémon: Let’s Go! had come about and Masuda explained that it had a lot to do with Pokémon GO. “With the release of Pokémon GO, many new players caught Pokémon all around the world and the awareness of Pokémon in general increased. “At the same time, I knew that there were many kids under t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Fowl play: Untitled Goose Game captures the pure joy of being a huge nuisance - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/oct/31/fowl-play-untitled-goose-game-captures-the-pure-joy-of-being-a-huge-nuisance</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFDfVs4iX9OGd3ZQ0XFBrPYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 22:32:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/games/2018/oct/31/fowl-play-untitled-goose-game-captures-the-pure-joy-of-being-a-huge-nuisance" target="_blank"&gt;Fowl play: Untitled Goose Game captures the pure joy of being a huge nuisance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Untitled Goose Game has a very simple pitch: you are a horrible goose and your aim is to ruin everybody’s day. “We thought this was a funny thing, with niche appeal,” says programmer Nico Disseldorp of House House, the four-person Melbourne-based development studio behind Untitled Goose Game. “We thought, ‘Oh, we’d love a game about a naughty animal.’ “We completely underestimated that everyone else seemed to want the same thing.” Related: Red Dead Redemption 2 gamers queue for midnight release After their initial PC trailer became something of a breakout hit, House House found themselves b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Sony and Nintendo pin hopes on new games launches - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9732c41c-dc39-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMm-OnYFzvPKy60iOswZ7o0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 14:11:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9732c41c-dc39-11e8-9f04-38d397e6661c" target="_blank"&gt;Sony and Nintendo pin hopes on new games launches&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new presidents of Nintendo and Sony are betting heavily on the seasonal temptations of Wild West gunslingers, ancient Greek mercenaries and a madcap punch-up as Japan’s games console giants battle to maintain record earnings into 2019. The companies’ focus on their respective pipelines of new games come as Sony said it was targeting a second consecutive full year of record profits led by its PlayStation division. Nintendo, meanwhile, reaffirmed a sales goal that calls for it to sell nearly 15m units of its Switch console between October 1 and the end of March. The two companies, which r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Here Are All The Free PlayStation Plus Games For November (2018) - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/31/here-are-all-the-free-playstation-plus-games-for-november-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHQ11b6wwTVMmakJRfZxg6IqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 16:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/31/here-are-all-the-free-playstation-plus-games-for-november-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are All The Free PlayStation Plus Games For November (2018)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullet Storm: Full Clip Edition is one of November’s free PS Plus games. November is just hours away at this point, so it may feel like Sony is a bit tardy with next month’s free PlayStation Plus games announcement. That’s because the PlayStation 4 manufacturer always announces the following month’s free games on the last Wednesday of the month, and then releases those games on PS+ the following Wednesday. Since Halloween, the last day of October, falls on a Wednesday, that means we had to wait a little longer than usual to find out. The games in this list will become available on November ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Adi Shankar Could Be In Talks To Make A New TV Series For 'The Legend Of Zelda' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/10/30/adi-shankar-could-be-in-talks-to-make-a-new-tv-series-for-the-legend-of-zelda/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEISEouaXsuE-4eyKzgx37ScqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 08:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/10/30/adi-shankar-could-be-in-talks-to-make-a-new-tv-series-for-the-legend-of-zelda/" target="_blank"&gt;Adi Shankar Could Be In Talks To Make A New TV Series For 'The Legend Of Zelda'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘The Legend of Zelda’ may receive a new series. Producer Adi Shankar recently revealed that he is working on producing a new TV series based on a famous Japanese gaming property and it looks like it could be The Legend of Zelda. While Shankar said that the official reveal of the series would be on November 16, according to The Wrap the series in question could be The Legend of Zelda. If true, this would not be the first time the Zelda games have received their own series. Back at the end of the 80s, there was a 13 episode cartoon made for Zelda. Though this was mostly terrible, with utterly...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Sega Is Having Some Exciting Talks About Dreamcast Games On Switch - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2018/10/24/sega-is-having-some-exciting-talks-about-dreamcast-games-on-switch/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDAMLMdYkHJlnlBs0QoaasqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 09:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jasonevangelho/2018/10/24/sega-is-having-some-exciting-talks-about-dreamcast-games-on-switch/" target="_blank"&gt;Sega Is Having Some Exciting Talks About Dreamcast Games On Switch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The possibility of Dreamcast games arriving on the Nintendo Switch via the Sega AGES program is dancing much closer to reality today. In a recently published interview with Famitsu, Sega M2 President Naoki Horii has revealed the company is having serious discussions about whether to emulate the games or utilize existing source code to port them over. Dreamcast games on Switch inch closer to reality. That this conversation is happening at all should fill Dreamcast fans with bright rays of hope. Up to this point Sega has shown ambition for adding classic Dreamcast games to the Sega AGES lineu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>'Dragon Quest Builders 2' Will Have Online Multiplayer - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/10/26/dragon-quest-builders-2-will-have-online-multiplayer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHts3Tf1aN6LX1XruhkvRHgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 03:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/10/26/dragon-quest-builders-2-will-have-online-multiplayer/" target="_blank"&gt;'Dragon Quest Builders 2' Will Have Online Multiplayer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Dragon Quest Builders 2′ is released in Japan this December. In a recent update, it looks like the upcoming Dragon Quest Builders 2 will have online multiplayer. The original Dragon Quest Builders had an asynchronous share setup, where you could build things and randomly share them with other players in the free play mode. In the latest issue of Weekly Jump though, it looks like the team at Square Enix has built on this online setup even further. Specifically, it now looks like you will be able to have a total of four players working together online to build and craft items. Communication ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Nintendo Switch is headed to school - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/23/tech/nintendo-labo-switch-education-classroom/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBhRTlrUhFM4rUmXyM3qpPkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMKrxrwU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 15:40:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/23/tech/nintendo-labo-switch-education-classroom/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nintendo Switch is headed to school&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nintendo has long been synonymous with entertainment. But now the gaming giant is getting into education. The company announced on Tuesday it is partnering with education nonprofit Institute of Play to bring its popular Switch gaming console and DIY Labo kits to 100 classrooms across the United States. The effort aims to help kids build communication and critical thinking skills in science, technology, engineering, art and mathematics (STEAM). The Nintendo Switch, which is both a handheld and home console, sold roughly 10 million units after its launch. In January 2018, the company introduc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Don't Wait: GameStop's Best Ever 'Xbox One X' Trade-In Deal Ends Today - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/28/dont-wait-gamestops-best-ever-xbox-one-x-trade-in-deal-ends-today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC1Ko88ahTE_dZCYDGSECgwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/28/dont-wait-gamestops-best-ever-xbox-one-x-trade-in-deal-ends-today/" target="_blank"&gt;Don't Wait: GameStop's Best Ever 'Xbox One X' Trade-In Deal Ends Today&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss this amazing deal on an Xbox One X. GameStop is offering some pretty amazing trade-in deals if you’re in the market for an Xbox One X. The only problem? The deals end today. You have mere hours left to upgrade to Microsoft’s best console, something you should absolutely do if you want to play games in actual 4K. There’s no denying that cross-platform games look best on the Xbox One X (though Sony still leads the pack when it comes to excellent PlayStation 4 exclusives like God of War and Marvel’s Spider-Man. In any case, here’s what GameStop is offering for your hardware trade-in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>How Nintendo Is Bringing Labo Into Classrooms - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2018/10/23/how-nintendo-is-bringing-labo-to-classrooms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEr819gMjtf1Xo7E5StWlfUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 17:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattperez/2018/10/23/how-nintendo-is-bringing-labo-to-classrooms/" target="_blank"&gt;How Nintendo Is Bringing Labo Into Classrooms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nintendo partners with Institute of Play to bring Nintendo Labo to Douglas G Grafflin School on Friday, Oct. 12, 2018 in Chappaqua, N.Y. Nintendo’s quirky cardboard construction set, Labo, always seemed ripe for exploration as an educational tool, and now the company wants to put that theory to the test. Nintendo is partnering with the Institute of Play for an initiative to bring Labo into classrooms as a facilitator of STEAM learning. The two companies have just concluded early pilot programs introducing Nintendo Labo into 11 elementary schools in the New York tri-state area. Their next st...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The New Crossover Pokémon Meltan Can Evolve Into Melmetal - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/10/25/the-new-crossover-pokemon-meltan-can-evolve-into-melmetal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOkyndM6sOO1fe2kgfuMFOIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 09:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/olliebarder/2018/10/25/the-new-crossover-pokemon-meltan-can-evolve-into-melmetal/" target="_blank"&gt;The New Crossover Pokémon Meltan Can Evolve Into Melmetal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new evolved form of Meltal, Melmetal. In an interesting piece of news, the crossover Pokémon Meltan can now evolve into the much larger and more potent Melmetal. In a new video (shown below), we get to see the recently announced Meltan Pokémon evolve into Melmetal. Considering that Meltan is a new Pokémon that promotes the crossover between Pokémon GO on mobile and the upcoming Pokémon: Let’s Go! on the Switch, the Pokémon’s evolution into Melmetal is similarly structured. Meltan will only evolve into Melmetal in Pokémon GO and will need 400 Meltan Candies. You can get Meltan Candies by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Here's Where You Can Get An Xbox One X For $200, With Trade-in - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/22/heres-where-you-can-get-an-xbox-one-x-for-200-with-trade-in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMBJDMaNcARr8GV7wlyG-V0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 17:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2018/10/22/heres-where-you-can-get-an-xbox-one-x-for-200-with-trade-in/" target="_blank"&gt;Here's Where You Can Get An Xbox One X For $200, With Trade-in&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xbox One X Console and Controller. It’s not Black Friday yet, but as it turns out this is a very good time to get an Xbox One X. We just recently heard about a Red Dead Redemption 2 bundle that gives you $100 off any console along with the hotly-anticipated open-world cowboy game, and now it seems that Gamestop is giving us another opportunity to upgrade our hardware with an excellent-sounding trade-in deal. Under Gamestop’s new trade-in deal, you can get $300 off of a new Xbox One X by trading in a PlayStation 4 Pro, it’s less-powerful but generationally equivalent Sony counterpart. Which ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>The Good, The Bad And The Ugly Of 'Starlink: Battle For Atlas' - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/18/the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly-of-starlink-battle-for-atlas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB6xarAVFqrqEom8F9xX_EQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2018/10/18/the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly-of-starlink-battle-for-atlas/" target="_blank"&gt;The Good, The Bad And The Ugly Of 'Starlink: Battle For Atlas'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starlink: Battle For Atlas is great fun, but it’s held back by expensive toys-to-life DLC that limits its gameplay potential. Without really getting into the story of Starlink: Battle For Atlas, I want to talk about the time I’ve spent with the game and why I think it’s such a great space adventure. Ubisoft is attempting to revive the Toys-to-Life genre here, with a game that links physical spaceships and miniatures to the digital experience. It does so in one of the best, most stylish ways I’ve ever seen. For one thing, the spaceships themselves are really cool toys, and the minis—all char...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item></channel></rss>