<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Child marriage - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREkxTTNOaUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-ZW&amp;gl=ZW&amp;ceid=ZW:en</link><language>en-ZW</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:27:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>'Multi-faceted strategies needed to curb child marriages' - NewsDay</title><link>https://www.newsday.co.zw/2018/12/multi-faceted-strategies-needed-to-curb-child-marriages/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiWmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5ld3NkYXkuY28uencvMjAxOC8xMi9tdWx0aS1mYWNldGVkLXN0cmF0ZWdpZXMtbmVlZGVkLXRvLWN1cmItY2hpbGQtbWFycmlhZ2VzL9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 12:23:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsday.co.zw/2018/12/multi-faceted-strategies-needed-to-curb-child-marriages/" target="_blank"&gt;'Multi-faceted strategies needed to curb child marriages'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;NewsDay&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MULTI-FACETED strategies are needed to curb the prevalence of child marriages, a practice which has disadvantaged many young girls in Zimbabwe who are ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsday.co.zw">NewsDay</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/ZWR8wPVsjoS1ADNqltBA0jdbyJBVs8MKPctUTy7UTkIS3RsKjo_1dCqDH9r0yK2cNWp3VM8Jko7DnvrPBOLWZ7hO6kJNynGK04Rf1j9P1YkfTciMwBR6b3z4pjpoWqEuMmO8nsOHrZkP90kk5WuaoM-tMusQvU89AAGHOLlgFgMvJ79PFc_-uod56Via7KZXlGK3ZH-Mwmu_ZQvl6_N-wxmR238w2tWhqAPoXGkIrZ8GquDtHIHRviQ15wE_bH0JpK7TrPeZjBIEfjrzzYSSwLKjapFOS3WCsftrWzyKhyIq0pb4voNbfgt47YYU00Hs7iiAAS5xyb6FjpEfoWUuwrepqtkxhBPvRjk=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>I am a man, I call for an end to forced child marriages - The Herald</title><link>https://www.herald.co.zw/i-am-a-man-i-call-for-an-end-to-forced-child-marriages/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiUGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmhlcmFsZC5jby56dy9pLWFtLWEtbWFuLWktY2FsbC1mb3ItYW4tZW5kLXRvLWZvcmNlZC1jaGlsZC1tYXJyaWFnZXMv0gGdAWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LWhlcmFsZC1jby16dy5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3d3dy5oZXJhbGQuY28uencvaS1hbS1hLW1hbi1pLWNhbGwtZm9yLWFuLWVuZC10by1mb3JjZWQtY2hpbGQtbWFycmlhZ2VzL2FtcC8_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 04:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.herald.co.zw/i-am-a-man-i-call-for-an-end-to-forced-child-marriages/" target="_blank"&gt;I am a man, I call for an end to forced child marriages&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Herald&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forced child marriage is both a symptom of poverty and a conduit through which it is perpetuated, as some families that struggle to provide for their children view ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.herald.co.zw">The Herald</source></item><item><title>UNICEF USA BrandVoice: To Build A Better Future, Yemen's Children Must Be Educated - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2018/12/06/to-build-a-better-future-yemens-children-must-be-educated/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDk8xx76CR10QMbVo9upMsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:19:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/unicefusa/2018/12/06/to-build-a-better-future-yemens-children-must-be-educated/" target="_blank"&gt;UNICEF USA BrandVoice: To Build A Better Future, Yemen's Children Must Be Educated&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For over 70 years, UNICEF has been putting children first, working to protect their rights and provide the assistance and services they need to survive and thrive all over the world. Almost four years of fighting have taken a devastating toll on the people of Yemen, and children have suffered most of all. “Nearly 1.5 million children have been displaced, many of them living a life that is a mere shadow of what childhood should be,” says UNICEF Regional Director for Middle East and North Africa Geert Cappelaere. [id=0] Cappelaere recently visited Yemen to see how UNICEF and partners are hel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Facebook under fire for posts on auction of child bride - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/20/africa/south-sudan-child-bride-facebook-auction-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJaxyxxv6gnBPyOxDWWtKmMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 13:53:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/20/africa/south-sudan-child-bride-facebook-auction-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook under fire for posts on auction of child bride&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story has been updated and further details added about the role of Facebook in the auction based on new reporting and information. Facebook has come under fire after posts discussing the sale of a child bride were made and shared on its site. An auction was discussed on the social media platform for a girl aged 16 or 17 in South Sudan that sought payment for her hand in marriage. Facebook said the post was taken down as soon as the company learned of it, but that wasn't until after the girl involved was married. According to children's rights organization Plan International, the girl w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>'Barbaric use of technology': Facebook slammed over child bride auction - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-22/facebook-slammed-over-child-marriage-auction-in-south-sudan/10518232</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGvGwlcnFMiy4NMVOKfpkfkqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 21:18:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-22/facebook-slammed-over-child-marriage-auction-in-south-sudan/10518232" target="_blank"&gt;'Barbaric use of technology': Facebook slammed over child bride auction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has been criticised for allowing a 16-year-old child bride in South Sudan to be auctioned off to the highest bidder on its platform. Her father received 500 cows, two luxury cars, two bikes, a boat, some mobile phones and $13,800 in exchange for his daughter. It is the largest dowry ever paid in the civil war-torn country, according to the Government. Five men bid on the girl, including high-ranking South Sudanese government officials, according to children's rights organisation Plan International. The post advertising the girl was first shared on October 25, but it took Facebook u...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Facebook criticised for post promoting child bride auction - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/21/facebook-criticised-for-post-promoting-child-bride-auction</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPKCwcZ0A8eyrRBTdndejywqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 17:02:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/21/facebook-criticised-for-post-promoting-child-bride-auction" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook criticised for post promoting child bride auction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has been criticised for failing to remove a viral post promoting an auction of a child bride in South Sudan, which eventually led to the payment of the largest dowry ever recorded in the civil war-torn country. The highest bidder was a man three times the age of the 17-year-old girl who was auctioned. At least four other men in Eastern Lakes state competed, including the region’s deputy governor, said Philips Anyang Ngong, a human rights lawyer who tried to stop the bidding last month. “She has been reduced to a mere commodity,” Ngong told the Associated Press, calling it “the bigg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Five-year-old girl 'forced into marriage with 22-year-old man in Pakistan' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/child-marriage-forced-five-year-old-girl-pakistan-islam-a7863576.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJCrrpuOTrTrO3EcvCq8lLQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 21:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/child-marriage-forced-five-year-old-girl-pakistan-islam-a7863576.html" target="_blank"&gt;Five-year-old girl 'forced into marriage with 22-year-old man in Pakistan'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A girl aged just five has reportedly been forced into marriage with a 22-year-old man in Pakistan. Police were called to the ceremony in the village of Raman Shar near Dakhan Town but arrived too late to halt the marriage, according to Pakistani newspaper Dawn. The groom was reportedly arrested along with his father and the registrar. The little girl is believed to have also been taken into custody along with her mother. UK news in pictures - 68 show all UK news in pictures - 1/68 27 July 2017 A nurse shows a message on his phone to colleagues as they take part in a protest near Downing Str...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>India Police Rescue Trafficked Women, Help Them Make a New Life - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3819675.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBOwet5rlArz_8REVfQhbkkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 02:28:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3819675.html" target="_blank"&gt;India Police Rescue Trafficked Women, Help Them Make a New Life&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police in the Indian state of West Bengal are going beyond the call of duty by raising funds for the women they rescue from sex traffickers to help them get back on track. “The girls are hardly literate, have no access to bank loans, and government schemes are not enough to sustain them in the long run,” said police officer Chandra Sekhar Bardhan, who is spearheading the program in eastern India. “We had to do something, even though it did not fall in the realm of our duties.” The scheme, the first of its kind, began this month, with 22 rescued women singled out for rehabilitation. Police t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Impoverished families flout Guatemala's child marriage ban - experts - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-guatemala-child-marriage-idUSKBN13B2BI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ91M8xho8YP5yox5aX2HDMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 17:31:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-guatemala-child-marriage-idUSKBN13B2BI" target="_blank"&gt;Impoverished families flout Guatemala's child marriage ban - experts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Anastasia Moloney BOGOTA (Thomson Reuters Foundation) - A year after Guatemala passed a law banning child marriage, poor families who regard girls as a financial burden are still marrying them off as prolonged drought plunges many into deeper poverty, campaigners say. Guatemala has one of the highest rates of child marriage in Latin America, long driven by poverty and cultural acceptance especially among the country's Maya indigenous communities, with around one third of girls married by 18. Each year more than 15 million girls worldwide are married before they turn 18, campaign group Gi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>War And Looming Famine Are Pushing More Yemeni Girls Into Child Marriage - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/yemen-child-marriage-war_us_58daa5f0e4b07634059fa6e2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGSNpDQbeGuAGPhchqubzDQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 22:43:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/yemen-child-marriage-war_us_58daa5f0e4b07634059fa6e2" target="_blank"&gt;War And Looming Famine Are Pushing More Yemeni Girls Into Child Marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rate of child marriage in Yemen has skyrocketed over the course of the country’s devastating civil war, according to a UNICEF report released on Monday. More than two-thirds of girls in the country are now married off before their 18th birthday, up from 50 percent before the conflict. The increase in child marriage is one of the ripple effects of the two-year civil war that has killed more than 10,000 people and left around 19 million people in need of some form of humanitarian aid. The report estimates that one child dies every 10 minutes in Yemen from preventable causes, and that 80 p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Saving Syrian refugees from early marriage - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2017/02/21/pkg-amanpour-jordan-child-marriage.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEj_pgZGCDhDrAJ7qRapnq4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 19:21:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2017/02/21/pkg-amanpour-jordan-child-marriage.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Saving Syrian refugees from early marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many Syrian refugee girls in Jordan are getting married very young, but there's also a movement underway to keep them in school. Christiane Amanpour reports. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>New York state raises legal age of marriage from 14 to 18 in bid to prevent forced weddings for child brides - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/new-york-law-change-forced-marriage-age-14-18-child-brides-a7855026.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFvvXaJiiVau8UYDKD-D7m4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 19:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/new-york-law-change-forced-marriage-age-14-18-child-brides-a7855026.html" target="_blank"&gt;New York state raises legal age of marriage from 14 to 18 in bid to prevent forced weddings for child brides&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The state of New York has raised the legal age of marriage from 14 to 18, overturning a little-known law that saw hundreds of young girls become child brides each year, often through coercion. New York was previously one of just three out of the 50 states to allow 14-year-olds to marry without parental permission, the other two being North Carolina and Alaska. More than 3,850 minors married in New York between 2000 and 2010, with 84 per cent involving cases of child brides and adult men. - Read more British girls are being sold as child brides like I was, says activist The new law bans marr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Turkish govt supports bill that sets child rapists free if they marry victim - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/367459-turkey-child-rape-marriage-law/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJt7Df5wS7IrgzvhX7_ECXEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 23:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/367459-turkey-child-rape-marriage-law/" target="_blank"&gt;Turkish govt supports bill that sets child rapists free if they marry victim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey’s ruling government has brought a motion to Parliament that would allow rapists to go free if they marry their victims, as a way to alleviate the legal complications associated with child marriage. The Justice and Development Party (AKP) supported a motion, which was brought to the floor of the General Assembly on Thursday night, that would allow the immediate release of more than 4,000 convicted rapists from Turkish prisons if they marry their victim, reports Turkish Minute. READ MORE: 33% of Turkish marriages involve underage brides – women's rights advocate The AKP has defended th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Sold into marriage: how Rohingya girls become child brides in Malaysia - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-childbrides-insight-idUSKBN15U007</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHb0KHexr9ZzXjf9fhoMkkEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 00:07:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-childbrides-insight-idUSKBN15U007" target="_blank"&gt;Sold into marriage: how Rohingya girls become child brides in Malaysia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Rozanna Latiff and Ebrahim Harris KUALA LUMPUR (Reuters) - The slight girl in a turquoise headscarf held back tears as she recalled what happened when she fled to Malaysia from Myanmar's violence-hit Rakhine state. Just 12-years-old at the time, she was forced to wed a man she did not know, and who was more than a decade older than her. The teenager, who is not being named by Reuters because she is still only 13, is like hundreds of Rohingya girls escaping persecution, violence and apartheid-like conditions in Rakhine, only to be sold into marriage to Rohingya men in neighboring Malaysia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Germany to dissolve child marriages - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/05/germany-dissolve-child-marriages/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ4mrBREPkaZo5hHaqwK3S4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 15:35:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/05/germany-dissolve-child-marriages/" target="_blank"&gt;Germany to dissolve child marriages&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Germany’s cabinet has agreed a new draft law banning child marriages after the recent refugee influx saw brides even younger than 14 arrive in the country. The draft law, agreed by the cabinet on Wednesday, has been drawn up to protect minors, especially for girls, by annulling foreign marriages involving underage children. Youth welfare workers will be allowed to take underaged girls into care, even if they were legally married abroad. If necessary, they will also be separated from their husbands. The draft law is set to receive parliamentary approval by July. "Children do not belong in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Wednesday's Morning Email: Following Houston Devastation, Harvey Makes Landfall In Louisiana - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/wednesdays-morning-email-following-houston-devastation-harvey-makes-landfall-in-louisiana_us_59a69b86e4b063ae34da1e15</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMT5yn1BMqEuoVAtNbPw-6wqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 11:30:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/wednesdays-morning-email-following-houston-devastation-harvey-makes-landfall-in-louisiana_us_59a69b86e4b063ae34da1e15" target="_blank"&gt;Wednesday's Morning Email: Following Houston Devastation, Harvey Makes Landfall In Louisiana&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TOP STORIES (And want to get The Morning Email each weekday? Sign up here.) HARVEY’S DEVASTATION CONTINUES Here’s what you need to know about the storm, which has broken the continental U.S. rainfall record, making landfall in Southwest Louisiana. This dramatic time-lapse shows the flood waters rising in Houston. And George W. Bush’s press secretary says Donald Trump’s response to Harvey was missing this one thing. [HuffPost] [Tweet | Share on Facebook] UN CONDEMNS NORTH KOREA’S FIRING OF A BALLISTIC MISSILE OVER JAPAN But no new sanctions were announced. And in South Korea, residents remai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>UK ends £5.2m taxpayer support for Ethiopian girl band project - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/priti-patel-yegna-girl-effect-52-million-uk-taxpayer-international-aid-ethiopia-a7513956.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELHqK6CFXyifrEv1gNs-o4EqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 20:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/priti-patel-yegna-girl-effect-52-million-uk-taxpayer-international-aid-ethiopia-a7513956.html" target="_blank"&gt;UK ends £5.2m taxpayer support for Ethiopian girl band project&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;British taxpayers' money will no longer be used to fund the project behind an Ethiopian girl band, the Department for International Development (DfID) has said. The five-piece pop group Yegna was formed as part of the Girl Effect programme and officials had previously praised the impact the project was having. But International Development Secretary Priti Patel was challenged about a reported £5.2m grant to the scheme when she appeared before MPs in December and indicated that the programme was under review. - Read more Government defends foreign aid over 'Ethiopian Spice Girls' claims DfID...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Child bride auction in South Sudan goes viral, sparks anger - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/02afe2620f9546a6a92a19015aed5620</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPaejYW2IVRwk4fZqkA7nUEqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 14:59:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/02afe2620f9546a6a92a19015aed5620" target="_blank"&gt;Child bride auction in South Sudan goes viral, sparks anger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUBA, South Sudan (AP) — Five hundred cows, two luxury cars, $10,000, two bikes, a boat and a few cell phones made up the final price in a heated bidding war for a child bride in South Sudan that went viral after the auction was pointed out on Facebook. It is the largest dowry ever paid in the civil war-torn country, the government said. The highest bidder was a man three times the 17-year-old's age. At least four other men in Eastern Lakes state competed, said Philips Anyang Ngong, a human rights lawyer who tried to stop the bidding last month. Among the bidders was the state's deputy gove...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Thousands of Turks Protest Proposed Child-marriage Law - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/thousands-turks-protest-proposed-child-marriage-legislation/3604200.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGwTbd4vDJbgOmkOSugqjCUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 01:14:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/thousands-turks-protest-proposed-child-marriage-legislation/3604200.html" target="_blank"&gt;Thousands of Turks Protest Proposed Child-marriage Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thousands of Turks took to the streets of Istanbul on Saturday, protesting against a proposed law that critics say would allow men convicted of child sexual assault to avoid punishment by marrying their victims. With signs reading "Punish the rapist, not the child," and other expressions of defiance, including "Rape cannot be pardoned," an estimated 3,000 protesters marched in Kadikoy square in the city's Asian sector. Opponents of the legislation, which was approved in a first reading Thursday, were reported to include an organization that employs a daughter of President Recep Tayyip Erdog...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Turkey Withdraws Child Sex Law That Drew Protests, International Outrage - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/ap-turkey-government-withdraws-proposed-child-marriage-law/3606680.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL5XmP_92JXIDvOSPj5xgBMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 07:45:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/ap-turkey-government-withdraws-proposed-child-marriage-law/3606680.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey Withdraws Child Sex Law That Drew Protests, International Outrage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Turkish government has withdrawn a proposed law that would have given amnesty to those convicted of having sex with a girl under the age of 18 if they marry the victim. The bill drew national protests and international condemnation. Dorian Jones reports from Istanbul. Turkish Prime Minister Binali Yildirim announced the withdrawal just hours before parliament was set to vote the legislation into law. In the face of widespread condemnation Yildirim said the legislation would now be reconsidered, adding that "these issues will be discussed by a parliamentary commission." Yildirim said i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Activists in Zimbabwe Train Sights on Child Marriage - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/activists-in-zimbabwe-train-sights-on-child-marriage/3611453.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMbd2Y9gR5WL6wgtNjo-cuoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 15:31:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/activists-in-zimbabwe-train-sights-on-child-marriage/3611453.html" target="_blank"&gt;Activists in Zimbabwe Train Sights on Child Marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Zimbabwe, as in other countries, Friday marks the start of an official 16-day campaign against gender violence, which mainly targets women and girls. Activists in Zimbabwe are concentrating on early marriage, a practice that remains very common despite the Constitutional Court declaring it illegal this year. Official statistics released this week say about 5,000 Zimbabwean children have left school this year alone because of early marriages, something that worries officials, U.N. agencies and activists who want children to complete their education. On Friday, Zivai Makanda, from the loc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Grown Men Are Exploiting Loopholes In State Laws To Marry Children - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/child-marriage-state-laws_us_59a5e70ee4b00795c2a27e19</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG62M0jrcXojL9ioOUilhYEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMM2GuAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 04:01:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/child-marriage-state-laws_us_59a5e70ee4b00795c2a27e19" target="_blank"&gt;Grown Men Are Exploiting Loopholes In State Laws To Marry Children&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loopholes in state laws are allowing child marriage to flourish in the U.S., despite research showing that the practice puts young people at risk of serious, lifelong harm. More than 200,000 children under 18 were married from 2000 to 2015 in the U.S., according to a report released Wednesday by the Tahirih Justice Center, a nonprofit organization working to end gender-based violence. The vast majority were underage girls who married adult men. “America really does have a child marriage problem,” said Jeanne Smoot, author of the report. “It hurts children here, just as it does globally, and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>11-year-old girl 'forced to marry her rapist' from church in Florida - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/11-year-old-girl-forced-to-marry-rapist-florida-church-child-marraige-a7761816.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDR620laYfrzTifWJDtfKlwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/11-year-old-girl-forced-to-marry-rapist-florida-church-child-marraige-a7761816.html" target="_blank"&gt;11-year-old girl 'forced to marry her rapist' from church in Florida&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman from Florida has claimed she was forced to marry her rapist at age 11. Sherry Johnson says she was raped four times by members of her family’s church congregation as a child. As a result, she became pregnant at age 10. When investigators began looking into her case, she claims her family tried to protect her rapist by forcing her to marry him. - Read more New Jersey refuses to ban child marriage outright “My mom asked me if I wanted to get married, and I said, ‘I don’t know, what is marriage, how do I act like a wife?’” Ms Johnson told The New York Times. “She said, ‘Well, I guess y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Female Islamic clerics declare rare fatwa against child marriage - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/female-islamic-clerics-child-marriage-fatwa-muslim-indonesia-java-a7707201.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENFSt8RaY15RzwLWIfOneAMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 10:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/female-islamic-clerics-child-marriage-fatwa-muslim-indonesia-java-a7707201.html" target="_blank"&gt;Female Islamic clerics declare rare fatwa against child marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Female scholars of Islam have decreed that child marriage should be banned after a rare congress held in Indonesia. Dozens of women from the Muslim-majority country as well as scholars from Saudi Arabia, India and Pakistan gathered for what is believed to be the first major meeting of female clerics in Cirebon, Java, issuing a raft of religious decrees on Thursday after three days of discussions. Among the most important was a fatwa calling on the government to raise the age of marriage for girls from 16 to 18. Mother and Daughter in video message defying fatwa on cycling in public in Iran ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Chinese children marry each other aged 13 - the wife is already five months pregnant - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/china-children-13-year-old-marry-wife-pregnant-five-months-hainan-a7858466.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHUJ1AEPSfO0-fG8Z66_PmoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 08:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/china-children-13-year-old-marry-wife-pregnant-five-months-hainan-a7858466.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese children marry each other aged 13 - the wife is already five months pregnant&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month, two 13-year-old Chinese children married one another. The small ceremony took place in Ding’an County, Hainan Province in Southern China. Footage has since emerged of the wedding on YouKu, a Chinese streaming service. The nuptials were reportedly arranged by the couple’s parents. In the short clip, the newlyweds can be seen wearing red costumes and bowing to one another as is typical of a traditional Chinese wedding, surrounded by their friends and family. The bride was reportedly five months pregnant at the time. (YouKu) Whilst their actual ages remain unconfirmed, with the maj...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>New MTV Dramas in Egypt and India Tackle FGM, Sex Work - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/mtv-egypt-india-fgm-sex-work/3941588.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL9tnRs_1YCHtY1d0nSKA7cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 19:24:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/mtv-egypt-india-fgm-sex-work/3941588.html" target="_blank"&gt;New MTV Dramas in Egypt and India Tackle FGM, Sex Work&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;American cable television channel MTV is launching drama series in Egypt and in India with storylines on female genital mutilation, child marriage and sex work with the aim of generating debate around issues often seen as taboo. Both series by the Viacom-owned youth entertainment broadcaster will feature soundtracks to appeal to young audiences and popular local actors who will be trained on the issues to help stimulate debates via social media. "We will be using gripping plots based on true stories from young people so that we can destigmatize issues, debunk unhelpful stereotypes and catal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>New Jersey Could Be First in US to Ban Child Marriages, Activists Say - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3845011.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE6Miq0DSX57LE0D87fD4JgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 20:27:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3845011.html" target="_blank"&gt;New Jersey Could Be First in US to Ban Child Marriages, Activists Say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A measure to ban child marriage could become law this week in New Jersey, which would become the first of the 50 states in America to outlaw the practice without exception, activists say. Viewed as the strongest such bill to be considered in the United States, it would prohibit any marriage of children under age 18. Activists say the practice of underage marriage is rampant in the United States, where about 170,000 children were wed between 2000 and 2010. Most are underage girls married to older men. While age 18 is the minimum for marriage in most of the United States, states have legal lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Groom jailed in Australian-first child bride case - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-21/groom-sentenced-in-australian-first-child-bride-case/8966746</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3qAPrRs6JW7qMUDT_ziagqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 02:41:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-21/groom-sentenced-in-australian-first-child-bride-case/8966746" target="_blank"&gt;Groom jailed in Australian-first child bride case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man has been sentenced to 12 months in prison for illegally marrying a 14-year-old bride in an Islamic wedding in Melbourne last year. The Burmese asylum seeker has already spent nearly a year in custody so will be returned to immigration detention indefinitely on his release in a fortnight. It is the first prosecution in Australia under the laws since they were established in 2013. The man, aged in his 30s, had pleaded guilty to going through a formal ceremony of marriage with a person not of marriageable age at Noble Park last September. He and his bride cannot be identified for legal r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Republican refuses to repeal child marriage law allowing girls aged 13 to wed - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/republican-child-marriage-law-repeal-david-bates-new-hampshire-state-girls-boys-13-years-old-girl-a7762776.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHApf-JvIdT5jVvffqXVpzQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 12:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/republican-child-marriage-law-repeal-david-bates-new-hampshire-state-girls-boys-13-years-old-girl-a7762776.html" target="_blank"&gt;Republican refuses to repeal child marriage law allowing girls aged 13 to wed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Republican politician apparently refused to back legislation to prevent child marriage in part because "a minor doing a Girl Scout project" had proposed it. Cassandra Levesque, 17, campaigned in her native New Hampshire to raise the minimum age for marriage to 18 — from 13 for girls and 14 for boys, with parental consent and a judge's permission. But a bill to set the higher age in law was rejected in the state's legislature. - Read more 11-year-old girl 'forced to marry her rapist' in Florida According to The Times, Republican David Bates said: "We're asking the legislature to repeal a l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>9yo girls 'physically &amp; spiritually' ready to marry – Malaysian MP - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/383580-malaysia-child-marriage-rape/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKKOT4JzWCIX45mIT8XjADIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 12:00:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/383580-malaysia-child-marriage-rape/" target="_blank"&gt;9yo girls 'physically &amp; spiritually' ready to marry – Malaysian MP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Girls as young as nine are “physically and spiritually” ready for marriage, a Malaysian MP says, also claiming there’s “nothing wrong” with females marrying their rapists. It comes after Malaysia failed to criminalize child marriage in a recent law. “They reach puberty at the age of nine or 12. And at that time, their body is already akin to them being 18 years old. So physically and spiritually, it is not a barrier for the girl to marry,” Shabudin Yahaya, a member of the Barisan Nasional Coalition, told Parliament on Tuesday, as quoted by Reuters. He went on to say there is “nothing wrong”...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Turkey: Motion 'protecting child marriage' draws debate - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/11/turkey-motion-protecting-child-marriage-draws-debate-161118124734306.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKqr10nUzQbBn41tCVxGup4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:27:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/11/turkey-motion-protecting-child-marriage-draws-debate-161118124734306.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey: Motion 'protecting child marriage' draws debate&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A government proposal to quash the convictions of men convicted of child sex assaults if they marry their victim has sparked furious debate in Turkey, with critics accusing it of encouraging child rape and the ruling party insisting it will protect those who were too young to marry legally. Thursday's motion stated that in the case of sexual abuse of a minor committed before November 11, if the act was committed without "force, threat, or any other restriction on consent" and if the aggressor "marries the victim" the sentence will be postponed. The motion was issued as part of a 49-article ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Dear world, I wasn't all bad. Signed, 2016 - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2016/12/29/world/good-things-that-happened-2016-trnd/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDV3Fuk0I-9C4dVUDMQ5PcAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 06:05:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2016/12/29/world/good-things-that-happened-2016-trnd/" target="_blank"&gt;Dear world, I wasn't all bad. Signed, 2016&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know, I know. You're SO over me. You lost a favorite celebrity. Your Samsung Galaxy exploded. You got really tired of Pokemon Go really fast. But look a little closer. I was also all kinds of awesome - in ways that left you a better place. THE WORLD There's finally peace in Colombia • Non-violent protests helped impeach a president in South Korea • Gambia voted out a dictator • The military no longer rules Myanmar • Lebanon picked a leader - after 45 tries • A Pope and a Russian Orthodox patriarch met for the first time in 1,000 years THE ENVIRONMENT That big ozone hole over the Antarctic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Germany to crack down on immigrant child brides, underage marriages - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/383587-germany-child-marriages-law/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELAV_pTHv-Pz3Wk5TmWDbd4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 13:17:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/383587-germany-child-marriages-law/" target="_blank"&gt;Germany to crack down on immigrant child brides, underage marriages&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Germany’s government has moved to stamp out child marriages by drafting a law that will raise the age of consent to 18 and give authorities the ability to break up unions involving minors. The law is an effort to tackle underage marriages prevalent in some immigrant communities, according to local reports, after the Federal Ministry of the Interior released statistics showing 1,475 foreign children had been documented as married last year. BM @HeikoMaas zu RegE zum Verbot der #Kinderehe: "Das Wohl der Minderjährigen muss im Mittelpunkt stehen" Mehr: https://t.co/LTJD0367UU pic.twitter.com/H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Police Bust Traffickers Selling Indian Child Brides in the Gulf - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/police-bust-trafficers-selling-indian-child-brides-in-the-gulf/4039022.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECOxyjdJg62RPQOkktSt2rIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 20:10:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/police-bust-trafficers-selling-indian-child-brides-in-the-gulf/4039022.html" target="_blank"&gt;Police Bust Traffickers Selling Indian Child Brides in the Gulf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police have rescued a dozen trafficked girls in the southern Indian city of Hyderabad and arrested more than 20 members of a major network selling brides to wealthy men in the Gulf. Omanis, Qataris, hotel owners, brokers and qazis - who perform Islamic marriages - were arrested in Wednesday's crackdown, which a campaigner said could help stem the trade. "Innocent Muslim girls are dragged into the trap of marriage to wealthy sheikhs of Arab countries," Mahendar Reddy, Hyderabad police commissioner, said in a statement. "After reaching the new country, they are exploited at the hands of sever...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>11-year-old American girl 'forced to marry her rapist' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/life/11-year-old-american-girl-forced-marry-rapist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG5WbamT-28p768j3YJV4rEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDqy7cF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 12:37:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/life/11-year-old-american-girl-forced-marry-rapist/" target="_blank"&gt;11-year-old American girl 'forced to marry her rapist'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An American woman has described to the New York Times how she was forced to marry a man who raped her when she was just 11-years-old. Sherry Johnson, from Florida, told interviewer Nicholas Kristof she was raped by both a minister and a parishioner at her conservative Pentecostal church. She fell pregnant and gave birth to a baby girl when she was just 10-years-old. As child welfare authorities started investigating her case, Ms Johnson says her family and church officials organised her marriage to the 20-year-old perpetrator in order to avoid a criminal case. “It was forced on me,” she sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Melbourne man pleads guilty to child marriage - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-18/melbourne-man-pleads-guilty-to-child-marriage/8451474</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJpDjQmHOLMyulZQJmuolBwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 07:16:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-18/melbourne-man-pleads-guilty-to-child-marriage/8451474" target="_blank"&gt;Melbourne man pleads guilty to child marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 34-year-old Melbourne man has cried in court while pleading guilty to illegally marrying a 14-year-old bride in an Islamic wedding last year. Mohammad Shakir pleaded guilty to going through a formal ceremony of marriage with a person not of marriageable age at Noble Park last September. The "wedding" was conducted by former imam Ibrahim Omerdic. As part of Shakir's plea, two charges were withdrawn by prosecutors in the Melbourne Magistrates' Court on Tuesday. They included allegations Shakir had sex with the girl between September 30 and October 1, following their wedding. Shakir, who has...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Man ‘raped 14-year-old child bride after illegal ceremony’ - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/australasia/man-child-marriage-rape-illegal-ceremony-australia-a7563916.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKVWAzFXO9HAXzi-8gdyR1wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 16:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/australasia/man-child-marriage-rape-illegal-ceremony-australia-a7563916.html" target="_blank"&gt;Man ‘raped 14-year-old child bride after illegal ceremony’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A girl was allegedly raped after being forced into a marriage aged only 14, a court has heard. Mohammed Shakir, 34, from Melbourne, is accused of having sex with the girl in 2016, following their wedding, which was conducted by ex-imam Ibrahim Omerdic, 61, who also faces charges related to the marriage. The girl, who has not been named, has “ongoing health issues” and is currently in a “fragile state”, prosecutor Ranjani Padmanabhan told Melbourne Magistrates Court. Read more - Tanzania and Gambia have banned child marriage - Young girl campaigns against child marriage from her own refugee ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Norway could introduce a third gender option on passports for people who identify neither male nor female - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/norway-third-gender-passport-option-hen-identify-male-female-han-hun-labour-party-youth-wing-a7568271.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6TfqtkK6seDlzqnqQZdcAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 10:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/norway-third-gender-passport-option-hen-identify-male-female-han-hun-labour-party-youth-wing-a7568271.html" target="_blank"&gt;Norway could introduce a third gender option on passports for people who identify neither male nor female&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Norwegian Labour Party is considering introducing a third gender category on passports and other official documents. The party's youth wing has said it would like a new category — 'hen' — created for people who identify as neither male ('han') nor female ('hun'). Labour, which is the largest party in Norway's parliament, had previously said it would consider the move in its 2017-2021 draft party programme. Read more - Non-binary student calls for ‘third gender option’ in Canadian census - India gets first transgender news anchor months after third gender - India court recognises transge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>#BridesDoGood: Would you buy a second hand wedding dress? And will you donate yours? - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/fashion/style/bridesdogood-would-buy-second-hand-wedding-dress-will-donate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOxr530NSG4MM_qACYWZWbkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCq098D</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:16:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/fashion/style/bridesdogood-would-buy-second-hand-wedding-dress-will-donate/" target="_blank"&gt;#BridesDoGood: Would you buy a second hand wedding dress? And will you donate yours?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new charity initiative wants brides past, present and future to consider the appeal of a second hand wedding dress, as part of their aim to end child marriage around the world. Brides Do Good, which has a pop-up store opening at Bicester Village this week, is encouraging married women to donate their pre-loved designer dresses, receiving a third of the gown’s resale price for themselves, while a third goes to charity and a third to company overheads. Each bride’s donation is split between two partner charities, Plan International and Too Young To Wed, both of which are working towards the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>‘Traffickers take all that makes you human’: faces of modern slavery – in pictures - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/gallery/2017/jul/30/traffickers-take-all-makes-you-human-faces-modern-slavery-in-pictures</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENxjM8xRc6a8EWm1iTZ37LcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:00:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/gallery/2017/jul/30/traffickers-take-all-makes-you-human-faces-modern-slavery-in-pictures" target="_blank"&gt;‘Traffickers take all that makes you human’: faces of modern slavery – in pictures&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Princess, 43, trafficked from Nigeria into prostitution in Italy We saw people return from Europe rich. A woman said she would give me work in a Nigerian restaurant in Italy. When I arrived I was told I had to pay back a £40,000 debt before I could leave. They said they would kill me if I didn’t work as a prostitute. The work was so dangerous. I was stabbed twice. I managed to leave, and now I work to help other women escape. These traffickers take everything from you – all that makes you human. I say to the women I help: ‘Let us not rest until we have brought them all to justice’ Photograp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Bad Santa: German town sacks Father Christmas over alleged far-right support - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/11/22/bad-santa-german-town-sacks-father-christmas-alleged-far-right/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFR7TyRTM4zwDdXdseN4tikqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 16:02:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/11/22/bad-santa-german-town-sacks-father-christmas-alleged-far-right/" target="_blank"&gt;Bad Santa: German town sacks Father Christmas over alleged far-right support&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A town in Germany has sacked Santa Claus over alleged links to a far-Right movement. Peter Mück has dressed as Santa and distributed sweets to children at the annual Christmas market in the Bavarian town of Mühldorf for 30 years. But this year the Christmas market opened without him after the mayor of Mühldorf announced that he had been fired. Mr Mück was dismissed over comments he wrote on Facebook in support of a post by the far-Right “Identitarian Movement”, which campaigns against immigration and Islam, and has been accused of open racism. “I explained to him that this movement, in my v...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Man pleads guilty to 'marrying' 14-year-old girl amid spate of underage girls forced to become child brides - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/14-year-old-melbourne-mosque-girl-forced-marriage-man-20-years-older-a7750061.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDnNh4Feirf4M39ToPu3cTcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 19:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/14-year-old-melbourne-mosque-girl-forced-marriage-man-20-years-older-a7750061.html" target="_blank"&gt;Man pleads guilty to 'marrying' 14-year-old girl amid spate of underage girls forced to become child brides&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 14-year-old girl was forced to marry a man 20 years her senior in a Melbourne mosque, a court has heard. In video footage of the ceremony, the young teenager can be seen dressed in a light-blue headscarf in a tiny room hidden at the back of the suburban mosque as she waits in silence to be married to a man she has reportedly known for just a few days. The ceremony took place last September but the film has come to light amid a dramatic increase in reports of forced underage marriages in Australia in the past few years. Mohammad Shakir, now 35, sobbed in court as he pleaded guilty to going...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Women and vulnerable people are paying for Turkey’s authoritarianism - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/nov/24/women-vulnerable-turkey-child-rape</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIa5JP27Z1TFjjTl1zw_L04qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 11:11:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/nov/24/women-vulnerable-turkey-child-rape" target="_blank"&gt;Women and vulnerable people are paying for Turkey’s authoritarianism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two wrongs don’t make a right, right? Yet in Turkey, a close shave with a controversial motion dubbed by many the “child rape bill” proves that quite the opposite is considered true when talking about the abuse of women. Under the proposal put forward last week, men convicted of sex with an underage girl before 11 November this year would be pardoned if they married their victim, as long as the act was committed without “force, threat or any other restriction on consent”. The shocking bill met with support in parliament last Thursday but failed to reach the necessary majority and was later ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Polygamous Mormon Church Allowed to Keeps Its Police Force - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2017/04/21/polygamous-mormon-church-allowed-to-keeps-its-police-force.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPRcNW85U-0wcg8FR81Va_EqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMIv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2017/04/21/polygamous-mormon-church-allowed-to-keeps-its-police-force.html" target="_blank"&gt;Polygamous Mormon Church Allowed to Keeps Its Police Force&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An inter-state police force that serves a polygamous fundamentalist Mormon community won’t be required to disband—despite alleged discrimination against nonbelievers, surveillance of dissidents, and facilitation of child abuse. Instead, officers in the Colorado City Marshal’s Office will be required to attend annual training sessions to ensure they comply with federal laws and don’t discriminate against the community’s non-religious minority. The Marshal’s Office has been serving the adjoining towns of Hildale, Utah and Colorado City, Arizona since 1985. Together, the two towns make up Shor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Growing Runner Beans to Avert Child Marriage, Trafficking in Eastern India - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/runner-beans-help-avert-child-marriage-trafficking-in-eastern-india/3776684.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWqopq4whm8A5DXarTD6HsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 05:29:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/runner-beans-help-avert-child-marriage-trafficking-in-eastern-india/3776684.html" target="_blank"&gt;Growing Runner Beans to Avert Child Marriage, Trafficking in Eastern India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a teenager, Sarjana Biswas has rather modest ambitions: finish school, go to college and become a government healthcare worker in her village. But for young girls like Biswas in India's eastern state of West Bengal, even these would have been impossible dreams just a few years ago in a district plagued by a high rate of school dropouts, early marriage and human trafficking. Thanks to a state program to keep young girls in school with cash incentives, coupled with efforts by land rights advocacy group Landesa to teach land literacy, girls like Biswas are daring to dream and plan for bett...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>British girls are being sold as child brides like I was, says women's rights campaigner - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/british-girls-sold-child-brides-gabriella-gillespie-yemen-issy-womens-rights-campaigners-a7617621.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOpiH4bi4ZuOpmtvhrDzRD0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 10:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/british-girls-sold-child-brides-gabriella-gillespie-yemen-issy-womens-rights-campaigners-a7617621.html" target="_blank"&gt;British girls are being sold as child brides like I was, says women's rights campaigner&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Gabriella Gillespie was six her father killed her mother; when she was 13 he took her and her sisters to his native Yemen and sold them as child brides. Her 17-year-old sister Issy killed herself on her wedding night rather than marry the man in his 60s to whom she had been promised. Dressed in her wedding finery, she hurled herself from the roof of the building where guests had gathered to celebrate. Despite her sister's suicide Gillespie was not spared. She spent a decade trapped in a violent marriage with a man who raped and beat her so badly she was “left at death's door many times...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Ethiopian Spice Girls' given £5m in British foreign aid despite previous outcry - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/12/19/ethiopian-spice-girls-given-5m-british-foreign-aid-despite-previous/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIOp_BvWp8ef0RhP4pA5fSAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 08:09:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/12/19/ethiopian-spice-girls-given-5m-british-foreign-aid-despite-previous/" target="_blank"&gt;'Ethiopian Spice Girls' given £5m in British foreign aid despite previous outcry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An all-female pop group dubbed Ethiopia’s Spice Girls has received another £5.2 million in British foreign aid despite previous criticism of the funding. Yegna received the taxpayer money through a contract to develop their 'branded media platform', which includes a radio drama and music. The revelation comes despite outcry in 2013 when it was revealed the group had been given £4 million via Girl Hub, a UK-funded project. The independent aid watchdog has previously questioned whether funding Girl Hub provided value for money and suggested it should end. Yegna, a five-person pop group, is de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Texas, One Of Worst States For Child Marriage, Just Banned It - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/texas-bans-child-marriage-law_us_594402a4e4b06bb7d272b673</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJrwMUdMkyR3pAT8IkGuL9gqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMM2GuAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 17:58:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/texas-bans-child-marriage-law_us_594402a4e4b06bb7d272b673" target="_blank"&gt;Texas, One Of Worst States For Child Marriage, Just Banned It&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Texas just passed a law to make marriage under age 18 illegal. On Thursday, Texas Gov. Greg Abbott signed a bill banning child marriage, in the state with the second highest rate of underage marriage. Before this new law, 16- and 17-year-olds could marry in Texas with parental consent, according to advocacy group Tahirih Justice Center, which helped draft and drive the bill to get passed. What’s more, a child of any age could get married with judicial approval. This new law includes one exception: Those ages 16 and 17 can marry if they have been legally emancipated from their parents. In ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Report: India Needs New Ways to Fight Scourge of Child Marriage - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/india-child-marriage-unicef-report/3953408.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHpYOJ8ohfhixBrOk7EaS4oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 11:20:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/india-child-marriage-unicef-report/3953408.html" target="_blank"&gt;Report: India Needs New Ways to Fight Scourge of Child Marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India must campaign on social media, rewrite text books and engage its young men if it is to tackle child marriage in a country where nearly half of females wed before the legal age, according to a report released on Friday. Despite a law banning girls from marrying before they turn 18, the practice is deeply rooted in tradition and widely accepted in society. Yet it is rarely reported as a crime and officials are often reluctant to prosecute offenders. As a result, India ranks among countries with the highest rates of child marriage in the world, accounting for a third of the global total ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Malawi Outlaws Child Marriage - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3824898.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ0KO8d3zOUMJPRQMagwOjkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 16:21:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3824898.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malawi Outlaws Child Marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malawi President Peter Mutharika has signed a constitutional amendment raising the legal marriage age to 18. The amendment marks the final step in a years-long process in Malawi to outlaw child marriage. But rights campaigners say it is just a start, and the country must now enforce the ban. Parliament approved the change to the constitution in February. Prior to the amendment, the constitution allowed minors aged 15 and older to marry with parental consent. The amendment comes into effect two years after parliament passed a revised family code that raised the marriage age to 18. "That amen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Mobile App Aims to Help End Child Marriage in India's Bihar - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/mobile-app-aims-help-end-child-marriage-india-bihar-state/4035893.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM9sUEsFVgro_Ws2EfR_630qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 23:06:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/mobile-app-aims-help-end-child-marriage-india-bihar-state/4035893.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mobile App Aims to Help End Child Marriage in India's Bihar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mobile phone app is the latest tool for campaigners seeking to end child marriage in India's Bihar state, where nearly two-thirds of girls in some of its rural areas are married before the legal age of 18. The app, Bandhan Tod, was developed by Gender Alliance — a collective of more than 270 charities in Bihar focused on gender rights — and launched this week by Deputy Chief Minister Sushil Kumar Modi. It is backed by the U.N. Population Fund. India ranks among countries with the highest rates of child marriage in the world, accounting for a third of the global total of more than 700 mill...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>New York's New Child Marriage Law Is Still Bad For Girls - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-york-finally-banned-child-marriage_us_5949738ee4b0e84975504d42</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHk1XhkPZpGD3BhgqGtZOoUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 13:01:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/new-york-finally-banned-child-marriage_us_5949738ee4b0e84975504d42" target="_blank"&gt;New York's New Child Marriage Law Is Still Bad For Girls&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York has joined a growing list of U.S. states that have restricted child marriage. But a new law leaves room for young people to wed ― and to face the risks that come with children becoming married. New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo signed legislation Tuesday that prohibits all marriages before age 17. But 17-year-olds can wed if they get a judge’s permission, according to Human Rights Watch. Human rights advocates who helped draft the law say they were disappointed that New York failed to become the first U.S. state to raise the legal age for marriage to 18, with no exceptions. As it stands, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Survey: Many Leaders Clueless on Issues Facing Girls, Women - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/many-leaders-clueless-issues-women-girls-survey/4037456.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGRLrEgjM9nRKwTQOYgnNk4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 21:12:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/many-leaders-clueless-issues-women-girls-survey/4037456.html" target="_blank"&gt;Survey: Many Leaders Clueless on Issues Facing Girls, Women&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Policymakers in developing nations may not know enough facts and figures about problems facing women and girls to help reach gender equality, research showed Wednesday. Only a handful of policymakers could estimate the maternal death rate in their countries, and only a quarter came close to estimating child marriage rates, according to a study conducted for Equal Measures 2030, a group promoting gender equality. The research cast doubt on how well nations might reach gender equality by 2030, a goal included in the 17 Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) adopted by the United Nations two yea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Turkey: Controversial bill on sexual assault withdrawn - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/11/turkey-controversial-bill-sexual-assault-withdrawn-161122083358851.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECaBcxI7iek7WZEnYgqDMHQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 09:45:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/11/turkey-controversial-bill-sexual-assault-withdrawn-161122083358851.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey: Controversial bill on sexual assault withdrawn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey's government has withdrawn a controversial bill that could have overturned men's convictions for child-sex assault, following an angry public backlash. The controversial proposal sought to address whether all cases of marriage with people under the legal age of 18 should classify as "sexual assault". Critics feared the proposal could have legitimised the practice of men marrying girls under the age of 18, which is the age of consent in Turkey. Thousands took to the streets in protest over the weekend. On Tuesday, Turkish Prime Minister Binali Yildirim said the government was withdraw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>‘Only 10 years old': Yemen sees spike in parents marrying off young daughters for cash - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/391116-yemen-war-child-marriage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIuTfvhnWu5m1JpLuRjQ6psqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 13:39:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/391116-yemen-war-child-marriage/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Only 10 years old': Yemen sees spike in parents marrying off young daughters for cash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extremely young girls are paying the price for Yemen's brutal civil war, being married off by their own families, which are struggling to make ends meet. RT spoke to a mother who managed to save her 10-year-old daughter from becoming a child bride. A woman by the name of Nasrine told RT that her 10-year-old daughter Mlak has already been engaged to an elderly man, a deal which was apparently arranged by the girl’s father against the Nasrine’s will. The mother and daughter were able to receive help from the Yemen Women’s Union, and the deal did not go through. However, Nasrine says she is st...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>13-year-old girl forced to marry her 'rapist' step-brother - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/rape-tunisia-13-year-old-girl-pregnant-article-227-child-marriage-womens-right-consent-a7483941.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECgUt4TSmZjGwG6vmmq9VGEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 09:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/rape-tunisia-13-year-old-girl-pregnant-article-227-child-marriage-womens-right-consent-a7483941.html" target="_blank"&gt;13-year-old girl forced to marry her 'rapist' step-brother&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man in his 20s has married his 13-year-old step-sister after making her pregnant. The marriage took place in the northwest region of Kef in Tunisia, in the presence of their parents who had previously attempted to stop the wedding. Although having sex with someone under the age of 15 is punishable by up to six years in prison under Tunisian law, according to article 277 of the country’s criminal code, if no force was used during the attack an alleged rapist can halt his prosecution by marrying his victim. Read more - Former Israeli president released after five years in jail for rape - Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Tunisian court approves marriage of pregnant 13-year-old - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2016/12/14/middleeast/tunisia-court-child-marriage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMHEgnp7iYUB6Yp7CSbZ-qEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 04:55:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2016/12/14/middleeast/tunisia-court-child-marriage/" target="_blank"&gt;Tunisian court approves marriage of pregnant 13-year-old&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Tunisian court Tuesday has approved the marriage of a 13-year-old girl to a 20-year-old relative who made her pregnant, a move that caused an uproar among organizations concerned with children's rights in the country. The marriage between the girl, from the northwestern region of Kef, and the brother of her brother-in-law took place in the presence of their parents, despite attempts to stop it. The judge was relying on an article in the Tunisian Criminal Code which stipulates that while sex with a girl under 15 without the use of force is punishable by six years in prison, the culprit can...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Nigeria Joins AU Campaign to End Child Marriage - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/nigeria-joins-african-union-campaign-child-marriage/3618453.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENbSrcQ4HoEa0Y_GMEVUKHkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 01:24:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/nigeria-joins-african-union-campaign-child-marriage/3618453.html" target="_blank"&gt;Nigeria Joins AU Campaign to End Child Marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women's rights activists on Wednesday urged Nigeria to accelerate efforts to end child marriage after it joined an African Union campaign to eliminate the practice. Nigeria launched this week a nationwide drive to end child marriage by pushing for policies that protect girls' rights and help the justice system to punish perpetrators. It became the 16th country to join the AU's campaign. The government made child marriage illegal in 2003, but only two-thirds of the country's 36 states have implemented the law. At least four in 10 girls in Nigeria are married off before they turn 18, while al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>'Who do you turn to for help?' The horror of being a child bride - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/life/do-turn-help-horror-child-bride/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEnYZDEZsW2DZlCIbygYB3IqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDqy7cF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/life/do-turn-help-horror-child-bride/" target="_blank"&gt;'Who do you turn to for help?' The horror of being a child bride&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Bangladesh came under fire last week for proposing a clause to its child marriage bill which would allow girls under the age of 18 to marry in 'exceptional circumstances,' many were shocked that such a troubling legal loophole could pass muster in 2017. But sadly, this came as no surprise to me: I was made a child bride at the age of 13, and know only too well about the devastation it causes. I knew nothing about marriage when I was sold by my father to a man in a village in Yemen. I had been taken there on my birthday alongside my two sisters so that we could be wed - we had no idea w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Spike in number of Syrian teens marrying as child brides in Jordan - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/child-brides-jordan-syrian-teenage-refugees-a7880831.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDgYUbhIkPtZg6O65Nk34JAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/child-brides-jordan-syrian-teenage-refugees-a7880831.html" target="_blank"&gt;Spike in number of Syrian teens marrying as child brides in Jordan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Married at 15 and divorced at 16, a Syrian teen says she regrets having said yes to a handsome suitor — a stranger who turned into an abusive husband. Yet the reasons that transformed her into a child bride have become more prevalent among Syrians who live in Jordanian exile because of a six-year-old civil war back home. More families marry off daughters to ease the financial burden or say marriage is the way to protect the “honour” of girls seen as vulnerable outside their homeland. Figures from Jordan's population census document the long suspected increase for the first time. In 2015, br...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Homegrown Solar Farm, Wind Turbines Keep Kenyan Community Buzzing - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/homegrown-solar-farm-wind-turbines-keep-kenyan-community-buzzing/3694521.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELA5muaHhdysYinbGYfKKGUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 21:46:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/homegrown-solar-farm-wind-turbines-keep-kenyan-community-buzzing/3694521.html" target="_blank"&gt;Homegrown Solar Farm, Wind Turbines Keep Kenyan Community Buzzing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the first few residents of this village in the Ngong hills installed solar panels nearly a decade ago, the only aim was to power their own homes. Their town had no connection to the national power grid. But today the community, south of Nairobi in the Rift Valley, is buzzing with solar and wind energy, which powers everything from the dispensary and church to shops, homes and even a rescue center for girls fleeing child marriage and the threat of female genital mutilation. Residents say they banded together to buy the shared energy system themselves, recognizing that the substantial up...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The case for gender equality in the Muslim world - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/04/case-gender-equality-muslim-world-170424095756513.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDpT8hdUJyhuze8_dnxy0fcqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 06:27:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/04/case-gender-equality-muslim-world-170424095756513.html" target="_blank"&gt;The case for gender equality in the Muslim world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you want to go forward, you have to give education to girls. And once you educate girls, you change the whole community. You change the whole society." These were the wise words of Nobel laureate Malala Yousafzai, upon being appointed the youngest ever UN Messenger for Peace at a ceremony in New York. Malala's groundbreaking appointment, given with special consideration for her work promoting education for women, comes at a pivotal moment for women worldwide. For just a week earlier, the United States announced it would strip all US funding from the United Nations Population Fund (UNFPA...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>India's child brides for sale - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2017/01/30/india-child-brides-sale.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHu6dS_yfrfizGMUPMpn7vEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 11:37:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2017/01/30/india-child-brides-sale.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;India's child brides for sale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Muneera Beguma was just 12 years old she was sold into marriage with a man aged 70. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Turkey withdraws bill to pardon men for sex with underage girls - Financial Times</title><link>http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/592a3ad4-b0bb-11e6-a37c-f4a01f1b0fa1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOK3__vy_ttbGRl5chVU6_EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 16:55:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/592a3ad4-b0bb-11e6-a37c-f4a01f1b0fa1.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey withdraws bill to pardon men for sex with underage girls&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey’s ruling party has withdrawn a bill to pardon men convicted of having sex with underage girls if they married them after the proposal provoked a public outcry. The bill was seen as an attempt by the Justice and Development party (AKP) to placate its more conservative members who have also demanded restoration of the death penalty and dilution of the secular constitution. But it drew widespread criticism, even from members of the AKP, which has Islamist roots, and triggered street protests by women’s groups and human rights activists. The decision to bow to pressure marks a rare insta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Bengaluru attacks: Misogyny by night and day - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/01/170106092800676.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECAbGXw1U11LSlxBWizot48qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 13:49:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/2017/01/170106092800676.html" target="_blank"&gt;Bengaluru attacks: Misogyny by night and day&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mass molestation of women in Bengaluru during the midnight celebrations at New Year brings to mind the similar outrageous incident that took place in Cologne last year. The kneejerk reaction of the Indian political establishment was to blame "western culture" - Karnataka's Home Minister G Parameshwara blamed young women for their western attire, while Samajwadi Party leader Abu Azmi blamed the late-night revelries as a western import. Rewind to a year ago, and in another part of the world, immigrants were blamed for the sexual violence, asylum seekers were rounded up as suspects, and th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Experts: More African Girls Going to School, Yet Poorest Miss Out - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/more-african-girls-in-school-poorest-miss-out-experts-say/3890123.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMibfhX7PXtgleI5JDa4pRgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 01:53:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/more-african-girls-in-school-poorest-miss-out-experts-say/3890123.html" target="_blank"&gt;Experts: More African Girls Going to School, Yet Poorest Miss Out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More girls are completing secondary school across sub-Saharan Africa as attitudes change and state spending rises, but some of the most marginalized girls — like those married young or forced to work — are still missing out, education experts say. The percentage of girls completing secondary school has risen in all regions of Africa since 2005, said a recent report by the African Development Bank, the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development, and the U.N. Development Program. Almost twice as many girls in East Africa and three times as many in Central Africa completed secondary...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Lebanon Repeals 'Marry the Rapist' Law - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/lebanon-abolishes-marry-your-rapist-law/3987863.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA6lq7qttPLDNIwUqGT74dMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 13:54:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/lebanon-abolishes-marry-your-rapist-law/3987863.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lebanon Repeals 'Marry the Rapist' Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lebanon's parliament on Wednesday abolished a law that allowed rapists to avoid prison by marrying their victims. The repeal of the law, which had been in place since the 1940s, follows years of campaigning by women's rights advocates. Tunisia, Morocco and Egypt have canceled similar "marry the rapist" clauses over the years, and Jordan's parliament recently repealed a similar law. The clause remains on the books in Algeria, Iraq, Kuwait, Libya, the Palestinian territories and Syria, as well as several countries in Latin America and in the Philippines and Tajikistan, according to Human Righ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>5 easy things you can do to make World Children’s Day 2018 more meaningful - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90270855/5-easy-things-you-can-do-to-make-world-childrens-day-2018-more-meaningful</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJl-La8Twq7oBmp9dvMYa2sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 13:43:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90270855/5-easy-things-you-can-do-to-make-world-childrens-day-2018-more-meaningful" target="_blank"&gt;5 easy things you can do to make World Children’s Day 2018 more meaningful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today is a good day to feel blue and for once it’s not because of the news cycle, but for a good cause. On this date way back in 1959, the UN General Assembly adopted the Declaration of the Rights of the Child. It is also the date in 1989 when the UN General assembly adopted the Convention on the Rights of the Child. Now, November 20 marks World Children’s Day and people are going blue to show their support for giving every child a childhood. To mark the occasion, Stranger Things star Millie Bobby Brown, the youngest UNICEF Goodwill Ambassador, teamed up with a few other UNICEF Goodwill Amb...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Malaysia Decides Not to Criminalize Child Marriage - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/malaysia-child-marriage/3796918.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPnYDnuSm3CbA-QrmHz6llYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 09:41:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/malaysia-child-marriage/3796918.html" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia Decides Not to Criminalize Child Marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Malaysian MP said girls as young as nine were "physically and spiritually" ready for marriage, as the Muslim-majority Southeast Asian country passed a law on sexual offences against children without criminalizing child marriage. Tasek Gelugor, a member of the Barisan Nasional coalition, made the comments in response to a proposal by an opposition member of parliament to amend the Sexual Offences Against Children bill to include a ban on child marriages. The proposal was voted down by the majority of parliament. "They reach puberty at the age of nine or 12. And at that time, their body is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>