<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Johann Rupert - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRGxmYzJJMEVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-ZW&amp;gl=ZW&amp;ceid=ZW:en</link><language>en-ZW</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:27:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Bell Pottinger cuts ties with controversial South African group - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/b4a8fb6e-1f7b-11e7-b7d3-163f5a7f229c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF9d3klwMoj_vbP3b_aaXwEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 14:13:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/b4a8fb6e-1f7b-11e7-b7d3-163f5a7f229c" target="_blank"&gt;Bell Pottinger cuts ties with controversial South African group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bell Pottinger, the financial public relations group with several big City names on its client list, has cut ties with a company owned by South Africa’s Gupta family, who have been accused of using ties to President Jacob Zuma to influence government decisions. The move follows claims in the South African press that Bell Pottinger was stoking racial tensions in media campaigns to support Mr Zuma and the Guptas. Oakbay, the holding company of the Guptas’ mining-to-media conglomerate, agreed the termination of the contract just over a week ago. In a statement on Wednesday, Bell Pottinger said...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Richemont founder backs universal basic income - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/90af2da4-36ec-11e7-99bd-13beb0903fa3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBHr1LwxlbcPFpwugMnD9H8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 10:44:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/90af2da4-36ec-11e7-99bd-13beb0903fa3" target="_blank"&gt;Richemont founder backs universal basic income&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Johann Rupert, wealthy founder of Swiss luxury group Richemont, has said he backs governments introducing “universal basic incomes” for all citizens to cope with economic upheaval. He also announced his son and a former top Google executive would join the company’s board to help it adjust to new technologies. The chairman of the group behind brands such as Cartier and Montblanc warned changes in industrial processes and the rise of artificial intelligence would leave many people unemployable. “I’m a proponent of universal basic income,” he told journalists on Friday. “We have to give time t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Scandal-hit Bell Pottinger hires BDO to advise on sale - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d5da3292-9255-11e7-a9e6-11d2f0ebb7f0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVwyAKSXaO806Uc53xEL8kqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:41:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d5da3292-9255-11e7-a9e6-11d2f0ebb7f0" target="_blank"&gt;Scandal-hit Bell Pottinger hires BDO to advise on sale&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bell Pottinger has hired the accountancy firm BDO to advise on a potential sale of the public relations business, as it fights to retain clients and top staff in the wake of two damning reports that found it had stoked racial tensions in South Africa. A day after the British PR industry’s trade body expelled the company for at least five years over its work for the powerful Gupta family, banking group HSBC became the first big-name client to confirm it was dropping the firm. “We have used Bell Pottinger for specific projects in the past, but will not be doing so in the future,” the bank sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Richemont watch chief Georges Kern departs for rival Breitling - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8373c9c2-688a-11e7-9a66-93fb352ba1fe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAsn3pNA79glceaup4k7u5wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 12:27:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8373c9c2-688a-11e7-9a66-93fb352ba1fe" target="_blank"&gt;Richemont watch chief Georges Kern departs for rival Breitling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A top executive at Richemont has resigned unexpectedly to join rival Swiss watchmaker Breitling in a blow to the luxury group’s efforts to weather the downturn in high-quality timepieces. Georges Kern took over as head of watchmaking at Richemont only in April. He will take an unspecified new role at Breitling, the previously family-owned watchmaker in which CVC Capital Partners, Europe’s largest private equity group, took an 80 per cent stake in April, according a person familiar with Mr Kern’s plans. Mr Kern also had responsibilities for marketing and digital strategies at Richemont. He h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Richemont chairman abolishes chief executive role - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/95c4f286-a274-11e6-aa83-bcb58d1d2193</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECl8It4xHxlKxZPFJ-EDk8UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 12:16:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/95c4f286-a274-11e6-aa83-bcb58d1d2193" target="_blank"&gt;Richemont chairman abolishes chief executive role&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richemont’s wealthy founder has overhauled the leadership structure of the Swiss luxury goods group and warned that the business, which owns the Cartier and Montblanc brands, needs to “slim down” as watch and jewellery sales slow. Johann Rupert, 66, who has a record of shaking up day-to-day management when Richemont’s performance has weakened, also bolstered his role as Richemont’s executive chairman by abolishing the post of chief executive. However, the veteran South African — who is Richemont’s controlling shareholder — denied he was taking control to avert a crisis. “I have been involve...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Richemont sells Shanghai Tang as part of portfolio shake-up - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/390a97e4-5fca-11e7-8814-0ac7eb84e5f1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELJ6SFr4mgyy0lpVTfahC78qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/390a97e4-5fca-11e7-8814-0ac7eb84e5f1" target="_blank"&gt;Richemont sells Shanghai Tang as part of portfolio shake-up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swiss luxury group Richemont has sold Shanghai Tang, the Chinese fashion brand, to an Italian businessman. The owner of jewellers Cartier, Van Cleef &amp; Arpels and Piaget said it had sold the fashion group, founded by Hong Kong businessman Sir David Tang, to a business controlled by Alessandro Bastagli last week. The Swiss group declined to say how much the deal was worth but said on Monday that the sale would “have no material impact” on its results for the year to March 2018. It gave no details of Shanghai Tang’s financial performance, but the losses it has wracked up are expected to be dis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>PR industry reads last rites for scandal-hit Bell Pottinger - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/11c12f02-9253-11e7-a9e6-11d2f0ebb7f0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFqM80eEPsVGwIBFY7_Ttv0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:59:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/11c12f02-9253-11e7-a9e6-11d2f0ebb7f0" target="_blank"&gt;PR industry reads last rites for scandal-hit Bell Pottinger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Lord Tim Bell was asked whether Bell Pottinger’s role in stoking racial tensions in South Africa marked the end for the PR firm he co-founded almost 30 years ago, he offered a typically definitive, eye-catching quote on the scandal. “It’s the end of the company,” Lord Bell told the Financial Times. “That’s 25 years of hard work gone down the tubes. It’s a great pity.” Bell Pottinger is paying a heavy price for its work in South Africa for the powerful Gupta brothers, who stand accused of buying influence with President Jacob Zuma and inflaming already fragile racial tensions in a count...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Richemont strikes China ecommerce partnership with Alibaba - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/3e58d3fe-d8e2-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKnsAcWDlXBMFpih1qQ-gw4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 06:09:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3e58d3fe-d8e2-11e8-a854-33d6f82e62f8" target="_blank"&gt;Richemont strikes China ecommerce partnership with Alibaba&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swiss luxury group Richemont has formed a joint venture with Chinese ecommerce giant Alibaba in one of the strongest signs yet of how the combined forces of China and online retail are reshaping the global luxury goods industry. The partnership will see Richemont-owned online retail sites Net-a-Porter and Mr Porter launched on Alibaba’s Tmall Luxury Pavilion, an ecommerce site created specifically to try to appease brands’ concerns about online shopping not being luxurious enough. Johann Rupert, Richemont chairman, said: “Our digital offering in China is in its infancy and we believe that p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Cartier maker Richemont hands Lambert reins for digital era - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-richemont-agm/richemont-reintroduces-ceo-role-as-sales-rise-idUSKCN1LQ0GN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPqb-J5hg5hgmwZsj-gOEjUqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 08:35:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-richemont-agm/richemont-reintroduces-ceo-role-as-sales-rise-idUSKCN1LQ0GN" target="_blank"&gt;Cartier maker Richemont hands Lambert reins for digital era&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cartier maker Richemont (CFR.S: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) made Jerome Lambert chief executive on Monday, handing the luxury goods veteran the task of continuing to take the group, in particular its watch brands, digital. Richemont, also known for its IWC and Piaget watches, scrapped the CEO role a year and a half ago, when Richard Lepeu retired, appointing instead a senior executive committee. The appointment of Lambert, which coincided with the announcement of a 10 percent rise in constant currency sales growth in the five months to Aug. 31, was read as a sign Richemont control...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Richemont appoints Lambert as chief executive - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ff1de800-b4ba-11e8-bbc3-ccd7de085ffe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEICx173ODUUld3OnY1orS8oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 06:08:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ff1de800-b4ba-11e8-bbc3-ccd7de085ffe" target="_blank"&gt;Richemont appoints Lambert as chief executive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richemont’s wealthy founder has appointed a chief executive to run the Swiss luxury goods group, after holding the post vacant for almost two years, as it reports strong sales growth in the first five months of its financial year. Jérôme Lambert, currently chief operating officer, would take the helm with immediate effect of the group which includes brands such as Cartier and Montblanc, Richemont said on Monday. The appointment marked a reversal by Johann Rupert, the group’s chairman and controlling shareholder, who abolished the role in November 2016 - a move widely seen at the time as bol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Richemont buys UK-based Watchfinder - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/55dafc62-65c1-11e8-a39d-4df188287fff</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECAFfrpV7CNAD6xTszyiw-QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 17:35:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/55dafc62-65c1-11e8-a39d-4df188287fff" target="_blank"&gt;Richemont buys UK-based Watchfinder&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swiss luxury goods company Richemont has made its first move into the second-hand luxury watch market by acquiring the UK-based Watchfinder online and shop-based company for an undisclosed sum. The deal is the latest expansion of Richemont’s retail strategy following its move in January to take full control of Yoox Net-a-Porter, the Milan-listed online luxury retailer. Watchfinder, founded in 2002, buys and sells upmarket “pre-owned” watches online and via seven boutiques, as well as operating a customer service centre. Johann Rupert, Richemont’s chairman, is overhauling the group’s distrib...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Yoox Net-a-Porter open to Chinese partnerships - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/5aa16b86-550a-11e8-b24e-cad6aa67e23e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8u3SuTV4e1vNjqBUVTyH8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 14:01:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5aa16b86-550a-11e8-b24e-cad6aa67e23e" target="_blank"&gt;Yoox Net-a-Porter open to Chinese partnerships&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yoox Net-a-Porter is opening the doors to a deal with a Chinese online retailer as it looks to embark on a new stage of growth after its buyout by Richemont. Chief executive Federico Marchetti told the Financial Times in an interview that his aim now was for the etailer to become “a really unbeatable company”, aided by the Swiss luxury group’s “broad shoulders and additional resources”. Mr Marchetti’s comments come as Richemont, owned and chaired by South African billionaire Johann Rupert, this week secured its €5.2bn takeover of YNAP after investors tendered almost 95 per cent of the etail...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Richemont offers to take full control of Yoox Net-a-Porter - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/452e443a-ff43-11e7-9650-9c0ad2d7c5b5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBUIYUsTOgXtuPYv0gJxnqYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 07:18:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/452e443a-ff43-11e7-9650-9c0ad2d7c5b5" target="_blank"&gt;Richemont offers to take full control of Yoox Net-a-Porter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swiss luxury group Richemont has launched an offer to take full control of Yoox Net-a-Porter, the Milan-listed luxury e-retailer, as it ramps up its internet retail strategy. Richemont has a 49 per cent stake in Yoox Net-a-Porter, which it hopes to increase to at least 90 per cent. It is offering €38 a share, representing a premium of 26 per cent compared with Friday’s close. Richemont expects to delist Yoox Net-a-Porter but it would continue to act as a separate business. Federico Marchetti, the Italian company’s chief executive, had agreed to accept the offer for his shares but was expect...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Richemont bids to take full control of Yoox Net-a-Porter - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/aba16fdc-ff55-11e7-9650-9c0ad2d7c5b5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM2MMPC3z6O8By2AhFS2BpoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 10:49:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/aba16fdc-ff55-11e7-9650-9c0ad2d7c5b5" target="_blank"&gt;Richemont bids to take full control of Yoox Net-a-Porter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swiss luxury group Richemont has launched a bid to take full control of Yoox Net-a-Porter, as it bids to ramp up its internet retail strategy. Richemont wants to increase its 49 per cent stake in the Milan-listed luxury eretailer to at least 90 per cent and acquire the 75 per cent of the voting rights it does not own. Richemont has offered €38 a share, representing a premium of 26 per cent compared with Friday’s close. The bid sent shares in the Milan-listed luxury eretailer up more than 24 per cent. The Swiss luxury group plans to take YNAP private but the online group will continue to act...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>