<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Kembo Mohadi - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRE50YUY4Mll4SUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-ZW&amp;gl=ZW&amp;ceid=ZW:en</link><language>en-ZW</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:50:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Mohadi's company pricing services at black market rates - Bulawayo24 News</title><link>https://bulawayo24.com/index-id-news-sc-national-byo-150335.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiQGh0dHBzOi8vYnVsYXdheW8yNC5jb20vaW5kZXgtaWQtbmV3cy1zYy1uYXRpb25hbC1ieW8tMTUwMzM1Lmh0bWzSAQA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://bulawayo24.com/index-id-news-sc-national-byo-150335.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mohadi's company pricing services at black market rates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Bulawayo24 News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malindi Transit Shed (MTS), a Beitbridge-based company in which Vice President Kembo Mohadi is a major shareholder is charging storage fees for vehicles ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://bulawayo24.com">Bulawayo24 News</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/6e3EtsBWSvcfiwodkumxt8L3wlcCuvhO3TXSr_Fahd_QvRvk7hXknfL-LB42HWO9e5fK68mt7hBuQYni08fW0ioyyDuT-dodnewj=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>VP Mohadi named in mysterious deaths and farm scandals? - Bulawayo24 News</title><link>https://bulawayo24.com/index-id-news-sc-national-byo-149329.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiQGh0dHBzOi8vYnVsYXdheW8yNC5jb20vaW5kZXgtaWQtbmV3cy1zYy1uYXRpb25hbC1ieW8tMTQ5MzI5Lmh0bWzSAQA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://bulawayo24.com/index-id-news-sc-national-byo-149329.html" target="_blank"&gt;VP Mohadi named in mysterious deaths and farm scandals?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Bulawayo24 News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whistleblower Prisca Mutema has sensationally that Vice President Kembo Mohadi is involved in a series of scandals involving multiple farm grabbing and nu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://bulawayo24.com">Bulawayo24 News</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/6e3EtsBWSvcfiwodkumxt8L3wlcCuvhO3TXSr_Fahd_QvRvk7hXknfL-LB42HWO9e5fK68mt7hBuQYni08fW0ioyyDuT-dodnewj=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Mugabe reconciles with the man who ousted him after Mnangagwa sends private jet to pick up Grace - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/07/mugabe-reconciles-man-ousted-mnangagwa-sends-private-jet-pick/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI71ZFW1oF8Uukx2m9KKROYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 19:32:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/07/mugabe-reconciles-man-ousted-mnangagwa-sends-private-jet-pick/" target="_blank"&gt;Mugabe reconciles with the man who ousted him after Mnangagwa sends private jet to pick up Grace&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert Mugabe has forgiven Emmerson Mnangagwa, the man who threw him out of power last year, and says that the new president is the right man to rule Zimbabwe. Mr Mugabe, 94, on Thursday said: "There was an election. Zanu-PF was represented by Emmerson Mnangagwa and [Nelson] Chamisa represented MDC-Alliance and results came out saying the person who won was Emmerson Mnangagwa. "We have accepted the result and we hope that we will continue respecting the will of the people. The gun does not and should not lead politics." He added that he was grateful Mr Mnangagwa, 75, had hired a luxury airc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Zimbabwe blast rocks stadium in apparent assassination attempt on President - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/23/africa/zimbabwe-rally-blast/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECJOD0aCNXCEeI0i_Mqc8aEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 18:09:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/23/africa/zimbabwe-rally-blast/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zimbabwe blast rocks stadium in apparent assassination attempt on President&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zimbabwe's government is calling an explosion Saturday an assassination attempt on President Emmerson Mnangagwa, who was holding a campaign rally at a stadium. The President escaped injuries, but others were injured and hospitalized. A security officer had to have a leg amputated, presidential spokesman George Charamba said. The blast occurred at White City Stadium in Bulawayo. Zimbabwean President Emmerson Mnangagwa at Saturday's rally. ZINYANGE AUNTONY/AFP/Getty Images Forty-nine people were injured, Charamba said. "This incident doesn't stand in the way of (the) electoral program," he sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Zimbabwe leader calls assassination attempt 'cowardly act' - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/c85677b9e578493aa84bda144c16334f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF2oOmqfawXL1LHtS1El2y4qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 17:32:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/c85677b9e578493aa84bda144c16334f" target="_blank"&gt;Zimbabwe leader calls assassination attempt 'cowardly act'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HARARE, Zimbabwe (AP) — Zimbabwe's president was unscathed Saturday by an explosion at a campaign rally that state media called an attempt to assassinate him, later visiting his two injured vice presidents and declaring the "cowardly act" will not disrupt next month's historic elections. Dramatic footage showed a smiling President Emmerson Mnangagwa walking off the stage and into a crowded tent where the blast occurred seconds later, sending up smoke as people screamed and ran for cover. Officials said Mnangagwa was whisked from the stadium rally to a nearby government building in Bulawayo,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Zimbabwe’s leader escapes bomb blast in Bulawayo - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/23/mnangagwa-zimbabwe-escapes-blast-bulawayo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAXGCuxRPLO08Px0r8k-ofcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 19:32:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/23/mnangagwa-zimbabwe-escapes-blast-bulawayo" target="_blank"&gt;Zimbabwe’s leader escapes bomb blast in Bulawayo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emmerson Mnangagwa, the president of Zimbabwe, called for peace, love and unity in the small southern African state last night, hours after escaping an apparent assassination attempt during an election campaign rally in the southern city of Bulawayo. At least eight people were injured in the attack at around 2pm,​ the state-run Herald newspaper reported. Footage posted online showed Mnangagwa, 75, waving to the crowd in the White City stadium, turning to step off the podium and walking into the open-sided VIP tent where seconds later the explosion occurred. People ducked and screamed as smo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Zimbabwe explosion sullies hopes for an election free of tension - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/06/zimbabwe-explosion-sullies-hopes-election-free-tension-180623201111127.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFHRmvkYjvkesvXRwj700noqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 08:43:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/06/zimbabwe-explosion-sullies-hopes-election-free-tension-180623201111127.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zimbabwe explosion sullies hopes for an election free of tension&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bulawayo, Zimbabwe - The blast that wounded several people as President Emmerson Mnangagwa left a campaign rally in the city of Bulawayo may have significantly changed the country's political landscape ahead of next month's tight poll race, analysts say. Dewa Mavhinga, Southern Africa Director of Human Rights Watch described the incident as "awful and appalling" but he commended Mnangagwa's immediate condemnation of the blast and calls for peace ahead of presidential and parliamentary polls on July 30. "The authorities must swiftly and thoroughly investigate the incident and hold accountab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Zimbabwe's president calls for peace after stadium blast attack - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/23/zimbabwe-explosion-rocks-stadium-rally-president-emmerson-mnangagwa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO1SqhkYkTwift2vwjaBnsUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 14:31:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/23/zimbabwe-explosion-rocks-stadium-rally-president-emmerson-mnangagwa" target="_blank"&gt;Zimbabwe's president calls for peace after stadium blast attack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emmerson Mnangagwa, the president of Zimbabwe, has called for peace, love and unity hours after escaping an apparent assassination attempt during an election campaign rally in the southern city of Bulawayo. At least eight people were injured in the explosion, the state-run Herald newspaper reported. Related: 'We have a new chance': Zimbabwe gears up for elections after Mugabe Footage posted online showed Mnangagwa, 75, waving to the crowd in the White City stadium at about 2pm on Saturday afternoon, turning to step off the podium and walking into the open-sided VIP tent, where seconds later...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Zimbabwe president accuses ‘normal enemies’ of bomb blast - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/699a0190-7795-11e8-bc55-50daf11b720d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHY3BpbfQv11I2lvi6In6LAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 12:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/699a0190-7795-11e8-bc55-50daf11b720d" target="_blank"&gt;Zimbabwe president accuses ‘normal enemies’ of bomb blast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zimbabwean President Emmerson Mnangagwa indirectly accused disaffected elements within his ruling Zanu-PF party for an explosion at a weekend rally that injured dozens of supporters, including the country’s vice-president. The explosion ripped through a stage seconds after Mr Mnangagwe has ended his speech to party supporters in Bulawayo, Zimbabwe’s second-biggest city. Mr Mnangagwa, who became president last year after a military takeover ended Robert Mugabe’s 37 years of rule, said that the “cowardly act” would not derail elections, which he has promised would be free, fair and peaceful. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Where Did Zimbabwe's Diamond Money Go? - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zimbabwe-parliament-shine-light-diamond-sector-robert-mugabe/4342344.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBFssoB3b0sbn97WO3OANQ8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 17:11:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zimbabwe-parliament-shine-light-diamond-sector-robert-mugabe/4342344.html" target="_blank"&gt;Where Did Zimbabwe's Diamond Money Go?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lawmakers in Zimbabwe are preparing to summon ex-president Robert Mugabe to answer for his management of the diamond sector, which he nationalized in 2016. Mugabe announced the state seizure two years ago on Zimbabwe state TV, saying, "There has been a lot of secrecy … and we have been blinded. We have not received much from the diamond industry at all." Foreign mining companies operating in the country were quick to challenge the stop-work orders in court, and some cases are still pending. But analysts question Mugabe's 2016 assertion that as much as $15 billion in diamond revenue was miss...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>General Who Led Mugabe Ouster Now Zimbabwe Vice President - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zimbabwe-vice-president/4182458.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELlDnBc-ZN6bDEdp0rR5NhUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 11:46:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zimbabwe-vice-president/4182458.html" target="_blank"&gt;General Who Led Mugabe Ouster Now Zimbabwe Vice President&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An army general who led the operation that forced Zimbabwean President Robert Mugabe to resign last month is now one of the country’s two vice presidents. Critics are calling President Emmerson Mnangagwa’s Cabinet a “coupnet” because of the three army generals who have prominent roles. A day after President Mnangagwa appointed them as Zimbabwe’s vice presidents, retired general Constantino Chiwenga and Defense Minister Kembo Mohadi took their oaths of office Thursday before the country’s chief justice, Luke Malaba. President Emmerson Mnangagwa (center) flanked by his just sworn in vice pres...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Zimbabwe's Mnangagwa appoints former army boss as party VP - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zimbabwe-politics/zimbabwes-mnangagwa-appoints-former-army-boss-as-party-vp-idUSKBN1EH0FL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKTrt7FwXCRTsdS-s4GpG_YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 14:02:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zimbabwe-politics/zimbabwes-mnangagwa-appoints-former-army-boss-as-party-vp-idUSKBN1EH0FL" target="_blank"&gt;Zimbabwe's Mnangagwa appoints former army boss as party VP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HARARE (Reuters) - Zimbabwean President Emmerson Mnangagwa appointed retired army boss Constantino Chiwenga and veteran politician Kembo Mohadi as the ruling party's vice presidents, a spokesperson said on Saturday. The appointments paved the way for the two to ascend to similar positions in government, officials said. Mnangagwa, who took over last month from 93-year-old Robert Mugabe after the intervention of the military, is under pressure from opposition parties and the public to implement political reforms. Under Mugabe's 37-year rule political space was limited, with the latter part of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Constantino Chiwenga named ZANU-PF deputy - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/12/constantino-chiwenga-named-zanu-pf-deputy-171223151740442.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIWLAu8FESIj9VoiA-Lx55QqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 16:50:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/12/constantino-chiwenga-named-zanu-pf-deputy-171223151740442.html" target="_blank"&gt;Constantino Chiwenga named ZANU-PF deputy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zimbabwean President Emmerson Mnangagwa has appointed a military commander who played a big part in the ousting of former leader Robert Mugabe as one of his deputies in the ruling party. The appointment of retired generalConstantino Chiwenga at the senior ZANU-PF position, was announced on in a statement by the presidential press secretary. Kembo Mohadi, a long-serving state minister, was also named ZANU-PF vice president. Chiwenga, who resigned this week from his military role, was instrumental in a coup last month that eventually forced 93-year-old Mugabe to hand in his resignation letter...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Zimbabwe’s Mnangagwa Taps Ex-general for Ruling Party VP - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/zimbabwe-zanu-pf-chiwenga/4176605.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPnbIH_iWvG7amLPsCyfVqAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 17:43:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/zimbabwe-zanu-pf-chiwenga/4176605.html" target="_blank"&gt;Zimbabwe’s Mnangagwa Taps Ex-general for Ruling Party VP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zimbabwe’s President Emmerson Mnangagwa appointed a recently retired army general and a defense official Saturday as the country’s ruling party vice presidents. General Constantino Chiwenga, who retired last Sunday, led the military takeover in November that precipitated the resignation of the country’s longtime leader. Defense Minister Kembo Mohadi is the other person appointed as the ZANU-PF party's vice president. The announcement was made in a statement Saturday by George Charamba, spokesman for Mnangagwa. It was General Chiwenga who in November led the apparent coup that forced Preside...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Special Report: 'Treacherous shenanigans' - The inside story of Mugabe's downfall - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zimbabwe-politics-mugabe-specialrepor/special-report-treacherous-shenanigans-the-inside-story-of-mugabes-downfall-idUSKBN1DQ0AG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAaygmzAGz1w02nNIKV_-JgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 14:40:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-zimbabwe-politics-mugabe-specialrepor/special-report-treacherous-shenanigans-the-inside-story-of-mugabes-downfall-idUSKBN1DQ0AG" target="_blank"&gt;Special Report: 'Treacherous shenanigans' - The inside story of Mugabe's downfall&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By MacDonald Dzirutwe, Joe Brock and Ed Cropley HARARE (Reuters) - Inside State House in Harare, Robert Mugabe was in the tightest spot of his 37-year rule. Tanks were on the streets and troops had occupied the state broadcaster, from where the army had announced it had taken control of Zimbabwe. Mugabe, 93 years old but still alert, remained defiant. The only leader the country had known since independence was refusing to quit. At a tense meeting with his military top brass on Nov. 16, the world's oldest head of state put his foot down: "Bring me the constitution and tell me what it says,"...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>