<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRGN3TjNKMkVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:09:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Yasmin relinquishes position as MDEC CEO - The Sun Daily</title><link>https://www.thesundaily.my/business/yasmin-relinquishes-position-as-mdec-ceo-JC224038</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780128136211</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thesundaily.my/business/yasmin-relinquishes-position-as-mdec-ceo-JC224038" target="_blank"&gt;Yasmin relinquishes position as MDEC CEO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Sun Daily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/yasmin-mahmood-to-step-down-as-ceo-of-mdec-on-jan-15/" target="_blank"&gt;Yasmin Mahmood to step down as CEO of MDEC on Jan 15 - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/lifestyle/bots/2018/12/437879/datuk-yasmin-relinquishes-position-ceo-mdec" target="_blank"&gt;Datuk Yasmin relinquishes position as CEO of MDEC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/12/06/mdec-ceo-yasmin/" target="_blank"&gt;Yasmin Mahmood to relinquish MDEC CEO post on Jan 15 next year - Tech News&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/116629" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC chief to step down on January 15&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Malaysian Insight&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWlUMktlbWpZQU1FWlItRVc5cTBvY0dLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thesundaily.my">The Sun Daily</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/aSBqcyVaFoMoZYKDG5gEm_nHsg9bhuZLxam1Q20jSO0elRW9AZya7qNEAdL9o11kUdDbXp0HsC6HGSm-ZjHY52r4AC4KgtpHhcCWMvYyNsKDHaabsU8lSDFGg-fPvHQRR5i78EYbrKEzYJ6EtIUZnRq9cJfkfU-vkkiU8arDtg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>MDEC wants more startups to get to WORQ - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/07/20/mdec-pushes-tech-startups-with-worq/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFAB_rOE9OloIPCmj5G4xgcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 10:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/07/20/mdec-pushes-tech-startups-with-worq/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC wants more startups to get to WORQ&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The Malaysian Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) today announced WORQ as a new Malaysia Digital Hub, one of MDEC’s initiatives to grow the Malaysian digital economy and produce successful startups. This means that local startups based in the newly established WORQ Coworking Space – located in Glo Damansara Shopping Mall – will be able to enjoy access to funding, coaching and mentorship, corporate tax exemptions and high speed broadband. The Malaysia Digital Hub status is given by MDEC to coworking spaces that have fulfilled certain criteria, such as organising talent developm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>PM launches the Digital Free Trade Zone - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/03/22/mdec-and-alibaba-launch-the-dftz/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPRxJeBZN5qA84OYKuyw-4oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMKKsiAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 11:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/03/22/mdec-and-alibaba-launch-the-dftz/" target="_blank"&gt;PM launches the Digital Free Trade Zone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prime Minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak launched the Digital Free Trade Zone (DFTZ), an e-hub established together with the Alibaba Group and the Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC). According to Alibaba Group executive chairman Jack Ma, who was speaking at the launch, Malaysia’s DFTZ will be the first outside of China and is meant to allow SMEs (small and medium enterprises) and “the younger generation”, as Ma puts it, more access to global markets by lowering trade barriers. Under the DFTZ, the plan is to establish an e-fulfilment hub, which is a logistics hub in close proximity...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC urges UK firms to tap into Malaysia’s ICT ecosystem - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2016/11/22/mdec-urges-uk-firms-to-tap-into-malaysias-ict-ecosystem/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP851gvrx1Gwyg89xmM-FekqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 11:21:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2016/11/22/mdec-urges-uk-firms-to-tap-into-malaysias-ict-ecosystem/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC urges UK firms to tap into Malaysia’s ICT ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: UK technology companies on a three-day trade mission to Kuala Lumpur starting Tuesday are encouraged to tap into Malaysia’s information and communications technology (ICT) ecosystem. The trade mission, comprising representatives from leading technology companies and potential investors, should also look at Malaysia as the gateway to other emerging markets in the Asean region, Malaysia Digital Economy Corp (MDEC) said in a statement. The visit by the delegation of business leaders and companies to Malaysia is part of the UK Technology Trade Mission 2016 organised by the UK Depa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Briefs - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/smebiz/news/2016/10/31/briefs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcMEbz_BXm6_jnY6gKVzE4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/smebiz/news/2016/10/31/briefs/" target="_blank"&gt;Briefs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digital to add above 20% to GDP by 2020 Malaysia's digital economy is expected to contribute more than 20% to the country's Gross Domestic Product (GDP) by 2020, exceeding the earlier target of 18.2%, set under the 11th Malaysia Plan. Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) chief executive officer Datuk Yasmin Mahmood attributed the revised projected growth to players' efforts, especially content creators. The industry's current contribution to the GDP is 17.8%. "I was told that our animation content, which is, among others, full of family value, is unique compared to that of other coun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Grab MYTrafficHack hackathon to address traffic woes and road safety - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/04/03/grab-to-organise-mytraffichack-hackhaton/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENAX9pds6j06FqtQqa8Y4a8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 08:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/04/03/grab-to-organise-mytraffichack-hackhaton/" target="_blank"&gt;Grab MYTrafficHack hackathon to address traffic woes and road safety&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grab, the popular ride hailing service, will be organising a hackathon called MyTrafficHack this weekend (April 8 to 9) to unearth new solutions and ideas for traffic problems and road safety. Taking place at the Asean Data Analytics eXchange (ADAX) at Bangsar South, the 24-hour hackathon will address the four key areas – hidden patterns in traffic accidents, citizen empowerment and better road safety, emergency response for road crashes and transport policy planning. The participants will work on their solutions with the assistance of open source tools and traffic data from OpenTraffic, th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDec signs MoU with China’s Hangzhou Municipal Government and Alibaba - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/05/12/mdec-signs-mou-with-hangzhou-municipal-government-and-alibaba/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBtAkzhyRlW5eCyHcMkmgmQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 09:47:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/05/12/mdec-signs-mou-with-hangzhou-municipal-government-and-alibaba/" target="_blank"&gt;MDec signs MoU with China’s Hangzhou Municipal Government and Alibaba&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) has signed a three-way Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Hangzhou Municipal Government and Alibaba Company Ltd to facilitate cross-border trade among small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) under the Electronic World Trade Platform (eWTP). In a statement, MDec said the MoU seeks to enable the building of infrastructure for seamless cross-border ecommerce trade between Malaysia and China. The three parties agree to work together to explore potential strategic collaborations, consistent with Alibaba’s vision of eWTP. It said the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Locally produced children's show goes global with Netflix - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/04/27/hogie-the-globehopper-is-the-first-malaysian-made-animated-series-to-join-netflix/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBLUvMKxgYU5cEMTDxDX3tMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 06:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/04/27/hogie-the-globehopper-is-the-first-malaysian-made-animated-series-to-join-netflix/" target="_blank"&gt;Locally produced children's show goes global with Netflix&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian-made animated series Hogie The Globehopper is the first homegrown production to join Netflix’s extensive global catalogue. It will run the complete 52-episode (11 minutes each) show starting late this year here, in the United States, Canada, United Kingdom, Ireland, Australia and South-East Asia. Created by Lil Critter Workshop, the series follows Hogie the curious Tree Frog on his adventures around the world with his friends Bernie the Dragonfly and Lorna the Duck. Even before signing the lucrative deal with Netflix, Hogie The Globehopper was already a winner, clinching the Best ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bandar Malaysia, a catalyst for economic growth - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/05/02/bandar-malaysia-a-catalyst-for-economic-growth/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVsHKOd5ecZmXot9lNV_joqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/05/02/bandar-malaysia-a-catalyst-for-economic-growth/" target="_blank"&gt;Bandar Malaysia, a catalyst for economic growth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Bandar Malaysia project, which will be developed under the public-private partnership (PPP) model with an estimated cumulative gross development value of RM150bil, has the potential to be a catalyst for future economic growth, said master developer TRX City Sdn Bhd. Chief executive officer Datuk Azmar Talib said this development offered many business and investment opportunities including in the commercial sector, creative services and tourism and hospitality industries, such as MICE (meetings, incentives, conventions and exhibitions) and theme parks. “We foresee Bandar Ma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Fillip for fintech firms to forge ahead in digital era - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2016/12/23/fillip-for-fintech-firms-to-forge-ahead-in-digital-era/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhup3nR-lh0mC6rBi0QO5YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2016/12/23/fillip-for-fintech-firms-to-forge-ahead-in-digital-era/" target="_blank"&gt;Fillip for fintech firms to forge ahead in digital era&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LAST week, we had the privilege of pitching as one of the top 20 finalists during the Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) Fintech SMAC Bootcamp Demo Day. This event marked the climax of the inaugural Fintech SMAC Developer Bootcamp, a six-week mentorship and training programme that brought together more than 50 emerging Malaysian fintech (financial technology) companies with key industry experts, regulators and leading financial institutions. The dialogue and exchange between the multiple stakeholders helps to strengthen the overall fintech ecosystem in Malaysia. The Fintech Bootcam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Animation talent get Kre8tif in Cyberjaya - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/08/10/kre8tif-conference-and-content-festival-2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMww1SUzkyD5mlkNxChEl-cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 08:16:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/08/10/kre8tif-conference-and-content-festival-2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Animation talent get Kre8tif in Cyberjaya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Animation industry experts from all over the world converged in Cyberjaya for the Kre8tif! Conference and Content Festival 2017, held for the sixth year running. Organised by the Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) at the Cyberview Resort and Spa, Cyberjaya, the event saw the participation of over 500 industry players from Malaysia, South Korea, India, China, Japan, Singapore and the Philippines. This year, the conference was themed “Emotion in Motion”, reflecting on the passion of the animation industry in bringing their vision to life, while continuously perfecting the art-form. A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Data centre revenue forecast to surpass RM1bil this year - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/01/12/data-centre-revenue-forecast-to-surpass-rm1bil-this-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDQvpFscWRD9vDySE2UowksqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 09:09:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/01/12/data-centre-revenue-forecast-to-surpass-rm1bil-this-year/" target="_blank"&gt;Data centre revenue forecast to surpass RM1bil this year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Digital Economy Corp Sdn Bhd (MDEC) is optimistic that revenue generated by the data centre service industry in the country would exceed RM1bil this year. Director of digital enablement Wan Murdani Wan Mohamad (pic) said MDEC also planned a 10%-15% annual growth for the data service sector, while turning it into a RM2bil revenue generating industry by 2020, with the provision of more incentives to attract foreign players The industry is currently valued at around RM900mil, which is relatively low, when compared to leading players like Singapore and Hong Kong. He told ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Preparing the young for digital careers - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2017/09/23/preparing-the-young-for-digital-careers-fair-a-showcase-of-students-creativity-and-provides-insight/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEy0Z-jmBJ7ctGSRDLuHCHgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2017/09/23/preparing-the-young-for-digital-careers-fair-a-showcase-of-students-creativity-and-provides-insight/" target="_blank"&gt;Preparing the young for digital careers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia’s first-ever science and technology fair – #mydigitalmaker Fair 2017 – was a major success with more than 20,000 visitors turning up to view and experience digital projects created by students. The two-day youth-engagement event organised by Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) took place at Hall 6 of the Kuala Lumpur Convention Centre. It was held in conjunction with the Petrosains Science Festival 2017. The event focused on creating awareness among students and parents on how technology will play a huge part in the future job landscape. It also celebrated the ingenious cre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC aims to have 20,000 data professionals by 2020 - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/09/14/mdec-aims-to-have-20000-data-professionals-by-2020/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELu353RlmA_JuavSzyREEh0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 14:05:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/09/14/mdec-aims-to-have-20000-data-professionals-by-2020/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC aims to have 20,000 data professionals by 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Digital Economy Corp (MDEC) aims to have 20,000 data professionals by 2020, said its head of strategic partnership, N. Somasundaram.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC’s Data Star to produce 20,000 data professionals by 2020 - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/10/02/mdecs-data-star-to-produce-20000-data-professionals-by-2020/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMY0wxOh6qQdjzrt26L0TT0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMKKsiAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/10/02/mdecs-data-star-to-produce-20000-data-professionals-by-2020/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC’s Data Star to produce 20,000 data professionals by 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) is accelerating the growth of data professionals in Malaysia with its Data Star programme. A public-private initiative, Data Star is a data science finishing school in Kuala Lumpur, designed to fast track the development of world-class data professionals. Participants will undergo a paid six-month programme that includes two months of intensive data science enablement and mentorship with experienced data scientists and placement at industry partners. The programme is curated in accordance with the Data Professional Skills Framework, a platform tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC records new investments of RM16.3bil in 2016 - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/03/16/mdec-registers-new-investments-of-rm16-3bil-in-2016/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBTSPB5LJ0O8V-gD9RU7R5YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 05:04:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/03/16/mdec-registers-new-investments-of-rm16-3bil-in-2016/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC records new investments of RM16.3bil in 2016&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysian Digital Economy Corp (MDEC) has today announced that Multimedia Super Corridor (MSC) companies have recorded new investments of RM16.3bil in 2016, of which RM6.43bil were from new investors. The new investments reflected a 40% increase from last year. Malaysia also saw a steady increase in export sales from MSC-status companies, at an 18% growth from 2015, contributing RM19.1bil. The Creative Content and Technology (CCT) cluster recorded the highest growth in export sales, with a contribution of RM1.17bil to total export sales in 2016. Despite uncertain economic cond...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC and UOA Holdings to set up gaming hub - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2016/11/18/mdec-and-uoa-holdings-to-set-up-gaming-hub/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEzNdiPY9VHyCoivjMJ5KdQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 09:51:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2016/11/18/mdec-and-uoa-holdings-to-set-up-gaming-hub/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC and UOA Holdings to set up gaming hub&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Malaysia Digital Economy Corp (MDEC) and UOA Holdings Sdn Bhd have signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) to set up a game hub in Bangsar South here with the objective of enhancing Malaysia’s gaming industry. Under the MoU, UOA Holdings will provide the infrastructure for a gaming hub while MDEC will facilitate the search for local talents and provide programmes to train and enhance their skills. MDEC chief executive officer Datuk Yasmin Mahmood said Malaysia had an exceptional talent pool for the gaming industry and the world was beginning to sit up and take notice. “...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Sin Chew wins coveted award at WCIT - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/09/14/sin-chew-wins-coveted-award-at-wcit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN8qkWcUhsCkAp22S2wcI3UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 09:38:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/09/14/sin-chew-wins-coveted-award-at-wcit/" target="_blank"&gt;Sin Chew wins coveted award at WCIT&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TAIPEI: Sin Chew Media Corporation Berhad was among the Malaysian winners at the World Congress on Information Technology (WCIT) 2017 in Taipei, Taiwan. The Malaysian delegation bagged seven awards, including the Outstanding User Organisation Award which was won by Sin Chew Media Corporation Berhad, at the awards held between Sept 10 and 13. It was the second time Taiwan had hosted the WCIT, touted as the "Olympics" of the ICT industry, after a lapse of 17 years. The event saw the participation of more than 3,700 IT industrial leaders from over 80 countries and territories. The Malaysian de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>The serious side of cartoons - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2016/10/18/the-serious-side-of-cartoons/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECnU0SSbaBGbYJ2EI0IGpjkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 09:13:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2016/10/18/the-serious-side-of-cartoons/" target="_blank"&gt;The serious side of cartoons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE characters from Upin &amp; Ipin, BoBoiBoy, Bola Kampung and Johan the Young Scientist could be funny but behind the scene, they are all serious enterprises raking in millions of ringgit as aspired by Malaysia Digital Economy Corp (MDEC). From 2D to 3D, the fast-paced animation industry has not only evolved in terms of technology, but in content with relatable local characters and settings fast attracting the public’s attention. Realising this demand, MDEC provides assistance in all areas of the animation industry eco-system from talent, market access, IP development to creating awareness. M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC: Adapt to new technology - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/07/24/mdec-adapt-to-new-technology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMJEwnR7lgDxwgiP_rJNBGwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/07/24/mdec-adapt-to-new-technology/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC: Adapt to new technology&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CYBERJAYA: All practices, be it the education system or human resources (HR), will have to change and adapt to new technology which has also created new jobs in its wake. Malaysian Digital Economy Corp Sdn Bhd (MDEC) talent and digital entrepreneurship director Siti Norliza Mohd Sahar said the education system in Malaysia has to be more practical-based and implement a more hands-on approach. “With the emergence of new technology and jobs such as big data analysts and drone traffic optimisers, which were unheard of five years ago, the skill sets required for jobs will also change. “There is ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>GetCover unveils app that leverages on motor insurance detariffication - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/09/30/getcover-unveils-app-that-leverages-on-motor-insurance-detariffication/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF286dDPAQ-HM52Xn-sTRnkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/09/30/getcover-unveils-app-that-leverages-on-motor-insurance-detariffication/" target="_blank"&gt;GetCover unveils app that leverages on motor insurance detariffication&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: GetCover launched a new mobile phone application that allow consumers to purchase motor insurance from its platform. The company said in a statement that the app leverages on the recent motor insurance detariffication. “With a thorough understanding of the rising trends on digital transactions, we have placed extra attention to details, to ensure that all transactions are made through a trusted and secure payment system. “Through the continuous efforts of our technical team, users may look forward to a seamless, easy and secure experience thanks to the advancement in interfac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hasnul’s Top 5 Best Games of All Time - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/02/27/hasnuls-top-5-best-games-of-all-time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFz_6paqOBi9z5DAKB1FfxMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMKKsiAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2017/02/27/hasnuls-top-5-best-games-of-all-time/" target="_blank"&gt;Hasnul’s Top 5 Best Games of All Time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The director of the Creative Multimedia division of MDEC gives his list of five of the best games ever. Here we list the favourite titles of Hasnul Hadi Samsudin, the director of the Creative Multimedia Division in Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC), who is responsible for ­promoting Malaysian game developers and animators both locally and ­internationally. “This is tough! As tough as asking me what my top five films are! I can’t do ­justice to all the great games out there,” he says. “So hopefully it doesn’t offend any of my friends in the industry. There are a whole lot more game...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Two winners in National Big App Challenge - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/smebiz/news/2016/12/21/two-winners-in-national-big-app-challenge-team-watchus-bags-professional-prize-with-its-emergency-re/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG9v0zJJliLKBtVS3K9LXGgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/smebiz/news/2016/12/21/two-winners-in-national-big-app-challenge-team-watchus-bags-professional-prize-with-its-emergency-re/" target="_blank"&gt;Two winners in National Big App Challenge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BIG Data Analytics (BDA) was the driver behind the development of innovative and life-changing applications at the third National Big APP Challenge, organised by Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC). Serving as a strategic platform to encourage the extensive use of BDA in the public and private sectors, the challenge called upon developers, entrepreneurs, and students to create applications for the betterment of businesses and the public in general. The challenge was concluded with the announcement of winners for two of its tracks – professional and academia. WatchUs, an emergency re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Malaysian tech icoons gain-ing momentum globally - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/01/10/tech-icons-gain-ing-momentum-globally/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKjyCNqKNtfQcxBYDFxq0roqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/01/10/tech-icons-gain-ing-momentum-globally/" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysian tech icoons gain-ing momentum globally&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The digital economy has been identified by the Government as a key driver of economic growth and a catalyst for the country to transform to a knowledge-based economy. This year has been identified as the “Year of the Internet Economy” for Malaysia and among the major initiatives to be rolled out are the digital tech hub and digital free zone. This has led the Government to place a strong emphasis on developing the country’s digital economy. Another initiative launched in 2015 by Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) is its Global Acceleration and Innovation Network (GAI...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>M’sia, Japan hold inaugural meeting on information and communications cooperation - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMo8wrf3ST5WAf_QMx_6nJoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 11:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia and Japan today held the inaugural meeting of the Joint Working Committee (JWC) on Information and Communications Cooperation, discussing ways in which the two governments could deepen cooperation in information technology, broadcasting sector and postal services. The meeting was co-chaired by Malaysia's Communications and Multimedia Ministry secretary-general Mohd Ali Mohamad Nor and Japan’s Internal Affairs and Communications Ministry director-general for International Affairs, Global Strategy Bureau Akihiko Miyamoto. The four-hour meeting at the ministry’s building in Putrajaya ...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>eSports all set to take region by storm - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/04/esports-all-set-to-take-region-by-storm-rm10mil-allocation-a-boost-for-gaming-industry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENRBIVZvoeLLIj5M61BzzyUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/04/esports-all-set-to-take-region-by-storm-rm10mil-allocation-a-boost-for-gaming-industry/" target="_blank"&gt;eSports all set to take region by storm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: With 2.4 million enthusiasts in the country and RM10mil thrown in under Budget 2019, Malaysia is off to a great start to become an eSports hub of the region. That is the sentiment of the Malaysia Digital Economy Corpor­ation (MDEC), which said it looked forward to working with the Youth and Sports Ministry following Friday’s announcement. MDEC said eSports was more than just playing games as it also provided high-quality jobs such as software developers, engineers, graphic designers, illustrators and marketeers and advertisers. “The Budget announcement gives legitimacy and em...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Razer CEO pledges RM10mil for eSports in Malaysia: Budget 2019 - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/11/02/razer-ceo-on-budget-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEmH47ypQtDEYgZnPYMjZpQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/11/02/razer-ceo-on-budget-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;Razer CEO pledges RM10mil for eSports in Malaysia: Budget 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The CEO of Razer, global gaming hardware company, Min-Liang Tan has responded positively on the government’s Budget 2019 announcement to allocate RM10mil towards the development of eSports in Malaysia. He replied to a tweet posted by Youth and Sports minister Syed Saddiq on the announcement, saying that he too would like to pledge a RM10mil investment for eSports in Malaysia. Bro, it's an incredibly progressive budget for Malaysia to commit MYR10M to esports for the youth and millennials. In light of that, I will also be investing MYR10M for esports in Malaysia in 2019. Let's...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC partners with iCandy Interactive to promote blockchain games - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/10/30/mdec-and-icandy-partner-to-develop-blockchain-games/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELUVQQvOgjL-aO6wtroOi5AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 13:17:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/10/30/mdec-and-icandy-partner-to-develop-blockchain-games/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC partners with iCandy Interactive to promote blockchain games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Videogame investor iCandy Interactive Limited is seeking to promote blockchain technology in game making in Malaysia through a collaboration with Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC). Its CEO Desmond Lee announced the company would provide funding and knowledge sharing as part of its efforts to nurture local game makers that are developing blockchain-powered games. On the other side of the partnership, MDEC would help iCandy recruit game studios keen to venture into the niche space. The two organisations signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) on the partnership during the Level U...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘A national digital ID for all’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/12/a-national-digital-id-for-all-gobind-plans-in-the-works-to-ease-verification-and-fight-fraud/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA5M-YijvW1FZQpFT-v04-IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/12/a-national-digital-id-for-all-gobind-plans-in-the-works-to-ease-verification-and-fight-fraud/" target="_blank"&gt;‘A national digital ID for all’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: All Malaysians may soon have a national digital ID, says the Communications and Multimedia Minister. Gobind Singh Deo (pic) said his ministry was looking to develop this “platform of trust” in cyberspace to eliminate elements of fraud and cheating. “A plan for a national digital ID is being formulated. This digital ID is not meant to replace the MyKad nor would it be mandatory for everyone,” he said at the launch of the Malaysiakini e-commerce summit here yesterday. Gobind added that a national digital ID, which is likely to be out by the middle of next year, was meant to prov...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC predicts bright future for data professionals - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/02/mdec-predicts-bright-future-for-data-professionals/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELO8QkP-hWUvAimqQlqDSGEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 09:34:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/02/mdec-predicts-bright-future-for-data-professionals/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC predicts bright future for data professionals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR (Bernama): Job opportunities in the field of big data are expected to exceed the country's target of producing 20,000 data professionals by 2020, said Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) chief executive officer Datuk Yasmin Mahmood. She said current global competition required each company as well as government agency to apply the technology in their system. "Data is the new oil, they have no choice, the problem is that they have to get the right people. Nowadays, there are many banks and telco companies that already use data, besides that, we have a lot of start-ups th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Malaysians sceptical of using technology for financial transactions - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/10/02/malaysians-sceptical-of-using-technology-for-financial-transactions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOE9Gi714-dswBbzKxKq92QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 09:36:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/10/02/malaysians-sceptical-of-using-technology-for-financial-transactions/" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysians sceptical of using technology for financial transactions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia’s financial technology ecosystem has grown tremendously over the past two years, but Malaysians continue to be sceptical over the use of technology to conduct their financial transactions. Malaysian Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) Chief Operating Officer Datuk Ng Wan Peng said the adoption of cashless payments, especially among small and medium enterprises (SMEs), is still relatively low. “Continuous efforts (to promote cashless payments) are being done together with the central bank as it is much safer and the cost of handling money is relatively cheaper,” she tol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Gobind calls for investigation into MDEC on its ADAX project - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/30/gobind-calls-for-investigation-into-mdec-on-its-adax-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECaAzmYMxG0I7t0LT497uU0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 09:45:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/30/gobind-calls-for-investigation-into-mdec-on-its-adax-project/" target="_blank"&gt;Gobind calls for investigation into MDEC on its ADAX project&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The Communications and Multimedia Minister has called for an investigation into a project called Asean Data Analytics Exchange (ADAX) by the Malaysian Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC). "I have called for a full investigation into the concerns raised over this project. "A probe is currently being undertaken by MDEC into the matter. I am informed that MDEC has further requested the National Audit Department to conduct an audit, which is also currently underway, on the said project," its Minister Gobind Singh Deo said in a statement on Saturday (June 30). Gobind said the proje...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC collaborates with Grab to beat KL traffic - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/04/13/mdec-and-grab-mou-on-malaysia-city-brain-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENOxrQkNYjRHHPJVJ9-boXEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMKKsiAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 10:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/04/13/mdec-and-grab-mou-on-malaysia-city-brain-project/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC collaborates with Grab to beat KL traffic&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysian Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) has formalised its collaboration with ride-hailing service Grab to use its real-time, anonymised traffic data to manage KL traffic. MDEC Data Economy director Dr Karl Ng Kah Hou said Grab's contribution to the Malaysia City Brain initiative is invaluable as the Artificial Intelligence (AI) ecosystem is vitally dependent on the richness and variety of its data sources. “No two cities are the same, and the sharing of such data resources by Grab will also help our city planners to better understand the unique transportation needs of each city and ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Maxis, MDEC team up to build IoT ecosystem for businesses - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/03/09/maxis-mdec-team-up-to-build-iot-ecosystem-for-businesses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEV7OIBxNIyO4yHjDi_emd4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 07:21:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/03/09/maxis-mdec-team-up-to-build-iot-ecosystem-for-businesses/" target="_blank"&gt;Maxis, MDEC team up to build IoT ecosystem for businesses&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Maxis Bhd is working with Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation's (MDEC) Internet of Things (IoT) solution providers to enhance the IoT ecosystem for businesses. In a joint statement, Maxis said it would leverage on its IoT solutions and 4G network to work with MDEC to offer innovative solutions. Among Maxis’ IoT offerings include mDrive, a fleet tracking solution which is used internally for its own business operations. This tracking solution enables businesses to reduce cost and promotes safer driving habits within the fleet management of a company. Maxis’ head of business so...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pikom reveals plans to boost investments in startups - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/03/09/pikom-chairman-announces-plans-including-sea-dragon-investments/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIltfUqHCtnQYzdVHp8XO9EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/03/09/pikom-chairman-announces-plans-including-sea-dragon-investments/" target="_blank"&gt;Pikom reveals plans to boost investments in startups&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National ICT Association of Malaysia (Pikom) aims to super charge regional startups with its Sea Dragon initiative that would match them with investors to raise up to US$25mil (RM97.82mil) in funding. Its chairman Ganesh Kumar Bangah said they would narrow down 20 promising startups – mostly Malaysians, though it was open to regional companies too – for the first upcoming session in May. Sea Dragon would be an annual sustainable Venture Pitch Platform for South-East Asian startups seeking investments, growth and global market expansion, done in collaboration with Malaysia Digital Econom...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC: Cyber security specialist in high demand, commands lucrative pay - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/02/09/mdec-rolls-out-pride-programme-to-increase-cyber-security-specialist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1Ec6m9u7zOBGt9iYGxNJwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/02/09/mdec-rolls-out-pride-programme-to-increase-cyber-security-specialist/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC: Cyber security specialist in high demand, commands lucrative pay&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cyber security looks to continue being a highly lucrative career, even as Malaysian agencies and educators attempt to bring fresh blood into the market. Protection Group International (PGI) chief corporate development officer Sebastian Madden said IT professionals that up-skill to specialise in security could easily see a 20% pay bump, while many studying the field were already landing job offers before graduation. "Demand is outgrowing supply and pushing up pay, as companies compete for the best talent," he said, adding that the demand was growing exponentially as countries introduced regu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Alibaba to take on Kuala Lumpur’s traffic in first foreign project - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/01/29/alibaba-to-take-on-kuala-lumpurs-traffic-in-first-foreign-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENlPyNDBDF5nAmqv5x5il_UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 08:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2018/01/29/alibaba-to-take-on-kuala-lumpurs-traffic-in-first-foreign-project/" target="_blank"&gt;Alibaba to take on Kuala Lumpur’s traffic in first foreign project&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Alibaba Group will set up a traffic control system harnessing artificial intelligence for Malaysia's capital Kuala Lumpur, its first such service outside China, as the e-commerce giant pushes to grow its cloud computing business. Alibaba Cloud, the cloud computing arm of Alibaba Group, said on Monday it plans to make live traffic predictions and recommendations to increase traffic efficiency in Kuala Lumpur by crunching data gathered from video footage, traffic bureaus, public transportation systems and mapping apps. It is partnering with state agency Malaysia Digital Economy ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDEC to expand startup co-working space beyond Klang Valley - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/11/14/mdec-to-expand-startup-co-working-space-beyond-klang-valley/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFz2DYKqLQBa4-15YH6Rg4YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 12:57:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/11/14/mdec-to-expand-startup-co-working-space-beyond-klang-valley/" target="_blank"&gt;MDEC to expand startup co-working space beyond Klang Valley&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Digital Economy Corp (MDEC) is looking to expand startup co-working space under the Malaysia Digital Hub outside of the Klang Valley early next year.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib: Almost 2,000 SMEs want in on Digital Free Trade Zone - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/31/najib-almost-2000-smes-want-in-on-digital-free-trade-zone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDjPY1YvWp58iV7MAPEZjwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 10:10:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/31/najib-almost-2000-smes-want-in-on-digital-free-trade-zone/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib: Almost 2,000 SMEs want in on Digital Free Trade Zone&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Digital Free Trade Zone (DFTZ) initiative that will be opened this Friday (Nov 3) has received an overwhelming response from Malaysian small and medium enterprises (SMEs), says Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak (pic). The Prime Minister said the e-hub set up with China's Alibaba Group and the Malaysia Digital Economy Corporation (MDEC) initially targeted to rope in 1,500 SMEs to be involved in the DFTZ. However, Najib said more than 1,900 SMEs have so far shown their interest to do business in the DFTZ. "This means than nearly 2,000 SMEs now stand to get easier access to the glob...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MDec: Budget 2018 will enhance Digital Malaysia - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/10/27/budget-2018-will-enhance-digital-malaysia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAm7_LLcTqzk_f3rZA8dEycqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:45:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/10/27/budget-2018-will-enhance-digital-malaysia/" target="_blank"&gt;MDec: Budget 2018 will enhance Digital Malaysia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia Digital Economy Corp (MDec) CEO Datuk Yasmin Mahmood lauded Budget 2018's focus on accelerating growth and enhancing the well being of the rakyat in addition to further enhancing Digital Malaysia. Among the initiaitives in the budget highlighted by MDec, she noted that the RM100mil allocation for the eRezeki and eUsahawan programmes would ensure that the Digital Economy continues to be inclusive for the well-being of the rakyat, and in particular the B40 and M40 groups. "With both programmes going into their third year, we estimate that 150,000 rakyat would be trained...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>