<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Abu Kassim bin Mohamed - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyY3ZNVEl3ZEhoblpqTVNBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:31:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Abu Kassim: A-G's office told MACC some things missing in 1MDB audit report - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/07/abu-kassim-a-gs-office-told-macc-some-things-missing-in-1mdb-audit-report/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMihwFodHRwczovL3d3dy5mcmVlbWFsYXlzaWF0b2RheS5jb20vY2F0ZWdvcnkvbmF0aW9uLzIwMTgvMTIvMDcvYWJ1LWthc3NpbS1hLWdzLW9mZmljZS10b2xkLW1hY2Mtc29tZS10aGluZ3MtbWlzc2luZy1pbi0xbWRiLWF1ZGl0LXJlcG9ydC_SAQA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/07/abu-kassim-a-gs-office-told-macc-some-things-missing-in-1mdb-audit-report/" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Kassim: A-G's office told MACC some things missing in 1MDB audit report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Former anti-graft chief Abu Kassim Mohamed today revealed the auditor-general's office had informed them that “some things were not published” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/8vGy3ordeVClGfZiSzQyD3AogbsytoNVC9Cr1s1HghVCkzQHYl1OGCm80RNGYeDmocnPKQ2pS0Nqt1HRODgKHMlwa0lCeFi6LZF7TuoE-hMgqzCBVb32u76kRk3JEmJK-8p9Pu5YAblfOVj4b90=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>MACC not involved in any tampering of 1MDB report, says former chief - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/macc-not-involved-in-any-tampering-of-1mdb-report-says-former-chief/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFbfHucjeqAFhu3y05LhBZUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:14:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/macc-not-involved-in-any-tampering-of-1mdb-report-says-former-chief/" target="_blank"&gt;MACC not involved in any tampering of 1MDB report, says former chief&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) was not involved in any alleged tampering of the final 1MDB audit report, claims Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed. The former MACC chief said: "Not at all. (but) we tried to get the original (report)." Abu Kassim, who now heads the governance, integrity and anti corruption centre, said he had spoken to the then-auditor general on the report. "We tried to get a briefing on the report which was not published," he said. On Nov 25, Auditor General Tan Sri Madinah Mohamad said that one of the changes made to the 1MDB final audit report was the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Former MACC chief commissioner Dzulkifli Ahmad summoned to MACC over 1MDB probe - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/former-macc-chief-commissioner-dzulkifli-ahmad-summoned-to-macc-over-1mdb-probe/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFOp6ynCu_jlWMGDgOLj0IQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 04:32:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/former-macc-chief-commissioner-dzulkifli-ahmad-summoned-to-macc-over-1mdb-probe/" target="_blank"&gt;Former MACC chief commissioner Dzulkifli Ahmad summoned to MACC over 1MDB probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA (Bernama): Former Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief commissioner Tan Sri Dzulkifli Ahmad has been summoned as part of investigations into amendments to the 1Malaysia Development Bhd (1MDB) final audit report. Dzulkifli - who arrived at the MACC headquarters here on Wednesday (Dec 5) at 10.25 am - is among the witnesses sought after the MACC reviewed the original 1MDB final audit report for comparison with the final draft issued by the National Audit Department Malaysia (JANM). On Nov 25, Auditor-General Tan Sri Dr Madinah Mohamad revealed that the 1MDB final audit ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Umno deputy: Don’t blame us for 1MDB scandal - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/02/umno-deputy-dont-blame-us-for-1mdb-scandal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELztJ3GBTJJhsZcWdQ3WrAoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 13:14:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/02/umno-deputy-dont-blame-us-for-1mdb-scandal/" target="_blank"&gt;Umno deputy: Don’t blame us for 1MDB scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: It is unfair, unreasonable and illogical for any party to continue blaming Umno for the 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB) scandal, says party deputy president Datuk Seri Mohamad Hasan (pic). He urged all parties to be “mature, open and fair” to Umno. “Umno is an innocent party and has absolutely no involvement with any of 1MDB’s operations or transactions,” he posted on the party website, Umno Online, on Friday (Nov 2). “Umno and I are sympathetic to the former president (Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak) who had to deal with all this (blame),” he said, adding that the case must ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Still time for MPs to declare their assets, says Kota Melaka MP - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/10/02/still-time-for-mps-to-declare-their-assets-says-kota-melaka-mp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdQSY937eXja7WUO4735K8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/10/02/still-time-for-mps-to-declare-their-assets-says-kota-melaka-mp/" target="_blank"&gt;Still time for MPs to declare their assets, says Kota Melaka MP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A PARLIAMENTARIAN has clarified that his peers in Pakatan Harapan have until Oct 15 to submit their asset declaration forms. Kota Melaka MP Khoo Poay Tiong said the deadline was based on a letter sent to them by the National Centre for Governance, Integrity and Anti-Corruption (GIACC) and signed by its chairman Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed. He said the letter clearly stated that the MPs had to submit their asset declaration forms within three months from the date they were sworn in, which was on July 16. ”So, the three-month period given to us will only lapse on Oct 15,” he told reporters aft...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Kota Melaka MP says GIACC letter clearly states Oct 15 deadline for asset declaration - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/29/kota-melaka-mp-says-giacc-letter-clearly-states-oct-15-deadline-for-asset-declaration/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILxBrmH4A0WchNS0oi0IA8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 08:05:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/29/kota-melaka-mp-says-giacc-letter-clearly-states-oct-15-deadline-for-asset-declaration/" target="_blank"&gt;Kota Melaka MP says GIACC letter clearly states Oct 15 deadline for asset declaration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MELAKA: A DAP lawmaker has clarified that all Pakatan Harapan MPs have until Oct 15 to submit their asset declaration forms as required by the Pakatan Government. Kota Melaka MP Khoo Poay Tiong (pic) said the deadline was based on a letter sent to them by the National Centre for Governance, Integrity and Anti-Corruption (GIACC) and signed by its chairman Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed. He said the letter clearly stated that the MPs needed to submit their asset declaration forms within three months from the date of their swearing-in which was on July 16 this year. "Therefore, the three-month per...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Singapore court allows return of RM46mil 1MDB, SRC International funds to Malaysia - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/10/singapore-court-allows-return-of-rm46mil-in-1mdb-src-funds-to-malaysia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOzLTYPAcCASIsEDgG3VDacqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 04:38:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/10/singapore-court-allows-return-of-rm46mil-in-1mdb-src-funds-to-malaysia/" target="_blank"&gt;Singapore court allows return of RM46mil 1MDB, SRC International funds to Malaysia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The Singapore State Courts have granted disposal orders in respect of monies that were misappropriated from 1Malaysia Development Bhd (1MDB) and SRC International. Tan, Rajah and Cheah, the solicitors for the Malaysian government, 1MDB and SRC International, said the monies recovered are in various currencies with a total value of some S$15.3mil (RM45.9mil). "These monies are being transferred to the special 1MDB recovery bank account in Kuala Lumpur. "Efforts to recover other unlawfully misappropriated assets are ongoing," the law firm said in a statement on Monday (Sept 10)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Chief sec Ali Hamsa to retire on Aug 29 - report - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8-Knz_TfbcUfO_LV3amlcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 00:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chief secretary to the government Ali Hamsa will retire on Aug 29 , reported The Star today. This is despite a proposal for Prime Minister Dr Mahathir Mohamad to retain the 63-year-old top official to stay until end of this year. Citing sources in the chief secretary's office, the report said Ali's last day will be on Aug 29. Another source in the Prime Minister's Office (PMO) said Ali’s contract of would not be renewed. “It was the previous administration that extended his contract,” said a source. With Ali’s pending retirement, Putrajaya is already abuzz over his successor, said the repor...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Info about RM24mil diamond possibly leaked by disgruntled customs officers - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/11/abu-kassim-old-video-resurfaces/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEwG-5ehBohwoHw3iPm0-5cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 10:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/11/abu-kassim-old-video-resurfaces/" target="_blank"&gt;Info about RM24mil diamond possibly leaked by disgruntled customs officers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: A video has surfaced of a former Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief saying that information about a RM24mil diamond ring, allegedly purchased by Datin Seri Rosmah Mansor in 2011, was leaked by disgruntled Customs Department officers. In the undated video, former MACC chief Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed was giving a speech when he made the claim that angry Customs officers had leaked the information in an attempt to smear the reputation of former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak. Abu Kassim's audience, believed to be MACC officers, were told that this was ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>RM24mil ring making its rounds again - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/12/rm24mil-ring-making-its-rounds-again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF2TjU0IC_SZoSSkdV5xZ6EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/12/rm24mil-ring-making-its-rounds-again/" target="_blank"&gt;RM24mil ring making its rounds again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The RM24mil diamond ring allegedly purchased by the former prime minister’s wife Datin Seri Rosmah Mansor in 2011 is back in the news after a video emerged showing Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed (pic) claiming that it was disgruntled Customs Department officers who had sparked the controversy by leaking information about it. In the undated video uploaded two weeks ago on YouTube, the former Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief was seen giving a speech when he made the claim about Rosmah and the controversial ring. He said the Customs officers had leaked the “Borang K...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Dr M: Those holding public office must name proxies - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/14/dr-m-those-holding-public-office-must-name-proxies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENxpndlu4e4PinV_YFdf3aoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 04:24:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/14/dr-m-those-holding-public-office-must-name-proxies/" target="_blank"&gt;Dr M: Those holding public office must name proxies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(NST) – THOSE holding public office will be compelled to name their proxies. They will be expected to do this when they declare their assets, an administrative process that will be made compulsory for ministers, deputy ministers and political secretaries, as is the case with civil servants. This requirement, Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad said, would be extended to (Pakatan Harapan) members of parliament. Dr Mahathir had, in June, said the three groups of appointees would be required to declare their assets to him and that the information would be passed on to relevant agencies. Thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Ex-MACC boss: Customs officers ‘retaliated’ against Najib, sparked ‘diamond ring’ saga - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/11/ex-macc-boss-customs-officers-retaliated-against-najib-sparked-diamond-ring-saga/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIyDjX1j4nT08aX1rcp36lMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 10:24:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/11/ex-macc-boss-customs-officers-retaliated-against-najib-sparked-diamond-ring-saga/" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-MACC boss: Customs officers ‘retaliated’ against Najib, sparked ‘diamond ring’ saga&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Mkini) – Disgruntled Royal Malaysian Customs Department officers allegedly leaked information on the transit of a diamond ring worth RM24 million in 2011 to damage then prime minister Najib Abdul Razak’s reputation. This allegation was made by former Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief Abu Kassim Mohamed (above) in a speech delivered later that year and which has now made its way on video-sharing site YouTube (view video below). During the speech, Abu Kassim said the errant officers had leaked a document known as “Borang Kastam 1” which showed the item entering the country wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>So, Rafizi lied about the RM24 million diamond ring after all - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/11/so-rafizi-lied-about-the-rm24-million-diamond-ring-after-all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJmsYKeaJzTBpVaeMib_e-kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 09:37:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/11/so-rafizi-lied-about-the-rm24-million-diamond-ring-after-all/" target="_blank"&gt;So, Rafizi lied about the RM24 million diamond ring after all&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I can understand lowly-educated Malay fishermen, farmers and Felda settlers believing in lies and fake news. But how come Chinese who receive a far superior Chinese school education can also get fooled so easily? Are Chinese schools really that superior after all if they breed a whole generation of idiots? NO HOLDS BARRED Raja Petra Kamarudin Rafizi Ramli wants to be the next Deputy President of PKR. According to what Rafizi told his people, he has the support of Anwar Ibrahim and Dr Wan Azizah Wan Ismail who are very upset with Azmin Ali because of his alliance with Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Ministers to declare assets once procedures finalised, says Abu Kassim - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/12/ministers-to-declare-assets-once-procedures-finalised-says-abu-kassim/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAzSZ-t10qFkO1fdETxVtS8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 07:32:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/12/ministers-to-declare-assets-once-procedures-finalised-says-abu-kassim/" target="_blank"&gt;Ministers to declare assets once procedures finalised, says Abu Kassim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The Prime Minister and his Cabinet can start declaring their assets as required once the code of ethics is finalised and the official form is ready, said Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed. The Governance, Integrity and Anti-Corruption Centre (GIACC) director-general said he had asked the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) - in charge of drawing up a form - to fast track it to ensure the process of asset declaration can be done soon. Once ready, the form as well as amendments to the code of ethics for members of the administration and lawmakers would be presented to the Cabinet ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>1MDB task force confirms freeze of bank accounts - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/29/1mdb-task-force-confirms-freeze-of-bank-accounts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE1maJhLxFDgpKS4yYIg5ycqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 04:46:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/29/1mdb-task-force-confirms-freeze-of-bank-accounts/" target="_blank"&gt;1MDB task force confirms freeze of bank accounts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB) task force confirms it has frozen several bank accounts of individuals and organisations, the latter including Umno and other political parties. This was because it believes the individuals and organisations were involved in the misappropriation of 1MDB funds. “Several accounts belonging to associations and companies were also frozen in connection with the case. The investigation will be conducted fairly and professionally based on the rule of law,” the task force said in a statement on Friday (June 29). The task force also called on al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Abu Kassim may replace Ali Hamsa as Chief Secretary, says report - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/18/abu-kassim-possible-replacement-ali-hamsa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDylbgzNvv-K6AzeAr4LbEMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 02:05:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/18/abu-kassim-possible-replacement-ali-hamsa/" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Kassim may replace Ali Hamsa as Chief Secretary, says report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SHAH ALAM: Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed (pic) has been mentioned as a possible replacement for Tan Sri Dr Ali Hamsa as Chief Secretary to the Government (KSN), reported Sinar Harian. Ali, 63, will retire in August after his service was continued on a contractual basis during the administration of former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak. If this suggestion gets the approval from Yang di-Pertuan Agong, Sultan Muhammad V under the advice of Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad, the National Centre for Governance, Integrity and Anti-Corruption (GIACC) that is helmed by Abu Kassim could...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Abu Talib: Probe on 1MDB almost complete - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/22/abu-talib-probe-on-1mdb-almost-complete/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOHswc6dOzHTRe6_hvZt8o8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 12:32:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/22/abu-talib-probe-on-1mdb-almost-complete/" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Talib: Probe on 1MDB almost complete&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB) special committee chairman Tan Sri Abu Talib Othman said the multiple investigations into the troubled state-owned investment fund are almost complete. He told reporters, after meeting Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief Datuk Mohd Shukri Abdull and his predecessor Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed, that the 1MDB taskforce had briefed him on the latest developments. “Investigations are progressing well and almost ready to be submitted to the Attorney General Chambers for its attention,” he said as he was leaving Ilham Tower here, where the m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Senior officers forced out over 1MDB make comeback - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/23/senior-officers-forced-out-over-1mdb-make-comeback/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEJwn8kDM1BV9IT-gjHPMNwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/23/senior-officers-forced-out-over-1mdb-make-comeback/" target="_blank"&gt;Senior officers forced out over 1MDB make comeback&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The return of Datuk Nor Shamsiah Mohd Yunus to helm Bank Negara marks the culmination of comebacks for many senior officials who had been forced out at the height of investigations into the 1Malaysia Development Bhd (1MDB). They have either “opted for early retirement” or were removed from their positions from late 2015 to 2016. The former deputy governor had spearheaded investigations into the scandal-ridden company at the central bank level. She had left Bank Negara on Nov 15, 2016, with no formal announcements or explanations by the central bank, then led by Tan Sri Muhamm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Ambrin out of retirement to head panel on governance - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/07/ambrin-out-of-retirement-to-head-panel-on-governance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEbN95pabZLEhVT28o7xpIIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/07/ambrin-out-of-retirement-to-head-panel-on-governance/" target="_blank"&gt;Ambrin out of retirement to head panel on governance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Just over a year after he retired as Auditor-General, Tan Sri Ambrin Buang (pic) is back in the fray – this time as chair of a special committee to investigate governance in ministries and agencies. Ambrin, 68, is the latest addition to the ranks of former high-ranking officials roped in by Tun Dr Maha­thir Mohamad’s Pakatan Harapan administration to address the previous administration’s wrongdoings and improve governance. Others who have been recalled to serve include former Attorney General Tan Sri Abdul Gani Patail, former Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>New centre to fight corruption - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/02/new-centre-to-fight-corruption-existing-antigraft-agencies-may-be-restructured-or-disbanded/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGWKxV9AZpR0GqH_T4pDCcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/02/new-centre-to-fight-corruption-existing-antigraft-agencies-may-be-restructured-or-disbanded/" target="_blank"&gt;New centre to fight corruption&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Existing agencies looking into governance, integrity and anti-corruption may be restructured or disbanded following the setting up of a centre to oversee these areas in the administration. The National Centre for Gover­nance, Integrity and Anti-Corrup­tion (GIACC) has been set up by the Pakatan Harapan Government to realise its election pledges on these issues. A statement by the Prime Minister’s Office (PMO)said the scope of the centre would not overlap that of existing agencies. “In fact, the agencies will either be restructured to be more effective or be disbanded,” the statem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Azmin and Abu Kassim turn up for surprise meeting with CEP - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/26/azmin-and-abu-kassim-turn-up-for-surprise-meeting-with-cep/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECmVPjJsvbxiM64r3yVBNkYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/26/azmin-and-abu-kassim-turn-up-for-surprise-meeting-with-cep/" target="_blank"&gt;Azmin and Abu Kassim turn up for surprise meeting with CEP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Two unexpected personalities have shown up at Menara Ilham to meet with the Council of Eminent Persons (CEP). Media personnel staking out the entrance of the building were surprised to see Economic Affairs Min­ister Datuk Seri Azmin Ali arriving at about 9.50am yesterday. Azmin later gave reporters the slip and left the building via a different exit. Former Malaysian Anti-Corrup­tion Commission chief Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed arrived two hours later, but also left without addressing the media. Azmin and Abu Kassim were not on the list of those invited to brief the CEP. Among ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Make haste on corruption - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2018/05/31/make-haste-on-corruption/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA3AuXdISvWMTtKiz9F_43AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2018/05/31/make-haste-on-corruption/" target="_blank"&gt;Make haste on corruption&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE recently constituted Institutional Reform Committee has its work cut out. Corruption is high on the agenda as it attracted a lot of attention and focus during the recent general election. The public is concerned over the perceived sad state of affairs on corruption. It would be a fallacy and naivety to believe that corruption entered the Malaysian scene only over the past 10 years, however. As a backdrop, the fight against corruption took a fresh turn in 2009. The concern was to address the worrisome prevailing rising trend of corruption in Malaysia. The then existing Anti-Corruption Ag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Xavier Justo spotted at MACC HQ; believed to be meeting 1MDB task force - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/24/xavier-justo-spotted-at-macc-hq-believed-to-be-meeting-1mdb-task-force/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJtrBhTdY3p4VsLQ7jzbYEEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 02:06:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/24/xavier-justo-spotted-at-macc-hq-believed-to-be-meeting-1mdb-task-force/" target="_blank"&gt;Xavier Justo spotted at MACC HQ; believed to be meeting 1MDB task force&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Former PetroSaudi executive Xavier Andre Justo (pic) has arrived at the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) headquarters. The Swiss international was spotted at the building at 9am, where he is believed to be meeting the 1MDB Special Task Force. Former MACC chief commissioner Tan Sri Abu Kassim, who is part of the task force, had said Wednesday that the team had met up with Justo to help facilitate investigation into 1MDB. Besides Abu Kassim, other members of the task force are former Attorney-General Tan Sri Abdul Gani Patail, MACC chief commissioner Datuk Seri Shukri Ab...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>CEP meets ex-MACC boss Abu Kassim, Azmin Ali, TM chairman and FGV top brass - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/25/cep-meets-ex-macc-boss-abu-kassim-azmin-ali-tm-chairman-and-fgv-top-brass/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI-eRAvJ4DlQ_4GGXNeS6QsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 05:53:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/25/cep-meets-ex-macc-boss-abu-kassim-azmin-ali-tm-chairman-and-fgv-top-brass/" target="_blank"&gt;CEP meets ex-MACC boss Abu Kassim, Azmin Ali, TM chairman and FGV top brass&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohammed has met with the Council of Eminent Persons. Abu Kassim was seen entering Ilham Tower at 11.50am on Friday where the meeting was held, but did not speak to media personnel waiting outside. Earlier, Telekom Malaysia chairman Tan Sri Dr Sulaiman Mahbob met the council. Dr Sulaiman, who is also former acting chairman of Felda Global Ventures Holdings Berhad (FGVH), was spotted leaving the building at 11.36am but did not speak to the media either when approached. Also meeting the council Friday wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shukri aims to put things right after two years in wilderness and endless threats - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/23/fears-tears-and-unfinished-business-shukri-aims-to-put-things-right-after-two-years-in-wilderness-a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG00GiDIIAW176vOYMp1WzsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/23/fears-tears-and-unfinished-business-shukri-aims-to-put-things-right-after-two-years-in-wilderness-a/" target="_blank"&gt;Shukri aims to put things right after two years in wilderness and endless threats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: It was an emotional tell-all for back-from-the-twilight Datuk Seri Mohd Shukri Abdull. The former Malaysian Anti-Corrup­tion Commission (MACC) de­pu­ty chief commissioner is back as the head honcho after two years in the wilderness. He choked while speaking, wiped away tears and had his head buried in his hands as he relived the harrowing two years since his “retirement”. He told a story of bitter disappointment, fear and disillusionment but the real story was of his comeback – and his determination to finish some unfinished business. Shukri, who has made a stunning comeback afte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Malay Rulers rebutt MACC chief, saying they did give serious attention to 1MDB issue - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/22/malay-rulers-rebutt-macc-chief-saying-they-did-give-serious-attention-to-1mdb-issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIaJarG29vgZsSgixHDX7wkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 14:56:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/22/malay-rulers-rebutt-macc-chief-saying-they-did-give-serious-attention-to-1mdb-issue/" target="_blank"&gt;Malay Rulers rebutt MACC chief, saying they did give serious attention to 1MDB issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Malay Rulers have given serious attention to the 1Malaysia Development Bhd (1MDB) issue, says the Keeper of the Rulers’ Seal Tan Sri Syed Danial Syed Ahmad. Responding to remarks made by Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief commissioner Datuk Seri Mohd Shukri Abdull during a special media conference yesterday, he said the Rulers had issued a statement on the issue on Oct 6, 2015. “In fact, on the Rulers’ decree, I invited the chief commissioner of the MACC, his deputy and senior officers to have an audience with the Rulers to give relevant briefings. “Within t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>New MACC chief breaks down in recounting what he went through - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/22/new-macc-chief-breaks-down-in-recounting-what-he-went-through/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL8EpvEPoBpgzXxm032usSYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 04:03:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/22/new-macc-chief-breaks-down-in-recounting-what-he-went-through/" target="_blank"&gt;New MACC chief breaks down in recounting what he went through&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Newly appointed Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief commissioner Datuk Seri Mohd Shukri Abdull broke down when he recounted his time running away from Malaysian authorities to the United States. This came after his former boss Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed at the MACC decided to indict former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak over the RM2.6bil that was found in his personal bank account. However, on the day he was going to do, former Attorney-General Gani Patail was removed from his position, Shukri told a press conference at the MACC headquarters here on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>1MDB task force starts work today - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/22/1mdb-task-force-starts-work-today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK_u98lo7KOB5_5x6O3vz28qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/22/1mdb-task-force-starts-work-today/" target="_blank"&gt;1MDB task force starts work today&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The newly formed 1Malaysia Development Bhd (1MDB) special task force is getting to work quickly by having its first meeting a day after its formation was announced. Its co-head Tan Sri Abdul Gani Patail said the task force, which was set up by the Prime Minister’s Office, would meet today. “We will speak to you guys then,” said the former Attorney-General when approached by reporters after the meeting yesterday. With Abdul Gani were other co-heads – MACC chief commissioner Datuk Seri Mohd Shukri Abdull as well as his predecessor Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed. They entered the bui...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>I met with rulers, ministers over 1MDB but got nothing, says MACC chief - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/22/i-met-with-rulers-ministers-over-1mdb-but-got-nothing-says-macc-chief/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECfcACfjv3lBqtPcRaX3WbAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 07:45:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/22/i-met-with-rulers-ministers-over-1mdb-but-got-nothing-says-macc-chief/" target="_blank"&gt;I met with rulers, ministers over 1MDB but got nothing, says MACC chief&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief Mohd Shukri Abdull today claimed he and his chief at the time, Abu Kassim Mohamad, had met with the Council of Rulers to ask for their help to remove Najib Razak from office but to no avail. “We told them the scandals involving 1MDB were more than just rumours, and that for the good of the country, Najib had to be removed. But our pleas were not entertained,” he said at a press conference at the MACC headquarters today. Shukri also claimed they had gone to ministers prior to meeting the Council of Rulers for the same objective. “But ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Dr M: Shukri Abdull to head MACC - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/17/dr-m-shukri-abdull-to-head-macc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBooia_9KQz-P6i4YV-tyRYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 06:58:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/17/dr-m-shukri-abdull-to-head-macc/" target="_blank"&gt;Dr M: Shukri Abdull to head MACC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – Retired Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) deputy chief commissioner Datuk Seri Mohd Shukri Abdull (pic) will return to lead the anti-graft agency. Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahahtir Mohamad made the announcement during a press conference at Yayasan Selangor here Thursday. “To replace Tan Sri Dzulkifli Ahmad, we have appointed Shukri to head the MACC,” he said. Dzulkifli had reported back to the Attorney-General’s Chambers (AGC) on Tuesday (May 15). On Monday (May 14), Dzulkifli sent a letter to end his contract as the MACC head to Chief Secretary to the Government Tan Sri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Former chief Abu Kassim to return to MACC? - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/14/former-chief-abu-kassim-to-return-to-macc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENwBavvdDARXh3ghr7JkdOkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 07:01:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/14/former-chief-abu-kassim-to-return-to-macc/" target="_blank"&gt;Former chief Abu Kassim to return to MACC?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Following the resignation of Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief commissioner Tan Sri Dzulkifli Ahmad, his predecessor Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed (pic) is widely tipped to take over as the top graft-buster. A source said Abu Kassim would most likely return to head the MACC and “finish what he left behind” after he was replaced by Dzulkifli in August 2016. Abu was appointed MACC commissioner on Jan 1, 2010. While many thought he had retired, the source said Abu Kassim was “exiled” to a small department in UiTM. On speculation that Abu Kassim would be the upcoming...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Abu Kassim and Shamsiah Yunus to be in 1MDB Task Force - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/15/abu-kassim-and-shamsiah-yunus-to-be-in-1mdb-task-force/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKJ7uszae_YpU0-RMFRU1wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 04:57:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/15/abu-kassim-and-shamsiah-yunus-to-be-in-1mdb-task-force/" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Kassim and Shamsiah Yunus to be in 1MDB Task Force&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daim said former Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission chief commissioner Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed and former BNM deputy governor Datuk Shamsiah Yunus will join a task force probing 1MDB. (MMO) – The Team of Eminent Persons advising the government has identified key individuals to help in a task force which will reopen investigations into the US$4.5 billion (RM17.7 billion) allegedly lost by 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB). The Straits Times (ST) quoted two-time finance minister Tun Daim Zainuddin as saying those identified include former Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Shukri is back to helm MACC - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/18/shukri-is-back-to-helm-macc-two-years-after-retirement-he-returns-to-answer-call-of-duty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJNsQmVo2Tb8XhTR4syMKogqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/18/shukri-is-back-to-helm-macc-two-years-after-retirement-he-returns-to-answer-call-of-duty/" target="_blank"&gt;Shukri is back to helm MACC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: In 2016, he opted to retire and deliver an emotional parting shot but two years on, Datuk Seri Mohd Shukri Abdull is back in charge of the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC). The country’s former No.2 graft buster admitted that he was surprised by the “call of duty”. “At the moment, I don’t want to comment about my appointment,” he said when contacted. Yesterday, Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad announced that the 58-year-old would take over the post of MACC chief commissioner. “He has vast experience and a lot of information (on past wrongdoings of the previou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Former MACC chief checks in at AGC - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/15/former-macc-chief-checks-in-at-agc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHbQnhknwIPmOYM65rA-PiAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:45:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/15/former-macc-chief-checks-in-at-agc/" target="_blank"&gt;Former MACC chief checks in at AGC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Former Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief Tan Sri Dzulkifli Ahmad has reported back to the Attorney-General's Chambers (AGC) on Tuesday (May 15). Dzulkifli arrived at 8.05 am at the AGC office here in Presint 4 in a Proton Perdana and waited a few minutes in the car before exiting. Dressed in a black suit, Dzulkifli just smiled and waved at the media waiting for him before walking into the lobby and registered at the counter. On Monday, Dzulkifli said he had sent a letter to end his contract as the MACC chief to the Chief Secretary to the Government Tan Sri Dr Ali ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Outgoing MACC chief to report back to A-G’s Chambers on May 15 - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/14/outgoing-macc-chief-to-report-back-to-attorney-general-chambers-on-may-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDVc6qAHFb_lMLC83asWqNMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 12:26:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/14/outgoing-macc-chief-to-report-back-to-attorney-general-chambers-on-may-15/" target="_blank"&gt;Outgoing MACC chief to report back to A-G’s Chambers on May 15&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Outgoing Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) chief commissioner Tan Sri Dzulkifli Ahmad (pic) will report back to the Attorney-General’s Chambers on Tuesday (May 15). Dzulkifli was previously the National Revenue Recovery Enforcement Team director at the A-G’s Chambers before he took over as MACC chief commissioner from Tan Sri Abu Kassim Mohamed in August 2016. He earlier submitted his resignation letter to chief secretary to the Government Tan Sri Ali Hamsa on Monday. "I have submitted my letter of termination for my contract as the MACC chief to the chief secretary...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>