<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Hishammuddin Hussein - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNRGQ2TmpsekVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:24:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Former defence minister Hishammuddin defends himself on Malaysia's role in Yemen war - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/hishammuddin-defends-himself-on-msia-role-in-yemen-war/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFyzr6WNOQTnRzfYmA0m9xsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/hishammuddin-defends-himself-on-msia-role-in-yemen-war/" target="_blank"&gt;Former defence minister Hishammuddin defends himself on Malaysia's role in Yemen war - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former defence minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein has asked Deputy Defence Minister Liew Chin Tong, to declassify intelligence ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hishammuddin broke law by deploying troops to Yemen without cabinet approval - Patriot - New Straits Times</title><link>https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/437076/hishammuddin-broke-law-deploying-troops-yemen-without-cabinet-approval</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMKyIenDTxNKjIg9LXv4tQ8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow9sveCjC0m9YBMPDtoQM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 04:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/437076/hishammuddin-broke-law-deploying-troops-yemen-without-cabinet-approval" target="_blank"&gt;Hishammuddin broke law by deploying troops to Yemen without cabinet approval - Patriot&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The National Patriots Association (Patriot) has urged former defence minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein to come clean on the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nst.com.my">New Straits Times</source></item><item><title>Explain why troops sent to Saudi Arabia, Patriot tells Hishammuddin - The Malaysian Insight</title><link>https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/116676</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiLGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZW1hbGF5c2lhbmluc2lnaHQuY29tL3MvMTE2Njc20gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:29:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/116676" target="_blank"&gt;Explain why troops sent to Saudi Arabia, Patriot tells Hishammuddin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Malaysian Insight&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mohamad Arshad Raji says the National Security Council has no authority on overseas military deployment.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com">The Malaysian Insight</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/FnKcNDyU0R0aipdqOeJa95X7HJ2h6n8rNdoc9C7aek4z1f1d-lV750O_92BH4dtny36yVav-hHWmDjeNAhR1vC99_V-4aybsBqwlr2yvYdyMTpMNofImvfGoo5zhUvoo_F6ILk6K3Xn-Ec3rInYg5uoQtavrtj7IxaMGK5F6W_ytIh8bMOqrNA=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Hishammuddin welcomes probe on Ops Yemen 2 - New Straits Times</title><link>https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/438205/hishammuddin-welcomes-probe-ops-yemen-2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM3pyxyh1o8rSGshPhgvrVsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow9sveCjC0m9YBMJHSoQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 05:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/438205/hishammuddin-welcomes-probe-ops-yemen-2" target="_blank"&gt;Hishammuddin welcomes probe on Ops Yemen 2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein has welcomed the government's decision to establish a Special Parliamentary Committee for Defence ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nst.com.my">New Straits Times</source></item><item><title>Kit Siang: Hishammuddin still trying to bring Jho Low back to face justice? - The Sun Daily</title><link>https://www.thesundaily.my/local/kit-siang-hishammuddin-still-trying-to-bring-jho-low-back-to-face-justice-HB210786</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMic2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZXN1bmRhaWx5Lm15L2xvY2FsL2tpdC1zaWFuZy1oaXNoYW1tdWRkaW4tc3RpbGwtdHJ5aW5nLXRvLWJyaW5nLWpoby1sb3ctYmFjay10by1mYWNlLWp1c3RpY2UtSEIyMTA3ODbSAQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 02:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thesundaily.my/local/kit-siang-hishammuddin-still-trying-to-bring-jho-low-back-to-face-justice-HB210786" target="_blank"&gt;Kit Siang: Hishammuddin still trying to bring Jho Low back to face justice?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Sun Daily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: What has happened to Datuk Seri Hishamuddin Hussein's self-appointed role and offer to bring Low Taek Jho or Jho Low back to Malaysia t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thesundaily.my">The Sun Daily</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/Fftbge6Di-zGI8KpHttgsvwk8b3SVJq5C40dQ6xkuN96PsNn_KBAhgFRgZ2-slge4WsdpWDIs7QBs2eXHjUCla-Yz6G7In9gtxRdDvIR_bUgd7SCAjWEhYaEy9vKfIAcUaUsn1H8-lpPA5L9lHLIYKjZLmonAdIWSvDrQ_6J0w=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Hishammuddin answers issues on Ops Yemen 2 - The Sun Daily</title><link>https://www.thesundaily.my/local/hishammuddin-answers-issues-on-ops-yemen-2-JJ218957</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiVGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZXN1bmRhaWx5Lm15L2xvY2FsL2hpc2hhbW11ZGRpbi1hbnN3ZXJzLWlzc3Vlcy1vbi1vcHMteWVtZW4tMi1KSjIxODk1N9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thesundaily.my/local/hishammuddin-answers-issues-on-ops-yemen-2-JJ218957" target="_blank"&gt;Hishammuddin answers issues on Ops Yemen 2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Sun Daily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former Defence Minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Tun Hussein has asked the government to declassify details of the National Security ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thesundaily.my">The Sun Daily</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/kLDxAscAJ8SQuCNb5LeWj5vBfPVko1OrFNPnTsidd5vFlnCoqawCmondCLwUpWLpoXOAxqQLWNIBeLJeX9-Z1HkdDTQ70HsKTkMG5HOpg8Xvb_bHZd35xuKDXkXMOeMi17wVMre1F5f_ZTma7pmG_FojMm6egiS_QFS25Bd6=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Since when could NSC deploy troops overseas, veterans ask Hisham - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_kKf621zTJmvJkvGD69EYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:09:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Armed forces veterans group Patriot wants former defence minister Hishammuddin Hussein to explain how troop deployments abroad can be sanctioned by the National Security Council (NSC). "We seek Hishammuddin to explain where it is stipulated in the NSC Act that the NSC is empowered to deploy forces overseas and be part of a force engaged in a war with another country?" Patriot president Mohamed Arshad Raji said in a statement today. "Is he implying that the NSC is the authority to sanction the deployment of armed forces troops overseas?" Arshad added, asking if Hishammuddin also meant that c...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Liew Chin Tong: No directive came from NSC on Ops Yemen 2 - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/liew-chin-tong-no-directive-came-from-nsc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA695uM1LnYtIuXXd5j_8rAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:49:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/liew-chin-tong-no-directive-came-from-nsc/" target="_blank"&gt;Liew Chin Tong: No directive came from NSC on Ops Yemen 2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: There was no "initiating directive" from the National Security Council (NSC) to involve the Malaysian military in Ops Yemen 2, says Deputy Defence Minister Liew Chin Tong. He disputed former defence minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein, who claimed on Wednesday (Dec 5) that the NSC handled the operation. "I am disappointed that the former defence minister (Hishammuddin) is not here today. "He said that the NSC had made a decision but after checking, the NSC did not produce any initiating directive. "When an operation needs to be carried out, it needs the initiating directi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakatan Harapan must declassify information on Ops Yemen 2 immediately - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/12/05/pakatan-harapan-must-declassify-information-on-ops-yemen-2-immediately/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFARdlWoDapGSc3CggfkFngqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 08:05:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/12/05/pakatan-harapan-must-declassify-information-on-ops-yemen-2-immediately/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan Harapan must declassify information on Ops Yemen 2 immediately&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – Former defence minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein (pic) has asked Deputy Defence Minister Liew Chin Tong, to declassify intelligence information regarding Ops Yemen 2. He said this today (Dec 5) in response to the bombshell dropped by Liew on Monday (Dec 3) in Parliament that Malaysian Armed Forces (ATM) personnel were deployed to assist military operations in Saudi Arabia in relation to the Yemen war without Cabinet approval. Hishammuddin claimed the matter was handled by the National Security Council (NSC). “He said the matter wasn’t brought to the Cabinet. (He should) ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Former defence minister Hishammuddin defends himself on Malaysia's role in Yemen war - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N4NtCuIh72s</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN5oFuA-YVqEkE_Mf4sy2ywqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMJOsiAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:14:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N4NtCuIh72s" target="_blank"&gt;Former defence minister Hishammuddin defends himself on Malaysia's role in Yemen war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former defence minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein has asked Deputy Defence Minister Liew Chin Tong, to declassify intelligence information regarding Ops Yemen 2. He said this in response to the bombshell dropped by Liew on Monday (Dec 3) in Parliament that Malaysian Armed Forces (ATM) personnel were deployed to assist military operations in Saudi Arabia in relation to the Yemen war without Cabinet approval.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Act Of Treason – Cousin Brothers Najib &amp; Hishammuddin Deployed Military To “Yemeni Civil War” Without Approval - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/12/06/act-of-treason-cousin-brothers-najib-hishammuddin-deployed-military-to-yemeni-civil-war-without-approval/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAHI52FYYzI57ub12zo0stQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:51:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/12/06/act-of-treason-cousin-brothers-najib-hishammuddin-deployed-military-to-yemeni-civil-war-without-approval/" target="_blank"&gt;Act Of Treason – Cousin Brothers Najib &amp; Hishammuddin Deployed Military To “Yemeni Civil War” Without Approval&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Najib and his cousin brother Hishammuddin had essentially placed the country at risk of “terrorism target” because the operation was held during the peak of Syrian War. Finance Twitter We raised our suspicions two years ago in 2016 when Saudi Arabia bragged about their massive military exercise – Northern Thunder – which involved 350,000 troops from 20 countries, including Saudi Arabia, Kuwait, Bahrain, Qatar, the UAE, Oman, Jordan, Pakistan, Djibouti, Mauritania, Senegal, Sudan, Chad, Tunisia, Morocco, Comoros, Mauritius, Egypt, Maldives and Malaysia. Saudi news media boasted that the for...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Our officials implicated in Aussie case - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/12/03/our-officials-implicated-in-aussie-case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC_p7yXRnjs7A0xZcRec9BIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInmnwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 04:23:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/12/03/our-officials-implicated-in-aussie-case/" target="_blank"&gt;Our officials implicated in Aussie case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person identified was business-man Haris Hussein – the brother of Datuk Hishammuddin Hussein and cousin of Datuk Seri Mohd Najib Razak. Gurdial SinghNijar, The Sun Daily YET again a scandal has emerged involving Malaysian officials. Implicated in receiving bribes from two companies owned by the Reserve Bank of Australia (RBA), Securency and Note Printing Australia, to win contracts to print the RM5 note with polymer plastic coating. This newspaper reported the story on July 30, 2014. But it soon disappeared from public view as an Australian court made “unprecedented” suppression orders ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Liew: There was no Cabinet approval for Ops Yemen 2 - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/03/liew-there-was-no-cabinet-approval-for-ops-yemen-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE5G_VsqA8UzJeTSZcrFT4YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 07:27:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/03/liew-there-was-no-cabinet-approval-for-ops-yemen-2/" target="_blank"&gt;Liew: There was no Cabinet approval for Ops Yemen 2&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Cabinet did not approve Ops Yemen 2 that saw the Malaysian Armed Forces being deployed to Saudi Arabia to assist its military operations in Yemen. Deputy Defence Minister Liew Chin Tong (pic) said that from June 11, 2015, about 27 officers and 62 rank-and-file troops were deployed to Riyadh, Saudi Arabia on a rotational basis every three months for Ops Yemen 2. However, the troops were withdrawn following the Pakatan Harapan government's decision on Sept 4 this year. “Actually, Malaysia was not involved in combat activities but was merely there to give logistics support to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib rubbishes claims of attempts to 'buy over' Malay-Muslim Pakatan MPs - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/21/najib-rubbishes-claims-of-attempts-to-buy-over-malaymuslim-pakatan-mps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK2Nv03xEdfzMi4vQ3Uos3wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 06:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/21/najib-rubbishes-claims-of-attempts-to-buy-over-malaymuslim-pakatan-mps/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib rubbishes claims of attempts to 'buy over' Malay-Muslim Pakatan MPs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak has denied any attempts to buy over support or entice any Malay-Muslim Pakatan Harapan lawmakers in a bid to form a government on May 9. "There is no instruction made by Umno to buy support from any Pakatan Harapan lawmakers. If it comes from other parties, I do not know about it. "But there was none from me on that night," he told reporters at the Parliament lobby on Wednesday (Nov 21). On Monday (Nov 19), Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad said that there were some Malay-Muslim leaders within the Pakatan coalition who were...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MP: It’s normal for us to get together - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/17/mp-its-normal-for-us-to-get-together-having-different-views-doesnt-mean-we-cant-be-friendly-say-poli/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ0bhu-UUcByXTR3_BcXclgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/17/mp-its-normal-for-us-to-get-together-having-different-views-doesnt-mean-we-cant-be-friendly-say-poli/" target="_blank"&gt;MP: It’s normal for us to get together&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: A recent video and photo showing PKR president-elect Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim being friendly with several Umno lawmakers in the MPs’ lounge in Parliament have raised eyebrows and led to speculation about political manoeuvres. But many have pointed out that it is quite common for MPs to put aside their political differences and just ... well, get along. It is in fact common in the Dewan Rakyat for lawmakers to clash and fiercely defend their opinions but be friendly with each other in the MPs’ lounge, which is next to the august Hall. Sometimes while trading barbs, MPs often j...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hisham asks if Defence Ministry able to buy assets with reduced budget - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/15/hisham-asks-if-defence-ministry-able-to-buy-assets-with-reduced-budget/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK7qYV77jQPoT9XruVpHbrsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 05:50:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/15/hisham-asks-if-defence-ministry-able-to-buy-assets-with-reduced-budget/" target="_blank"&gt;Hisham asks if Defence Ministry able to buy assets with reduced budget&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Pakatan Harapan government needs to do a reality check on its promise and allocation pertaining to the Defence Ministry in its recently tabled Budget 2019. Former Defence Minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein, who said Pakatan had reduced the ministry's budget, questioned if it was able to buy military assets on its restricted allocations. "The Defence Minister (Mohammad Sabu) said the ministry would like to purchase some (military assets) but the allocation has been reduced by RM2bil. "If before (during Barisan Nasonal), we were unable to purchase such assets, how is h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Umno and PAS racial card have limited impact says Kadir Jasin - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/15/umno-and-pas-racial-card-have-limited-impact-says-kadir-jasin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENMYsTNBo3YbDwPeFNLHbzIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 15:52:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/15/umno-and-pas-racial-card-have-limited-impact-says-kadir-jasin/" target="_blank"&gt;Umno and PAS racial card have limited impact says Kadir Jasin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Attempts by Opposition parties to exploit racial and religious issues to win support will bring limited results, said the Prime Minister’s media adviser Datuk A. Kadir Jasin. Responding to a question from the floor during a dinner talk organised by a law firm here, Kadir said Malaysians of all races had proven that they were united in rejecting such attempts. “If you go by the May 9 results, the race and religious card are important but I don’t think they have the same kind of weightage as in past. “I think Malaysians of all races and religions vocied out their opposition to t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib free to issue any statement as long as not against the law, says Kadir - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/16/najib-free-to-issue-any-statement-as-long-as-not-against-the-law-says-kadir/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBX7T2_lz54UJJe7qQUXXhgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 02:54:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/16/najib-free-to-issue-any-statement-as-long-as-not-against-the-law-says-kadir/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib free to issue any statement as long as not against the law, says Kadir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR (Bernama): Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak is free to issue any statement on social media as long as it is not against the law, says Datuk A. Kadir Jasin (pic). Kadir, media and communications adviser to Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad, said that as far as he knew, an accused person could still make any statement outside the court if it was not related to the case he was charged on. "If it is not against the law, I supposed we should not stop him, I don't think there are people who go to support him after they get rid of him. If he is not found guilty ye...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>How Malaysia’s education system went to the dogs since 1974 - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/13/how-malaysias-education-system-went-to-the-dogs-since-1974/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChyV04YqICrcw8Fe-3sAAQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMOvrnwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 10:38:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/13/how-malaysias-education-system-went-to-the-dogs-since-1974/" target="_blank"&gt;How Malaysia’s education system went to the dogs since 1974&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Malay nationalists such as Mahathir Mohamad, Musa Hitam, Sulaiman Daud, Abdullah Badawi, Anwar Ibrahim, Hishammuddin Hussein, Mustapha Mohamed, Khaled Nordin, Muhyiddin Yassin, Idris Jusoh, Mahdzir Khalid (and now Maszlee Malik) used education as their political platform (just like what DAP and MCA are doing with the Chinese schools and Chinese education issue — using them as political platforms). And that was why Malaysia’s education system went to the dogs. NO HOLDS BARRED Raja Petra Kamarudin The Pakatan Harapan government loves blaming the previous Prime Minister for all the country...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Hishammuddin says willing to work with IGP to track down Jho Low - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/30/hishammuddin-says-willing-to-work-with-igp-to-track-down-jho-low/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIloTiX6qMS6GHF668nyC8sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 06:42:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/30/hishammuddin-says-willing-to-work-with-igp-to-track-down-jho-low/" target="_blank"&gt;Hishammuddin says willing to work with IGP to track down Jho Low&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein says he will cooperate with the Inspector-General of Police (IGP) Tan Sri Fuzi Harun in the hunt for rogue businessman Low Taek Jho, or better known as Jho Low, to seek closure over the 1MDB controversy. "If he (Jho Low) is in China, why didn't the authorities hand him over to us? That is why, as I understand, that the Royal Malaysian Police (PDRM) and the Chinese authorities have formed a close working relationship. "I will also work closely with the IGP, who previously said that he welcomes efforts in my personal capacity to assist them in thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Is Mahathir planning to hold GE15 next year? - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/30/is-mahathir-planning-to-hold-ge15-next-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECG8nQbYXsHWf4jtF3JC7eYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMPrlnwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 08:28:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/30/is-mahathir-planning-to-hold-ge15-next-year/" target="_blank"&gt;Is Mahathir planning to hold GE15 next year?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad planning to dissolve Parliament and call for a snap general election as soon as Anwar Ibrahim makes his move to take over as Malaysia’s Eighth Prime Minister? In that case, this explains why Pakatan Harapan is still in election mode and explains why the 2015-2018 election campaign is still ongoing almost six months after GE14. THE CORRIDORS OF POWER Raja Petra Kamarudin The hot news today is about 1MDB, the RM2.6 billion-donation, statements by the Saudi minister, statements by the former MACC boss, statements by the former PAC boss, statements about former Prime ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>When talk turns into reality - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/29/when-talk-turns-into-reality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB8aVKwC9SHLd0074H5CQjEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 05:56:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/29/when-talk-turns-into-reality/" target="_blank"&gt;When talk turns into reality&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Umno members have been inundated with claims that their party will be deregistered soon but is that enough to drive the rank and file into the arms of Dr Mahathir? Joceline Tan, The Star DATUK Seri Mustapa Mohamed was spotted on Saturday making his way through Subang airport to catch a flight to Kota Baru. The man, who rarely makes news, made the headlines after joining Parti Pribumi Bersatu Malaysia the night before. He has been quite a catch for Bersatu because he is known for his credibility, brains and diligence. There is also talk that he will soon be joining the Mahathir Cabinet, pre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>IGP welcomes Hisham's offer to track down Jho Low - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/24/igp-welcomes-hishams-offer-to-track-down-jho-low/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAGmmohCU3wNOIb1tWYnVXoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 02:18:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/24/igp-welcomes-hishams-offer-to-track-down-jho-low/" target="_blank"&gt;IGP welcomes Hisham's offer to track down Jho Low&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Bukit Aman welcomes Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein's assistance in tracking down fugitive businessman Low Taek Jho or better known as Jho Low, said Tan Sri Mohamad Fuzi Harun. The Inspector-General of Police said while police are unsure of the former defence minister's motive, his offer of assistance is much welcomed. "On our part, we have utilised our resources in tracking down Jho Low, his father and a few others, including contacting our foreign counterparts as well as Interpol. "While there is no encouraging leads yet, we are not giving up," he told a press conference aft...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Khairy: Hisham's offer to go after Jho Low interesting, but it should not be a personal effort - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/23/khairy-hishams-offer-to-go-after-jho-low-interesting-but-it-should-not-be-a-personal-effort/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJy8LLdiQoSi_2Qgwjt97AcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 08:48:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/23/khairy-hishams-offer-to-go-after-jho-low-interesting-but-it-should-not-be-a-personal-effort/" target="_blank"&gt;Khairy: Hisham's offer to go after Jho Low interesting, but it should not be a personal effort&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Umno lawmaker Khairy Jamaluddin (pic) supports Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein's offer to find fugitive financier Low Taek Jho, also known as Jho Low, but says it should not be a personal effort. Khairy (BN-Rembau) said the offer was interesting, but if the former defence minister had any information on Low's whereabouts, he should have given it to authorities. "If he (Hishammuddin) has any information, he should share it with the government, because that is the best way to bring Jho Low back to face investigation," he told reporters at the Parliament lobby on Tuesday (Oct 23)...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hard to give a timeline, says Dr M - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/26/hard-to-give-a-timeline-says-dr-m-ending-southern-thailand-unrest-is-complex/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE2UacS-Cqq6Ov_FWFWpqUkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/26/hard-to-give-a-timeline-says-dr-m-ending-southern-thailand-unrest-is-complex/" target="_blank"&gt;Hard to give a timeline, says Dr M&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WILL take time to resolve the unrest in southern Thailand as the matter is complex, said Prime Mi­­nister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad. He said it was hard to put a timeline on when the matter could be settled as it involved several groups. Asked about the demands on autonomy and separation by rebel groups in the province, Dr Mahathir said there were many definitions on autonomy. “In Jogjakarta in Indonesia, even though autonomy is given, the central government is still strong. “Acheh is also still strong although Jakarta has given it autonomy. We don’t know to what extent the de­­mand (by th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘Better to give us info on Jho Low than go after him’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/26/better-to-give-us-info-on-jho-low-than-go-after-him/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3Zntze_57ibawMFLLeCjIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/26/better-to-give-us-info-on-jho-low-than-go-after-him/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Better to give us info on Jho Low than go after him’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reports by MARTIN CARVALHO, RAHIMY RAHIM and CLARISSA CHUNG Deputy Home Minister Datuk Azis Jamman has asked Datuk Seri His­hammuddin Hussein to provide information on Low Taek Jho, better known as Jho Low, to the autho­rity instead of going after the fugitive financier himself. “This is my view, if he has information about Jho Low’s where­abouts, it would be good if he gives that information to us. “The best way is for him to give the information to the (Home) mi­­nistry. “There is no need for him to go there himself,” Azis told reporters at Parliament lobby. On Monday, Hishammuddin who i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hisham: I’ll bring Jho Low back to Malaysia - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/23/hisham-ill-bring-jho-low-back-to-malaysia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELJ4HbrRHKm1f-GNGiNm8y8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/23/hisham-ill-bring-jho-low-back-to-malaysia/" target="_blank"&gt;Hisham: I’ll bring Jho Low back to Malaysia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Tun Hussein (pic) has personally offered to help go after Low Taek Jho until the “end of earth” and bring the fugitive businessman back to Malaysia to face the music. The former defence minister said he would use his previous contacts and links with the Chinese government and friends to try and bring back Jho Low if he is in China. “I think all Malaysians want to know the truth. So we need to bring him back to face justice. “It has nothing to do with ­whether you are from the opposition or the government. This is about justice,” he said at the Parliamen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hisham offers to help with Jho Low, vows to not rest ‘until the end of the world’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/22/hisham-offers-to-help-with-jho-low-vows-to-not-rest-until-the-end-of-the-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECXtKgdU5dM1C6RHlZgK6e0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 04:57:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/22/hisham-offers-to-help-with-jho-low-vows-to-not-rest-until-the-end-of-the-world/" target="_blank"&gt;Hisham offers to help with Jho Low, vows to not rest ‘until the end of the world’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former defence minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein has offered in his personal capacity to try and bring fugitive financier Low Taek Jho back to Malaysia, vowing to do “until the end of the world”. Hishammuddin said he would use his previous contacts and links with the Chinese government to try and bring back Low, also known as Jho Low, if he is in China. “I think all Malaysians want to know the truth. If they want to know the truth, we need to bring him back to face justice. “It has nothing to do whether you are from the opposition or the government, this is about justic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>An offer I could not refuse - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/making-progress/2018/10/25/an-offer-i-could-not-refuse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGUN7AUMC7CB2z57beHdCMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 07:39:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/making-progress/2018/10/25/an-offer-i-could-not-refuse/" target="_blank"&gt;An offer I could not refuse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Bukit Gantang by election in February 2009, the attention of the country was fixated on the UMNO election in March 2009. It was interesting because Tan Sri Muhyuddin Yassin, who led the chorus of calls for Tun Abdullah Ahmad Badawi to resign as UMNO President and Prime Minister after Barisan Nasional’s disastrous showing in the 12th General Election (GE12) had thrown his hat in the ring for the post of Deputy President of UMNO and by convention, if he wins, he would be the Deputy Prime Minister. Tan Sri Muhyuddin always came across as a stern and no-nonsense individual. He was art...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Muhyiddin was ‘happy to be sacked’, says MCA man - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/22/muhyiddin-was-happy-to-be-sacked-says-mca-man/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK2V0x-n5jVLQejCTZzhfpcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 05:53:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/22/muhyiddin-was-happy-to-be-sacked-says-mca-man/" target="_blank"&gt;Muhyiddin was ‘happy to be sacked’, says MCA man&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – Former MCA president Dr Chua Soi Lek says Muhyiddin Yassin and Najib Razak were never close despite their time together in Umno’s top leadership. In fact, Chua said, Muhyiddin had told him that he was “happy to be sacked” in 2015 as Najib’s deputy in the Cabinet as he would no longer need to bear Najib’s “political baggage”. “He told me he could not be a yes-man as the Umno deputy president and deputy prime minister at that time when 1MDB and the RM2.6 billion donation issues were not being addressed by Najib,” he said in his biography, “Like Me or Hate Me: Rising From The Political...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Putrajaya sends SOS to Hisham to help restore Saudi ties - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/06/putrajaya-sends-sos-to-hisham-to-help-restore-saudi-ties/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMI04Oob93nroE81bLCMmCwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 07:15:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/06/putrajaya-sends-sos-to-hisham-to-help-restore-saudi-ties/" target="_blank"&gt;Putrajaya sends SOS to Hisham to help restore Saudi ties&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(TMI) – PUTRAJAYA has turned to former special functions minister Hishammuddin Hussein to help revive fractured ties with Saudi Arabia, said sources. Some decisions by the new government have affected its relationship with Riyadh, which was warmer under Najib Razak’s administration, sources told The Malaysian Insight. One of these is the axing of the King Salman Centre for International Peace (KSCIP) proposed by King Salman Abdul Aziz Al-Saud during his visit to Malaysia last year. The request for Hishammuddin’s involvement came about after leaders from the Middle East kingdom indicated the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Saifuddin Abdullah: Hisham never hired to mend ties with Saudi - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/06/saifuddin-abdullah-hisham-never-hired-to-mend-ties-with-saudi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDabt2Yaal8_hZCfE30R3bcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 07:54:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/06/saifuddin-abdullah-hisham-never-hired-to-mend-ties-with-saudi/" target="_blank"&gt;Saifuddin Abdullah: Hisham never hired to mend ties with Saudi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Foreign Minister Datuk Saifuddin Abdullah (pic) has denied reports that the government had engaged former defence minister Datuk Seri Hishamuddin Hussein to help mend ties with Saudi Arabia. Saifuddin said that during a courtesy call from Saudi Arabian Ambassador Mahmoud Hussien Saeed Qattan three months ago, he had explained Malaysia's stand and both had agreed that the relationship between both countries was already strong and would be strengthened further. Saifuddin also said that he had met with Saudi foreign minister Adel Al-Jubair at the sidelines of the United Nations ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Parallel lives - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/07/parallel-lives/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAprQLzs5_LRNEI155ors-4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/07/parallel-lives/" target="_blank"&gt;Parallel lives&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT first glance, Hishamuddin Rais and Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim, appear to have lived parallel lives. Student rebels and political detainees, their paths have come together a number of times since both were at the forefront of the student leadership during the 1974 clampdown by the government. Most recently Hishamuddin was part of the Pakatan Harapan GE14 campaign which was fought at least partially on the premise that Anwar would be freed from prison and eventually appointed prime minister. “We came from Malay College Kuala Kangsar and then Universiti Malaya, and he is my senior. People hav...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Mohd Hishamudin appointed new MyCC chairman - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/28/mohd-hishamudin-appointed-new-mycc-chairman/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM9vD_9okRYp9zzFZ9PRECQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 04:29:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/28/mohd-hishamudin-appointed-new-mycc-chairman/" target="_blank"&gt;Mohd Hishamudin appointed new MyCC chairman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Former Court of Appeal Judge Datuk Seri Mohd Hishamudin Yunus has been appointed the chairman of the Malaysian Competition Commission (MyCC). The appointment by Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad under the Competition Commission Act 2010 (Act 713) took effect on Sept 5. Mohd Hishamudin is replacing his predecessor Datuk Che Mohamad Zulkifly Jusoh, and will serve a term of three years. Established in 2011, the MyCC is an independent body under the Competition Commission Act 2010 aimed to protect the competitive process for the benefit of businesses, consumers and the econo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hisham: I'm not leaving Umno - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/25/hisham-i-m-not-leaving-umno/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEChcymls3uFJy_oK74kYsYQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 11:20:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/25/hisham-i-m-not-leaving-umno/" target="_blank"&gt;Hisham: I'm not leaving Umno&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHOR BARU: Sembrong MP Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Tun Hussein (pic) has rubbished speculation that he will be leaving Umno. He said he has no plans to leave Umno but would work with its leadership to strengthen the party, especially in Johor. Hishammuddin also said that he personally felt that the move to boycott the Port Dickson by-election was not a good one. "However, as a division chief, I will abide by the party's decision but the party leadership should explain the reason to our members there. "What are they to do on the day of the election? Do they vote for the opposition? But this wil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Believe it or not - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/on-the-beat/2018/09/23/believe-it-or-not-stranger-things-have-happened-postgeneral-elections-but-losers-seeking-the-winning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAcyHGjzock-kqn_TjHUA8cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/on-the-beat/2018/09/23/believe-it-or-not-stranger-things-have-happened-postgeneral-elections-but-losers-seeking-the-winning/" target="_blank"&gt;Believe it or not&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stranger things have happened post-general elections, but losers seeking the winning party’s advice is certainly curious. POLITICS in Malaysia gets stranger with each passing day. As the adage goes, truth is stranger than fiction, and it seems to apply well here. That saying simply means sometimes what happens in real life is more bizarre than anything that could have been imagined. Shortly after the general election in May, where the Barisan Nasional was trounced and consigned to the scrap heap, then acting Umno president Datuk Seri Dr Zahid Hamidi raised eyebrows when he called on Tun Dr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>17 more Umno MPs to resign? I don’t know, says Shahidan - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/19/17-more-umno-mps-to-resign-i-dont-know-says-shahidan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJwJjEcUU8ccFxUkGuz5WH8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 07:19:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/19/17-more-umno-mps-to-resign-i-dont-know-says-shahidan/" target="_blank"&gt;17 more Umno MPs to resign? I don’t know, says Shahidan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – A list claiming that 17 Umno MPs will quit the party is making the rounds following the resignation of two senior leaders, Mustapa Mohamed and Anifah Aman. The majority of MPs listed are former ministers or Umno Supreme Council members while others are ordinary members who won in the May 9 general election. Mustapa and Anifah are also on the list. Arau MP Shahidan Kassim, who is one of the parliamentarians named, refused to confirm or deny the list. “How am I to deny it? I don’t know,” he told FMT. He added that there could be a “negotiator” trying to convince Umno party leaders to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>PM hints Najib may face more charges on top of 25 - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/22/pm-hints-najib-may-face-more-charges-on-top-of-25/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJd197TbL63W4nHZEPtngiUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/22/pm-hints-najib-may-face-more-charges-on-top-of-25/" target="_blank"&gt;PM hints Najib may face more charges on top of 25&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak could be facing more charges, on top of the 25 counts of corruption and money laundering that he has been slapped with, says Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad (pic). The Prime Minister however said it was not up to him to decide if the number was excessive and it was entirely up to the police. “Whatever the police decide is worth charging him for, it is their business. I have no interest in it. “But, we all know he did a lot of things that were wrong. Now we have 25, and I’m told there are many more,” said Dr Mahathir after chairing a meetin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hishamudin Yunus, known for his bold judgements, appointed to Judicial Appointments Commission - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/hishamudin-yunus-known-for-his-bold-judgements-appointed-to-judicial-appointments-commission/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIpog5EEIDnB184NeU5U2oEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 04:40:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/hishamudin-yunus-known-for-his-bold-judgements-appointed-to-judicial-appointments-commission/" target="_blank"&gt;Hishamudin Yunus, known for his bold judgements, appointed to Judicial Appointments Commission&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former Court of Appeal judge Datuk Seri Hishamudin Yunus has been appointed as a Member of the Judicial Appointments Commission. Hishamudin was known for striking down a provision in a Negri Sembilan State Syariah Enactment, which punishes Muslim men for cross-dressing for being unconstitutional in 2014. In 2011, he also held, in a majority Court of Appeal judgment, that Section 15(5)(a) of the Universities and University Colleges Act, which prohibits students from expressing support for or opposition towards any political party, contradicted the right to freedom of speech ens...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MACC questions Hishammuddin over spy agency case - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/04/macc-questions-hishammuddin-over-spy-agency-case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMO9B-wFmTDDepTkYUaqRfgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 14:56:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/04/macc-questions-hishammuddin-over-spy-agency-case/" target="_blank"&gt;MACC questions Hishammuddin over spy agency case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Datuk Seri Hishammuddin was interrogated between 10am and 1pm on Monday (Sept 3) by the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC), sources confirmed. According to sources, the former Defence Minister was questioned as part of investigations into alleged misappropriation of government funds for the 14th General Election involving former spy agency chief Datuk Hasanah Abdul Hamid. According to The Malaysian Insight, Hishammuddin said he went voluntarily to give a statement after his name came up during Hasanah’s remand hearing. Her lawyer, Datuk Shaharudin Ali, was quoted as ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Which Hishammuddin, please? - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/03/which-hishammuddin-please-spy-chiefs-lawyers-want-to-know-who-antigraft-agency-was-referring-to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFl3IHqCVzvhLQU4MWnqLeoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/03/which-hishammuddin-please-spy-chiefs-lawyers-want-to-know-who-antigraft-agency-was-referring-to/" target="_blank"&gt;Which Hishammuddin, please?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHOR BARU: The Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission must make it clear as to who is the person it wants to interview over its investigation into alleged misappropriation of government funds for the 14th General Election. Lawyer Datuk Shaharudin Ali, who is representing former Malaysia External Intelligence Organisation (MEIO) director-general Datuk Hasanah Abdul Hamid, said the deputy public prosecutor (DPP) in the magis-trate’s court mentioned “Hishammuddin”. “Unless there is another gentleman by the name of Hishammuddin, then everybody in court has made a mistake,” said Shaharudin. “It c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Probe still continuing on three escorts for Hishammuddin, says Mat Sabu - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/27/probe-still-continuing-on-three-escorts-for-hishammuddin-says-mat-sabu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPq34Xmb2gxE-W3EuuK2kE0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 09:36:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/27/probe-still-continuing-on-three-escorts-for-hishammuddin-says-mat-sabu/" target="_blank"&gt;Probe still continuing on three escorts for Hishammuddin, says Mat Sabu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: An investigation by the Malaysian Armed Forces (MAF) is underway on claims that three of their personnel are still serving as escorts for former defence minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Tun Hussein. Current Defence Minister Mohamad Sabu ordered the investigation following reports by a news portal that the three were still working for the former minister. The report also alleged that the three were drawing salaries from both the MAF and Hishammuddin. “Let the MAF investigate. We have also asked the three MAF staff to report for duty at the ministry,” he said to a press conferen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MAF: Hishammuddin not provided with security personnel post-GE14 - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/26/maf-refutes-claims-three-personnel-serving-hisham/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECFF5dhsHVGd_n6dnws3wXYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 07:15:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/26/maf-refutes-claims-three-personnel-serving-hisham/" target="_blank"&gt;MAF: Hishammuddin not provided with security personnel post-GE14&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The Malaysian Armed Forces (MAF) has refuted claims that three security personnel were provided for former Defence Minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein. In a statement on Sunday (Aug 26), the MAF said the duties of the three Special Forces personnel were halted after the 14th General Election. “However, following the statement made by Defence Minister Mohamad Sabu, we are investigating the allegations. “We also will take necessary action to ensure all personnel in service are not given duties with parties that do not have the rights or relevance with the current times,” t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Armed forces: Duties of Hisham’s escorts halted after May 9 - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/27/armed-forces-duties-of-hishams-escorts-halted-after-may-9/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKXHt_pa6LxfDyOe_G74gREqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/27/armed-forces-duties-of-hishams-escorts-halted-after-may-9/" target="_blank"&gt;Armed forces: Duties of Hisham’s escorts halted after May 9&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The armed forces said military escorts to former defence minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein (pic) officially ended after the 14th General Election. In a statement yesterday, the armed forces said the duties of three special forces personnel were halted after May 9. “However, following the statement made by Defence Minister Mohamad Sabu, we are investigating the allegations. “We will also take the necessary action to ensure all personnel in service are not given duties with parties that do not have the right or relevance with the current times,” the statement read and al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hishammuddin: I have given employment offers to Armed Forces personnel protecting me - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/25/hishamuddin-i-have-given-employment-offers-to-armed-forces-personnel-protecting-me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENmVINN-sm1IUyB9126WDkoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 12:35:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/25/hishamuddin-i-have-given-employment-offers-to-armed-forces-personnel-protecting-me/" target="_blank"&gt;Hishammuddin: I have given employment offers to Armed Forces personnel protecting me&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The three Armed Forces personnel currently protecting Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein have been given offers of employment, the former defence minister said on Saturday (Aug 25). He however added that if the three accept, they must resign from the Armed Forces with immediate effect. "They are so close to my family and I, having served us for so many years," said Hishammuddin. He added that the two Navy special operations force (Paskal) officers and the Army commando working as his bodyguards were part of his security detail for a temporary period. Earlier on Saturday, Defence...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Mat Sabu: Probe launched into claim of military protection of Hishammuddin - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/25/mat-sabu-probe-launched-into-claim-of-military-protection-of-hishammuddin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOIqnrrHOLjSvHtT9elYYkwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 10:43:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/25/mat-sabu-probe-launched-into-claim-of-military-protection-of-hishammuddin/" target="_blank"&gt;Mat Sabu: Probe launched into claim of military protection of Hishammuddin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: An investigation will be conducted into allegations that three Armed Forces personnel are still assigned as security personnel protecting. Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein, said Defence Minister Mohamad Sabu. "The necessary action will be taken if there is any infringement of rules and regulations," he said in a Facebook post on Saturday (Aug 25). He was commenting on a report by Malaysiakini saying that the three were still assigned to Hishammuddin. The portal reported that two Navy special operations force (Paskal) officers and a commando were still working as escorts for H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Khairy: National Service programme not used for political indoctrination - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/13/khairy-national-service-programme-not-used-for-political-indoctrination/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBy0hkWNhLV_WZ_g_QH16IUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 10:58:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/13/khairy-national-service-programme-not-used-for-political-indoctrination/" target="_blank"&gt;Khairy: National Service programme not used for political indoctrination&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former Youth and Sports minister Khairy Jamaluddin has denied allegations that the National Service Programme (PLKN) was used as a platform by the previous government for the purpose of political indoctrination. He said the programme was set up to promote the spirit of nationalism and boost patriotism. "Under the PLKN 2.0, where I was directly involved with former Defence Minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein, we focused on skills training. "That is why we produce new modules such as financial literacy, communication skills, including in English and options for them to purs...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hishammuddin to Mat Sabu: Learn first, I'll critique later - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/hishammuddin-to-mat-sabu-learn-first-ll-critique-later/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJhTz9SDYjRgurpixa7XgSsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 07:49:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/hishammuddin-to-mat-sabu-learn-first-ll-critique-later/" target="_blank"&gt;Hishammuddin to Mat Sabu: Learn first, I'll critique later&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former defence minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein is waiting for his successor Mohamad Sabu's "honeymoon period" to be over, before he starts airing his views on the current minister's administration. "I purposely did not say anything this (Parliament) meeting because I wanted to give him some time to learn and see what is going on in the ministry. "I wanted to see what decisions he would make in this time, but once Pakatan Harapan's 100 days are up, I will state my views, starting with the King Salman Centre, defence assets, and the welfare of our servicemen, families a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>I will be silent no more, Hishammuddin warns Mat Sabu - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/08/i-will-be-silent-no-more-hishammuddin-warns-mat-sabu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAO9i4VuDIe4fVrtuv1dWScqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 05:52:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/08/i-will-be-silent-no-more-hishammuddin-warns-mat-sabu/" target="_blank"&gt;I will be silent no more, Hishammuddin warns Mat Sabu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former defence minister says he will start criticising his successor’s actions, starting with the decision to shutter the King Salman Centre for International Peace. (FMT) – Former defence minister Hishammuddin Hussein today warned his successor Mohamad Sabu that he would start making his views heard soon as Mohamad’s “honeymoon period” is almost over. Hishammuddin, who held the defence portfolio during the Barisan Nasional (BN) administration, said he had purposely remained silent on issues relating to the defence ministry. “I purposely didn’t say anything this session because I wanted to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Hisham: Cancelled King Salman's Centre ‘a loss to nation's security’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/07/hisham-cancelled-king-salman-centre-a-loss-to-nation-security/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPnX9flmp_01CDJdLNx16uAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 06:54:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/07/hisham-cancelled-king-salman-centre-a-loss-to-nation-security/" target="_blank"&gt;Hisham: Cancelled King Salman's Centre ‘a loss to nation's security’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Pakatan Harapan’s decision to cancel the King Salman Centre for International Peace (KSCIP) is a loss to the Government and the nation, says Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein. The former defence minister said violent extremism is increasingly undermining global security, especially in the Muslim world. “This problem, because of its borderless nature, requires cooperation and coordination amongst nations. “The centre was formed to position Malaysia as a strategic nation to jointly combat global violent extremism and terrorism on the ideological front, together with the Kingdom o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Khairy: Zahid's like an older brother to me - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/25/khairy-zahids-like-an-older-bro-to-me/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENFdXh1z1YtOwi3tY1yP6vEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 12:48:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/25/khairy-zahids-like-an-older-bro-to-me/" target="_blank"&gt;Khairy: Zahid's like an older brother to me&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former Umno Youth chief Khairy Jamaluddin says he is still on good terms with party president Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi. Khairy - who went up against Dr Ahmad Zahid in the Umno presidential elections last month - admitted that there was "some tension but after all that, he is like an older brother to me." "He spoke to me just now for the first time since the walk-out last week. He asked if I was speaking today and I said yes. We are on good terms," the Rembau lawmaker told reporters at the Parliament lobby on Wednesday (July 25). Asked about Dr Ahmad Zahid's comment th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Not just another day at the House - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/22/not-just-another-day-at-the-house-drama-and-tantrums-were-the-rule-of-the-opening-act-at-last-weeks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3ebCidMqAmv6ayONwFy_4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/22/not-just-another-day-at-the-house-drama-and-tantrums-were-the-rule-of-the-opening-act-at-last-weeks/" target="_blank"&gt;Not just another day at the House&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ALL the world’s a stage and the biggest in the Malaysian political scene opened last week with a bang. There was drama, some comedic lines, plenty of trantrums and even a banishment. In short, the new Parliament is set to be interesting. With Pakatan Harapan assuming the mantle of federal governance and Barisan Nasional becoming the Opposition, this Parliament is new in every sense of the word. Economic Affairs Minister Datuk Seri Azmin Ali captured it best when, taking a question from Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi (BN-Bagan Datuk) on the High Speed Rail, he quipped: “It’s my honour to a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Kadir Jasin backs Ku Li to save Umno - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/16/kadir-jasin-backs-ku-li-to-save-umno/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEP7Y05uioCkJUjb9isgf20qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 07:50:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/16/kadir-jasin-backs-ku-li-to-save-umno/" target="_blank"&gt;Kadir Jasin backs Ku Li to save Umno&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Tengku Razaleigh Hamzah is the right and only man to revive a shell-shocked Umno, according to Datuk A. Kadir Jasin. The former chief editor of the New Straits Times said the politician also known as Ku Li was relatively youthful at 81, which he noted was over a decade younger than Malaysia’s 92-year-old prime minister, Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad. Seeing that Ku Li was still weighing whether to contest for the Umno presidency, Kadir urged the Kelantan prince to take the plunge by saying the latter has never had a better chance to lead the Malay nationalist party. “If I may offer advice...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Ku Li confirms he’ll stand for Umno presidency - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/16/ku-li-confirms-hell-stand-for-umno-presidency/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMxPZ6nG0PiZHqJT_OPgBBYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 06:42:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/16/ku-li-confirms-hell-stand-for-umno-presidency/" target="_blank"&gt;Ku Li confirms he’ll stand for Umno presidency&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ku Li said Umno would uphold Malay rights while looking after the interests of other communities. (FMT) – Tengku Razaleigh Hamzah has announced his candidacy for the Umno president’s post, setting up a showdown between himself and the party’s acting president Ahmad Zahid Hamidi. He announced this at a press conference at his Langgak Golf residence here today. “I am making this decision in the interest of Umno. I want to make sure Umno can play its role as an opposition. As an Umno leader I will still look after our grassroots,” he said. He added that Umno would uphold Malay rights while loo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>On-the-run Jamal Yunos proposes Anwar as Umno president in election campaign video - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/13/ontherun-jamal-yunos-proposes-anwar-as-umno-president-in-election-campaign-video/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIKF0_zO97ihO1_f98UDpWAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 03:36:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/13/ontherun-jamal-yunos-proposes-anwar-as-umno-president-in-election-campaign-video/" target="_blank"&gt;On-the-run Jamal Yunos proposes Anwar as Umno president in election campaign video&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUNGAI BESAR: Politician on-the-run Datuk Seri Jamal Yunos is back with another video, this time proposing PKR leader Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim as Umno president. The Sungai Besar Umno division chief released a election campaign video for the upcoming party elections via Whatsapp. In the one minute 44 second video, he stood in front of a big red banner that reads: "I, Jamal Md Yunos, offer myself to contest as Umno Youth Chief". On the left of the banner are his proposed candidates for various positions, with a photo of Anwar and de facto acting Umno President Datuk Seri Ahmad Zahid Hamidi, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Activist Hishamuddin Rais denies posting seditious article against Agong - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/08/activist-hishamuddin-rais-denies-posting-seditious-article-against-agong/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB0fa9ZhgwkWdVgPgT4F-LAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 05:35:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/08/activist-hishamuddin-rais-denies-posting-seditious-article-against-agong/" target="_blank"&gt;Activist Hishamuddin Rais denies posting seditious article against Agong&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Social activist Hishamuddin Rais has denied uploading a seditious article against Yang di-Pertuan Agong, Sultan Muhammad V on his blog yesterday. His lawyer, Zaid Malek said Hishamuddin had lodged a police report at the Petaling Jaya police headquarters this evening, claiming his blog had been hacked by certain parties who wrote and published the article. “Following that, the police recorded a statement from Hishamuddin at the Petaling police station tonight to assist in investigations,” he said when contacted by Bernama. Zaid said the recording took 80 minutes and ended at midnight.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Zahid to contest Umno president post, Mohd Hasan tries for deputy - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/02/zahid-to-contest-umno-president-post-mohd-hasan-tries-for-deputy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1vf4Rei_EqMoDJqN5tbl8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 09:03:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/02/zahid-to-contest-umno-president-post-mohd-hasan-tries-for-deputy/" target="_blank"&gt;Zahid to contest Umno president post, Mohd Hasan tries for deputy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi has confirmed that he will be running for Umno's top post in the upcoming party polls. The confirmation was made by his press secretary Mej-Jen Datuk Fadzlette Othman Merican that the acting Umno president had registered to contest for the post. “Datuk Seri had filled up all the forms on Friday (June 1) to contest the presidency post,” she said when contacted. However, Umno vice-president Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein has yet to decide which post to contest, according to one of his aides who declined to be named. Hishammuddin has taken on th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Heat on Zahid and Hishammuddin to give way - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/29/heat-on-zahid-and-hishammuddin-to-give-way/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECv1jnVIQNdhHoZDGlJNhwgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 08:20:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/29/heat-on-zahid-and-hishammuddin-to-give-way/" target="_blank"&gt;Heat on Zahid and Hishammuddin to give way&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Sun Daily) – The pressure is on acting Umno president Datuk Seri Ahmad Zahid Hamidi and vice-president Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein to step down for new leadership to enable reform and recovery of the party. The calls for change at the once-dominant party included proposals for former finance minister and party veteran Tengku Razaleigh Hamzah for president. There were also suggestions for Hishammuddin to move up and contest the top post. One branch in Terengganu has pushed for this, The Malaysian Insight reported today. Some want Razaleigh to team up with Youth chief Khairy Jamaludd...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>How the MH370 tragedy unfolded without a solution - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-29/how-the-mh370-tragedy-unfolded/9404182</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFLBo-xhfinwJ4UxzmkL_CEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtiw4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 18:49:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-29/how-the-mh370-tragedy-unfolded/9404182" target="_blank"&gt;How the MH370 tragedy unfolded without a solution&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today brings an end to the latest search for MH370, which has lasted about four months and covered at least 85,000 square kilometres On March 8, 2014, the news broke about a missing plane. A Boeing 777 had vanished between Kuala Lumpur and Beijing with 239 people on board. These were the last words heard from the cockpit as the plane left Malaysian airspace, 38 minutes after take-off: Air traffic control: Malaysian three seven zero contact Ho Chi Minh. One two zero decimal nine good night. Pilot: Good night Malaysian three seven zero. Distressed relatives at Beijing Airport were among the f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Johor Umno leader wants Hishammuddin and Khairy to lead Umno - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/21/johor-umno-leader-wants-hishammuddin-and-khairy-to-lead-umno/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOdBmgrj9Y7oSrAA-BbPrEIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 14:44:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/21/johor-umno-leader-wants-hishammuddin-and-khairy-to-lead-umno/" target="_blank"&gt;Johor Umno leader wants Hishammuddin and Khairy to lead Umno&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHOR BARU: Tebrau Umno division chief Datuk Maulizan Bujang (pic) is calling for vice-president Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Tun Hussein to contest the party’s top post. Although this was his personal opinion, Maulizan claimed the suggestion had already gained support from several division leaders here. “We have already come to an agreement. As members, we are asking Hishammuddin to contest for party president during Umno’s election,” he said to reporters after attending Johor Umno meeting here on Monday (May 21). Maulizan added Hishammuddin and youth chief Khairy Jamaluddin as Umno’s top two c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>UMNO acting president denies he was approached over 1MDB scandal - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/23/umno-acting-president-denies-he-was-approached-over-1mdb-scandal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEws7FgOkqgUHC5XuT7ADqsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 16:49:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/23/umno-acting-president-denies-he-was-approached-over-1mdb-scandal/" target="_blank"&gt;UMNO acting president denies he was approached over 1MDB scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(CNA) – UMNO acting president Ahmad Zahid Hamidi on Tuesday (May 22) denied claims by Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) Chief Commissioner Mohd Shukri Abdull that the latter had approached him to ask Najib Razak to step down as prime minister in the wake of the 1MDB scandal. “It is outside of my knowledge. No (meeting),” the former deputy prime minister told reporters after chairing the monthly UMNO meeting at the party’s headquarters. Ahmad Zahid was asked to comment on the revelation by the MACC chief at a press conference earlier on Tuesday that the MACC had approached several ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Zahid: No, Shukri didn’t see me to ask Najib to quit as PM - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/23/zahid-no-shukri-didnt-see-me-to-ask-najib-to-quit-as-pm/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFjgAgO7tRzIanFRsLt7Aw8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 16:53:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/23/zahid-no-shukri-didnt-see-me-to-ask-najib-to-quit-as-pm/" target="_blank"&gt;Zahid: No, Shukri didn’t see me to ask Najib to quit as PM&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zahid Hamidi says MACC chief Shukri Abdull never met him on the issue of 1MDB and Najib Razak (FMT) – Ahmad Zahid Hamidi has denied claims by Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission chief commissioner Shukri Abdull that he was approached by him to ask Najib Razak to step down as prime minister in the wake of the 1MDB scandal. “It is outside of my knowledge. No (meeting),” the former deputy prime minister told reporters after chairing the monthly Umno meeting at the party’s headquarters here today. Zahid, who is Umno acting president, was asked to comment on the revelation by Shukri at a press ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Shukri aims to put things right after two years in wilderness and endless threats - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/23/fears-tears-and-unfinished-business-shukri-aims-to-put-things-right-after-two-years-in-wilderness-a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG00GiDIIAW176vOYMp1WzsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/23/fears-tears-and-unfinished-business-shukri-aims-to-put-things-right-after-two-years-in-wilderness-a/" target="_blank"&gt;Shukri aims to put things right after two years in wilderness and endless threats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: It was an emotional tell-all for back-from-the-twilight Datuk Seri Mohd Shukri Abdull. The former Malaysian Anti-Corrup­tion Commission (MACC) de­pu­ty chief commissioner is back as the head honcho after two years in the wilderness. He choked while speaking, wiped away tears and had his head buried in his hands as he relived the harrowing two years since his “retirement”. He told a story of bitter disappointment, fear and disillusionment but the real story was of his comeback – and his determination to finish some unfinished business. Shukri, who has made a stunning comeback afte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Culture of no-contest for top Umno posts must stop, leaders say - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/19/culture-of-no-contest-for-top-umno-posts-must-stop-leaders-say/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENrCnwUv9GoJ9KZAJlJkTSwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 07:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/19/culture-of-no-contest-for-top-umno-posts-must-stop-leaders-say/" target="_blank"&gt;Culture of no-contest for top Umno posts must stop, leaders say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – A couple of senior Umno members have said the organisation’s old mindset where certain leadership positions should not be contested or challenged during the party’s election must go. Youth chief Khairy Jamaluddin said that no seat, including the party’s top post currently held by acting president Datuk Seri Zahid Hamidi should be considered sacred, as it was this practice that was one of the reasons behind Umno’s devastating defeat in GE14. “Oh, no, no, no, no, we cannot have this no contest rule anymore in Umno. I mean, you know… you are sending a bad message to the public. I disag...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Separation of functions is crucial - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/20/separation-of-functions-is-crucial-we-cannot-in-this-day-and-age-have-a-situation-where-the-attorney/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHU0g5KLSxrXV0b4ejQpdkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/20/separation-of-functions-is-crucial-we-cannot-in-this-day-and-age-have-a-situation-where-the-attorney/" target="_blank"&gt;Separation of functions is crucial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Pakatan Harapan Government has promised many things to reform the system of governance in Malaysia. One of the critical changes that must take place is the role of the Attorney General (AG). Calls have been made over the decades for a bifurcation of the function of the AG as the Government’s chief legal adviser and the Public Prosecutor (PP). The Barisan Nasional government has never paid any attention to these calls before because the status quo was to its leaders’ advantage. It mattered not that the notion of check and balance and doctrine of separation of powers between the Executive...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>DS Hihsam: UMNO needs new leadership - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/12/ds-hihsam-umno-needs-new-leadership/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGlTKKcc7LeI1JcOkKTLiE8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 06:27:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/05/12/ds-hihsam-umno-needs-new-leadership/" target="_blank"&gt;DS Hihsam: UMNO needs new leadership&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(NST) – Umno vice president Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein agrees that the party is in need of a new leadership. In a statement posted on his Facebook page, Hishammuddin said he agrees with party members as well as the rakyat on the matter, adding that this has to be done in an orderly manner so the party’s dignity and principles can be restored. “To beloved Umno members, do not act emotionally. We are doing this for the future and our unity. “I have passed this on to the top leadership including to the party’s wings. “I call on all parties to be patient and to give us room so we can execu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Umno must reform, remain united and be credible opposition, says KJ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/14/umno-must-reform-remain-united-and-be-credible-opposition-says-kj/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGSvZwxrEWgdxBMNpYlWIPkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 09:40:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/14/umno-must-reform-remain-united-and-be-credible-opposition-says-kj/" target="_blank"&gt;Umno must reform, remain united and be credible opposition, says KJ&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Umno members facing the upcoming party elections must have the will to reform the party and be "matured", said Khairy Jamaluddin (pic). The Umno Youth chief reminded party members that competition in the party polls must not disrupt its unity. "Our focus should be on reforming the party. "Umno should be led by those who are sincere in revitalising and reforming the party," he told a press conference, after the Umno supreme council meeting on Monday (May 14). In pledging full support to Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi and Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein in leading Umno, Khairy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>