<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Kukup Island - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRE41T0hZek5SSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:24:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Kadir to Johor MB: Explain what happened to Pulau Kukup - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/06/kadir-to-johor-mb-explain-what-happened-to-pulau-kukup/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780127780279</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/06/kadir-to-johor-mb-explain-what-happened-to-pulau-kukup/" target="_blank"&gt;Kadir to Johor MB: Explain what happened to Pulau Kukup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/116610" target="_blank"&gt;Continue using Pulau Kukup as national park, says Johor sultan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Malaysian Insight&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/not-right-for-johor-pakatan-govt-to-blame-bn-for-pulau-kukup-issue-says-surendran/" target="_blank"&gt;Not right for Johor Pakatan govt to blame BN for Pulau Kukup issue, says Surendran - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/06/pulau-kukup-to-remain-a-national-park-decrees-johor-sultan/" target="_blank"&gt;Pulau Kukup to remain a national park, decrees Johor Sultan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/06/bn-made-the-decision-but-you-enforced-it-lawyer-tells-johor-govt-on-pulau-kukus/" target="_blank"&gt;BN made the decision but you enforced it, lawyer tells Johor govt on Pulau Kukup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWkzLTVHbWpZQU1FVzhwd2dBQk1VcTlLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/uOks-qy-E_Xj0W-zy_n0CEKdxIZQXtRPxKfwClBLQQC2u4FgnFF_nu6H_f14W18SM_fcYbq2qBVZHI7cwHbZoEmj7t-nRa44L_x8ZNo01EuKPGQoPq7XP8JfK4kDyz5uHC4IvhaWUhQj2v5QVTLcn9BL7rfiSqfzwE91Qhi8sQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Pulau Kukup to change from national park to Sultanate land, says TMJ - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/pulau-kukup-to-change-from-national-park-to-sultanate-land-explains-tmj/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJyIrOO-IHiQSy5cF0B2r0MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 02:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/pulau-kukup-to-change-from-national-park-to-sultanate-land-explains-tmj/" target="_blank"&gt;Pulau Kukup to change from national park to Sultanate land, says TMJ - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHOR BARU: Pulau Kukup will become Sultanate land after the Johor state government has de-gazetted it from a national park said Tunku Mahkota Johor ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Johor MB told to come clean on Pulau Kukup - New Straits Times</title><link>https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/438117/johor-mb-told-come-clean-pulau-kukup</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDGG_dB9KTeC8LjX37IR1gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow9sveCjC0m9YBMPDtoQM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/438117/johor-mb-told-come-clean-pulau-kukup" target="_blank"&gt;Johor MB told to come clean on Pulau Kukup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Johor Menteri Besar Datuk Osman Sapian must explain how Pulau Kukup had been taken over and is now considered Sultanate land after ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWp4M09xbWpZQU1FUk9QWXM0SU5hQWZLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nst.com.my">New Straits Times</source></item><item><title>Cabinet: Pulau Kukup's status as a national park must be retained - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAGH-RK0hrHAI6mmU3jNFUcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 07:52:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pulau Kukup's status as a Johor national park must be retained, the cabinet has decided. "(This is) to ensure that it stays as the world's second largest uninhabited mangrove island," Water, Land, and Natural Resources Minister Dr Xavier Jayakumar said in a statement. Pulau Kukup is one of the few remaining pristine wetlands in Southeast Asia and is one of five Ramsar sites in Malaysia. Ramsar sites are wetland sites designated to be of international importance under the United Nations Convention on Wetlands. Xavier said any change to Pulau Kukup's status "could impact its recognition" as a...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Johor govt needs to further discuss degazetting of Pulau Kukup - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RsGiY1VLm18</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJbKQF7gczhS20c5P38Gvg8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMJOsiAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:37:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RsGiY1VLm18" target="_blank"&gt;Johor govt needs to further discuss degazetting of Pulau Kukup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Johor legislative assembly on Thursday passed an emergency motion on the degazetting of Pulau Kukup as a national park. That means the state executive council will need to further discuss the matter as there are concerns that the degazetting of the national park in Pontian will not help protect the attraction.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pulau Kukup to keep national park status - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/pulau-kukup-to-keep-national-park-status-johor-palace-confirms-it-will-continue-to-be-protected/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIFSOSJHKdl1bDBzJrSYUiQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/pulau-kukup-to-keep-national-park-status-johor-palace-confirms-it-will-continue-to-be-protected/" target="_blank"&gt;Pulau Kukup to keep national park status&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHOR BARU: Pulau Kukup, said to be among the biggest uninhabited mangrove forests in the world, will remain a national park following confirmation from the Johor palace. The state assembly also app­roved an emergency motion yesterday, saying that the national park status should be maintained for environmental preservation. Pulau Kukup, which is about one kilometre away from the mainland near Pontian, came under the spotlight when a gazette dated Oct 25 about the state authorities cancelling its status as a protected national park went viral on social media. Yesterday, Tunku Mahkota Johor T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>TMJ: Why politicise Pulau Kukup’s national park status? - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/tmj-why-politicise-pulau-kukup-national-park-status/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIyueOS1qdHTWzEmbg3UWegqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:41:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/tmj-why-politicise-pulau-kukup-national-park-status/" target="_blank"&gt;TMJ: Why politicise Pulau Kukup’s national park status?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Tunku Mahkota Johor Tunku Ismail Ibni Sultan Ibrahim (pic) says he does not understand why the status of Pulau Kukup as a national park is being “politicised”. “I do not understand why this issue has to be blown up and politicised as land matters are the prerogative of state government," he tweeted late on Wednesday nights (Dec 5). “I am confident that any decision by Sultan Ibrahim Sultan Iskandar and the Johor government was in the best interest and sovereignty of Johor.” He was replying to Twitter user @TheDukeofKL, who told him to claim Malaysia’s victory over Thailand in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Please rethink de-gazetting of Pulau Kukup - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2018/12/06/please-rethink-degazetting-of-pulau-kukup/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKXtCtSOn38-AxKEBLXjGOQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2018/12/06/please-rethink-degazetting-of-pulau-kukup/" target="_blank"&gt;Please rethink de-gazetting of Pulau Kukup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I REFER to the report “Pulau Kukup may lose its status” (The Star, Dec 5) on the Johor state government’s de-gazetting of the status of Pulau Kukup as a national park. This area is the second largest mangrove island in the world. We can build the second largest hotel or even the second largest oil refinery in the world but there is one thing we can never build or even create – the second largest pristine mangrove island in the world. Mangroves forests have evolved to thrive in flooded coastal areas over hundreds of years. As a unique natural resource, mangroves, among others, protect coastl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakatan blames BN for de-gazetting Pulau Kukup - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/pakatan-blames-bn-for-degazetting-pulau-kukup/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELCic6a4btofWM6K_Oy8zuoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/pakatan-blames-bn-for-degazetting-pulau-kukup/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan blames BN for de-gazetting Pulau Kukup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHOR BARU: The Pakatan Harapan-led Johor government has blamed the previous Barisan Nasional administration for de-gazetting Pulau Kukup as a national park. State senior executive committee member Aminolhuda Hassan claimed that the current administration had no knowledge of it. “We do not know about this because the approval came during an exco meeting by the previous administration held in March. “We only knew about this after a decision had been made and approved,” he said when met outside the state assembly which was held at Bangunan Sultan Ismail here yesterday. Meanwhile, in a tweet, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Vessel seized for anchoring in M’sian waters - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/03/15/vessel-seized-for-anchoring-in-msian-waters/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBl528NLem2hKQed2ottYp0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/03/15/vessel-seized-for-anchoring-in-msian-waters/" target="_blank"&gt;Vessel seized for anchoring in M’sian waters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHOR BARU:A foreign merchant ship was seized in the waters off Kukup, Pontian for anchoring without permission. Johor Bahru Malaysian Maritime Enforcement Agency (MMEA) deputy director (operations) Com­mander Iskandar Ishak said an MMEA patrol unit seized the vessel at about 5pm, about 2.5 nautical miles south of Pulau Kukup. He said the ship, 'MV Sima Prestige' was registered in Singapore. In a statement, Iskandar said while the ship was not carrying any cargo, there were 19 crew including the captain on board. He said the crew – comprising Iranians, Indians, Sri Lankan, Filipinos and Ban...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MMEA searching for man missing near Pulau Pisang - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/28/mmea-searching-for-man-missing-near-pulau-pisang/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE-V2Ddo6rX4GEc78UX9NjQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 08:53:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/28/mmea-searching-for-man-missing-near-pulau-pisang/" target="_blank"&gt;MMEA searching for man missing near Pulau Pisang&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PONTIAN: The Malaysian Maritime Enforcement Agency (MMEA) has launched a search and rescue operation for a missing man along the Straits of Melaka. Johor MMEA (operations) deputy director Maritime Captain Sanifah Yusof said the agency received a report on the missing man at around 10.30am on Monday (May 28). “The missing man has been identified as 58-year-old Abdul Rashid Padang from Pontian Besar. He was in a boat heading towards Pulau Pisang," Sanifah said. It is learnt that Abdul Rashid had gone to Pulau Pisang to search for some fruits he wanted to sell during the month of Ramadan. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Fisherman missing off Johor waters - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/12/16/fisherman-missing-off-johor-waters/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ1FAjbg82JFZDsYKYzp9LQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 04:54:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/12/16/fisherman-missing-off-johor-waters/" target="_blank"&gt;Fisherman missing off Johor waters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHOR BARU: A fisherman is missing after falling overboard while out fishing in Pulau Kukup waters near Pontian. Malaysian Maritime Enforcement Agency Johor Bahru deputy director (Operations) Commander Haris Fadzillah Abdullah said Putra Aminurrashid Zaidi, (pix) 21, was with two colleagues when he lost his balance and fell overboard due to strong waves. “MMEA received a distress call about the incident at around 6.45pm and immediately deployed KM Nipah to the location to search for the missing person,” he said in a statement here on Saturday. “I like to remind the maritime community to i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>