<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Muhammad Shafee Abdullah - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyY3ZNVEl5Y1RseWNtUVNBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:02:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Shafee wants judge hearing his case to be recused - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/shafee-wants-judge-hearing-his-case-to-be-recused/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780126872279</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 09:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/shafee-wants-judge-hearing-his-case-to-be-recused/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee wants judge hearing his case to be recused - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/05/judge-refuses-to-recuse-himself-so-shafee-to-file-formal-application/" target="_blank"&gt;Judge refuses to recuse himself, so Shafee to file formal application&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/crime-courts/2018/12/437631/shafee-wants-judge-hearing-his-case-be-recused" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee wants judge hearing his case to be recused&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpYeGRxbGpZQU1FUWRzVVJvanVHSW5LQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/QbCivob7XB1ZfT1L6qThTdoa99deayqK1eORmfgDSOo5iMngdl4bTIhiKw-VXQtOpO4KZjF89NGl1a9xqyaUZjYit48ihwVqeB3f6zqkFP1043kC4USpFMHs592j4GGsxsjCd1X3AWRHz22z3fYQhY_gNaWdAcIOMriU=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Court allows Shafee to intervene in Anwar's appeal - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/29/court-allows-shafee-to-intervene-in-anwars-appeal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMib2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZyZWVtYWxheXNpYXRvZGF5LmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yeS9uYXRpb24vMjAxOC8xMS8yOS9jb3VydC1hbGxvd3Mtc2hhZmVlLXRvLWludGVydmVuZS1pbi1hbndhcnMtYXBwZWFsL9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/29/court-allows-shafee-to-intervene-in-anwars-appeal/" target="_blank"&gt;Court allows Shafee to intervene in Anwar's appeal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The Court of Appeal today allowed lawyer Muhammad Shafee Abdullah to intervene in Anwar Ibrahim's appeal regarding the latter's civil action ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/YZB0K0phB9kq-DZ48kKvT3Cs5ZmDjoOQCaZq5NFXCIMxsXQNnSxUJGuf-63f6ehD_cvSz91xI2E8290UQo0eTYUUc9cMFlLdHUN0cQHvNX-7Yp2gs3A40Hz5crTglGk6hMndCr18TCVpelJPD273tr9BMbDEeFoMvVt-X5I=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Najib, Mohd Irwan's CBT case involving RM6.636bil transferred to High Court - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/najib-mohd-irwans-cbt-case-involving-rm6636bil-transferred-to-high-court/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL6gHz1jMOCqZ61fO4bznuIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:51:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/najib-mohd-irwans-cbt-case-involving-rm6636bil-transferred-to-high-court/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib, Mohd Irwan's CBT case involving RM6.636bil transferred to High Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A RM6.636bil criminal breach of trust (CBT) case involving former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak and former Treasury secretary-general Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah has been transferred to the High Court. High Court Judicial Commissioner Rozana Ali Yusoff approved counsel Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah's oral application to transfer the case from the Session’s Court on Friday (Dec 7). Muhammad Shafee, who is acting for Najib, said that the transfer application was pursuant to Section 417(1)(e) of the Criminal Procedure Code. "There are several cases which...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Appeals Court allows Shafee to intervene in Anwar's appeal over sodomy conviction - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/29/appeals-court-allows-shafee-to-intervene-in-anwars-appeal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGxQgojHcUo_xYb7e2tPha4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:46:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/29/appeals-court-allows-shafee-to-intervene-in-anwars-appeal/" target="_blank"&gt;Appeals Court allows Shafee to intervene in Anwar's appeal over sodomy conviction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA (Bernama): The Court of Appeal on Thursday (Nov 29) allowed lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah (pic) to intervene in Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim's appeal regarding his (Anwar's) civil action against the government over his sodomy conviction. Justice Datuk Vernon Ong Lam Kiat, who led a three-man panel, said Muhammad Shafee's legal interest would be affected as the gist of the claim in Anwar's originating summons was regarding allegations of RM9.5mil payment to the former. "It is quite clear not only Muhammad Shafee was made a party in a discovery (of documents) application at th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Sri Ram: 'Secret' documents in Najib CBT trial need to be reclassified - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/29/sri-ram-secret-documents-in-najib-cbt-trial-need-to-be-reclassified/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECeXC9605286wJUvKiLsQDoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:32:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/29/sri-ram-secret-documents-in-najib-cbt-trial-need-to-be-reclassified/" target="_blank"&gt;Sri Ram: 'Secret' documents in Najib CBT trial need to be reclassified&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Documents classified as "official secrets" will be reclassified in the RM6.636bil criminal breach of trust (CBT) trial of former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak and former Treasury secretary-general Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah. Datuk Seri Gopal Sri Ram, who was appointed by the Attorney General’s Chambers to lead the prosecution, informed Sessions Court judge Azman Ahmad that there were several documents classified under the Official Secrets Act (OSA) which had to be reclassified for the trial to go on. "All documents are there, but it takes time to reclas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib's defence ‘irresponsible’ for last minute attempt to disqualify prosecutor - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/29/najib-defence-irresponsible-for-last-minute-attempt-to-disqualify-prosecutor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC33dlfcQiGrvSQY9e68W4AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 10:18:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/29/najib-defence-irresponsible-for-last-minute-attempt-to-disqualify-prosecutor/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib's defence ‘irresponsible’ for last minute attempt to disqualify prosecutor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The defence in Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak’s case was “irresponsible” for filing an application to challenge the appointment of senior lawyer Datuk Sulaiman Abdullah (pic) at the eleventh hour, the High Court heard. Sulaiman, who was appointed by the Attorney General's Chambers as lead prosecutor in Najib’s case for abusing RM42mil from SRC International Sdn Bhd, said the defence should have filed the application from the first day of the case. “We just received the application (to challenge the appointment). It should be done on Day 1,” he said during the case mention here on ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib's lawyers question motive behind A-G's 1MDB audit tampering claims - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/25/najibs-lawyers-question-motive-behind-a-gs-1mdb-audit-tampering-claims/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOeGzGIp1dgG6UO-n0vV6UQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 15:20:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/25/najibs-lawyers-question-motive-behind-a-gs-1mdb-audit-tampering-claims/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib's lawyers question motive behind A-G's 1MDB audit tampering claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak’s lawyers have questioned the motive behind Auditor-General Tan Sri Dr Madinah Mohamad's revelation that the original audit report on 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB) had been altered. In a statement issued by Messrs Shafee &amp; Co, Najib’s lead defence lawyer Tan Sri Shafee Abdullah (pic) questioned why Madinah, by her own admission, released her statement on Sunday (Nov 25) morning after being told to do so following a briefing to the Cabinet on Friday (Nov 23). “The Auditor-General’s press statement read by any ordinary pers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Ex-CJ Arifin backs judges' extensions; 1MDB-linked BSI banker jailed - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO5M2bU_gsWM_VHm_gTlyzYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 23:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KINI ROUNDUP | Here are the key headlines from yesterday you may have missed, in brief. Ex-CJ Ariffin backs judges' extensions Former chief justice Arifin Zakaria defended the tenure extensions of Chief Justice Md Raus Shariff and President of the Court of Appeal Zulkefli Makinuddin as constitutional and confirmed he had before retiring, advised for the two judges' terms to be extended. However, Arifin's predecessor Abdul Hamid Mohamed said the extensions were not a smart move as it raises doubts on the judiciary and the two judges' integrity, as well as suggests political interference. Mea...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Bukit Aman looking into allegations of 1MDB audit tampering - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/26/bukit-aman-looking-into-allegations-of-1mdb-audit-tampering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGJ7NN57VPM2eGdlLH91exwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 10:58:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/26/bukit-aman-looking-into-allegations-of-1mdb-audit-tampering/" target="_blank"&gt;Bukit Aman looking into allegations of 1MDB audit tampering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Several witnesses will be called up in connection with the alleged tampering of the 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB) audit report, says Comm Datuk Seri Amar Singh. The Bukit Aman Commercial Crime Investigation Department (CCID) director said the investigation will cover several aspects, including the involvement of a civil servant in producing a false record or document. “Another aspect is falsifying a document with the intention of cheating. “We are investigating the aspect of falsifying a document in the official capacity of the civil servant,” he said in a statement Mon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib says he is 'lucky' that he hasn't been charged with sodomy - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/26/najib-says-he-is-lucky-that-he-hasnt-been-charged-with-sodomy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECSGVsUheQNVowF6UTkMu9sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 00:35:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/26/najib-says-he-is-lucky-that-he-hasnt-been-charged-with-sodomy/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib says he is 'lucky' that he hasn't been charged with sodomy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Former premier Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak made a sarcastic jibe saying he was lucky that he has not been charged with sodomy amid pending court trial on the 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB) case. He said this in his Facebook account on Sunday (Nov 25) after the revelation by Auditor General Tan Sri Dr Madinah Mohamad that the original audit report on 1MDB had been altered. “It is very clear that the Pakatan Harapan government is using all the power in the government, agencies and media to influence the people’s thoughts to tarnish my name even though the 1MDB case is await...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Govt, Shafee ordered to respond to Anwar’s RM9.5 mil bank transfer suits - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/govt-shafee-ordered-to-respond-to-anwars-rm9-5-mil-bank-transfer-suits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILzzD16YnsZbBNLreacMRMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 05:39:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/govt-shafee-ordered-to-respond-to-anwars-rm9-5-mil-bank-transfer-suits/" target="_blank"&gt;Govt, Shafee ordered to respond to Anwar’s RM9.5 mil bank transfer suits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Najib Razak, who is party to Anwar Ibrahim’s application to disclose bank account details, was not represented by a lawyer during case management today (FMT) – The High Court today ordered the government to respond to a suit by former opposition leader Anwar Ibrahim to quash his sodomy conviction on grounds that he was denied a fair trial, following a claim that a senior prosecutor had received millions of ringgit from the prime minister. Lawyer Latheefa Koya said the High Court also ordered counsel Muhammad Shafee Abdullah to file his case in response to Anwar’s application to compel the U...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>16 more Geng Devan members charged - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/19/geng-devan-members-charged/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBTD6J13TNFEsTQiRC2_O4wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 06:34:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/19/geng-devan-members-charged/" target="_blank"&gt;16 more Geng Devan members charged&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A total of 16 men have claimed trial to being members of Gang 360 Devan, an organised crime group. The accused, aged between 24 and 48 years old, were brought to the High Court here on Wednesday to have their charges read to them. They were D.R. Yasotharan, S. Manimaran, C. Murugan, L. Lengas Seperan, D. Sivanantha, S.T. Anthony Balan, S. Maran, M. Sathia Tamil Siva, P. Sures, P. Murugan, B. Ravindran, D.R. Yasothanaraj, M. Murugan, D. Manivannan, K. Ram Kumar and S. Logonanthan. They were charged with becoming members of the group at MV Empayer Sdn Bhd, Jalan Perniagaan Masri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>The men behind Prebet Adam’s freedom - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/08/13/the-men-behind-prebet-adams-freedom/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI5p3aerxQow-XbG9BbPthgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/08/13/the-men-behind-prebet-adams-freedom/" target="_blank"&gt;The men behind Prebet Adam’s freedom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PREBET Adam Jaafar owes his life to two key individuals. If it was not for Leftenan Jeneral (R) Datuk Abdul Ghani Abdullah who persuaded Adam to surrender peacefully, he could have been killed during his standoff with the police on Oct 19, 1987. And if it was not for his defence lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah who convinced the judge he was not of sound mind when he ran amok, Adam might have been doomed for the gallows. Abdul Ghani was the Assistant Commander for the Ground Forces Operation when he received news of a soldier going on a rampage in Chow Kit. By the time he arrived nea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>KJ: Disappointing if 1MDB audit report was really tampered with - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/26/kj-disappointing-if-1mdb-audit-report-was-really-tampered-with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPnSyxn7oJPBC198cGME2_QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:50:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/26/kj-disappointing-if-1mdb-audit-report-was-really-tampered-with/" target="_blank"&gt;KJ: Disappointing if 1MDB audit report was really tampered with&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: It will be a disappointment if embattled former premier Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak, who is facing graft charges, had indeed ordered the 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB) audit report to be tampered with, says Khairy Jamaluddin. "If there is an order to erase Jho Low's attendance at 1MDB board meetings, then it is a serious move which is disappointing. "So, we should wait for the outcome of the ongoing investigation," the former Youth and Sports minister said to reporters when met at the Parliament lobby on Monday (Nov 26). According to Khairy, the presence of Low, whose real...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Judge rules Najib must attend case management - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/01/judge-rules-najib-must-attend-case-management/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIuzUmfb2YFRfbHESvT1sWQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/01/judge-rules-najib-must-attend-case-management/" target="_blank"&gt;Judge rules Najib must attend case management&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak, who is facing seven charges related to criminal breach of trust and money laundering involving RM42mil of SRC International Sdn Bhd funds, must turn up at his court proceedings even if it was just a case management. High Court judge Justice Mohd Nazlan Mohd Ghazali made this ruling following an application by Najib’s lead counsel Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah for his client to be exempted from attending a case management on Nov 29. Dr Muhammad Shafee asked for the court to consider excusing his client during the case mana...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Judge wants Najib to be present in court for every proceeding - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/judge-wants-najib-to-be-present-in-court-for-every-proceeding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPq3tT8uLMrotJyWaIY3Fn4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 12:17:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/judge-wants-najib-to-be-present-in-court-for-every-proceeding/" target="_blank"&gt;Judge wants Najib to be present in court for every proceeding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR (Bernama): Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak (pic), who is facing seven charges involving power abuse, criminal breach of trust (CBT) and money laundering involving SRC International Sdn Bhd amounting to RM42mil, must be present in court for every proceeding against him. High Court judge Mohd Nazlan Mohd Ghazali said the accused (Najib) should attend the proceedings, including case management so that he could follow his case directly. "I think he (the accused) should be here (in court), if the matter is not contested, then we can consider. At least the accused may directly follow the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee’s diplomatic passport revoked - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/30/shafees-diplomatic-passport-revoked-wisma-putra-no-reason-to-give-him-special-privileges-since-he-is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJfdXOhEKcHcUVqJFo2tTcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/30/shafees-diplomatic-passport-revoked-wisma-putra-no-reason-to-give-him-special-privileges-since-he-is/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee’s diplomatic passport revoked&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Wisma Putra has revoked the diplomatic passport issued to lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah (pic) on Sept 19. In a parliamentary written reply, the Foreign Ministry said the passport was issued between 2009 and 2015 in his capacity as a member of the Asean Human Rights Inter-govern­mental Commission (AICHR). The senior lawyer was again issued with the passport in his capa­city as the Ambassador-at-Large for Human Rights from 2016 for a two-year term ending in 2018. “The issuance of the passport was to ease his job as an official representative of Malaysia,” said the Fo­­...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>No live telecast of Najib's trial, says Gobind - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/01/no-live-telecast-of-najibs-trial-says-gobind/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMLRpbezAOToulUukZHYdXQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 06:24:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/01/no-live-telecast-of-najibs-trial-says-gobind/" target="_blank"&gt;No live telecast of Najib's trial, says Gobind&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Communications and Multimedia Minister Gobind Singh Deo has snubbed the proposal to have a live telecast of former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak's trial. "There will be no live telecast because we have limited channels for Bernama and RTM," he told reporters at the Parliament lobby on Thursday (Nov 1). Gobind was asked whether he would give permission to have a live telecast of the Najib's trial. It was reported that Najib's lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah said he had no issue with it as the proceedings would be carried out in a transparent manner. Gobind, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Former Malaysia PM, Treasury and Spy Chiefs Charged With Graft - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/former-malaysia-pm-treasury-and-spy-chiefs-charged/4628526.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ7IZbblX9Z2sKpsFwKo_r8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 09:18:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/former-malaysia-pm-treasury-and-spy-chiefs-charged/4628526.html" target="_blank"&gt;Former Malaysia PM, Treasury and Spy Chiefs Charged With Graft&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Malaysian Prime Minister Najib Razak and his ex-treasury chief were jointly charged Thursday with criminal breach of trust involving 6.64 billion ringgit ($1.6 billion), while the former head of his spy agency was charged with misappropriating $12.1 million. The six new charges against Najib come on top of 32 earlier counts of corruption, breach of trust and money laundering that he faces linked to the multibillion-dollar looting of the 1MDB state investment fund. Malaysia’s new government has stepped up prosecution of Najib and other former officials over the 1MDB scandal and other ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Ex-PM and Irwan slapped with six counts of CBT - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/26/expm-and-irwan-slapped-with-six-counts-of-cbt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGDpqk-8tDhIJeVcyLfVmhIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/26/expm-and-irwan-slapped-with-six-counts-of-cbt/" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-PM and Irwan slapped with six counts of CBT&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak has been brought to court several times but yesterday, he shared a dock at the Sessions Court with former Treasury secretary-general Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah. The two were jointly charged with six counts of criminal breach of trust (CBT) involving funds totalling RM6.636bil that belongs to the government. Najib, 65, was the first accused while Dr Mohd Irwan, 61, was named as the second accused. According to the first two charge sheets, the two men were entrusted with dominion over RM1.2bil and RM655mil respectively...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib’s team eager for battle - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/26/najibs-team-eager-for-battle-shafee-well-have-fun-and-the-prosecution-will-have-nightmares/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECTeJdHu92OEATIcfgYO2EsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/26/najibs-team-eager-for-battle-shafee-well-have-fun-and-the-prosecution-will-have-nightmares/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib’s team eager for battle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak and Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah are charged with criminal breach of trust (CBT) involving billions of ringgit. And yet, their lawyers are “quite delighted” after seeing the charges and are eager to do battle in court. The Sessions Court here was told that Najib and Dr Mohd Irwan did not pocket a sen from the RM6.636bil at the heart of the six CBT charges. Najib’s lead counsel Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah said the money was used “purely to meet national obligations”. The prominent lawyer said he was told that the funds involved in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee: Money in charges purely for national obligations, defence delighted - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/shafee-money-in-charges-purely-for-national-obligations-defence-delighted/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOVRFGZcXpSv6XfUtonmAdIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 03:32:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/shafee-money-in-charges-purely-for-national-obligations-defence-delighted/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee: Money in charges purely for national obligations, defence delighted&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The money implicated in the six criminal breach of trust charges that Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak and Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah are jointly facing were "purely to meet national obligations", the former premier's counsel said. Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah said Najib did not benefit even a single sen from the amount mentioned in the six charges. The former prime minister and former Treasury secretary-general are being jointly charged with six counts of criminal breach of trust totalling RM6.636bil. "The first two charges are wholly unfounded because the decisi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Former Malaysian PM Najib faces six more corruption charges over state funds - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-najib/former-malaysian-pm-najib-faces-six-more-corruption-charges-over-state-funds-idUSKCN1MZ06Z</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAFS3ZMzISmrzHKUuLGeXwkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 06:53:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-malaysia-politics-najib/former-malaysian-pm-najib-faces-six-more-corruption-charges-over-state-funds-idUSKCN1MZ06Z" target="_blank"&gt;Former Malaysian PM Najib faces six more corruption charges over state funds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Malaysian premier Najib Razak was charged with six counts of criminal breach of trust involving government funds worth more than $1.5 billion on Thursday, adding to the 32 charges he already faces for money laundering and graft. His former treasury chief, Irwan Serigar Abdullah, was also charged with criminal breach of trust, becoming the highest-ranking civil servant to be charged since Najib was unexpectedly ousted in a general election in May. The two pleaded not guilty to all the charges. Each charge carries a jail term of up to 20 years, a financial penalty and a whipping senten...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Court sets RM1 million bail each for Najib, Irwan - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/25/court-sets-rm1-million-bail-each-for-najib-irwan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEATpUNuaII1NW_HvJCy_ZdEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 06:00:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/25/court-sets-rm1-million-bail-each-for-najib-irwan/" target="_blank"&gt;Court sets RM1 million bail each for Najib, Irwan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – The Sessions Court here has set RM1 million bail each for former prime minister Najib Razak and former Treasury secretary-general Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah in their criminal breach of trust (CBT) cases. Judge Azman Ahmad set the amount after hearing arguments from fiat prosecutor Gopal Sri Ram and lawyers Muhammad Shafee Abdullah, representing Najib, and Dev and Lavania Kumaraendran and their father K Kumaraendran, representing Irwan. The court also ordered the duo to surrender their passports pending disposal of the case. “Neither of them are allowed to contact any witnesses rela...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Najib supporters cry foul over 'last-minute' charge sheet - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/najib-supporters-cry-foul-over-lastminute-charge-sheet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDvPUa1S2qhs1m3F33C5P7wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 04:57:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/najib-supporters-cry-foul-over-lastminute-charge-sheet/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib supporters cry foul over 'last-minute' charge sheet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Supporters of former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak are crying foul over the supposedly last-minute nature of the charge sheet. Former special officer to Najib, Isham Jalil, who was with a group of supporters at the court complex where Najib and former Treasury secretary-general Irwan Serigar were being charged, said that the defendants only had an hour to prepare before appearing before the court. “This is unheard off. It is too short (a time) to go through a charge sheet,” he said on Thursday (Oct 25) when met at the Kuala Lumpur courts. He added that he wanted th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee says gleeful after seeing ‘absurd’ new charges against Najib - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/25/shafee-says-gleeful-after-seeing-absurd-new-charges-against-najib/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENdmsm-of0FkRafwx7OXed4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 06:31:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/25/shafee-says-gleeful-after-seeing-absurd-new-charges-against-najib/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee says gleeful after seeing ‘absurd’ new charges against Najib&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah lambasted the prosecution over the six charges filed against client Datuk Seri Najib Razak today, describing these as nonsensical and nebulous in nature. The senior private practitioner told the court that the activities from which the charges stemmed were all undertaken by his client as the finance minister at the time for the economic benefit of the country. He also blasted prosecutors for the vague charges, noting that these do not explain the exact nature of the action that constituted an offence under Section 409 of the Penal Code. “If you were ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Najib supporters cry foul over last-minute charge sheet - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/25/najib-supporters-cry-foul-over-last-minute-charge-sheet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOJ74zu2RKAO-R6XqyICXi4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 06:22:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/25/najib-supporters-cry-foul-over-last-minute-charge-sheet/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib supporters cry foul over last-minute charge sheet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – Supporters of former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak are crying foul over the supposedly last-minute nature of the charge sheet. Former special officer to Najib, Isham Jalil, who was with a group of supporters at the court complex where Najib and former Treasury secretary-general Tan Sri Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah were being charged, said that the defendants only had an hour to prepare before appearing before the court. “This is unheard off. It is too short (a time) to go through a charge sheet,” he said on Thursday (Oct 25) when met at the Kuala Lumpur courts. He ad...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Prosecution asks for RM3mil bail each, as Najib, Irwan plead not guilty - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/najib-irwan-serigar-charged-with-cbt-involving-rm66bil-plead-not-guilty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGnAjPI_L54fxmr1iORNqEMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 02:45:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/najib-irwan-serigar-charged-with-cbt-involving-rm66bil-plead-not-guilty/" target="_blank"&gt;Prosecution asks for RM3mil bail each, as Najib, Irwan plead not guilty&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak and former Treasury secretary-general Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah have pleaded not guilty to six charges of criminal breach of trust involving RM6.6bil at the Sessions Court. The charges were read out before Judge Azman Ahmad, to which both of them pleaded not guilty. Najib and Dr Mohd Irwan are jointly charged with six counts of CBT under Section 409 of the Penal Code. The first two charges were activities said to have been committed on Dec 21, 2016 involving RM1.2bil and RM655mil. In the third charge, Najib and Dr M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MACC to question several past key players in graft probe - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/27/macc-to-question-several-past-key-players-in-graft-probe/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKNqqYZqIl8HT1wyWdJ3gAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/27/macc-to-question-several-past-key-players-in-graft-probe/" target="_blank"&gt;MACC to question several past key players in graft probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Several key influential figures from the previous administration are expected to be hauled up for questioning as graft investigators dig deeper into scandals that allegedly occurred during Barisan Nasional’s administration. The names of several prominent individuals – from politicians to former senior civil servants – have cropped up as among those who will be called by the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) soon, possibly next week. Among those expected to be called up are former Federal Territories Minister Datuk Seri Tengku Adnan Tengku Mansor, former Attorney General...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Appeals Court dismisses Shafee's appeal over Sodomy 2 case - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/11/appeals-court-dismisses-shafees-appeal-over-sodomy-2-case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKfhwDb3PeHZAOB89WeLug4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 03:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/11/appeals-court-dismisses-shafees-appeal-over-sodomy-2-case/" target="_blank"&gt;Appeals Court dismisses Shafee's appeal over Sodomy 2 case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The Court of Appeal has dismissed the suit by senior lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah against the Malaysian Bar, Attorney General Tommy Thomas and two others over the Sodomy 2 appeal. Chief Judge of Sabah and Sarawak Wong Dak Wah, who chaired the three-man panel on Thursday (Oct 11), rejected the appeal on grounds that there was no merit in the application. Other judges on the panel were Justices Umi Kalthum Abdul Majid and Ahmadi Asnawi. Muhammad Shafee has indicated that he would appeal against the Court of Appeal's decision. On May 26, 2016, Muhammad Shafee had filed an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hour-long argument during case mention - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/05/hour-long-argument-during-case-mention/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOayadR3qf8_HNRdVUtU-M0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/05/hour-long-argument-during-case-mention/" target="_blank"&gt;Hour-long argument during case mention&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: What was supposed to be a simple case mention for Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak’s graft-related charges turned into a war of words that lasted almost an hour. His lawyers and the prosecution team argued mainly about the format of the documents served. The dispute also touched on the appointment of Datuk Sulaiman Abdullah as the lead prosecutor in the former prime minister’s trial next year. Najib’s lead counsel Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah said the documents were served in a rather unusual way – a CD-ROM – and that some of the documents contained could not be read or opened. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib's graft case incomparable with ordinary sodomy case, says Sulaiman - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/04/najibs-graft-case-incomparable-with-ordinary-sodomy-case-says-sulaiman/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGuc6hlZG5ZSRv_Dj8eba0gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 05:29:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/04/najibs-graft-case-incomparable-with-ordinary-sodomy-case-says-sulaiman/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib's graft case incomparable with ordinary sodomy case, says Sulaiman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The charges faced by former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak cannot be compared with an ordinary sodomy charge, said Datuk Sulaiman Abdullah. The lead prosecutor in Najib's criminal breach of trust, corruption and money laundering charges said the trial will depend heavily on documents. "We have got an enormous amount of documents. You cannot compare an ordinary sodomy case with a situation where an accused is charged with 'sodomising' the entire nation. "We haven't charged a former prime minister before, nor for that amount of money involved. It all depends on bank t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee unhappy over DPP's appointment being classified as ‘official secret’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/04/shafee-unhappy-over-dpps-appointment-being-classified-as-official-secret/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSxqaQ0VaNCHZD8jNm8NlMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 06:27:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/04/shafee-unhappy-over-dpps-appointment-being-classified-as-official-secret/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee unhappy over DPP's appointment being classified as ‘official secret’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak's lead counsel Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah (took a swipe at the "Malaysia Baru" touted by the government, claiming a lack of transparency in the appointment of the Deputy Public Prosecutor (DPP). Muhammad Shafee said to this date, the prosecution had not shown the appointment letter of its lead prosecutor Datuk Sulaiman Abdullah (pic), who replaced Attorney-General Tommy Thomas in the criminal case against Najib. He slammed Sulaiman for answering that his appointment was stamped by the Attorney-General as an "official se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>War of words erupt between Najib's lawyers and prosecution team over format of documents served - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/04/war-of-words-erupt-between-najibs-lawyers-and-prosecution-team-over-format-of-documents-served/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2njbdegYLnNGPLn1_qi4gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 03:29:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/04/war-of-words-erupt-between-najibs-lawyers-and-prosecution-team-over-format-of-documents-served/" target="_blank"&gt;War of words erupt between Najib's lawyers and prosecution team over format of documents served&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: What was supposed to be a case mention for Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak for his SRC International related charges turned into a war of words between his lawyers and lead prosecutor, Datuk Sulaiman Abdullah. They argued for around 50 minutes, chiefly on documents served to the defence team. Sulaiman raised an issue that the prosecution had tried to serve the documents under Section 51A of the Criminal Procedure Code, but were unable to do so despite all efforts. Najib's lead counsel, Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah said the documents were served in a CD-Rom format and not in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee: Najib has a strong defence, I also hope Jho Low turns up - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/04/shafee-najib-has-a-strong-defence-i-also-hope-jho-low-turns-up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHFDglzdc7Jrma8hv69dqZgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 06:19:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/04/shafee-najib-has-a-strong-defence-i-also-hope-jho-low-turns-up/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee: Najib has a strong defence, I also hope Jho Low turns up&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: There is evidence that the investigations against former premier Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak (pic)had not been completed before he was charged, claimed his lead counsel Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah. Muhammad Shafee said this in summing up his confidence in his team's ability to defend the case against his client. "We have a very strong defence. I'm also suspicious of the fact that these charges placed against my client have been done in a hurried fashion because I can see evidence of the investigations not being completed. "I'm confident that we will be able to defend th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee optimistic about Najib’s chances - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/05/shafee-optimistic-about-najibs-chances/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3ilJSv7WR57_SJFfttET4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/05/shafee-optimistic-about-najibs-chances/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee optimistic about Najib’s chances&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak’s lead counsel Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah is optimistic about his client’s chances in court because the senior lawyer believes that the former prime ­minister was charged before the investigations had been completed. “I’m quite inspired to be able to say that we have a very strong defence. “I’m also suspicious of the fact that these charges against my client were placed in a hurried fashion because I can see evidence of the investigations being incomplete. “I’m confident that we will be able to defend the case very effectively,” he said at the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee disputes ‘Whale’ author, insists book absolves Najib - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/04/shafee-disputes-whale-author-insists-book-absolves-najib/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBsG4R3OqCINAgKlbwKm2b8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 07:30:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/04/shafee-disputes-whale-author-insists-book-absolves-najib/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee disputes ‘Whale’ author, insists book absolves Najib&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah reaffirmed his claim that portions of Billion Dollar Whale demonstrated client Datuk Seri Najib Razak’s innocence in the 1MDB scandal, after a co-author said the lawyer misunderstood the book. Shafee went on to accuse Tom Wright, one of two Wall Street Journal reporters who wrote the book, of contradicting his own book with subsequent remarks to the media. The senior lawyer claimed to have read the book thrice and can pinpoint the specific discrepancies, before offering to debate Wright over the matter. He asserted that Wright was asked specifically ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Rosmah Mansor, wife of Najib Razak, charged with money-laundering in connection to Malaysia’s 1MDB scandal - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2018/10/04/rosmah-mansor-wife-of-najib-razak-charged-with-moneylaundering-in-connection-to-malaysias-1mdb-scand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEOL5aqrs8DcIm0ILpS6iFIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 04:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2018/10/04/rosmah-mansor-wife-of-najib-razak-charged-with-moneylaundering-in-connection-to-malaysias-1mdb-scand/" target="_blank"&gt;Rosmah Mansor, wife of Najib Razak, charged with money-laundering in connection to Malaysia’s 1MDB scandal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rosmah Mansor, the luxury-loving “Malaysian Imelda Marcos” and wife of disgraced former prime minister Najib Razak, was formally charged with 17 offences, including money-laundering, on Thursday as investigators appeared to be significantly widening their probe into the multibillion-dollar 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB) corruption scandal. She pleaded not guilty to all charges. Dressed in an orange floral baju kurung and a bright orange headscarf, the self-styled “First Lady of Malaysia” arrived at court after spending the night in the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission’s lock-up. Ba...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee applies to transfer cases to High Court - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/01/shafee-applies-to-transfer-cases-to-high-court/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBA24oUhEoU2fISw3gE_22oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 09:57:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/01/shafee-applies-to-transfer-cases-to-high-court/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee applies to transfer cases to High Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR (Bernama): Lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah has filed an application for the money laundering and incorrect tax filing cases against him to be transferred to the High Court. Lawyer Sarah Abishegam, representing Muhammad Shafee, told reporters that the application was made last week as it was the jurisdiction of the High Court to transfer the cases against her client who had been charged in the Sessions Court. “The application has been set for hearing on Oct 3 before Judge Datuk Azman Abdullah,” she said after the case management proceedings in chambers on Monday before...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘I am no thief and I will clear my name’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/21/i-am-no-thief-and-i-will-clear-my-name/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBL6_NBgLe5RYK1x_u9W75cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/21/i-am-no-thief-and-i-will-clear-my-name/" target="_blank"&gt;‘I am no thief and I will clear my name’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Embattled former premier Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak, who has been slapped with 25 fresh charges in relation to the controversial RM2.3bil found in his personal accounts, has once again reiterated that he is not a thief. “As we all know, the RM2.3bil issue was used relentlessly to criticise and tarnish my name all this while. “All the charges today will give me a chance to clear my name (and prove) that I am not a thief. “I hope my journey in court will uphold the truth and silence this RM2.3bil issue once and for all,” he said to reporters before leaving the Kuala Lumpur High ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Muhammad Shafee to file application to recuse Gopal Sri Ram - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/13/muhammad-shafee-to-file-application-to-recuse-gopal-sri-ram/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgPBr2fdLsd2XiRfgB9aTUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 07:39:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/13/muhammad-shafee-to-file-application-to-recuse-gopal-sri-ram/" target="_blank"&gt;Muhammad Shafee to file application to recuse Gopal Sri Ram&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah told the Sessions Court here that he will file an application to recuse Datuk Seri Gopal Sri Ram from leading the prosecution against him. Earlier, the prominent lawyer claimed trial to two charges of receiving money from the proceeds of illegal activities on Thursday (Sept 13). He pleaded not guilty to the two charges under the Anti-Money Laundering, Anti-Terrorism Financing and Proceeds of Unlawful Activities Act 2001 involving RM4.3mil and RM5.2mil received from former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak. He also pleaded not guilty ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Muhammad Shafee pleads not guilty to money laundering charges - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/13/muhammad-shafee-pleads-not-guilty-to-money-laundering-charges/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ6Xr7BIdYmvqqKb_9Lh48sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 06:59:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/13/muhammad-shafee-pleads-not-guilty-to-money-laundering-charges/" target="_blank"&gt;Muhammad Shafee pleads not guilty to money laundering charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – Prominent lawyer Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah has claimed trial to two charges of receiving money from the proceeds of illegal activities at the Kuala Lumpur Sessions Court. He pleaded not guilty to the two charges under the Anti-Money Laundering, Anti-Terrorism Financing and Proceeds of Unlawful Activities Act 2001 involving RM4.3mil and RM5.2mil received from former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak on Thursday (Sept 13). Dr Muhammad Shafee also pleaded not guilty to two charges of making incorrect returns by omitting or understating any income under the Income...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Muhammad Shafee expected to be charged with money laundering - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/13/muhammad-shafee-expected-to-be-charged-with-money-laundering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAjHu78AynHgpsA8LNWxmoUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 06:33:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/13/muhammad-shafee-expected-to-be-charged-with-money-laundering/" target="_blank"&gt;Muhammad Shafee expected to be charged with money laundering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – Senior lawyer Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah is expected to be charged by graft busters on Thursday (Sept 13) under the Anti-Money Laundering Act. He was believed to be arrested by the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) late Wednesday (Sept 12). Former judge Datuk Seri Gopal Sri Ram is leading the prosecuting team against Dr Muhammad Shafee. The other DPPs in his team are Kamal Baharin Omar, Ahmad Akram Gharib, Afzainizam Abdul Aziz and Regine Sin. As of 10.15am, Dr Muhammad Shafee has yet to be brought to court. The court interpreter called for Dr Muhammad Shafee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Shafee was eyeing AG post, claims Dr M - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/shafee-abdullah-wanted-to-be-ag-says-dr-m/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEvPlTMPNg-mnt_OwaDsYk8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:37:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/shafee-abdullah-wanted-to-be-ag-says-dr-m/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee was eyeing AG post, claims Dr M&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah badly wanted to be the Attorney General, claimed Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad. The Prime Minister claimed that Dr Muhammad Shafee had come to see him and informed him that the then Attorney General Tan Sri Abdul Gani Patail could not prosecute Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim. "He (Dr Muhammad Shafee) said he can win (the case). I said if he can win, then go and tell (former prime minister Datuk Seri) Najib Tun Razak lah. "At that time, I was still friendly with Najib," he said at a press conference after chairing the Parti Pribumi Bersatu Malaysia (Pri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Carpet guy Deepak accuses Shafee and Azeez of interfering in Altantuya murder case - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/15/carpet-guy-deepak-accuses-shafee-and-azeez-of-interfering-in-altantuya-murder-case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKNCZ2g-mxq8IdEUmsHm9BAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 15:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/15/carpet-guy-deepak-accuses-shafee-and-azeez-of-interfering-in-altantuya-murder-case/" target="_blank"&gt;Carpet guy Deepak accuses Shafee and Azeez of interfering in Altantuya murder case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Carpet trader Deepak Jaikishan (pic above left) has lodged a police report against senior lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah and Baling MP Datuk Seri Abdul Azeez Rahim for alleged interference in the murder case of Altantuya Shaariibuu (pic above right). Deepak claimed that both allegedly interfered in a suit filed by the widow of late private investigator P. Balasubramaniam over the murder of Mongolian model and translator Altantuya. He also claimed that he was forced to engage Muhammad Shafee as his lawyer by former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak. The repo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee’s son pays other half of bail - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/19/shafees-son-pays-other-half-of-bail-balance-of-lawyers-rm1mil-security-settled/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG1-lUJ-0uuAY3bQnzvP7R0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/19/shafees-son-pays-other-half-of-bail-balance-of-lawyers-rm1mil-security-settled/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee’s son pays other half of bail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah, who has been hit with money laundering charges, has posted the remaining RM500,000 of his RM1mil bail. His son Muhammad Farhan arrived at the court complex here at 11.50am yesterday with his two bailors for the bail procedure. The three men then went down to the bail counter at the basement. They left the court complex at 1.30pm. Muhammad Shafee, 66, was absent. Attempts to reach Muhammad Farhan for comments were unsuccessful as he rushed from the counter and did not stop to take questions. On Sept 13, Muhammad Shafee claimed trial in t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Police report lodged against Shafee and Abdul Azeez - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/16/police-report-lodged-against-shafee-and-abdul-azeez/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMjZfzrcqtx7Tb2etVCwjSsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/16/police-report-lodged-against-shafee-and-abdul-azeez/" target="_blank"&gt;Police report lodged against Shafee and Abdul Azeez&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: A police report has been lodged against senior lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah and Baling MP Datuk Seri Abdul Azeez Rahim. The report was lodged on Friday at the Dang Wangi police headquarters by carpet trader Deepak Jaikishan, who claimed that both had allegedly interfered in a suit filed by the widow of the late private investigator P. Balasubramaniam over the murder of Altantuya Shaariibuu. Deepak is also a defendant in the suit. In the report, he also claimed that he was forced to engage Muhammad Shafee as his lawyer by former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun R...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee pays remaining RM500,000 of his RM1mil bail - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/18/shafee-pays-remaining-rm500-000-of-his-rm1mil-bail/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIsBqeNJJLvfWRXfYsit81wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 07:24:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/18/shafee-pays-remaining-rm500-000-of-his-rm1mil-bail/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee pays remaining RM500,000 of his RM1mil bail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah, who has been hit with money laundering charges, has paid the remainder of his RM1mil bail by posting another RM500,000. His son, Muhammad Farhan, arrived at the court complex here at 11.50am on Tuesday (Sept 18) with his two bailors for the bail procedure. The three men then went down to the bail counter at the basement. They left the court complex at 1.30pm. Muhammad Shafee, 66, was absent. Attempts to reach Muhammad Farhan for comments was unsuccessful as he rushed out from the counter and did not stop to take questions. On Sept 13, M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Media personnel wait for arrival of Muhammad Shafee at court complex - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/13/media-waits-for-arrival-of-muhammad-shafie-at-court-complex/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMGPStF5Ea6hSyVHgkJwE84qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 01:52:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/13/media-waits-for-arrival-of-muhammad-shafie-at-court-complex/" target="_blank"&gt;Media personnel wait for arrival of Muhammad Shafee at court complex&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Reporters and cameramen are on standby at the main entrance of the Kuala Lumpur Court Complex ahead of the arrival of senior lawyer Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah. Dr Muhammad Shafee, who is leading the defence team for former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak, is expected to be charged by graft busters on Thursday (Sept 13) under the Anti-Money Laundering Act. He was said to have left the headquarters of the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) in a black Toyota Alphard and will arrive at the court complex soon. Dr Muhammad Shafee was believed to be arre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Clash of legal titans – Round Two - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/clash-of-legal-titans-round-two/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDEQ06a4CV9E_BexD4HjyXkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/clash-of-legal-titans-round-two/" target="_blank"&gt;Clash of legal titans – Round Two&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The charging of Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdul­lah with Datuk Seri Gopal Sri Ram over at the prosecution side will see a return of the clash of legal titans. The two fought each other during Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim’s Sodomy II case before the Federal Court in 2013, with Muhammad Shafee leading the prosecution and Sri Ram as chief architect of Anwar’s defence team. This time, it will be Muhammad Shafee in the dock over accusations that he received money from the proceeds of illegal activities. Veteran defence lawyer N. Sivananthan said the second Sri Ram vs Muhammad Shafee bat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>PM: I did not lobby for Shafee to be made prosecutor in Anwar’s trial - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/15/he-wanted-so-badly-to-be-made-ag-pm-i-did-not-lobby-for-shafee-to-be-made-prosecutor-in-anwars-trial/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMqI8qGAev0meFMBrFBBQD8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/15/he-wanted-so-badly-to-be-made-ag-pm-i-did-not-lobby-for-shafee-to-be-made-prosecutor-in-anwars-trial/" target="_blank"&gt;PM: I did not lobby for Shafee to be made prosecutor in Anwar’s trial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad has pooh-poohed Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah’s claim that he lobbied for him to be made prosecutor for the Sodomy 11 trial, saying it was the senior lawyer who wanted so badly to be made Attorney General. The Prime Minister said Muhammad Shafee had come to see him to say that the then AG, Tan Sri Abdul Gani Patail, could not prosecute Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim. Firing back at the lawyer who was charged on Thursday with money laundering, Dr Mahathir said: “According to him, I love him so much that if he is not made the AG, I am going to fight against...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Decision to issue affidavit on RM9.5mil alleged payment to Shafee came from AG, court told - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/decision-to-issue-affidavit-on-rm9-point-5mil-alleged-payment-to-shafee-came-from-ag-court-told/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECzFLVRT7U0buHhwJsVVpcEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 07:31:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/decision-to-issue-affidavit-on-rm9-point-5mil-alleged-payment-to-shafee-came-from-ag-court-told/" target="_blank"&gt;Decision to issue affidavit on RM9.5mil alleged payment to Shafee came from AG, court told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The Court of Appeal here was told that the instruction to issue an affidavit, claiming that RM9.5mil was paid to lawyer Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah came from Attorney General Tommy Thomas. This was said by Senior Federal Counsel Zureen Elina Mohd Dom during a proceeding here on Friday (Sept 14) after a three-man panel led by Justice Umi Kalthum Abdul Majid questioned the veracity of the affidavit, which was signed by an officer at the Attorney General Chambers, Siti Rahayu Mohd Mumazaini, on Sept 5. Justice Umi Kalthum said she found the filing of the affidavit peculiar. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib accuses Pakatan of denying him a fair trial again - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/najib-accuses-pakatan-of-denying-him-a-fair-trial-again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIEjilRjki_GRK6UwyZyHFoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/najib-accuses-pakatan-of-denying-him-a-fair-trial-again/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib accuses Pakatan of denying him a fair trial again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Just hours after his lead lawyer is charged with money laundering, Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak (pic) has claimed this as yet another attempt to deny him a fair trial in the SRC International case. Questioning the recent dropping of charges against Pakatan Harapan leaders, Najib also claimed that payments were made to several leaders from political donations given by Saudi Arabia. Najib said the charging of Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah could be seen as a way to intimidate or disqualify him and other lawyers from representing him in his case. “Prior to this, the judge in my ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib: Shafee's arrest is an attempt to prevent me from having a fair trial - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/13/najib-shafees-arrest-is-an-attempt-to-prevent-me-from-having-a-fair-trial/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIKzKPZIuQZzHc_dOxquFCcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 10:22:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/13/najib-shafees-arrest-is-an-attempt-to-prevent-me-from-having-a-fair-trial/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib: Shafee's arrest is an attempt to prevent me from having a fair trial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak claims that charges against his lawyer Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah is an attempt to prevent him from getting a fair trial. Najib said this could be seen as a move to intimidate or disqualify Dr Muhammad Shafee and other lawyers from representing him. "Prior to this, the judge in my case was suddenly changed and the Attorney General's Chambers (AGC) has appointed two external lawyers (Datuk Sulaiman Abdullah and Datuk Seri Gopal Sri Ram) to lead the prosecution case against me. "This is counter to the claim by Pakatan Ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘I am out in the open, I can’t be hiding’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/i-am-out-in-the-open-i-cant-be-hiding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGxEiK9NfkKDDuCaha1chtwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/i-am-out-in-the-open-i-cant-be-hiding/" target="_blank"&gt;‘I am out in the open, I can’t be hiding’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah (pic) has accused the authorities of being slow if they have not been able to catch him and not because he is in hiding. Calling the charges against him a “fix-up”, he said he was probably the busiest lawyer, agreeing with what his counsel Harvinderjit Singh had mentioned in court. “If you cannot catch me, it’s because you’re slow in going from place to place like I do. “I’m 66 but I travel very fast. They couldn’t catch up with me. It’s not because I’m in hiding. “I’m out in the open. I can’t be hiding. It’s crazy,” he told reporters after bei...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Press Statement by Shafee Abdullah regarding the RM9.5 million fees - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/09/press-statement-by-shafee-abdullah-regarding-the-rm9-5-million-fees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEElcu1uUBoho0p4U7HtXss4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 16:24:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/09/press-statement-by-shafee-abdullah-regarding-the-rm9-5-million-fees/" target="_blank"&gt;Press Statement by Shafee Abdullah regarding the RM9.5 million fees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;READ MORE HERE: PRESS STATEMENT BY SHAFEE ABDULLAH ON 9.5 (08.09.2018)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Four charges against Shafee - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/four-charges-against-shafee-lawyer-accused-of-money-laundering-to-the-tune-of-rm95mil/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOuvPiv4BcAOfDASPGJTMrIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/14/four-charges-against-shafee-lawyer-accused-of-money-laundering-to-the-tune-of-rm95mil/" target="_blank"&gt;Four charges against Shafee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Prominent lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah has claimed trial at a Sessions Court here to four charges of money laundering involving RM9.5mil that he received from Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak. The 66-year-old is accused of receiving proceeds of unlawful activity totalling RM4.3mil on Sept 13, 2013, and RM5.2mil on Feb 17, 2014, through two AmIslamic Bank Bhd cheques issued by the former prime minister. The cheques were remitted into Muhammad Shafee’s CIMB Bank account. He allegedly committed the two offences at CIMB Bank Bhd, J2 &amp; K1, Taman Tunku, Bukit Tunku here. The ch...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee: Dr M wanted me to prosecute - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/09/dr-m-wanted-me-to-prosecute-shafee-he-did-not-have-confidence-in-the-agc-to-competently-manage-anwar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM7W6Ymgb5Oa1xACRNrow6oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/09/dr-m-wanted-me-to-prosecute-shafee-he-did-not-have-confidence-in-the-agc-to-competently-manage-anwar/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee: Dr M wanted me to prosecute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Tan Sri Dr Muhammad Shafee Abdullah (pic) claimed that it was Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad who pushed for him to become the special prosecutor in Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim’s Sodomy II appeal. Dr Muhammad Shafee alleged that Dr Mahathir did not have confidence in the Attorney General’s Chambers to competently manage the appeal. “Datuk Seri Najib (Tun Razak) was not keen with the idea of appointing me as the prosecutor by way of fiat (authorisation) for these appeals because he did not want to offend the then attorney general Tan Sri Abdul Gani Patail. “In fact, he was most reluctant...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bar Council urged to act against Shafee for RM9.5m payment - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/09/bar-council-urged-to-act-against-shafee-for-rm9-5m-payment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMUV3SKUfQUzrIA5JBVuVUQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 06:58:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/09/bar-council-urged-to-act-against-shafee-for-rm9-5m-payment/" target="_blank"&gt;Bar Council urged to act against Shafee for RM9.5m payment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Mkini) – The Bar Council has been urged to take action against lawyer Muhammad Shafee Abdullah for allegedly receiving RM9.5 million from former prime minister Najib Abdul Razak. “We urge the Bar Council to uphold the rule of law and to invoke the provisions stipulated in the Legal Profession Act 1976 and to take necessary action against Shafee inter alia, by lodging a complaint with the disciplinary board,” Perak DAP legal bureau chief Leong Cheok Keng said in a statement today. Shafee purportedly received the payment for his services as special prosecutor in PKR president-elect Anwar Ibr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Affidavit from AGC claims Shafee received RM9.5mil from Najib - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/08/affidavit-from-agc-claims-shafee-received-rm95mil-from-najib/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOzmOaLHXp3fWOpAv0bW0eQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/08/affidavit-from-agc-claims-shafee-received-rm95mil-from-najib/" target="_blank"&gt;Affidavit from AGC claims Shafee received RM9.5mil from Najib&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The Attorney General’s Chambers has issued an affidavit claiming that lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah (pic) received payments amounting to RM9.5mil from former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak between 2013 and 2014. PKR president-elect Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim, in a statement issued by his office, said his lawyers had received the affidavit signed by an officer in the AG’s Chambers on Thursday morning. The affidavit, signed by Siti Rahayu Mohd Mumazaini, the special officer of the AG’s Chambers, said two cheques were deposited into Shafee’s CIMB Bank account ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shafee: Dr M pushed for Najib to appoint me as Anwar prosecutor - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/08/shafee-dr-m-pushed-for-najib-to-appoint-me-as-anwar-prosecutor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAHvqosogOrhSvStm-hrdgQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 09:31:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/08/shafee-dr-m-pushed-for-najib-to-appoint-me-as-anwar-prosecutor/" target="_blank"&gt;Shafee: Dr M pushed for Najib to appoint me as Anwar prosecutor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Mkini) – Lawyer Muhammad Shafee Abdullah claims it was Prime Minister Dr Mahathir Mohamad who had pushed for him to be appointed as a special prosecutor in Anwar Ibrahim’s Sodomy II trial. Shafee claimed that in 2013, then-prime minister Najib Abdul Razak was not keen on appointing him as a prosecutor by way of fiat, as he did not want to offend the attorney-general at the time, Abdul Gani Patail. “In fact, he was most reluctant. However, it was Mahathir who insisted that I be appointed as the special prosecutor in Anwar’s appeals, as Mahathir did not have the confidence that the Attorney-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Affidavit could see Anwar’s suit reinstated, says lawyer - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/07/affidavit-could-see-anwars-suit-reinstated-says-lawyer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHVPKTi_9Tm4_GBuZ3-KDtwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 06:06:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/07/affidavit-could-see-anwars-suit-reinstated-says-lawyer/" target="_blank"&gt;Affidavit could see Anwar’s suit reinstated, says lawyer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – A lawyer says the Court of Appeal is likely to reinstate Anwar Ibrahim’s suit following the revelation that Muhammad Shafee Abdullah who was ad hoc prosecutor at the time received RM9.5 million from Najib Razak to prosecute the former opposition leader in his Sodomy 2 case. SN Nair (pic) said the affidavit by Siti Rahayu Mohd Mumazaini from the Attorney-General’s Chambers was fresh evidence that would greatly assist Anwar’s lawyers. “This is an important piece of evidence that was not available to Anwar last year and is now coming from the government whom he named as a respondent. “...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Najib files appeal against High Court for dismissing gag order request - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/13/najib-files-appeal-against-high-court-for-dismissing-gag-order-request/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEmYUztVf3nfShAeZP6diy4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 10:32:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/13/najib-files-appeal-against-high-court-for-dismissing-gag-order-request/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib files appeal against High Court for dismissing gag order request&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak has filed an appeal against the High Court’s dismissal on a gag order to prevent the media from discussing the merits of his criminal case. Najib’s lead counsel Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah confirmed in a text message that a notice of appeal was filed at the Court of Appeal on Monday afternoon. A notice of appeal must be filed within 14 days of the court's decision. Last Friday (Aug 10), High Court judge Justice Mohd Nazlan Mohd Ghazali dismissed Najib’s application for the gag order. In his decision, Mohd Nazlan said a gag ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>High Court dismisses Najib's application for gag order on media - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/10/high-court-dismisses-najib-application-for-media-gag-order/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJy-SuyvEdeNdynH705UOzcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 09:22:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/10/high-court-dismisses-najib-application-for-media-gag-order/" target="_blank"&gt;High Court dismisses Najib's application for gag order on media&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The High Court here has dismissed an application by Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak for a gag order on the media, prohibiting it from discussing the merits of the criminal cases against him. In his decision Thursday, Justice Mohd Nazlan Mohd Ghazali said the application was unsustainable as there are existing laws available. "Those who overstep (in reporting) risk action being taken – such as contempt of court – and these remedies are readily available," he said. The judge, in his assessment, said that the applicant had fallen short of establishing his case. "I find the application...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>High Court: New charges against Najib to be merged with previous bribery, CBT charges - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/high-court-new-charges-against-najib-to-be-merged-with-previous-bribery-cbt-charges/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENgXP-wQen6QqhnpGmcKfI8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 03:13:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/high-court-new-charges-against-najib-to-be-merged-with-previous-bribery-cbt-charges/" target="_blank"&gt;High Court: New charges against Najib to be merged with previous bribery, CBT charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak's three new charges of money laundering will be merged with his other charges of bribery and breach of trust, linked to the 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB) scandal. The former prime minister on Wednesday (Aug 8) was slapped with fresh charges of receiving RM27mil, RM5mil and RM10mil, which were obtained from illegal activities, into his bank account in three separate transactions. The first and second offences were allegedly committed at AmIslamic Bank at Jalan Raja Chulan on Dec 26, 2014 while the third offence was allegedly committed at the sam...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Court dismisses Najib’s bid for gag on media - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/11/court-dismisses-najibs-bid-for-gag-on-media/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECch5Smx9vwPqEdmWgZrvhEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/11/court-dismisses-najibs-bid-for-gag-on-media/" target="_blank"&gt;Court dismisses Najib’s bid for gag on media&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The High Court here has dismissed an application by Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak for a gag order on the media to prevent it from discussing the merits of his criminal case. Justice Mohd Nazlan Mohd Ghazali said a gag order would be an extension of the existing contempt and defamation law. “Those who overstep in their reporting risk action being taken such as contempt of court and these remedies are readily available. “I find the application unsustainable. I dismiss this notice of motion,” he said. Najib’s lead counsel Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah submitted that the media fur...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib questions ‘unusual’ transfer of judges in letter to Chief Judge of Malaya - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/najib-questions-unusual-transfer-of-judges-in-letter-to-chief-judge-of-malaya/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPyNGhVOQzHIUa8lg7N2MosqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 09:29:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/najib-questions-unusual-transfer-of-judges-in-letter-to-chief-judge-of-malaya/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib questions ‘unusual’ transfer of judges in letter to Chief Judge of Malaya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak has sent a letter to Chief Judge of Malaya Tan Sri Zaharah Ibrahim over the “unusual” transfer of a trial judge presiding over his abuse of power and criminal breach of trust cases. His lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah said a copy of the letter was sent to current trial judge Justice Mohd Nazlan Mohd Ghazali and the previous judge Justice Datuk Mohd Sofian Abd Razak. “We find it strange that in the middle of the case being tried in Justice Sofian’s court, we now have a sudden transfer order. “We have no issue with either ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Attorney General's Chambers appeals against Jamal bail - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/07/attorney-generals-chambers-appeals-against-jamal-bail/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIuNPc7HJ5sLYcJH2tp2BagqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 07:50:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/07/attorney-generals-chambers-appeals-against-jamal-bail/" target="_blank"&gt;Attorney General's Chambers appeals against Jamal bail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Attorney General's Chambers is appealing against the decision of a Shah Alam High Court to grant Datuk Seri Jamal Md Yunos (pic) bail. A source at the AGC confirmed that a notice of appeal was filed at the Court of Appeal on Monday afternoon. An appeal can be filed within 14 days of a decision of the High Court. Last week, Jamal was released after the Shah Alam High Court reviewed a magistrate's court decision which rejected bail for Jamal on two trespassing charges. The 47-year-old was represented by lawyers Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah and Datuk Mohd Imran Tamrin. Ju...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Judge: I have Najib’s letter to chief judge, nothing else to say - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/09/judge-i-have-najibs-letter-to-chief-judge-nothing-else-to-say/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMBUI4mGZvTm58vhMT-Zc5sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/09/judge-i-have-najibs-letter-to-chief-judge-nothing-else-to-say/" target="_blank"&gt;Judge: I have Najib’s letter to chief judge, nothing else to say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A letter Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak wrote to Chief Judge of Malaya Tan Sri Zaharah Ibrahim has grabbed the attention at a court proceeding. Najib’s lead counsel Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah brought up the letter before Justice Mohd Nazlan Mohd Ghazali, who was presiding over the case for the first time after taking over High Court 3 from previous judge Justice Mohd Sofian Abd Razak. Justice Mohd Sofian, who was transferred to a civil court, became the subject matter in the letter. “This is an instruction by my client. It is not written in the view to recuse any judge. “Thi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Muhammad Shafee supports abolishment of Sosma - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/24/shafee-abdullah-on-sosma/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFYzGti1SjiFfrwk0VE9uikqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 00:32:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/24/shafee-abdullah-on-sosma/" target="_blank"&gt;Muhammad Shafee supports abolishment of Sosma&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Prominent lawyer Tan Sri Muhammad Shafee Abdullah (pic) has supported the abolishment of the Security Offences (Special Measures) Act 2012 (Sosma) as it is "draconian" and a rare legislation that robs the courts of its judicial powers. "Of course I support the abolishment of Sosma as it is a draconian legislation with no safeguards against police abuses and brutality and has given the police a Carte Blancs to indulge in corrupt practices on a large scale," he said in response to Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad's announcement to abolish the law. On Sunday (July 22), the Prime Minister...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>