<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Sulu - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZ5WkdNMkVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:13:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Second Lahad Datu incursion not possible, says expert - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/17/royal-sulu-force-in-disarray-says-expert/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELFiX1Fib0nJj4EKsd8N-ogqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 08:50:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/17/royal-sulu-force-in-disarray-says-expert/" target="_blank"&gt;Second Lahad Datu incursion not possible, says expert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KOTA KINABALU: The Royal Sulu Force (RSF) behind the 2013 Lahad Datu intrusion is in disarray and is in no position to plan a similar incursion. Jolo island-based anti kidnapping activist Prof Octavio Dinampo said the self styled Sulu Sultanate is disorganised as there many claimants to the “throne.” He said other armed groups in the Sulu province including the Abu Sayyaf were constantly trying to evade the ongoing Philippines military offensives against them. "These groups are incapable of doing anything," said Octavio. He said there would also be talk among local communities in Sulu provi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Indonesia, Malaysia, Philippines unite against Abu Sayyaf - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/18/indonesia-malaysia-philippines-unite-against-abu-sayyaf/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMDa-lLnV6c9COYJBgOIU80qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 04:27:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/18/indonesia-malaysia-philippines-unite-against-abu-sayyaf/" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia, Malaysia, Philippines unite against Abu Sayyaf&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA: Indonesia, Malaysia and the Philippines have agreed to initiate joint army training to advance efforts to secure the Sulu Sea from rampant piracy. Indonesian Defense Minister Ryamizard Ryacudu explained that each of the countries would first begin its own army personnel training in January 2017 before conducting the joint training later in the year. The military training will take place in Indonesia’s Tarakan in North Kalimantan, Malaysia’s Tawau in Sabah and the Philippines’ Bongao Island. Ryacudu said Army soldiers set to participate in the joint military training would form a sp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>IS' top commander in Southeast Asia gravely hurt - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/30/is-top-commander-gravely-hurt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPss3FbbLEPUhlEQoWscdAQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:50:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/30/is-top-commander-gravely-hurt/" target="_blank"&gt;IS' top commander in Southeast Asia gravely hurt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA: The top commander of the Islamic State (IS) terror group in Southeast Asia has been gravely wounded in air strikes by security forces hunting him in the southern Philippines, the Philippine military said Sunday. General Eduardo Ano told reporters that Isnilon Hapilon, chief of the Abu Sayyaf militant group, needed a blood transfusion. "He will die if he does not get proper medical treatment. He is bedridden. He can't walk yet. He is being carried around on an improvised stretcher by four of his men," said Gen Ano, Chief of Staff of the Armed Forces. He cited intelligence provided by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Dept: Strong winds coming - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/10/31/dept-strong-winds-coming/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEU_m1cJ7a5xjX5Zdw0waKEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/10/31/dept-strong-winds-coming/" target="_blank"&gt;Dept: Strong winds coming&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: A warning of strong winds and rough seas until Saturday has been issued by the Meteorological Department. These condition of strong winds and rough seas is dangerous to small crafts, recreational sea activities and sea sports. For Malaysian waters, the department forecast strong East-Northeasterly winds of 40-50kmph with waves up to 3.5m expected over waters off Perlis, Kedah, Penang, Kelantan, Terengganu, Sarawak, Labuan FT and Sabah (Interior, West Coast, Kudat and Sandakan) from today until Nov 5. For shipping, the department warned of strong East-Northeasterly winds of 40...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Philippine troops recover remains of beheaded German hostage - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-militants-german-idUSKBN16C032</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB07qAuNlzuXYhZ-OgV6VuoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 04:02:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-militants-german-idUSKBN16C032" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine troops recover remains of beheaded German hostage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA (Reuters) - Philippine soldiers have found the remains of a German man who was beheaded by Islamic State-linked Abu Sayyaf militants last week, a military official said late on Saturday, Both the head and body of Jurgen Kantner were recovered while the troops were conducting combat, search and retrieval operations in Indanan town in the remote southern province of Sulu, Colonel Cirilito Sobejana told reporters. Kantner's remains would be kept in a hospital morgue in Sulu while documents were being prepared to transport the body, said Sobejana, commander of the Joint Task Force Sulu. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Hisham: Sulu Sea safe with TMP - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/06/20/hisham-sulu-sea-safe-with-tmp-msia-indonesia-and-philippines-to-step-up-joint-patrols-in-area/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEBV5wrjCTqn7PLNMAd3rBEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/06/20/hisham-sulu-sea-safe-with-tmp-msia-indonesia-and-philippines-to-step-up-joint-patrols-in-area/" target="_blank"&gt;Hisham: Sulu Sea safe with TMP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TARAKAN (North Kalimantan): There will be few safe harbours on the Sulu Sea for militants, pirates and kidnappers from here on. With the official establishment of the Trilateral Maritime Patrol (TMP), Malaysia, Indonesia and the Philippines’ militaries have agreed to step up joint patrols and surveillance in the area. “The main objective is to ensure militant threats such as Daesh/Islamic State do not turn the Sulu Sea into their laluan tikus (hidden route) to gain entry into our countries,” Defence Minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein said at yesterday’s launch of TMP on board the KRI ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf leader with RM4.4mil bounty intends to surrender - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/04/15/abu-sayyaf-leader-with-rm44mil-bounty-intends-to-surrender/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO2ul0nn3lB0aDauRoVH2UYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 06:44:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/04/15/abu-sayyaf-leader-with-rm44mil-bounty-intends-to-surrender/" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf leader with RM4.4mil bounty intends to surrender&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY: Radulan Sahiron, the notorious leader of the Abu Sayyaf in Sulu, has expressed his intention to surrender due to old age. Lt. Gen. Carlito Galvez Jr., commander of the military’s Western Mindanao Command, said Sahiron has tapped some elders in Sulu to relay his intention to surrender. “The continuing operation against the Abu Sayyaf, up and down from Talipao, Patikul, Mainbubg and other parts of Sulu, this is taking a toll on the part of the Abu Sayyaf particularly to Sahiron,” Galvez said. Sahiron, the one-armed bandit leader of the Sulu-based Abu Sayyaf group, is believed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Two Indonesians freed by Abu Sayyaf in Sulu - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2016/12/12/two-indonesians-freed-by-abu-sayyaf-in-sulu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBAW5-GtCkHxgxRlCcx91NwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 10:19:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2016/12/12/two-indonesians-freed-by-abu-sayyaf-in-sulu/" target="_blank"&gt;Two Indonesians freed by Abu Sayyaf in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY: Two Indonesians were freed by their Abu Sayyaf abductors in Indanan, Sulu, on Monday afternoon. Major Filemon Tan Jr, spokesman of the military’s Western Mindanao Command, identified the freed victims as Mohammad Nazir and Rubin Peter. The two were released by their Abu Sayyaf captors, led by Alhabsy Misaya, and handed to Moro National Liberation Front (MNLF) commander Tahir Sali in Indanan. Nazir and Peter were the remaining seven boat crew members who were taken off the seas of Simisa Island in Sulu on June 22. The five others were freed earlier. The freed Indonesians were...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Indonesia, Malaysia and Philippines launch joint patrols to tackle ISIS threat - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/19/asia/indonesia-malaysia-philippines-isis/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJfuUqN3fLKv5__12A2jySMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 13:12:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/06/19/asia/indonesia-malaysia-philippines-isis/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia, Malaysia and Philippines launch joint patrols to tackle ISIS threat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three Southeast Asian nations have started trilateral naval patrols in the first concrete sign of cooperation against ISIS-inspired terror groups operating in the region. The Philippines, Malaysia and Indonesia will begin joint patrols and information-sharing to curb the influence of local Islamist terror groups, according to a joint statement released by the three governments. Southeast Asian terror cells aligned with the Iraq- and Syria-based group have been emboldened in recent years, culminating in a month-long battle for the city of Marawi on Mindanao island in the southern Philippines...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Army 'kills Abu Sayyaf commander' blamed for beheadings - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/army-kills-abu-sayyaf-commander-blamed-beheadings-170412052319125.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIX3bJCEa9JNLvGaobSllfMqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 06:18:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/army-kills-abu-sayyaf-commander-blamed-beheadings-170412052319125.html" target="_blank"&gt;Army 'kills Abu Sayyaf commander' blamed for beheadings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soldiers battling Abu Sayyaf in central Philippines are reported to have killed a key commander of the armed group who had been blamed for the beheadings of two Canadians and a German hostage. Military chief of staff General Eduardo Ano said troops recovered and identified the remains of Moammar Askali, also known as Abu Rami, at scene of the battle in a coastal village on Bohol island on Tuesday. Five other Abu Sayyaf members were killed in the fighting, along with four soldiers and policemen. Ano said troops took the picture of Askali after his death and that captured Abu Sayyaf fighters ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Piracy Prompts Shippers to Avoid Seas West of Philippines - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/piracy-shippers-west-philippines/3684485.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBzTjQbczQo2LwT7BeoBHxoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 08:41:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/piracy-shippers-west-philippines/3684485.html" target="_blank"&gt;Piracy Prompts Shippers to Avoid Seas West of Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A surge in piracy to the west of the Philippines is forcing shipowners to divert vessels through other waters, adding to their costs and the time it takes to transport goods such as Australian iron ore to key Asian destinations. There have been 16 attacks since last March on ships in the Sulu and Celebes seas, through which about $40 billion worth of cargo passes each year, according to the Regional Cooperation Agreement on Combating Piracy and Armed Robbery against Ships in Asia (ReCAAP). That government-backed anti-piracy organization says over a dozen crewmembers being held hostage by Fi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Southeast Asia Joint Patrols Aimed at Islamic Militants - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/3886146.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPlzjQnQGMRG1qlkYaF4tLYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 09:19:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/3886146.html" target="_blank"&gt;Southeast Asia Joint Patrols Aimed at Islamic Militants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joint patrols by three Southeast Asian countries in the Sulu Sea may be the start of a larger regional effort to keep Islamic militants at bay, officials said Sunday. The patrols will be conducted by forces from Indonesia, the Philippines and Malaysia, starting with sea operations this month, with air and land patrols starting at a later date. The initiative in the Sulu Sea, an area bounded by the Malaysian state of Sabah and the southern Philippines, is a “collective agreement that is followed by the operational level,” Indonesian Defense Minister Ryamizard Ryacudu said. It will feature jo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Fong relishes freedom, 17 years on - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/18/fong-relishes-freedom-17-years-on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDp0ThdUie_34RzF-cdxbG4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/18/fong-relishes-freedom-17-years-on/" target="_blank"&gt;Fong relishes freedom, 17 years on&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEMPORNA: For the past 16 years, dive instructor Ken Fong would look at his watch with dread at 8pm every April 23. He’ll be doing the same for the 17th time on Sunday. “I remember the date and time very well. It was a big event in my life. I look to see if it is 8pm. That is the time we were kidnapped,” said the 44-year-old who is based in Osaka. Fong was then having a BBQ party to celebrate Easter with foreign tourists in Sipadan island, one of the world’s top diving destinations, when Abu Sayyaf gunmen struck. The perpetrators whisked away Fong, eight Sabahans, two Filipino resort worker...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Four fishing boat crewmen abducted off Sulu - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2016/12/21/four-fishing-boat-crewmen-abducted-off-sulu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI27Npdbb4a8K2bUcRduasgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 05:09:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2016/12/21/four-fishing-boat-crewmen-abducted-off-sulu/" target="_blank"&gt;Four fishing boat crewmen abducted off Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY: Unidentified gunmen have snatched four crewmembers off a fishing boat while the vessel was sailing off Sulu, the Philippine military said on Wednesday. Major Filemon Tan Jr., the Western Mindanao Command spokesman, said the incident, which took place around 2:30am Tuesday, was confirmed when the crew of the sister ship of FB Ramona 2 raised the alarm after they did not receive any feedback from their companions. "At 5am, FB Melissa 2 proceeded to the location of her sister ship and found all crew on board missing and the VHF Radio/GPS stolen while other belongings were intac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Body of alleged Abu Sayyaf hostage found in yacht in Sulu - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/07/body-of-alleged-abu-sayyaf-hostage-found-in-yacht-in-sulu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJaDEbvVGgM9Q7kqZjc_bUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 03:48:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/07/body-of-alleged-abu-sayyaf-hostage-found-in-yacht-in-sulu/" target="_blank"&gt;Body of alleged Abu Sayyaf hostage found in yacht in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY: The military confirmed on Monday the recovery of a body inside an abandoned yacht in Sulu. The body was believed to be a companion of kidnapped German national Juergen Kantner. Major Filemon Tan Jr., spokesperson of Western Mindanao Command, said the body was found by a civilian around 6am on Sunday near Laparan Island, Pangutaran, Sulu. Tan said the body had gunshot wounds. The Abu Sayyaf on Sunday claimed it has held hostage Kantner, but killed his female companion. The military said it still did not have information on the kidnapping.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Sulu Sea To Sulawesi: Where ISIS Is Finding A Toehold In Asia - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphjennings/2017/07/11/sulu-sea-to-sulawesi-these-are-the-5-big-hotspots-for-isis-in-asia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED55ysYkTxbE7WR7NLcBe7QqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ralphjennings/2017/07/11/sulu-sea-to-sulawesi-these-are-the-5-big-hotspots-for-isis-in-asia/" target="_blank"&gt;Sulu Sea To Sulawesi: Where ISIS Is Finding A Toehold In Asia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARAWI CITY, PHILIPPINES – JUNE 03: A resident who escaped from the inner city being sieged by militants is being frisked by local police as part of their security processing, on June 3, 2017 in Marawi City, southern Philippines. (Jes Aznar/Getty Images) Feared terrorist organization Islamic State in Iraq and Syria makes no secret of its global reach. The group has said it was behind the suicide bombing that killed 22 at a concert in Manchester in May and the Florida night club shooting that killed 49 in June last year, for example. The same group, often abbreviated to ISIS, has been poking...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>US, Philippines Navy Ships Patrol Sulu Sea - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-philippines-patrol-sulu-sea/3924116.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ-AG8mVgXCD1XqnsZL--G4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 08:18:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-philippines-patrol-sulu-sea/3924116.html" target="_blank"&gt;US, Philippines Navy Ships Patrol Sulu Sea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States and Philippine navies held a joint naval patrol Saturday in dangerous southern Philippine waters, amid rising international concern about Islamist militancy and piracy in the region. U.S. Navy combat ship USS Coronado joined a Philippine Navy frigate, BRP Alcaraz, in patrolling the Sulu Sea, where numerous pirate attacks on commercial shipping have been made since 2015. “Our at-sea operations with the Philippine Navy demonstrate our commitment to the alliance and deter piracy and illegal activities,” U.S. Rear Admiral Don Gabrielson said in a statement issued by the U.S. e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Two of five Malaysian Abu Sayyaf hostages rescued - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/23/sabah-hostages-two-freed-jolo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE37fCE1E9JCAgdnXq2cihkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 05:11:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/23/sabah-hostages-two-freed-jolo/" target="_blank"&gt;Two of five Malaysian Abu Sayyaf hostages rescued&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KOTA KINABALU: Two of five Malaysian sailors held hostage by Abu Sayyaf gunmen have been rescued during an operation in waters between Jolo and Pata islands in southern Philipiines. The two Fandy Bakran, 26 and Abdul Rahim Sumas, 62, were rescued during a Philippines marine operation at Jolo’s coastal province of Kalingalan Caluang on the way Pata Island at about 2am Thursday. Philippines military spokesman Colonel Edgard Arevalo confirmed the rescue during the operations. The two, who were looking scared and tired were “alright” and have been sent to the Camp Teodulfo Station Hospital in B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Three crew missing from Sabah fishing boat found in Sulu sea - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/19/three-crew-missing-from-sabah-fishing-boat-in-sulu-sea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENgzryxEV7NeyJJPoqRMiKUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 12:51:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/19/three-crew-missing-from-sabah-fishing-boat-in-sulu-sea/" target="_blank"&gt;Three crew missing from Sabah fishing boat found in Sulu sea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KOTA KINABALU: Philippines authorities found a Sabah-registered fishing vessel listing in Sulu waters close to the Sabah border early Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘Motive still unknown’: Grenade explosion kills 4, injures 15 in the Philippines - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/382341-grenade-philippines-sulu-explosion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENK0Ql4wju2trFnDDPRnvUsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 11:55:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/382341-grenade-philippines-sulu-explosion/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Motive still unknown’: Grenade explosion kills 4, injures 15 in the Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A grenade attack has killed four people and injured around 15 others at a store in Jolo, an area in the southwest Philippines. The incident happened on the island of Jolo, capital of the Sulu province, when a grenade was thrown near a bakery on Saturday evening. Four people perished and scores more were wounded in the explosion, which, according to daily newspaper the Philstar, is suspected of being part of an escape attempt by a fleeing robber. However, the Northbound Philippines News Online report that the blast may be in retaliation to a shooting in which a child injured on Friday. READ ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Duterte Orders Troops to Blast Militants — and Their Hostages - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/duterte-orders-troops-blast-militants/3676883.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJU0GAL03lkzMLkXanxZItMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 02:57:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/duterte-orders-troops-blast-militants/3676883.html" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte Orders Troops to Blast Militants — and Their Hostages&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte, in a bid to stop a wave of kidnappings at sea, said Saturday that he had ordered his troops to bomb extremists who flee with their captives, calling the loss of civilian lives in such an attack "collateral damage." Duterte has previously said he told his Indonesian and Malaysian counterparts that their forces can blast away as they pursue militants who abduct sailors in waters where the three countries converge, and that they can bring their kidnap victims to the southern Philippines. He said in a speech late Saturday that he had given the same orders t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf militants behead kidnapped Philippine soldier: army - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-militants-idUSKBN17P04G</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJtzs5yD9e83SztWSc9-j-gqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 12:01:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-militants-idUSKBN17P04G" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf militants behead kidnapped Philippine soldier: army&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA (Reuters) - A Filipino soldier kidnapped last week in the southern Philippines by Abu Sayyaf militants was found beheaded, the military said on Sunday, hours after government troops killed three more members of the Islamic State-linked group in a clash elsewhere. The head of Sergeant Anni Siraji of the Army's 32nd Infantry Battalion was found 50 meters away from his body in Patikul town in Sulu, Brigadier General Cirilito Sobejana, commander of the Joint Task Force Sulu, said. Sobejana said Siraji was probably abducted and executed because of his involvement in peace initiatives in S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Sailor: Reunion with family a 'dream come true' - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/30/sailor-reunion-with-family-a-dream-come-true/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHnKvpkwz24ZNPS5BjZK3IoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 05:40:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/30/sailor-reunion-with-family-a-dream-come-true/" target="_blank"&gt;Sailor: Reunion with family a 'dream come true'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Traumatised and fatigued after eight months of captivity in a foreign country, Mohd Ridzuan Ismail was ecstatic to be reunited again with his wife and daughters. The 33-year-old sailor and his family members were inseparable when met at Prime Minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak's residence here on Thursday. Mohd Ridzuan was one of five Malaysians abducted by Abu Sayyaf militants from the waters off Dent Haven, Lahad Datu, on July 18 last year. Mohd Ridzuan, Fandy Bakran, 27 and Mohd Jumadil Rahim, 23, were rescued by the Filipino military in Jolo on March 26. According to Mohd...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf captives escape after fake ransom - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/08/13/abu-sayyaf-captives-escape-after-fake-ransom/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBDJgmC4YhfeGp71_A6XtEgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 05:05:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/08/13/abu-sayyaf-captives-escape-after-fake-ransom/" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf captives escape after fake ransom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA: Three men kidnapped by Islamist militants in Mindanao escaped while their captors prayed, dodging bullets as they ran, police said on Saturday after a ruse using fake ransom money failed. The fate of a fourth man who ran off in a different direction was unclear. The construction workers were taken to the police on Jolo Island on Friday, four weeks after being abducted by the Abu Sayyaf group, which is holding more than a dozen other hostages including several foreigners in remote jungles. Afternoon prayer The gunmen had received an undetermined amount of cash for the hostages on Thu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>M'sian-registered boat found in Philippine waters, crew missing - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDmiY4EGziCkbz3Dbdq-N3UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 03:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three Indonesian crewmen, aged between 26 and 47 years, who were in a fishing vessel near Sulu early Thursday morning were missing and their fate is still not known. The boat registered in Sandakan, Malaysia, was found with its engine still running. According to sources, Filipino security forces came across the fishing boat near Pulau Langawan. Meanwhile, the Eastern Sabah Security Command (Esscom) received a report on the matter and is still awaiting a full report on the incident which occurred in Philippine waters. - Bernama&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Engineering grad now one of world's most wanted terrorists - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/05/26/engineering-grad-now-one-of-worlds-most-wanted-terrorists/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMkd-E-2Yy1JdQ59d2PbeQIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 02:53:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/05/26/engineering-grad-now-one-of-worlds-most-wanted-terrorists/" target="_blank"&gt;Engineering grad now one of world's most wanted terrorists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAVAO CITY: An Arabic-speaking preacher with an engineering degree from the Philippines' top university, Isnilon Hapilon, 51, is one of the world's most wanted terrorists. Hundreds have died and millions have been spent in the hunt for the Abu Sayyaf chieftain designated by the Islamic State (IS) as its top man in South-east Asia last year. But he remains elusive. Hapilon moved out of the Abu Sayyaf's strongholds in Sulu province last year to bring bandit and terrorist groups in the southern Philippines under IS' banner. He gained notoriety in 2001 when he took part in the kidnapping of 20 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Philippine Marines Find Remains of Beheaded German Hostage - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/philippine-marins-find-remains-of-beheaded-german-hostage/3750270.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN6Z6Y6Jer6TPiQZqJ_GlvIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 12:25:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/philippine-marins-find-remains-of-beheaded-german-hostage/3750270.html" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine Marines Find Remains of Beheaded German Hostage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philippine troops have found the remains of a German hostage who was beheaded by Abu Sayyaf militants in the country's south, vowing Sunday to rescue more than 30 other captives and crush the ransom-seeking extremists. Marines dug up the head and body of Jurgen Gustav Kantner late Saturday in the mountainous hinterlands of Indanan town in Sulu province, where the militants are holding at least 31 other foreign and Filipino hostages, said regional military commander Maj. Gen. Carlito Galvez Jr. The 70-year-old Kantner was seized from his yacht with his female German companion off Malaysia's ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Philippines' Duterte asks China to patrol piracy-plagued waters - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippine-militants-china-idUSKBN15F1AV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECj-vI-FSL8hfaxBGxgfgCoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 11:57:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippine-militants-china-idUSKBN15F1AV" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines' Duterte asks China to patrol piracy-plagued waters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA (Reuters) - Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte on Tuesday said he had asked China to help in the fight against Islamic State-linked militants by sending ships to patrol southern waters plagued by raids on commercial vessels. Speaking to newly promoted army generals, Duterte said he had sought China's help in dangerous waters in the south to check the activities of Abu Sayyaf, a Muslim rebel group sustained by piracy and kidnap-for-ransom activities. A surge in piracy off parts of the Philippines is forcing ship-owners to divert vessels through other waters, pushing up costs and shi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Philippine Troops, Suspected Militants Clash; 9 Dead - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3805147.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFuG0h48BWn8vQGhwf5nFgEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 09:03:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3805147.html" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine Troops, Suspected Militants Clash; 9 Dead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least nine people were killed Tuesday in a gun battle between Philippine forces and suspected Abu Sayyaf militants on a central resort island, far from the extremists' southern jungle bases and in a region where the U.S. government has warned that the gunmen may be plotting kidnappings, officials said. Military officials said at least five gunmen, three soldiers and a policeman had died in the ongoing gun battle in a village in the coastal town of Inabanga in Bohol province. The island province is known for its beach resorts and wildlife and lies near Cebu province, a bustling commercial...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sulu-Sulawesi sea patrol pact signing put off - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/10/sulu-sulawesi-sea-patrol-pact-signing-put-off/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK4bPm_i2XFEqhZtWpsGxCkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 05:01:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/10/sulu-sulawesi-sea-patrol-pact-signing-put-off/" target="_blank"&gt;Sulu-Sulawesi sea patrol pact signing put off&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KOTA KINABALU: The much-anticipated signing of the Trilateral Maritime Patrol of Sulu and Sulawesi seas agreement here on Tuesday has been postponed as Philippines Defence Secretary Delfin Lorenzana will not be able to attend the ceremony. The ceremony was to be attended by Defence Minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein (pic), Indonesian Defence Minister Ryamizard Ryacudu and Lorenzana at the Malaysian naval base KD Sandakan. Hishammuddin issued a media statement late on Sunday saying that the event had been postponed indefinitely. "This is because he (Lorenzana) has been directed to acco...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hisham: Refugees entering M’sia via Sulu waters are latest threats - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/08/hisham-refugees-entering-msia-via-sulu-waters-are-latest-threats/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIwtokQnNT7msIQvWlveOBYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 15:25:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/08/hisham-refugees-entering-msia-via-sulu-waters-are-latest-threats/" target="_blank"&gt;Hisham: Refugees entering M’sia via Sulu waters are latest threats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Iraqi and Syrian refugees who are coming into the country through Sulu waters are Malaysia's latest security threats, said Datuk Seri Hishamuddin Tun Hussein. The Defence Minister said this is following offensive operations in the Islamic State stronghold of Mosul and Raqqa in Iraq recently. “I will be briefed by US Pacific Command and they will give the latest report on the offensive in Iraq and Syria,” Hishamuddin told reporters after chairing the Ummah Empowerment Convention preparatory meeting at the Dato Onn building here yesterday. “Among other threats involve making our...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Three more Malaysians rescued - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/27/malaysian-hostages-rescued-filipino-military-jolo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBxScU-wTUeP3afHDDDT5DMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 02:53:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/27/malaysian-hostages-rescued-filipino-military-jolo/" target="_blank"&gt;Three more Malaysians rescued&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KOTA KINABALU: The three remaining Malaysians held hostage by Abu Sayyaf for the last eight months were rescued by the Filipino military in Jolo late Sunday. Eastern Sabah Security Command (ESSCOM) commander Datuk Wan Bari Bari Wan Abd Khalid said that the three Fandy Bakran, 27, Mohd Jumadil Rahim 24, and Mohd Ridzuan Ismail, 33,are currently in the custody of the Philippines military. “We have been informed of their rescue and they are under the Philippines military,” he said but could not give immediate details of the Filipino operations that led to the release of the trio. Two other sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Fraught history of Islam in Philippines began long before Marawi - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-06-29/fraught-history-of-islam-in-philippines-began-long-before-marawi/8655306</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJghKaojIFM5QB9Wo0t6mbEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 05:05:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-06-29/fraught-history-of-islam-in-philippines-began-long-before-marawi/8655306" target="_blank"&gt;Fraught history of Islam in Philippines began long before Marawi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The occupation of the Philippine city of Marawi by Islamic militants has been a regular fixture in the news cycle for over a month now. The recent shooting of ABC journalist Adam Harvey by militants linked to ISIS brought it brutally close to home for many Australians, but conflicts of this nature are not a new phenomenon in the Philippines. Islam has been a potent force in the country since the 1400s, predating even Christianity's arrival. So, as tensions in the predominantly Catholic nation are reaching boiling point, we take stock of the long and volatile history of Islam in the Philippi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>SE Asian island nations take aim at pirates and militants - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/787e3590-18f6-11e7-a53d-df09f373be87</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGuo158t34yZbwQe3G71gLAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 08:34:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/787e3590-18f6-11e7-a53d-df09f373be87" target="_blank"&gt;SE Asian island nations take aim at pirates and militants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Southeast Asia’s big island nations are to launch a joint naval operation to combat piracy and Islamist militancy that threaten regional trade and security. Ships and troops from the Philippines, Indonesia and Malaysia plan to deploy next week around seas where hijackings and kidnappings have surged, as fears rise over mounting lawlessness and terrorist threats. Delfin Lorenzana, Philippine defence secretary, said he hoped the long-mooted campaign around the Sulu and Celebes seas would “keep the sailors safe and also prevent the movement of terrorists from one place to another” in an area w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Philippines military identifies IS-linked militant killed as Indonesian named 'Mohisen' - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/01/29/indonesian-militant-killed-in-operations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEClz5im2TDqdoisufl18P4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 03:20:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/01/29/indonesian-militant-killed-in-operations/" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines military identifies IS-linked militant killed as Indonesian named 'Mohisen'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;COTABATO CITY: Philippines military has identified one of the four Islamic State-linked militants killed in bombing operations in the southern Philippines as an Indonesian. According to the Philippine Daily Inquirer, Defence Secretary Delfin Lorenzana said the Indonesian as having the alias “Mohisen” was one of the four accompanying wanted IS-linked terrorist Isnilon Hapilon on his mission to create a caliphate in Mindanao. The military initially identified one of the four killed as a Malaysian. He said Hapilon was wounded in the military air strikes three days earlier in the mountain town ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>German sailing couple attacked in Tawi-Tawi waters - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/07/german-sailing-couple-attacked-in-tawi-tawi-waters/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDyhKVzW1CEeWo4SDVv5fhIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 09:44:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/07/german-sailing-couple-attacked-in-tawi-tawi-waters/" target="_blank"&gt;German sailing couple attacked in Tawi-Tawi waters&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KOTA KINABALU: The kidnapping of a 70-year-old German and the killing of his wife by Abu Sayyaf gunmen occurred in waters off the Tawi-Tawi chain of islands in the southern Philippines. Philippines intelligence sources said the incident happened at about 2.30am Monday off Tanjung Luuk Pisuk in Tawi-Tawi. The sources said the couple, Juegen Kantner and Sabina Wetch, were on a private yacht in Tanjong Luuk Pisuk, which in Tausug means muddy water. It is said that Wetch was shot dead while Kantner was kidnapped. Abu Sayyaf spokesman Muamar Askali alias Abu Rami told Philippines media that the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Militants dump hostages to escape army - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/28/militants-dump-hostages-to-escape-army/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBQOjtaqed7v6y6ZTDUBAQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/28/militants-dump-hostages-to-escape-army/" target="_blank"&gt;Militants dump hostages to escape army&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KOTA KINABALU: An overwhelming military presence in the rugged hilly jungle around a Jolo village forced notorious Abu Sayyaf gunmen to abandon the last three of their five Malaysian hostages. Intelligence sources believe that the gunmen, led by Abu Rami @Muammar Askali decided to leave the three sailors when the military started closing in on them. The group has been terrorising the southern Philippines with murders, kidnaps and beheadings including that of Malaysian hostage Bernard Then, 39, in November. The source said it became apparent to the gunmen that they were making no headway in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Another fabrication resurfaces - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/one-mans-meat/2016/11/12/another-fabrication-resurfaces-nur-misuaris-recent-claim-of-a-connection-between-malaysia-and-the-ab/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELtqBCKeLGX-f-StCiAEq_wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/one-mans-meat/2016/11/12/another-fabrication-resurfaces-nur-misuaris-recent-claim-of-a-connection-between-malaysia-and-the-ab/" target="_blank"&gt;Another fabrication resurfaces&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“HAS this serious allegation of involvement of Malaysian politicians with the Abu Sayyaf kidnappers been investigated?” Dr Anthony Tibok, a Parti Cinta Sabah (PCS) politician, WhatsApped me in a Sabah Politics group on Sunday. “Is this what Nur Misuari is talking about on the involvement of Malaysian leaders in kidnap-for-ransom by Abu Sayyaf, Tuan Philip Golingai?” The opposition politician attached a photograph of a 2007 blog report that Sabah Barisan National politicians hosted Abu Sayyaf leaders such as Ghalib Andang @ Commander Robot, Mujib Susukan and Radulan Sahiron at a five-star ho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Military checking reports of German beheading - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/02/26/military-checking-reports-of-german-beheading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBUnyuBf0n0kQFPvkhaU68kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 13:40:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/02/26/military-checking-reports-of-german-beheading/" target="_blank"&gt;Military checking reports of German beheading&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY – The military said it was confirming reports that the Abu Sayyaf has beheaded its kidnap victim—German national Jeurgen Kantner. Major General Carlito Galvez Jr., chief of the Western Mindanao Command, confirmed receiving reports about Kantner’s beheading, “but we need body of proof.” Peace Adviser Jesus Dureza earlier called on the Abu Sayyaf group holding Kantner to spare the life of the German national. “I am appealing to them to please spare the life of innocent and helpless Kantner,” Dureza said in a text message to the Inquirer. A Radyo Inquirer report on Sunday said t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Security forces bracing for revenge attacks - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/11/security-forces-bracing-for-revenge-attacks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELJvvRsQ4tvIdPOpy-AUCscqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/11/security-forces-bracing-for-revenge-attacks/" target="_blank"&gt;Security forces bracing for revenge attacks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KOTA KINABALU: Security forces are bracing for revenge attacks following the killing of three cross border kidnappers and the capture of two others in Sabah. Responding to claims in the Philippines that the Abu Sayyaf group was planning a revenge attack, Sabah Police Commissioner Datuk Abdul Rashid Harun (pic) said they had yet to identify the three dead men. “We are still interrogating the two kidnappers in our custody. “As for now, the search is still on for two more suspected kidnappers and a missing hostage,” he said, adding that all three were last spotted on a boat during Thursday’s s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Philippine troops recover body of beheaded German hostage - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/03/05/philippine-troops-recover-body-beheaded-german-hostage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEnKkJDtkODPBuVzxhQMVk8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 04:47:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/03/05/philippine-troops-recover-body-beheaded-german-hostage/" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine troops recover body of beheaded German hostage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philippine soldiers have found the remains of a German man who was beheaded by Islamic State-linked Abu Sayyaf militants last week, a military official said late on Saturday, Both the head and body of Jurgen Kantner were recovered while the troops were conducting combat, search and retrieval operations in Indanan town in the remote southern province of Sulu, colonel Cirilito Sobejana told reporters. Kantner's remains would be kept in a hospital morgue in Sulu while documents were being prepared to transport the body, said Sobejana, commander of the Joint Task Force Sulu. The Philippines and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Shippers avoid new 'pirate hotspot' in waters west of the Philippines - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-shipping-piracy-asia-idUSKBN1540UA</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKWGsSFqUGD0thZNFfONXLoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-shipping-piracy-asia-idUSKBN1540UA" target="_blank"&gt;Shippers avoid new 'pirate hotspot' in waters west of the Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Keith Wallis SINGAPORE (Reuters) - A surge in piracy to the west of the Philippines is forcing shipowners to divert vessels through other waters, stoking their costs and extending the time it takes to transport goods such as Australian iron ore to key Asian destinations. There have been 16 attacks since last March on ships in the Sulu and Celebes Seas, through which about $40 billion worth of cargo passes each year, according to the Regional Cooperation Agreement on Combating Piracy and Armed Robbery against Ships in Asia (ReCAAP). That government-backed anti-piracy organisation says ove...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Three Indonesians kidnapped by Abu Sayyaf released in Sulu - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2018/09/16/three-indonesians-kidnapped-by-abu-sayyaf-released-in-sulu/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBB_Uo_Mjvu5u1W4KCMxokkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 04:23:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2018/09/16/three-indonesians-kidnapped-by-abu-sayyaf-released-in-sulu/" target="_blank"&gt;Three Indonesians kidnapped by Abu Sayyaf released in Sulu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY (Philippine Daily Inquirer /Asia News Network): Three Indonesian nationals were released by their Abu Sayyaf captors on Saturday (Sept 15) afternoon in Barangay Buanza in Indanan town, Sulu. Colonel Gerry Besana, public affairs officer of the Western Mindanao Command, confirmed the release of three Indonesians but refused to give further details. In a report secured by the Philippine Daily Inquirer from the intelligence unit in Sulu, the release of three Indonesians in Buanza were facilitated by Joint Task Force Sulu Brig Gen Divino Rey Pabayo and Senior Supt Pablo Labra, th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Car bomb kills at least 10 in Philippines - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/31/asia/philippines-basilan-car-bomb-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENbOeMDOsrW25naM22Q1FNkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 06:32:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/31/asia/philippines-basilan-car-bomb-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Car bomb kills at least 10 in Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 10 people were killed when militants linked to the Abu Sayyaf terror group struck a military checkpoint with a car bomb in the southern Philippines Tuesday, officials said. Philippines Army Lieutenant Colonel Jonas Templo said an improvised explosive was detonated in the early hours of the morning, in the Sitio Maganda neighborhood of Lamitan, a city in Basilan province. Basilan Governor Jim Salliman said at least five others were wounded by the attack, which used a van and targeted a checkpoint manned by a Citizen Armed Force Geographical Unit (CAFGU) -- a paramilitary contingent ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Abu Sayyaf leader surrenders to military in Basilan - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2018/03/29/abu-sayyaf-leader-surrenders-to-military-in-basilan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFFN4-iowbYiq-57tWUFwsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 15:46:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2018/03/29/abu-sayyaf-leader-surrenders-to-military-in-basilan/" target="_blank"&gt;Abu Sayyaf leader surrenders to military in Basilan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ZAMBOANGA CITY: The military on Wednesday evening (March 28) confirmed the surrender of a notorious Basilan-based Abu Sayyaf leader and 13 of his followers. Lt Gen Carlito Galvez Jr, the commander of the Western Mindanao Command, said Nurhassan Jamiri and his men brought in their firearms when they yielded to soldiers in a remote village in Hadji Mohammad Ajul town in Basilan early Wednesday. Galvez said the firearms that Jamiri’s group turned in were 10 high-powered firearms, including M16 and M14 rifles; 40 assorted ammunition magazines, 651 pieces of live ammunition, an MK52 fragmentati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Malaysia, Indonesia, Philippines start joint air patrol in Sulu Sea - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/12/malaysia-indonesia-philippines-start-air-patrol-sulu-sea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENkoma14AmAe_IZH1fxCyX4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 08:51:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/12/malaysia-indonesia-philippines-start-air-patrol-sulu-sea/" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia, Indonesia, Philippines start joint air patrol in Sulu Sea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SHAH ALAM: The Trilateral Air Patrol (TAP) involving Malaysia, Indonesia and the Philippines has officially taken off. Defence Minister Datuk Seri Hishammuddin Hussein was joined by his Indonesia and Philippines counterparts, Ryamizard Ryacudu and Delfin Negrillo Lorenzana, for the launch at the Subang airbase Thursday. "The TAP, which serves as the second component of the Trilateral Cooperative Arrangement (TCA), will be conducted jointly with aircrew from all three countries on board the aircraft (on patrol). "The joint TAP will adopt a continuous monthly rotation," said Hishamuddin, addi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>