<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>China–Pakistan Economic Corridor - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRjk0Tlc1bmNSSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:46:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Why attacks on Chinese interests in Pakistan will continue - South China Morning Post</title><link>https://www.scmp.com/week-asia/opinion/article/2175238/attacks-chinese-nationals-and-interests-pakistan-are-likely</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH-ElJiGhUdIyFr2tDrapoMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowief2CjCJ2dUCMNvwrAU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.scmp.com/week-asia/opinion/article/2175238/attacks-chinese-nationals-and-interests-pakistan-are-likely" target="_blank"&gt;Why attacks on Chinese interests in Pakistan will continue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;South China Morning Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baloch separatists view Chinese investment, including the US$62b China-Pakistan Economic Corridor, as exploitation of local resources Pakistan's support for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.scmp.com">South China Morning Post</source></item><item><title>Chinese consulate attacked in Karachi: Incident is a manifestation of Baloch frustration on poor... - Firstpost</title><link>https://www.firstpost.com/world/chinese-consulate-attacked-in-karachi-incident-is-a-manifestation-of-baloch-frustration-on-poor-dividends-of-cpec-5614611.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI7nSNh1Qrmkz2XjbJxymBEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow5v6PATDrwA8w_uke</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.firstpost.com/world/chinese-consulate-attacked-in-karachi-incident-is-a-manifestation-of-baloch-frustration-on-poor-dividends-of-cpec-5614611.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese consulate attacked in Karachi: Incident is a manifestation of Baloch frustration on poor...&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Firstpost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the morning of Friday, 23 November, 2018 three gunmen attacked the Consulate of the People's Republic of China (PRC) at Karachi. In an hour-long gun ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.firstpost.com">Firstpost</source></item><item><title>Beijing has ‘oversold benefits’ of US$62 billion infrastructure link - South China Morning Post</title><link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/2174757/beijing-has-oversold-benefits-us62-billion-china-pakistan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECM7oGo_UFoDLo8HDyC6iUEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowief2CjCJ2dUCMKqaxwU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/2174757/beijing-has-oversold-benefits-us62-billion-china-pakistan" target="_blank"&gt;Beijing has ‘oversold benefits’ of US$62 billion infrastructure link&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;South China Morning Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The economic and energy security benefits of a Beijing-funded investment scheme in Pakistan have been overestimated, and China's lack of transparency about ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.scmp.com">South China Morning Post</source></item><item><title>Renault Trucks ventures into Pakistan, anticipates higher demand from CPEC - The Express Tribune</title><link>https://tribune.com.pk/story/1848346/2-renault-trucks-ventures-pakistan-anticipates-higher-demand-cpec/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiZ2h0dHBzOi8vdHJpYnVuZS5jb20ucGsvc3RvcnkvMTg0ODM0Ni8yLXJlbmF1bHQtdHJ1Y2tzLXZlbnR1cmVzLXBha2lzdGFuLWFudGljaXBhdGVzLWhpZ2hlci1kZW1hbmQtY3BlYy_SAbQBaHR0cHM6Ly90cmlidW5lLWNvbS1way5jZG4uYW1wcHJvamVjdC5vcmcvdi9zL3RyaWJ1bmUuY29tLnBrL3N0b3J5LzE4NDgzNDYvMi1yZW5hdWx0LXRydWNrcy12ZW50dXJlcy1wYWtpc3Rhbi1hbnRpY2lwYXRlcy1oaWdoZXItZGVtYW5kLWNwZWMvP2FtcD0xJmFtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://tribune.com.pk/story/1848346/2-renault-trucks-ventures-pakistan-anticipates-higher-demand-cpec/" target="_blank"&gt;Renault Trucks ventures into Pakistan, anticipates higher demand from CPEC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Express Tribune&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KARACHI : Renault Trucks, in partnership with Ghandhara Nissan Limited (GNL), introduced the full range of its vehicles to Pakistan's market, keeping in view ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://tribune.com.pk">The Express Tribune</source></item><item><title>What it means when countries sign onto China's Belt and Road - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-01/china-belt-and-road-what-does-it-mean-when-countries-sign-on/10562374</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMGrcc6RwUF-mUUge2NzmI0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 19:08:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-01/china-belt-and-road-what-does-it-mean-when-countries-sign-on/10562374" target="_blank"&gt;What it means when countries sign onto China's Belt and Road&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Michael Walsh More and more countries are choosing to ink agreements with China on its trillion dollar Belt and Road initiative, a global infrastructure push aiming to recreate the glory days of China's ancient Silk Road trade routes. Chinese state media says more than 100 countries and international organisations have signed Belt and Road cooperation agreements since 2013. The Victorian Government, the Philippines, Vanuatu and Tonga are some of the most recent recruits. But what are governments actually agreeing to when they choose to sign on Beijing's dotted line? Copies of the agreeme...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Malaysia, India, And IMF Could Spoil China's CPEC And Malaysia Mega-projects - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2018/11/19/malaysia-india-and-imf-could-spoil-chinas-cpec-and-malaysia-mega-projects/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAq3_eYFXCCYFhRgGkdSPtgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2018/11/19/malaysia-india-and-imf-could-spoil-chinas-cpec-and-malaysia-mega-projects/" target="_blank"&gt;Malaysia, India, And IMF Could Spoil China's CPEC And Malaysia Mega-projects&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malaysia, India, and IMF could spoil two of China’s mega-projects in the Indian Ocean — the China-Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC) and the Forest City. Investors should follow the growing controversy on both projects closely. It could add to the turbulence which has been shaking the markets of the region. CPEC is a mega-project for both China and its local partner, the Pakistani government. For China, CPEC is the western route to Middle East oil, and to Africa, rich in natural resources. It also serves Beijing’s strategic ambition to encircle India. And that makes Pakistan a natural ally. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Separatist rebels storm China's consulate in Pakistan, two policemen killed - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHFFMtUxdfuqBSr6UonkM4gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 10:20:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three suicide attackers tried to storm the Chinese consulate in Karachi today, but were killed before they could get into the building, the city's police chief said. At least two police officers were killed in the attack, which was claimed by the Baloch Liberation Army (BLA), a separatist insurgent group that opposes Chinese projects in the resource-rich southwestern province of Baluchistan. All Chinese staff at the consulate were safe, Pakistani Foreign Minister Shah Mahmood Qureshi and China's Foreign Ministry said. The assault was the most prominent attack in Pakistan against China, a ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chinese consulate attack: Four killed in thwarted raid in Karachi - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/asia/karachi-chinese-consulate-attack-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOM8FRV0e6KP_rtpWRabtXUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:13:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/asia/karachi-chinese-consulate-attack-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Chinese consulate attack: Four killed in thwarted raid in Karachi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Armed attackers attempted to storm the Chinese consulate in the Pakistani city of Karachi on Friday morning, killing four people, authorities said. Three attackers also were killed in the assault on the consulate in the city's high-security red zone, according to a Pakistani foreign ministry spokesman. The Baloch Liberation Army, a separatist group, claimed responsibility in a tweet that included a photo of three unidentified men and the message: "Karachi: Fidayeen of BLA attacked the Chinese embassy in Karachi." "Fidayeen" is an Arabic term that loosely translates as "one who sacrifices hi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>4 killed in brazen attack at Chinese consulate in Pakistan - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/21ddd4d9863f4f7995d22043ebc3e2a8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOdHWwXqLox2eV1Es9cBaYoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 18:07:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/21ddd4d9863f4f7995d22043ebc3e2a8" target="_blank"&gt;4 killed in brazen attack at Chinese consulate in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KARACHI, Pakistan (AP) — Armed separatists stormed the Chinese Consulate in Pakistan's southern port city of Karachi on Friday, triggering an intense hour-long shootout during which two Pakistani civilians, two police officers and all three assailants were killed, including one who was wearing a suicide vest, Pakistani officials said. The brazen assault, claimed by a militant group from the southwestern province of Baluchistan, reflected the separatists' attempt to strike at the heart of Pakistan's close ties with major ally China, which has invested heavily into road and transportation pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Seven killed as gunmen attack Chinese consulate in Pakistan - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/874472f8-eeea-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHXCGkOltvP3p2fDEg81VJkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 14:19:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/874472f8-eeea-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Seven killed as gunmen attack Chinese consulate in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gunmen stormed the Chinese consulate in Pakistan’s southern port city of Karachi on Friday, sparking a shootout that claimed the lives of seven people, including two police officers. The attack on the consulate prompted a demand from China that “the Pakistani side take practical measures to protect the safety of Chinese institutions in Pakistan”. The firefight broke out just after the consulate had opened. Two Pakistani civilians — a father and son who were applying for visas — died in the crossfire. Three attackers were killed. Authorities said about 21 Chinese citizens were inside the con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Gunmen attack Chinese consulate in Karachi - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/shots-heard-china-consulate-pakistan-karachi-181123051817209.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFrAgo_wv-ww0A3MrNjAiEQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 09:54:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/shots-heard-china-consulate-pakistan-karachi-181123051817209.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen attack Chinese consulate in Karachi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamabad, Pakistan - Armed attackers have killed two policemen as they stormed the Chinese consulate in the southern Pakistani city of Karachi, security officials say, in a raid claimed by ethnic Baloch separatists. Security forces killed all three attackers and secured the building shortly after the raid was launched on Friday morning, Pakistan's military said in a statement. No Chinese citizens or Pakistani civilians were killed, security officials said. "All of our Chinese friends and officials who work at the consulate, 21 in total, all of them are safe and they have been shifted to a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>CPEC: China And Pakistan Miscalculated Corruption -- And India - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/05/14/cpec-china-and-pakistan-miscalculated-corruption-and-india/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOLEuU2aMLIZOA44a-q6BX8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 18:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/05/14/cpec-china-and-pakistan-miscalculated-corruption-and-india/" target="_blank"&gt;CPEC: China And Pakistan Miscalculated Corruption -- And India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AFP PHOTO / dominique faget (Photo credit should read DOMINIQUE FAGET/AFP/Getty Images) A transparency commission and a name change won’t smooth the ride on the China-Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC), which is beginning to look like a “sand castle.” Investors should follow the developments surrounding the project closely, as they threaten to throw cold water on the markets of the region. Especially Pakistan’s hot market. CPEC is a gamble for both Pakistan and China. For Pakistan it’s a big infrastructure project, which could help the country make a big step forward, from emerging to a mat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Braving security fears, Chinese seek 'Silk Road' riches in Pakistan - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/08/28/braving-security-fears-chinese-seek-silk-road-riches-in-pakistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBw2MM5iruhq_WL21yAjPnoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 03:14:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/08/28/braving-security-fears-chinese-seek-silk-road-riches-in-pakistan/" target="_blank"&gt;Braving security fears, Chinese seek 'Silk Road' riches in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LAHORE, Pakistan/SHANGHAI (Reuters) - Zhang Yang, a businessman from Chongqing in southwest China, is searching online forums for fellow stout-hearted entrepreneurs willing to cast aside security concerns and join him on a scouting mission to Pakistan. Zhang, 48, is one of a growing number of Chinese pioneers sensing an opportunity across the Himalayas in Pakistan, where Beijing has pledged to spend $57 billion on infrastructure projects as part of its "Belt and Road" initiative. Numbering in the thousands, this second wave of Chinese arrivals are following in the wake of workers on Belt an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>CPEC Lifts Pakistan Up In World Competitiveness Rankings - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/09/28/cpec-lifts-pakistan-up-in-world-competitiveness-rankings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDOIGTqtuYAjOXeyX8pwI1oqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 00:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/09/28/cpec-lifts-pakistan-up-in-world-competitiveness-rankings/" target="_blank"&gt;CPEC Lifts Pakistan Up In World Competitiveness Rankings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shutterstock The China-Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC) is still a work in progress, but it has already helped Pakistan’s economy climb several notches on the global competitiveness scale. That’s according to a just published World Economic Forum Report (WEFR), which placed Pakistan 115th out of the 137 countries ranked. While this ranking is still low compared to neighboring countries, it’s a big improvement from the 122th position the country occupied last year, and the 133th position back in 2014—see tables. Competitiveness Ranking 2017-18 Country Ranking Pakistan 115 India 40 Malaysia ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Ten gunned down near China 'Belt and Road' projects in Pakistan - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/13/ten-gunned-down-near-china-belt-and-road-projects-in-pakistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECwRwKFhgkOtQTZlED01bNcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 09:40:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/13/ten-gunned-down-near-china-belt-and-road-projects-in-pakistan/" target="_blank"&gt;Ten gunned down near China 'Belt and Road' projects in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;QUETTA, Pakistan (Reuters) - Ten labourers were gunned down in southwestern Pakistan on Saturday while working on link roads to connect outlying towns to the country's $57-billion Chinese "Belt and Road" initiative, security officials confirmed. The attack on the Pakistani labourers took place some 20 kilometres from the emerging port city of Gwadar in Baluchistan province that forms the southern hub of the China-Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC). "All the labourers were shot at close range," said senior levies official Muhammad Zareef, adding that the shooters were travelling on a motorcyc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>CPEC Will Take Pakistan To A Place It Doesn't Want To Be - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/06/27/cpec-will-take-pakistan-to-a-place-it-doesnt-want-to-be/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFIZszHL6Rvz6M_1MwcSWs8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/06/27/cpec-will-take-pakistan-to-a-place-it-doesnt-want-to-be/" target="_blank"&gt;CPEC Will Take Pakistan To A Place It Doesn't Want To Be&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AFP PHOTO / BANARAS KHAN (Photo credit should read BANARAS KHAN/AFP/Getty Images) The China Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC) will take Pakistan back to a place it doesn’t want to be: knocking on the door of the IMF, as it did back in 2001. With a big difference this time around – the door may not be open. CPEC will do a lot of great things for Pakistan and its genuine partner, China. For Pakistan, it’s a major infrastructure project which will help the country make a big step forward, from an emerging to a mature economy, creating a lot of jobs in the process. For China, CPEC is the wester...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>China Trying to Extend Belt Plan to Afghanistan to Expand Influence - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/china-trying-to-extend-belt-plan-to-afghanistan/3842278.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBQsDLOp1OaWA-NGzD8qkfwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 14:07:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/china-trying-to-extend-belt-plan-to-afghanistan/3842278.html" target="_blank"&gt;China Trying to Extend Belt Plan to Afghanistan to Expand Influence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China is extending its Belt and Road Initiative (BRI) to troubled Afghanistan, causing analysts to wonder if Beijing is trying to expand its role in the Middle East and also putting itself at the center of the international battle against terrorism. China's connectivity program involves extending the China Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC), which is part of BRI, to Afghanistan, and then stretching the "belt" to its neighbors -Tajikistan, Turkmenistan and Iran. Reseacher Ahmad Bilal Khalil, with the Center for Strategic and Regional Studies in Kabul, who is in close touch with the Afghan gov...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan: A slice of China in Islamabad - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/08/pakistan-slice-china-islamabad-170830081303813.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGFZP1pVDvyOUudl_ANZiWwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 07:35:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/08/pakistan-slice-china-islamabad-170830081303813.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan: A slice of China in Islamabad&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamabad, Pakistan - Sitting in his open-air kitchen in the heart of a busy shopping centre in Pakistan's capital Islamabad, Zhang Yan Xu does not seem to have a care in the world. The tall, broad-shouldered chef seems a genial sort, who exults in his inability to communicate with his customers. "No English," he says, smiling broadly. "No Urdu." Behind him, his wife looks up briefly from the chopping board, before getting back to the serious business of rolling and folding fresh dumplings for the customers downstairs. The Xus work at Hong Du Ramen, the latest in a glut of Chinese restauran...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Pakistan eyes 2018 start for China-funded mega dam opposed by India - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/06/13/pakistan-eyes-2018-start-for-chinafunded-mega-dam-opposed-by-india/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGRRWwxuCti_1D0rtuqhqg8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 13:17:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/06/13/pakistan-eyes-2018-start-for-chinafunded-mega-dam-opposed-by-india/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan eyes 2018 start for China-funded mega dam opposed by India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISLAMABAD (Reuters) - Pakistan expects China to fund a long-delayed Indus river mega dam project in Gilgit-Baltistan, part of disputed Kashmir, with work beginning next year, Planning Minister Ahsan Iqbal said in an interview. Pakistan has been keen for years to build a cascade of mega dams along the Indus flowing down from the Himalayas, but has struggled to raise money from international institutions amid opposition from its nuclear-armed neighbour India. Those ambitions have been revived by China's Belt and Road infrastructure plans for Pakistan, a key cog in Beijing's creation of a mode...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>China condemns couple’s kidnapping in Pakistan - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/05/25/china-condemns-couple-kidnapping-in-pakistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEt-ZHUEZe8HCISlGR49u3oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 10:18:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/05/25/china-condemns-couple-kidnapping-in-pakistan/" target="_blank"&gt;China condemns couple’s kidnapping in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING: China condemned on Thursday the armed kidnapping of a Chinese couple in Pakistan, after the abduction raised safety concerns for Beijing’s multi-billion dollar investments in the country. “The Chinese government attaches high importance to the safety of Chinese citizens overseas,” foreign ministry spokesman Lu Kang said during a regular press briefing. “We condemn all forms of kidnapping activities,” Lu said, adding that the government was working closely with Pakistani authorities to ensure their release. The abduction happened Wednesday afternoon in Quetta, the capital of the sou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>What the World’s Emptiest International Airport Says About China’s Influence - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/09/13/magazine/what-the-worlds-emptiest-international-airport-says-about-chinas-influence.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKlZw52tmmt_zwHD-dj7B5sqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 09:00:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/09/13/magazine/what-the-worlds-emptiest-international-airport-says-about-chinas-influence.html" target="_blank"&gt;What the World’s Emptiest International Airport Says About China’s Influence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese projects all over the world can create debt traps for the countries they’re in — and perhaps also trap China on the road to empire.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Police office targeted in deadly Quetta suicide blast - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/pakistan-police-office-struck-deadly-quetta-blast-170623043059409.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjzImMjvTicrWbTKmyypgYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 11:03:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/pakistan-police-office-struck-deadly-quetta-blast-170623043059409.html" target="_blank"&gt;Police office targeted in deadly Quetta suicide blast&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamabad, Pakistan - At least 12 people have been killed and 14 wounded in a suicide car bomb attack near the provincial police chief’s office in the southwestern Pakistani city of Quetta, police officials told Al Jazeera. The explosion on Friday morning targeted a police checkpost near a complex that is housing the Balochistan police chief's office, local police officer Muhammad Akbar said. At least six police officers were among those killed, Ali Mardan, a senior police officer, told Al Jazeera. Initial reports indicated a vehicle approached the checkpost and explosives were set off when...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>China tells U.S. that Pakistan's security concerns must be respected - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-pakistan-china-idUSKCN1B408B</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMpyQpfIr3QsIfuawoSaAbYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 03:37:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-pakistan-china-idUSKCN1B408B" target="_blank"&gt;China tells U.S. that Pakistan's security concerns must be respected&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (Reuters) - The United States must value Pakistan's role in Afghanistan and respect its security concerns, China's top diplomat Yang Jiechi told U.S. Secretary of State Rex Tillerson in a phone call, according to Chinese state media. China's Foreign Ministry defended its ally Pakistan earlier this week after President Donald Trump said the United States could no longer be silent about militants using safe havens on Pakistani soil. On Monday, Trump committed the United States to an open-ended conflict in Afghanistan, signaling he would send more troops to America's longest war and vo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Suspected Pakistani militants gun down three workers on China 'Silk Road' project - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/19/suspected-pakistani-militants-gun-down-three-workers-on-china-silk-road-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcblq8EKJNQoXSqZ4u6srkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 12:42:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/19/suspected-pakistani-militants-gun-down-three-workers-on-china-silk-road-project/" target="_blank"&gt;Suspected Pakistani militants gun down three workers on China 'Silk Road' project&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;QUETTA, Pakistan (Reuters) - Suspected militants on Friday gunned down three Pakistani workers building a Chinese-funded "Silk Road" highway in the country's southwest, just days after a similar attack killed 10, officials said. There was no immediate claim of responsibility, but previous attacks in Pakistan's province of Baluchistan have been unleashed by separatists who fear the construction projects are a ruse to take over their land. Last week's attacks were claimed by the separatist Baluch Liberation Army (BLA). The men killed on Friday were part of a team working on a major highway li...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Gunmen kill five ethnic Hazara in sectarian attack in southwest Pakistan - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/10/09/gunmen-kill-five-ethnic-hazara-in-sectarian-attack-in-southwest-pakistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEALAKKJMVkwiT9ovFf0v9NEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 08:26:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/10/09/gunmen-kill-five-ethnic-hazara-in-sectarian-attack-in-southwest-pakistan/" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen kill five ethnic Hazara in sectarian attack in southwest Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;QUETTA, Pakistan (Reuters) - Gunmen killed five Shia Muslims from the ethnic Hazara minority in southwest Pakistan on Monday, a police official said, giving details of the second shooting targeting Hazaras in a month. The attack took place in Quetta, where nearly half a million Hazaras have settled since fleeing Afghanistan to escape the violence in their homeland during the past four decades. The attackers opened fire from a motorcycle killing the five men who were travelling in the back of a pick-up truck, on their way to sell vegetables at a market, the official said. "It was a sectarian...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Islamic State says it killed two Chinese teachers kidnapped in Pakistan - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-china-islamic-state-idUSKBN18Z20O</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbmuj-a3gJw_g-eOkNWKG8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 02:09:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-china-islamic-state-idUSKBN18Z20O" target="_blank"&gt;Islamic State says it killed two Chinese teachers kidnapped in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAIRO/QUETTA, Pakistan (Reuters) - Islamic State has killed two Chinese teachers it kidnapped in Pakistan's southwestern Baluchistan province last month, the militant group's Amaq news agency said on Thursday, in a blow to Islamabad's efforts to safeguard Chinese workers. China's Foreign Ministry said it was "gravely concerned" about the report and working to verify the information. Armed men pretending to be policemen kidnapped the two language teachers in the provincial capital, Quetta, on May 24. The kidnapping was a rare security incident involving Chinese nationals in Pakistan, where B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan scrambles to protect China's 'Silk Road' pioneers - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/06/11/pakistan-scrambles-to-protect-chinas-silk-road-pioneers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-0k5OikAx8J4fEIZLWn8kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 11:12:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/06/11/pakistan-scrambles-to-protect-chinas-silk-road-pioneers/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan scrambles to protect China's 'Silk Road' pioneers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISLAMABAD/PESHAWAR, Pakistan (Reuters) - Chastened by the Islamic State's claim to have killed two kidnapped Chinese teachers, Pakistan is beefing up security around Chinese citizens streaming into the country on the back of Beijing's "Belt and Road" infrastructure splurge. China has often urged Pakistan to improve security after pledging around $57 billion (44.72 billion pounds) to build power plants, railways, and roads that will cross the Himalayas to connect western China with Pakistan's Arabian Sea port of Gwadar. Pakistani officials have outlined to Reuters extensive security plans th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Gunmen kill four in sectarian attack in Pakistan - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/09/11/gunmen-kill-four-in-sectarian-attack-in-pakistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEy6BaNVMQw6ClccFGKL-CkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 07:35:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/09/11/gunmen-kill-four-in-sectarian-attack-in-pakistan/" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen kill four in sectarian attack in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;QUETTA, Pakistan (Reuters) - Gunmen in southwestern Pakistan killed four members of a Shi'ite Muslim Hazara family, including a 12-year-old boy, on Sunday, in the latest sectarian attack on the minority community, a senior police official said. Two men on a motorcycle opened fire on a family of eight while they at a filling station some 30 kilometres (19 miles) north of Quetta, the capital of Pakistan's Baluchistan province. Aside from those killed, two others were wounded. Two female members of the family were unscathed, having remained in their vehicle. "This was a sectarian attack," seni...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Tibet Border: Xi Tests Modi - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/07/17/tibet-border-xi-tests-modi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBx4zqugl0jzSqCbIiZ45rwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/07/17/tibet-border-xi-tests-modi/" target="_blank"&gt;Tibet Border: Xi Tests Modi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo credit should read MONEY SHARMA/AFP/Getty Images) China and India are on a collision course lately. At the Tibetan border, that is, where the leaders of the two countries have been testing each other. The two leaders have been upping the game, raising the chances of an “accident” that could lead into an outright war in the region with unpredicted consequences for the economies and the financial markets of the two large emerging economies. Border disputes between India and China are nothing new; and they have been the cause of war before. What’s new is China’s appetite for constructin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>China's Hambantota Deal Is Bad News For Both Pakistan And India - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/08/02/chinas-hambantota-deal-is-bad-news-for-both-pakistan-and-india/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO7RuKqKRSkeZIHObQLAK-0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 07:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/08/02/chinas-hambantota-deal-is-bad-news-for-both-pakistan-and-india/" target="_blank"&gt;China's Hambantota Deal Is Bad News For Both Pakistan And India&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;/ AFP PHOTO / Olga MALTSEVA (Photo credit should read OLGA MALTSEVA/AFP/Getty Images) Sri Lanka’s Hambantota port is officially China’s own port, for 99 years. That’s according to a landmark agreement signed early last week, which gives China Merchants Ports Holdings—an arm of the Chinese government–70 percent stake in the Indian Ocean’s prominent outpost. The Hambantota port expansion begun with loans from China. But when Shri Lanka could not pay back the loans, Beijing converted these loans to equity, in essence turning Sri Lanka into a “semi-colony,” as was the case with China’s own Sout...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>IS Says It Killed 2 Captive Chinese Nationals in Pakistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/islamic-state-says-it-killed-two-captive-chinese-nationals-pakistan/3892553.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTfq2zi_XCmg8kiuM5IMtkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 19:30:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/islamic-state-says-it-killed-two-captive-chinese-nationals-pakistan/3892553.html" target="_blank"&gt;IS Says It Killed 2 Captive Chinese Nationals in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamic State claimed Thursday that it had killed two captive Chinese nationals in southwestern Pakistan. The Chinese language instructors, a man and a woman, were kidnapped at gunpoint two weeks ago from Quetta, the capital of violence-hit Baluchistan province. A second Chinese woman accompanying them escaped the abduction while the gunmen were trying to force them in a vehicle. There had been no claims of responsibility until Thursday, when the Syria-based terrorist group's global media outlet, the Amaq News Agency, announced the executions. A provincial government spokesman, when contact...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Faces Challenges to Curb Militancy to Protect Chinese Investment - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3867404.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGU4D57s6pN-1HJTiL4JqgUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 17:57:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3867404.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Faces Challenges to Curb Militancy to Protect Chinese Investment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;For its proponents, a project to expand its port in Gwadar and link it to China as a way to provide jobs and an economic boost to Balochistan, the country’s poorest province. To get it built and functioning, though, the government needs to undercut a separatist insurgency and a variety of militant groups that have used poverty to fuel the flames of insurgency, analysts say. “If Pakistan is not able to control extremism in Balochistan, how could the government achieve the desired results it is currently portraying?” asked Hasan Askari, a prominent security and military analyst. Gunmen on Wed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sleepy Pakistani Village Rises as China's Gateway to Middle East - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistani-village-gwadar-china-gateway-to-middle-east/3816566.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECYO7UZrXKGKNqT9C3CxNz4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 21:00:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/pakistani-village-gwadar-china-gateway-to-middle-east/3816566.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sleepy Pakistani Village Rises as China's Gateway to Middle East&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the last six months, the skyline over the sleepy fishing city of Gwadar has been transformed by machines that dredge the Arabian Sea and cranes that set up shipping berths in what is projected to become Pakistan’s biggest international port. Infrastructure developments have enabled the hammer-shaped Gwadar peninsula to emerge as the centerpiece of China’s determined effort to shorten its trade route to the Persian Gulf and obtain access to the rich oil reserves there. A mini-“Chinatown” has appeared, with prefabricated living quarters, a canteen and a karaoke center. After hours, the w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>China Tries To Enircle India. It Won't Work - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/05/04/china-tries-to-enircle-india-it-wont-work/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIsYyzcoz-jBkiZemdMFS-EqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 01:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2017/05/04/china-tries-to-enircle-india-it-wont-work/" target="_blank"&gt;China Tries To Enircle India. It Won't Work&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Photo by Sean M. Castellano/U.S. Navy via Getty Images) China’s efforts to encircle India won’t work. That’s the message India and its allies, America and Japan are prepared to send to Beijing in a joint naval exercise. China has an official and an unofficial agenda for the Indian Ocean. The official agenda is to foster trade and economic growth for all countries in the region, from Pakistan to Sri Lanka, to India, and Bangladesh. The unofficial agenda is to encircle India, something investors should keep a close eye on, as it is expected to raise geopolitical risks in the region. Index/Fu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Pakistan: Slain Chinese Couple Preached Christianity Under Guise of Business - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-chinese-christians-islamic-state/3896930.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGhAsAUWFtMpvrg5NlLMu3cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 15:57:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-chinese-christians-islamic-state/3896930.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan: Slain Chinese Couple Preached Christianity Under Guise of Business&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakistan says a Chinese couple recently murdered by suspected Islamic State loyalists in southwestern Baluchistan province were preaching Christianity under the guise of doing business in the country. The slain Chinese nationals were kidnapped at gunpoint late last month from the provincial capital, Quetta. There were no claims of responsibility until Thursday when IS, through its global mouthpiece the Amaq News Agency, claimed executing the hostages. The kidnappers later released video footage showing the bloodied body of the Chinese man, Lee Zing Yang, taking his last breaths. Pakistani ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Gunmen kill four police in Pakistani city of Quetta - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-shooting-idUSKBN19Y143</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELX5yJfBunc4ghdPRu4ebJ4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 11:03:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-shooting-idUSKBN19Y143" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen kill four police in Pakistani city of Quetta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Gul Yousafzai QUETTA, Pakistan (Reuters) - Islamist gunmen on Thursday killed a senior police official and three other policemen guarding him in the Pakistani city of Quetta, police said, in an attack claimed by both the Pakistani Taliban and Islamic State. Superintendent of Police Mubarak Shah, 56, was killed en route to his office when four gunmen riding on motorcycles attacked his vehicle, said city police officer Muhammad Sultan. "The head and upper parts of all the four victims were targeted," said Sultan, adding that one policeman was critically wounded. A faction of the Pakistani ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China Calls Pakistan's CPEC Fastest and Most Effective of BRI Projects - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/china-calls-pakistan-cpec-fastest-and-most-effective-of-bri-projects/3951874.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAEos6tR3_hiB3ZHla34B0sqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 12:45:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/china-calls-pakistan-cpec-fastest-and-most-effective-of-bri-projects/3951874.html" target="_blank"&gt;China Calls Pakistan's CPEC Fastest and Most Effective of BRI Projects&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China says its large economic collaboration program with Pakistan has entered “the stage of early harvest", making it the “fastest and most effective" among all projects in Beijing’s Belt and Road Initiative, or BRI. President Xi Jinping launched the China-Pakistan Economic Corridor, or CPEC, two years ago, during his landmark visit to Islamabad. Cooperation has since cemented decades-old relations between the traditionally close allies. China is investing about $60 billion on a network of roads, railways, fiber optic cables, energy pipelines, industrial clusters and special economic zones...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Beijing in lockdown ahead of ‘New Silk Road’ summit - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/f89060ac-36c7-11e7-bce4-9023f8c0fd2e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB1-gXKiRn2rlXfNd0uTiaIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 05:17:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/f89060ac-36c7-11e7-bce4-9023f8c0fd2e" target="_blank"&gt;Beijing in lockdown ahead of ‘New Silk Road’ summit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beijing is enjoying an unusually long run of clear blue skies thanks to widespread industrial closures ahead of the most important international event hosted by President Xi Jinping. The “New Silk Road” summit has attracted 29 national leaders from four continents and also prompted a nationwide security clampdown, as authorities try to ensure that it proceeds without a hitch. More than 80 other countries, including North and South Korea, are dispatching lower-ranking representatives to the event. On Thursday morning, a number of subway stations near the defence ministry were closed abruptly...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>World's biggest building project aims to make China great again - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/may/12/chinese-president-belt-and-road-initiative</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHEPjg1LtmH8CN-viS68VrUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:25:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/may/12/chinese-president-belt-and-road-initiative" target="_blank"&gt;World's biggest building project aims to make China great again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the Chinese president, Xi Jinping, unveiled what some call the most ambitious development plan in history, Zhou Jun decided almost immediately he should head for the hills. The 45-year-old entrepreneur packed his bags and set off for one of his country’s most staggeringly beautiful corners: a sleepy, high-altitude border outpost called Tashkurgan that - at almost 5,000km (3,100 miles) from Beijing - is the most westerly settlement in China. “I saw a great opportunity to turn this little town into a mid-sized city,” Zhou explained during a tour of ‘Europa Manor’, a garish roadside spa h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>China takes ‘project of the century’ to Pakistan - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/05979e18-2fe4-11e7-9555-23ef563ecf9a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOYY3cDfqy7ECeW7DRR8kjUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 16:52:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/05979e18-2fe4-11e7-9555-23ef563ecf9a" target="_blank"&gt;China takes ‘project of the century’ to Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The signs in the lobby of the Pearl Continental Hotel in Lahore could hardly be more gushing. “Long live Pak-China Friendship,” they read, advertising a conference to promote the China-Pakistan Economic Corridor. The banners add: “Our friendship is higher than the Himalayas and deeper than the deepest sea in the world, and sweeter than honey.” That high, deep and sweet friendship is also worth a lot of money. The CPEC scheme, which will link western China to the Arabian Sea through Pakistan, is a cornerstone of the ambitious “One Belt, One Road”, a 65-nation strong initiative that aims to c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Isis says it killed 2 Chinese nationals in Pakistan - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/fa207068-4cd1-11e7-919a-1e14ce4af89b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDrfHWGOM16rfcfVaMvCUnUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 09:10:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/fa207068-4cd1-11e7-919a-1e14ce4af89b" target="_blank"&gt;Isis says it killed 2 Chinese nationals in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beijing has said it is “highly concerned” about a claim by Isis to have killed two Chinese teachers in the Baluchistan province of Pakistan, which is at the heart of a $55bn-plus infrastructure programme being developed by the two countries. Amaq, the Isis news agency, made the claim two weeks after the couple were kidnapped by armed men pretending to be policemen. Pakistan launched a raid on Isis positions last week in the hunt for the Chinese nationals, which officials said succeeded in killing several militant commanders but failed to find the pair. China said on Friday it had been told ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Pakistani Official Confirms Captive Chinese Nationals Are Dead - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-confirm-chinese-nationals-dead/3893445.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELPUMXfrZrn_aBx-Rm0cBboqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 09:20:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-confirm-chinese-nationals-dead/3893445.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani Official Confirms Captive Chinese Nationals Are Dead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamic State has released a video showing the bloodied body of a captive Chinese national the terrorist group claimed to have killed along with his female partner in southwestern Pakistan. A provincial government official confirmed to VOA that the man who seems to be taking his last breaths in the video is one of the two Chinese kidnapped last month from Quetta, capital of Baluchistan province. Mastung, Pakistan The official spoke on condition of anonymity because he said that authorities have not yet found the bodies of the Chinese nationals, and he would like to abstain from making any o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistani politician shot dead in Baluchistan province - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/07/06/pakistani-politician-shot-dead-in-baluchistan-province/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC6UKhyhatpzU3KuM8UPV4QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 11:37:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/07/06/pakistani-politician-shot-dead-in-baluchistan-province/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani politician shot dead in Baluchistan province&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;QUETTA, Pakistan (Reuters) - Gunmen on Thursday shot and killed a Pakistani regional political party leader in the city of Quetta, police said, the latest violence in the southwestern province of Baluchistan. Malik Naveed, 38, and his guard, Mohammad Zareef, 42, died en route to hospital after gunmen riding two motorcycles attacked his car shortly after he had left his home, Superintendent of Police Ashraf Jattak said. One of Naveed's relatives, who was with him in the car, was wounded. Naveed is one of the leaders of the opposition Baluchistan National Party, which advocates for more funds...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Karachi railway revival faces shanty town delay - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-railway-idUSKCN1AW1UO</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEPkPBM5k_eiwcmSe3fIwOQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 15:08:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-railway-idUSKCN1AW1UO" target="_blank"&gt;Karachi railway revival faces shanty town delay&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KARACHI, Pakistan (Reuters) - After many false starts, plans to resurrect a railway in Pakistan's teeming metropolis of Karachi are moving ahead with the help of Chinese cash. Not everyone is happy. The Chinese-funded $2 billion project to revive Karachi Circular Railways (KRC), nearly two decades since it was shut down, has been touted as a way to ease pollution and chronic congestion in the port city of 20 million people. It is also viewed with suspicion by Pakistanis who have built homes and businesses along the 43-km route connecting Karachi's sprawling suburbs with the industrial and c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Attack on Security Forces' Convoy in Pakistan Kills 3 Soldiers - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/attack-security-forces-convoy-pakistan-kills-three-soldiers/4014681.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPNy1YNQV0ZWYW05z_0FF0kqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 18:13:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/attack-security-forces-convoy-pakistan-kills-three-soldiers/4014681.html" target="_blank"&gt;Attack on Security Forces' Convoy in Pakistan Kills 3 Soldiers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unknown gunmen in southwestern Pakistan ambushed a security forces' convoy, killing at least three soldiers and injuring three others Monday. Local authorities said the convoy of the paramilitary Frontier Corps was returning from a counterinsurgency operation when it was attacked in the remote Panjgur district of Baluchistan province. There were no immediate claims of responsibility for the deadly assault. Prime Minister Shahid Khaqan Abbasi has "strongly" condemned the attack and "expressed grief over loss of precious lives of [Frontier Corps] officials," his office said in a statement. Pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>China, Russia, India Intensify Role in Afghanistan to Fight Homegrown Militants - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/china-russia-india-afghanistan-homegrown-militants/4030083.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPZvNbFilJPKqI1XkYCMK-gqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 08:35:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/china-russia-india-afghanistan-homegrown-militants/4030083.html" target="_blank"&gt;China, Russia, India Intensify Role in Afghanistan to Fight Homegrown Militants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A decision by the BRICS nations to name and denounce specific terrorist organizations in Afghanistan, Pakistan and elsewhere is sparking debate among academics and analysts in China. Earlier this month, the group, comprised of Brazil, Russia, India, China and South Africa, extended their support to Kabul’s counterterrorism efforts during a meeting in China. The move caused some nervousness in Islamabad, forcing Foreign Minister Khawaja Asif to first visit Beijing and then fly to Tehran, canvassing support for his country. This was the first time China had publicly denounced Pakistan-based t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>The geostrategic economics of One Belt, One Road - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/fd0eaf5a-3ecc-11e7-9d56-25f963e998b2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB6u9IGnnIfJFq9j-4gY9vcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 11:17:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/fd0eaf5a-3ecc-11e7-9d56-25f963e998b2" target="_blank"&gt;The geostrategic economics of One Belt, One Road&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In discussing China’s ambitious One Belt, One Road infrastructure project last week, we argued that the rest of the world must see it for what it is: not simply an investment plan to be assessed on conventional economic grounds but an attempt at shaping the geostrategic structure of the global economy in future decades. To better understand why, it is important to have a sense of how the economic relationship created by a successful Belt and Road initiative would add up to much more than the sum of their its parts. (Whether it could be successful is an important question, too. Christopher B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Pakistani separatists kill two naval officers in troubled Baluchistan - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-militants-idUSKBN19B0N3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHZ1Pf7ZWT7eitoS4SmJ34kqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 07:27:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-militants-idUSKBN19B0N3" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistani separatists kill two naval officers in troubled Baluchistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Gul Yousafzai QUETTA, Pakistan (Reuters) - Pakistani separatists riding motorcycles killed two naval officers in the restive southwestern province of Baluchistan, police officials said on Tuesday, near the site of a major Chinese-funded project. Senior police officer Abdul Hafeez Baloch said four armed men on Monday attacked a vehicle taking food to a naval base in the costal town of Jewani, about 80 km (50 miles) west of the port city of Gwadar. "One officer died on the spot while another succumbed while being moved to hospital," Baloch said, adding that three officers were wounded in t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>China &amp; Portugal step up cooperation on New Silk Road initiative - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/business/396218-china-portugal-cooperation-belt-road/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOOfHm9tiF5d7mfPvHMKpGEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwroQo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:27:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/business/396218-china-portugal-cooperation-belt-road/" target="_blank"&gt;China &amp; Portugal step up cooperation on New Silk Road initiative&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lisbon and Beijing are to broaden links as part of the Belt and Road Initiative which is bringing together dozens of countries in a global infrastructure project, Xinhua reports Thursday. Joining forces will give impetus to the initiative, as Portugal can help drive the Belt and Road project due to its geographic location, China's top legislator Zhang Dejiang said during a three-day visit to Lisbon. He went on to say that Beijing hopes a partnership with Portugal to be a win-win situation for the project. Portugal is actively supporting the plans according to Prime Minister Antonio Costa as...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>China vows maximum effort to recover kidnapped citizens in Pakistan - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/25/china-vows-maximum-effort-to-recover-kidnapped-citizens-in-pakistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJz83SmVOp9xccTqzBvh5bEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 10:56:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/25/china-vows-maximum-effort-to-recover-kidnapped-citizens-in-pakistan/" target="_blank"&gt;China vows maximum effort to recover kidnapped citizens in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (Reuters) - China said on Thursday it will do all it can to ensure the safe return of two citizens kidnapped in Pakistan and it promised new measures to protect Chinese people and companies working in the country, an important link on its Silk Road infrastructure plan. Gunmen pretending to be policemen kidnapped two Chinese language teachers in the Pakistani city of Quetta, in the violence-plagued province of Baluchistan, on Wednesday. "China will continue to make maximal efforts alongside Pakistan to strive for the safe return of the kidnapped individuals as soon as possible,” fore...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Two Chinese nationals kidnapped in Pakistan - provincial spokesman - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/24/two-chinese-nationals-kidnapped-in-pakistan--provincial-spokesman/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPAN5EeOrwQKC-nEzDRYCBIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 10:24:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/24/two-chinese-nationals-kidnapped-in-pakistan--provincial-spokesman/" target="_blank"&gt;Two Chinese nationals kidnapped in Pakistan - provincial spokesman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISLAMABAD (Reuters) - Two Chinese nationals working in Pakistan were kidnapped on Wednesday in the city of Quetta, a provincial government spokesman said, in the latest attack on workers from China likely to raise concern about its investment plans. "A Chinese couple has been kidnapped and their personal guard was injured during the incident," Anwar ul Haq Kakar, a spokesman for Baluchistan province, of which Quetta is capital, told Reuters. China's ambassador to Pakistan and other officials have urged Islamabad to improve security, especially in Baluchistan, where China is building a new p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>India's 'new Silk Road' snub highlights gulf with China - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/21/indias-new-silk-road-snub-highlights-gulf-with-china/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO7u2hniJA4XCxTl8XOElekqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 02:38:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/21/indias-new-silk-road-snub-highlights-gulf-with-china/" target="_blank"&gt;India's 'new Silk Road' snub highlights gulf with China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW DELHI (Reuters) - China invited Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi and six cabinet colleagues to its "new Silk Road" summit this month, even offering to rename a flagship Pakistani project running through disputed territory to persuade them to attend, a top official in Modi's ruling group and diplomats said. But New Delhi rebuffed Beijing's diplomatic push, incensed that a key project in its massive initiative to open land and sea corridors linking China with the rest of Asia and beyond runs through Pakistani controlled Kashmir. (GRAPHIC-China-Pakistan Economic Corridor http://tmsnrt.r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakistan says Chinese killed by Islamic State were preachers - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-china-idUSKBN1931DY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO1mGn9yVEe1W0PPDSd_6S0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:35:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-china-idUSKBN1931DY" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan says Chinese killed by Islamic State were preachers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Drazen Jorgic ISLAMABAD (Reuters) - Pakistan identified on Monday two Chinese nationals recently abducted and killed by the Islamic State and, in a new twist, said the two were preachers who had posed as business people to enter the country. The interior ministry named the two as Lee Zing Yang, 24, and Meng Li Si, 26, and said their violation of visa rules had contributed to their abductions. Previously officials said they were Chinese-language teachers. The two were abducted by armed men pretending to be policemen on May 24 in Quetta, the provincial capital of Baluchistan province. Last...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Railway Revival Clashes With Shanty Towns - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-railway-revival-clashes-with-shanty-towns/3989140.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBx9zcYQsISGHOTZQKiB9OoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwtOetBQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 01:46:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-railway-revival-clashes-with-shanty-towns/3989140.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Railway Revival Clashes With Shanty Towns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After many false starts, plans to resurrect a railway in Pakistan’s teeming metropolis of Karachi are moving ahead with the help of Chinese cash. Not everyone is happy. The Chinese-funded $2 billion project to revive Karachi Circular Railways (KRC), nearly two decades since it was shut down, has been touted as a way to ease pollution and chronic congestion in the port city of 20 million people. Women walk through a plot of land belonging to Pakistan Railways, outside the abandoned Nazimabad station in Karachi, Pakistan, May 23, 2017. Nazimabad station was once a stop along the Karachi Circu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>China’s money is a mixed blessing for Pakistan - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/543a4fb6-29ae-11e7-bc4b-5528796fe35c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDOHJDl-v8JBwRLP60Wm7WcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwgtt6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 17:21:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/543a4fb6-29ae-11e7-bc4b-5528796fe35c" target="_blank"&gt;China’s money is a mixed blessing for Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chinese can be forgiven for seeking out a reliable ally on their border. With Russia to the north, rival India to the south, an increasingly defiant North Korea to the east and Afghanistan in the throes of turmoil to the west, good neighbours are in short supply. That Pakistan comes closest to what the Chinese like to call an “all weather friend” shows how poor China’s options are. It is an odd relationship that has been decades in the making. China is consolidating it with billions of dollars in infrastructure and energy investment, military exports and bailout loans to prop up the Pak...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Pakistan Envoy Urges 'Accurate Appreciation' of Actions against Terrorism - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-defiant-us-ponders-south-asia-strategy/3962805.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOQDHuGel52bZUxHJIuqT3cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 19:00:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/pakistan-defiant-us-ponders-south-asia-strategy/3962805.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan Envoy Urges 'Accurate Appreciation' of Actions against Terrorism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Days after the Pentagon announced it is withholding $50 million intended for Pakistan as part of its Coalition Support Fund, the South Asian country’s ambassador told an audience in Washington that Pakistan remains determined to fight terrorism. “All that Pakistan has done in the fight against terrorism has not been sufficiently factored” into Pentagon’s decision, Ambassador Aizaz Ahmad Chaudhry lamented during a discussion at the Washington office of the London-based International Institute for Strategic Studies. Chaudhry said Pakistan considers it is in its own interest to fight terrorism...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Gunmen in Pakistan kill four Shi'ites in suspected sectarian attack - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/07/19/gunmen-in-pakistan-kill-four-shiites-in-suspected-sectarian-attack/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELMJLnKN8KvM7V8VaWwEkTUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 09:36:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/07/19/gunmen-in-pakistan-kill-four-shiites-in-suspected-sectarian-attack/" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen in Pakistan kill four Shi'ites in suspected sectarian attack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;QUETTA, Pakistan (Reuters) - Gunmen on Wednesday shot dead four members of the Shi'ite Muslim minority in Pakistan's southwestern province of Baluchistan, officials said, in what police suspect was a sectarian attack. Recent violence in Baluchistan has fuelled concern about security for projects in the $57-billion (£43.8 billion) China Pakistan Economic Corridor, a transport and energy link planned to run from western China to Pakistan's southern deep-water port of Gwadar. Provincial Home Minister Sarfraz Bugti said three men and a woman from the Hazara community were travelling to the sout...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Quetta: Gunmen kill Hazara Shia Muslim family members - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/gunmen-kill-sectarian-attack-pakistan-170911073842008.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIfHTycjxkhJ5VYhLKjZLHQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 09:50:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/09/gunmen-kill-sectarian-attack-pakistan-170911073842008.html" target="_blank"&gt;Quetta: Gunmen kill Hazara Shia Muslim family members&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gunmen in southwestern Pakistan killed four members of a Shia Muslim Hazara family, in the latest apparent sectarian attack on the minority community, officials said. Two men on a motorcycle opened fire on a family of eight while they were at a filling station some 30km north of Quetta, the capital of Pakistan's Balochistan province, late on Sunday. Aside from those killed, two others were wounded. Two female members of the family were unscathed, having remained in their vehicle. "This was a sectarian attack," senior police officer Tanveer Shah told the Reuters news agency, adding that no g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Holy month blackouts pile pressure on Nawaz Sharif - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/bee89ccc-4458-11e7-8519-9f94ee97d996</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEzIDjhUHziV3Kt8fHPp7UUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 16:00:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/bee89ccc-4458-11e7-8519-9f94ee97d996" target="_blank"&gt;Holy month blackouts pile pressure on Nawaz Sharif&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nawaz Sharif has ordered power companies not to cut electricity supplies in the hours before or after the daily Ramadan fast, as outages in the first few days of the Muslim holy month threaten to embroil Pakistan’s prime minister in a political crisis. As the fasting period began on Sunday, residents of Karachi, the country’s largest city, were unexpectedly plunged into darkness. The national distribution company blamed a line fault that caused two power stations to fail. But the outage has highlighted the fragility of Pakistan’s electricity network — a problem that threatens to undermine t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Assailants Gun Down at Least 10 in Pakistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/assailants-kill-construction-workers-in-pakistan/3850457.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAqTcZjthNl_RrsC-QQ17SYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 09:45:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/assailants-kill-construction-workers-in-pakistan/3850457.html" target="_blank"&gt;Assailants Gun Down at Least 10 in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unknown gunmen shot dead at least 10 construction workers and wounded several others Saturday in southwestern Pakistan, police said. The victims were building a road in the port city of Gwadar when assailants on motorbikes fired at them and fled the scene. There was no immediate claim of responsibility for the violence. Suicide bombing The attack happened a day after an Islamic State suicide bomber killed at least 25 people and wounded 40 others in the province of Baluchistan where Gwadar is located. Pakistani security officials stand guard at the site of a suicide bombing which killed doze...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Local, global security firms in race along China's 'Silk Road' - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-silkroad-security-analysis-idUSKBN17P10Y</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA0fRr11xx__Q-fTGg5npNsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 11:32:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-silkroad-security-analysis-idUSKBN17P10Y" target="_blank"&gt;Local, global security firms in race along China's 'Silk Road'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Brenda Goh, Michael Martina and Christian Shepherd SHANGHAI/BEIJING (Reuters) - Global security companies and their smaller Chinese rivals are jostling for business along Beijing's modern-day "Silk Road", the grandiose plan for land and sea routes connecting the world's second largest economy with the rest of Asia and beyond. Representing investments of hundreds of billions of dollars, the pet project of Chinese President Xi Jinping is seen boosting economic growth at home, and as positive for everything from steel prices to cement makers. Security firms also expect to tap the rush, offe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Learning Chinese Trending in Pakistan Amid Deepening Ties With China - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/learning-chinese-in-pakistan/3906187.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDPkmBAl_Hcq4AJUuTeKTxMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 12:06:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/learning-chinese-in-pakistan/3906187.html" target="_blank"&gt;Learning Chinese Trending in Pakistan Amid Deepening Ties With China&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China is investing billions of dollars in extensive roads, railways, special industrial zones and energy infrastructure in Pakistan. The massive collaboration dubbed the China-Pakistan Economic Corridor, or CPEC, is generating interest among Pakistani students and professionals to learn Mandarin. Li Xue Mei teaches compulsory Mandarin lessons to around 300 students ranging from grade five to middle school. She is one of the Chinese instructors at the private Roots millennium schools, where more than 7,000 children are learning the language. “They are good and they are very excited to learn ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indian Man on Death Row in Pakistan Seeks Clemency From Army Chief - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/indian-death-row-seeks-clemency-from-pakistan-army-chief/3912190.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPx3G_cdljSYvIWSWoeFx7MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 23:30:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/indian-death-row-seeks-clemency-from-pakistan-army-chief/3912190.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indian Man on Death Row in Pakistan Seeks Clemency From Army Chief&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indian man on death row in Pakistan after a military court sentenced him on charges of espionage, sabotage and terrorism has appealed to the country's army chief for clemency. India had earlier appealed to the International Court of Justice, the highest legal body under the United Nations, in the case of Kulbhushan Sudhir Jadhav. India said Pakistan had sentenced an innocent Indian citizen without granting him diplomatic access, which is in violation of an international treaty. The court ordered Pakistan last month to delay Jadhav's execution until the final verdict. Pakistan says Jadhav...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pakistan receives $1bn forex boost from Saudi Arabia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/416be242-ece3-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEzWHufpIp6nFKsox6JgxBEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 18:40:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/416be242-ece3-11e8-89c8-d36339d835c0" target="_blank"&gt;Pakistan receives $1bn forex boost from Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saudi Arabia has lent $1bn to Pakistan to help boost its liquid foreign currency reserves, giving Islamabad some breathing space during protracted bailout discussions with the IMF. The Saudi assistance is part of a $6bn package promised last month. Half of the Saudi package will go towards meeting payments for Saudi oil shipments to Pakistan during the financial year to June 2019 while the other half is meant to boost Pakistan’s depleting foreign currency reserves. Abid Qamar, spokesman for the State Bank of Pakistan, told the Financial Times the remaining $2bn promised by Saudi Arabia woul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>China’s Belt and Road hits problems but is still popular - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/814b39ea-e8cd-11e8-a34c-663b3f553b35</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIcbNVZ6wz_uI_uZjivt8gQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw8tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 18:52:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/814b39ea-e8cd-11e8-a34c-663b3f553b35" target="_blank"&gt;China’s Belt and Road hits problems but is still popular&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a narrative of pushback against the Belt and Road Initiative, China’s programme to finance and build infrastructure in about 88 countries around the world. Coming against the backdrop of US-China confrontation, this evidence of pushback is being read as a collective response to Chinese leader Xi Jinping’s overarching foreign policy concept. But this misses the detail of several deals in which the context is more one of renegotiation than cancellation. The fundamental logic of many of the BRI in developing countries neighbouring China remains intact. Such is the need for investment ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>China, Pakistan Agree to Conduct Bilateral Trade in Yuan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/china-pakistan-agree-to-conduct-bilateral-trade-in-yuan/4645164.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKtrO2jHsGfDlbXnKzPbqVQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 17:07:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/china-pakistan-agree-to-conduct-bilateral-trade-in-yuan/4645164.html" target="_blank"&gt;China, Pakistan Agree to Conduct Bilateral Trade in Yuan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China has agreed to carry out bilateral trade with Pakistan in the Chinese yuan instead of the U.S. dollar to help ease the South Asian ally's financial and economic woes. The unprecedented Chinese concession, officials and economists said, would go a long way in addressing Islamabad’s massive 87-percent trade deficit with Beijing and reducing pressure on Pakistan's depleting foreign currency reserves. "The agreement is part of practical steps being taken [by China] to support our [foreign] currency [reserves],” said Pakistani Information Minister Fawad Chaudhry. He told reporters in Islama...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>How China’s Belt and Road Initiative became a huge geopolitical controversy - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/long_reads/pakistan-imran-khan-belt-and-road-debt-trap-china-pakistan-economic-corridor-a8622351.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDlr4vw6OflTW-qRch7mUnQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 18:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/long_reads/pakistan-imran-khan-belt-and-road-debt-trap-china-pakistan-economic-corridor-a8622351.html" target="_blank"&gt;How China’s Belt and Road Initiative became a huge geopolitical controversy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An international conference took place last week in Gwadar, a dusty Pakistani town perched on the edge of the Indian Ocean – an unlikely place, one would have thought, for Imran Khan’s government to invite dignitaries from 26 countries. But the real aim was to display a vision of the future – a mighty port city and commercial centre for the region which would put Dubai and Bahrain in the shade. Not everything went according to plan. While the delegates were being shown around the site of this projected mega city, gunmen on motorcycles shot dead three workers and injured five others construc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>China says willing to help Pakistan over fiscal crisis - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/5fa67fbd536840ea9866fb108f57cd91</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDzC7CGgegmec0Hk55JqGIUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 07:42:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/5fa67fbd536840ea9866fb108f57cd91" target="_blank"&gt;China says willing to help Pakistan over fiscal crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Close ally China said Saturday it was willing to offer assistance to Pakistan to help it weather its current fiscal woes but that terms of such aid are still being discussed. That followed a meeting in Beijing between Chinese Premier Li Keqiang and Pakistan's newly elected Prime Minister Imran Khan, who met the previous day with Chinese President Xi Jinping. Pakistan's growing fiscal crisis has raised questions about its ability to repay Chinese loans granted as part of Beiing's "Belt and Road" infrastructure initiative. Pakistan has taken out billions of dollars in loans fro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>China to help Pakistan avert fiscal crisis, 'more talks needed' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/china-pakistan-avert-fiscal-crisis-talks-needed-181103141459907.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVrZJgK4jxVKy-vefuPEv8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 15:45:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/china-pakistan-avert-fiscal-crisis-talks-needed-181103141459907.html" target="_blank"&gt;China to help Pakistan avert fiscal crisis, 'more talks needed'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China is willing to provide Pakistan with economic aid to help it deal with its deteriorating finances but more discussions are needed on the details, according to a top Chinese diplomat. The comments on Saturday by Vice Foreign Minister Kong Xuanyou came after a meeting in Beijing between Chinese Premier Li Keqiang and new Pakistani Prime Minister Imran Khan. Pakistan's foreign reserves have plunged 42 percent since the start of the year and now stand at about $8bn, or less than two months of import cover. Late last month, Saudi Arabia pledged to give Pakistan a $6bn rescue package, but of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>China, Pakistan Seeking CPEC Extension to Afghanistan - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/china-pakistan-seeking-cpec-extension-to-afghanistan/4638366.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECptQuQid7lr8h4LO73_4RwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 15:36:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/china-pakistan-seeking-cpec-extension-to-afghanistan/4638366.html" target="_blank"&gt;China, Pakistan Seeking CPEC Extension to Afghanistan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China and Pakistan say they are exploring the extension of their bilateral infrastructure development project to Afghanistan. During the past four years of the China-Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC), Beijing has provided Islamabad $19 billion in soft loans and direct foreign investments, upgrading or constructing Pakistani transportation networks, power plants and the strategic Arabian Sea port of Gwadar. The stage is now set for “expansion and geographical extension” of CPEC to western Pakistan and to landlocked Afghanistan, say Pakistani and Chinese officials. They say later this year K...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>