<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Port of Penang - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZvWW1NMGNqUnFOQklDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:53:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Penang Port may lose 20% of cargo traffic volume - Business News - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/12/06/penang-port-may-lose-20pct-of-cargo-traffic-volume/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780128212021</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/12/06/penang-port-may-lose-20pct-of-cargo-traffic-volume/" target="_blank"&gt;Penang Port may lose 20% of cargo traffic volume - Business News&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/116636" target="_blank"&gt;Penang Port at risk of losing 20% of cargo traffic volume&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Malaysian Insight&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWkxcUt5bWpZQU1FZmFPQjM1VVhwUEJLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/hvIecllkfauH1Q-X0UowVtAyaKmHsTpyWJ8NgRJGdL1uShOMGH021YLLrb8JhaKY6fXZAP63tFtx5gJgsmAJ_smsJ6IKpYvpLd6LoxmPtfb1Bp_Cf-vsHaGjPamhDIUJtSJNmczd6EMKZpqJEI4Lj5pDA2OqQisIvgavQrdlS6G2gtYyoFqPkw=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Pearl of the Orient loses shine as 866 cruises stop visits - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/01/pearl-of-the-orient-loses-shine-as-866-cruises-stop-visits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPaM2Nyq3itI8iwSMa5pSTMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/01/pearl-of-the-orient-loses-shine-as-866-cruises-stop-visits/" target="_blank"&gt;Pearl of the Orient loses shine as 866 cruises stop visits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GEORGE TOWN: The number of cruise ships which called on Penang this year dropped by 866 from last year raising concerns that Penang is losing its lustre as a destination for cruise line operators. The sharp slump meant that Penang saw about 500,000 fewer cruise passengers than last year’s glowing record. Last year saw 1,985 cruise ship calls and this year, with only a month left, only 1,119 calls were recorded since the end of October. Not counting trips by Taipan and Leisure World, the two small cruise ships homeported in Swettenham Pier that make frequent “cruises to nowhere” from here, P...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Cruise tourism takes a beating with loss of ‘Superstar Libra’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/01/cruise-tourism-takes-a-beating-with-loss-of-superstar-libra/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOAFhhBn_O0qaKMMi-HWf7EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/01/cruise-tourism-takes-a-beating-with-loss-of-superstar-libra/" target="_blank"&gt;Cruise tourism takes a beating with loss of ‘Superstar Libra’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GEORGE TOWN: Cruise tourism here took a beating when Superstar Libra left Swettenham Pier, said Penang Port Sdn Bhd chief executive officer V. Sasedharan. “She left in the first quarter and returned last September but swit­ch­ed to a triple home port deploy­­ment. “That is how much impact a cruise ship has on passenger movements when it homeported in Pe­nang,” he said, explaining the reason for the sharp fall in cruise passenger arrivals this year. “We lost six to seven months of cruise passengers without that ship. “Cruise tourism is not something you can plan on the fly. “The schedules ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Penang cruise terminal to be expanded - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/09/penang-cruise-terminal-to-be-expanded-ceo-plans-in-progress-to-position-terminal-as-a-home-port-to-c/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMlgsc33wJ4xNNPeA-9dgzMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/09/penang-cruise-terminal-to-be-expanded-ceo-plans-in-progress-to-position-terminal-as-a-home-port-to-c/" target="_blank"&gt;Penang cruise terminal to be expanded&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GEORGE TOWN: After more than a year’s delay, the RM155mil expansion of the Swettenham Pier Cruise Terminal (SPCT) is set to begin early next year. Upon completion, the joint venture project between Penang Port Sdn Bhd (60%) and Royal Caribbean Cruises Ltd (40%) would be able to handle 1.7 million passengers a year by 2021. It can also cater to 12,000 passengers at any one time. The cruise segment registered 1.2 million passengers last year. Penang Port Sdn Bhd (PPSB) chief executive officer V. Sasedharan said plans were afoot to position the terminal as a home port to the cruise vessels in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Free Commercial Zone will boost Penang’s economy - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMC9M4Q998xunNKIoyItI80qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPTirwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 05:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LETTER | Although reinstating Penang’s free-port status is no longer an election promise used by BN to fish for votes, we are also at a stage where we need to examine if it is entirely necessary for Penang to possess the free-port status? The definition of a free port is as below: i) A port or airport where goods can be brought in from foreign countries without payment of duty if they are going to be exported again. ii) A free port is a free trade zone encompassing an entire port area such as Hong Kong, Isla Magarita, Panama, and Singapore, where imported merchandise may be stored duty-free...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Kenanga cuts MMC earnings forecast on weak 1H results - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/27/kenanga-cuts-mmc-earnings-forecast-on-weak-1h-results/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtl-zc_iQh7v2rEd5uIWfgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:54:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/27/kenanga-cuts-mmc-earnings-forecast-on-weak-1h-results/" target="_blank"&gt;Kenanga cuts MMC earnings forecast on weak 1H results&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Kenanga Research slashed MMC Corp Bhd's FY18-19E earnings by 45%-34% to RM105mil-RM128mil as 1H18 core net profit came in below expectations. The results for the first half of the year were dragged by lower associate contributions and higher-than-expected tax rate. Top-line was up by 33% due to higher work progress from the KVMRT-SPP line, increased volume handled at PTP and consolidation fo Penang Port Sdn Bhd while costs of sales increased 49%, causing gross profit to increase by only 7%. However, core net profit declined 62% on higher financing cost, lower contributions fro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>PPC risks hanging in limbo as chairman steps down - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/20/ppc-risks-hanging-in-limbo-as-chairman-steps-down/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELn9yF3SJmv1W_4puMnSfZgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/20/ppc-risks-hanging-in-limbo-as-chairman-steps-down/" target="_blank"&gt;PPC risks hanging in limbo as chairman steps down&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GEORGE TOWN: A “dream mansion” in an elite neighbourhood here is in the spotlight after it was put up for lease years after being left idle, and its owner Penang Port Commission (PPC) is also under intense attention as well for another reason. Questions were raised as to why after being idle for more than a decade, the 8,401sq m corner lot in Cantonment Road, which comes with a colonial mansion, is being offered on a 3+3-year lease. Said to be worth at least RM13mil, the residential lease offer is expected to attract the wealthy but PPC, which owns many pieces of prime land on top of regula...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Proposed acquisition of Sabah Ports aborted - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/04/07/proposed-acquisition-of-sabah-ports-aborted/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIyNh98WCrsn6C-2R-Q2IHQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/04/07/proposed-acquisition-of-sabah-ports-aborted/" target="_blank"&gt;Proposed acquisition of Sabah Ports aborted&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The proposed acquisition of Sabah Ports Sdn Bhd by MMC Corp Bhd’s subsidiary has been aborted. In a filing with Bursa Malaysia, state-owned port operator Suria Capital Holdings Bhd announced that it will continue to control the entire stake of Sabah Ports. “We wish to confirm that Suria Capital is no longer pursuing the proposed acquisition of Sabah Ports, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Suria Capital, by MMC Ports Holding Sdn Bhd, a wholly-owned subsidiary of MMC Corp Bhd and that Sabah Ports remains as a wholly-owned subsidiary of Suria Capital,” it said In August 2017, Suria ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>