<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Salahuddin Ayub - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRGx5ZG14aWF4SUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:57:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Agriculture Minister receives calf carcass, death threat - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/agriculture-minister-receives-calf-carcass-death-threat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780128024758</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/agriculture-minister-receives-calf-carcass-death-threat/" target="_blank"&gt;Agriculture Minister receives calf carcass, death threat - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/07/minister-salahuddin-ayub-receives-death-threat/" target="_blank"&gt;Minister Salahuddin Ayub receives death threat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/437972/salahuddin-says-no-idea-why-he-received-death-threat" target="_blank"&gt;Salahuddin says no idea why he received death threat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/salahuddin-initially-thought-death-threat-was-a-prank/" target="_blank"&gt;Salahuddin initially thought death threat was a prank - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thesundaily.my/local/salahuddin-ayub-puzzled-by-death-threat-LB223278" target="_blank"&gt;Salahuddin Ayub puzzled by death threat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Sun Daily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWkyOGFDbWpZQU1FWWxzSklKeHVKd0lLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/Q2Jpd0wOu1RdOiSRRp-pdvar4zmlGJSBjuIwn8Zfar0rqOdCR2yYgf_tsIJUiPUHGLJoncYOCMTuaHLAJrxPd_30FXo_Ay7mQQNZbpFoNNFMsiukPJW8yjfvaFFtZx-NigyYDs8JGqTzy4h0NkF4bZNTuQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Suspect remanded over calf carcass and death threat sent to Salahuddin - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/prank-turns-out-to-be-dead-serious-suspect-remanded-over-calf-carcass-and-death-threat-sent-to-salah/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ9FHvrTOzeswI7oaQG0UYYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:35:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/prank-turns-out-to-be-dead-serious-suspect-remanded-over-calf-carcass-and-death-threat-sent-to-salah/" target="_blank"&gt;Suspect remanded over calf carcass and death threat sent to Salahuddin - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A dead calf together with a death threat were sent to Agriculture and Agro-based Industry Minister Datuk Salahuddin Ayub, but he brushed it ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Returning to his roots - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/18/returning-to-his-roots-as-a-former-farmer-the-agriculture-and-agrobased-industry-minister-promises-t/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHi9I_dRDsHZwZFcBVtZhH8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/18/returning-to-his-roots-as-a-former-farmer-the-agriculture-and-agrobased-industry-minister-promises-t/" target="_blank"&gt;Returning to his roots - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a former farmer, the Agriculture and Agro-based Industry Minister promises to get his hands dirty on the ground to boost production in the local agricultural ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Salahuddin Ayub receives death threat, suspect remanded - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENH1UkNx3SWCuX7NGnN6zT4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:04:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Agriculture and Agro-based Industry Minister Salahuddin Ayub received a death threat from an unknown individual on Sunday. Salahuddin told reporters at the Parliament lobby yesterday that he had been called by the Muar district police headquarters to assist in investigations. The Pulai MP said he did not know the identity of the suspect and understood that the suspect was detained by the police. "What is important right now is for me to know the real motive. I have never quarrelled with anyone, nor have I been hostile and suddenly I received a threat like this," he said, adding it was the f...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chew: Pakatan leaders, including four ministers, benefitted from TAR UC and UTAR education - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/25/chew-pakatan-leaders-including-four-ministers-benefitted-from-tar-uc-and-utar-education/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKZeV3KOjNxezOfxnGt_8vcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 08:55:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/25/chew-pakatan-leaders-including-four-ministers-benefitted-from-tar-uc-and-utar-education/" target="_blank"&gt;Chew: Pakatan leaders, including four ministers, benefitted from TAR UC and UTAR education&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The MCA has pointed out that several Pakatan Harapan leaders were beneficiaries of MCA-linked institutions of higher learning. MCA central committee member Datuk Chew Kok Woh named ministers Teresa Kok, Anthony Loke, Datuk Salahuddin Ayub and Datuk Seri Saifuddin Nasution Ismail as the beneficiaries. He said even Penang Chief Minister Chow Kon Yeow and state executive councillor Chong Eng were products of Tunku Abdul Rahman University College (then known as KTAR, and now TAR UC). Kolej Tunku Abdul Rahman (KTAR) was founded in February 1969. It was upgraded to university colleg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>TAR UC deprived of grants for first time in 50 years - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/25/tar-uc-deprived-of-grants-for-first-time-in-50-years-wee-lower-income-group-will-feel-the-pinch-send/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHusfDJ-N6ftxkWYbHqOgRgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/25/tar-uc-deprived-of-grants-for-first-time-in-50-years-wee-lower-income-group-will-feel-the-pinch-send/" target="_blank"&gt;TAR UC deprived of grants for first time in 50 years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Lim Guan Eng has taken away government matching grants for Tunku Abdul Rahman University College (TAR UC) for the first time in its 50 years of existence, says MCA president Datuk Seri Dr Wee Ka Siong. While the Finance Minister might have made history among his eight predecessors, including Tun Dr Mahathir Moha­mad and Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim, Dr Wee said Lim, by doing so, had cast a gloom on affordable higher education for the lower income group. Set up by MCA 50 years ago as Tunku Abdul Rahman College (TAR College) before it was upgraded to TAR UC in 2013, he said all the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Opposition decodes intent behind free decoders - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/opposition-decodes-intent-behind-free-decoders/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMfdODLuc97QXCd0aCu6hMUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 04:49:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/opposition-decodes-intent-behind-free-decoders/" target="_blank"&gt;Opposition decodes intent behind free decoders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – BN was willing to spend more than RM800 million of taxpayer money “just to spread its propaganda” when it already had a “monopoly” on broadcasting stations. Pakatan Harapan leaders are crying foul over Prime Minister Najib Razak’s announcement last Tuesday that the government will be giving free digital television decoders to 4.2 million BR1M recipients in phases. Amanah deputy president Salahuddin Ayub, PKR vice-president Tian Chua and Amanah strategy director Dzulkefly Ahmad accused Putrajaya of wasting public funds to further Barisan Nasional’s political interest. They said it wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Shadow Cabinet promised early next year - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/shadow-cabinet-promised-early-next-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMbShnLWCJ0VuyWQgRlKZAcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 07:39:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/shadow-cabinet-promised-early-next-year/" target="_blank"&gt;Shadow Cabinet promised early next year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opposition says it has a line-up of leaders ready to take over. (FMT) – Pakatan Harapan will reveal its shadow cabinet early next year, said a senior opposition leader, responding to criticism that the opposition pact did not have one even while it harboured dreams of forming the government. Speaking to FMT, Amanah deputy president Salahuddin Ayub said the opposition doesn’t lack quality leaders. “I am confident that with the Pakatan Harapan leaders — more so now that Parti Pribumi Bersatu Malaysia leaders are with us — we have a line-up of leaders which can be presented as the country’s le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Amanah: Anwar’s ‘wise decision’ reflects need to remove distractions - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/amanah-anwars-wise-decision-reflects-need-to-remove-distractions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIhzSIaVPwbkuIjDZQeY144qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 06:52:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/amanah-anwars-wise-decision-reflects-need-to-remove-distractions/" target="_blank"&gt;Amanah: Anwar’s ‘wise decision’ reflects need to remove distractions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Salahuddin Ayub says he shares Anwar’s concern that PPBM’s proposition to occupy top two posts in Pakatan Harapan was worrying. (FMT) – Amanah has lauded Anwar Ibrahim’s move not to offer himself as Pakatan Harapan’s (PH) prime ministerial candidate for the 14th general election (GE14), saying it showed the PKR de facto leader’s determination to remove distractions coming in the path of defeating the ruling Barisan Nasional (BN). Its deputy president Salahuddin Ayub said it was a wise decision as the opposition coalition needs to move forward instead of being weighed down by issues over who...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Why ‘Protestant’ PAN opposes ‘Catholic’ PAS - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/why-protestant-pan-opposes-catholic-pas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDpRVOPephR3krVVYpAylysqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 06:57:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/why-protestant-pan-opposes-catholic-pas/" target="_blank"&gt;Why ‘Protestant’ PAN opposes ‘Catholic’ PAS&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The split in PAS and the creation of PAN a.k.a. Amanah has nothing to do with Islamic ideology but is due to politics and how Islam should play a role in politics and whether there should be a separation of church and state (MMO) – Despite its roots, Parti Amanah Negara (Amanah) leaders insist they are not ideologically identical to Islamist party PAS as they are fighting for a “progressive and inclusive Islam”. Responding to claims by MCA earlier this week, the leaders from the PAS offshoot also said Amanah has time and again proved their different stance and approach to key issues. “We ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Salahuddin wants Malaysia Today to apologise over article - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/salahuddin-wants-malaysia-today-to-apologise-over-article/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEz4gT12iyOys72yTJgydjoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 10:58:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/salahuddin-wants-malaysia-today-to-apologise-over-article/" target="_blank"&gt;Salahuddin wants Malaysia Today to apologise over article&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Amanah deputy president says a sub-heading in an article in Malaysia Today is misleading and can cause misunderstanding: he does not want Article 153 abolished or MARA to be open to non-Malays (Berita Daily) – Amanah deputy president Salahuddin Ayub today gave three days to online news portal Malaysia Today to retract an article that can mislead the people, or face legal action. Salahuddin also demanded an apology from the portal apart from retracting the article. He was referring to an article titled ‘Amanah leader: Singapore Malays better than Malaysian Malays’ (READ HERE) published i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Islam makes the Malays weak - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/islam-makes-the-malays-weak/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPxvkwnrC4uH7iLBpcY08QgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMOvrnwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 09:28:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/islam-makes-the-malays-weak/" target="_blank"&gt;Islam makes the Malays weak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Confusing is it not? The Tunku was ousted because he was accused of neglecting the Malays and they triggered May 13 as the catalyst to oust him and now they say the Malaysian Malays are failures because the government gave them preferential treatment if not the Malaysian Malays would be successful like the Singapore Malays. NO HOLDS BARRED Raja Petra Kamarudin PAN a.k.a. Amanah leader Salahuddin Ayub praises the late Singapore Prime Minister Lee Kuan Yew for making the Malays in Singapore successful while the Malays in Malaysia are failures (READ HERE). This has been the standard DAP argume...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Pakatan says Mahathir should not be judged or punished - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/pakatan-says-mahathir-should-not-be-judged-or-punished/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENyRwuEuOA0Jh5vqLt_bKTcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMOvrnwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 08:34:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/pakatan-says-mahathir-should-not-be-judged-or-punished/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan says Mahathir should not be judged or punished&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;No wonder the Chinese think the Malays are fooking idiots if this is the way Salahuddin is trying to sell Mahathir as the saviour of Malaysia. And is it not insulting for Salahuddin to use the examples of Prophet Muhammad, Nelson Mandela, Mahatma Gandhi and Martin Luther King Jr. to convince us to accept, trust and forgive Mahathir? NO HOLDS BARRED Raja Petra Kamarudin What is the difference between me and the Dapsters and Pakatuns? Well, the difference is I am honest about my intentions while the Dapsters and Pakatuns are either in self-denial or are trying to sell us a donkey and are tell...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Amanah’s double-stand on the Shariah Amendment Bill - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/amanahs-double-stand-on-the-shariah-amendment-bill/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM4aQLXpUYaMkRZ_xHRugxcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 06:13:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/amanahs-double-stand-on-the-shariah-amendment-bill/" target="_blank"&gt;Amanah’s double-stand on the Shariah Amendment Bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amanah accused of secretly supporting the bill but was opposing it to appease non-Muslim voters (FMT) – Amanah has rejected an accusation that it is playing politics in its show of opposition to proposed amendments to the Syariah Courts (Criminal Jurisdiction) Act. “The debate on the bill has not even taken place yet,” said the party’s deputy president, Salahuddin Ayub, in response to Malaysian Muslim Solidarity (Isma) deputy president Aminuddin Yahya, who said at a recent forum that Amanah was secretly supportive of the bill but was opposing it to appease non-Muslim voters. Salahuddin told...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Dr M takes jab at PAS; UN seeks visit to M’sia over human rights - Malaysiakini</title><link>http://www.malaysiakini.com/news/365872</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC5JbVPsRXUumqw16JI5I30qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 01:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysiakini.com/news/365872" target="_blank"&gt;Dr M takes jab at PAS; UN seeks visit to M’sia over human rights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KINI ROUNDUP Here are the key headlines you may have missed yesterday, in brief. Dr M calls PAS ‘confused Parti Pribumi Bersatu Malaysia (Bersatu) chairperson Dr Mahathir Mohamad called PAS a “confused” party over wanting to work with the opposition or the government for the general election. Parti Amanah Negara president Mohamad Sabu said early polls was unlikely due to the slowing economy. His deputy Salahuddin Ayub said Pakatan Harapan will hammer out a common logo for the next general election on Tuesday. He added that Amanah leaders will also be declaring their assets to the public. UN...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysiakini.com">Malaysiakini</source></item><item><title>Moving marine parks dept to ministry that maximises fisheries is wrong, say conservationists - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/moving-marine-parks-dept-to-ministry-that-maximises-fisheries-is-wrong-say-conservationists/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJf2jtLvcQBlQs8ez8D6weMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 06:55:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/moving-marine-parks-dept-to-ministry-that-maximises-fisheries-is-wrong-say-conservationists/" target="_blank"&gt;Moving marine parks dept to ministry that maximises fisheries is wrong, say conservationists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: It's not right to move a government department in charge of conservation to a ministry in charge of extracting resources, say conservationists. They say that moving the Department of Marine Parks Malaysia (DMPM) to the Agriculture and Agro-based Industry Ministry (MOA) will harm rather than protect the marine environment. A source from the Water, Land and Natural Resources Ministry (KATS) confirmed that the move from that ministry to MOA had been proposed to the Cabinet. But how can MOA, which oversees the Department of Fisheries, be in charge of marine park conservation as w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Salahuddin agrees on allowance cut for MPs who skip Parliament sittings - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/24/salahuddin-agrees-on-allowance-cut-for-mps-who-skip-parliament-sittings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED7Z5Ol9EPbyYYypT91XY5oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 15:22:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/24/salahuddin-agrees-on-allowance-cut-for-mps-who-skip-parliament-sittings/" target="_blank"&gt;Salahuddin agrees on allowance cut for MPs who skip Parliament sittings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR (Bernama): Agriculture and Agro-based Industries Minister Salahuddin Ayub (pic) agrees with the proposal to cut allowances of MPs who skip Parliament sittings. The Amanah deputy president said the action could be taken if the MPs concerned do not provide a valid reason for their absence. “If they purposely miss Dewan Rakyat sittings without valid reasons, it is appropriate for their respective parties to take action,” he told reporters when met at the Parliament lobby on Tuesday (July 24). He was commenting on a Twitter post by former cabinet member Tan Sri Rais Yatim, who sugg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>No more political ’recommendation’ needed for Tekun loans, says Salahuddin - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/05/no-more-political-recommendation-needed-for-tekun-loans/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC1IsFLMKKEs6FnrA02U3lUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 01:14:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/05/no-more-political-recommendation-needed-for-tekun-loans/" target="_blank"&gt;No more political ’recommendation’ needed for Tekun loans, says Salahuddin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SERDANG: Those applying for the National Entrepreneur Group Economic Fund (Tekun Nasional) loan are now no longer required to get a signature from any political party leaders as practiced previously, said Agriculture and Agro-based Industry Minister Salahuddin Ayub. He said the decision was made to reduce bureaucracy and political interference in the loan approval process, thus Tekun Nasional could continue to progress and provide good service to the people. “Previously, the loan approval process requires a ’recommendation’ from political leaders. “The most appropriate loan approval mechani...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Aid for Johor students to further studies - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/06/26/aid-for-johor-students-to-further-studies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDoEx4mQzS4pTFfWI79etG8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/06/26/aid-for-johor-students-to-further-studies/" target="_blank"&gt;Aid for Johor students to further studies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BATU PAHAT: Students in Johor who plan to further their studies at higher learning institutions can apply for aid from the “Insentif Harapan Siswaz” fund. Newly-appointed Johor Islamic Religious Affairs and Education Committee chairman Aminolhuda Hassan said the application could be made online at the Yayasan Pendidikan Johor website. “The application is open to all, including students who receive offers to study at private colleges and universities. However, priority will be given to those from the B40 group. “We hope this aid will help reduce their burden, especially in terms of travel co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Minister expects price of rice to come down after ending monopoly - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/06/18/minister-expects-price-of-rice-to-come-down-after-ending-monopoly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKwMZmXkeys8wIsllolWePMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/06/18/minister-expects-price-of-rice-to-come-down-after-ending-monopoly/" target="_blank"&gt;Minister expects price of rice to come down after ending monopoly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MUAR: Prices of rice will come down eventually since Padiberas Nasional Bhd (Bernas) no longer has a monopoly over rice import, says Salahuddin Ayub. The Agriculture and Agro-based Industries Minister said the move would benefit consumers as they could choose the rice they want. He said the ministry, the National Agriculture Advisory Council and the corporate sector would sit together to come up with the “best business model” on the country’s rice import. “Bernas will still import rice but other companies will be doing that as well,” Salahuddin said after receiving RM1mil donation for Tabun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Cheaper rice soon with Bernas monopoly broken - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/13/cheaper-rice-soon-with-bernas-monopoly-broken/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAWMy5NChu0U0vf9-9AuqXsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 06:19:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/13/cheaper-rice-soon-with-bernas-monopoly-broken/" target="_blank"&gt;Cheaper rice soon with Bernas monopoly broken&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MUAR: The price of rice will go down soon now that Padiberas Nasional Bhd (Bernas) no longer has a monopoly on rice imports, says Salahuddin Ayub. The Agriculture and Agro-based Industry Minister said the ministry, the National Agriculture Advisory Council and the corporate sector would now have to come out with the best business model to import rice for the country. "Bernas will still import rice, but there will also be other companies doing that," Salahuddin said in a press conference here on Wednesday (June 13). He said this would benefit consumers and that it was important to get feedba...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>NFC 'cowgate' investigation to be resumed says Salahuddin Ayub - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/24/nfc-cowgate-investigation-to-be-resumed-says-salahuddin-ayub/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJhkbEBSoIWRZwiEZWxmKPsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 09:51:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/24/nfc-cowgate-investigation-to-be-resumed-says-salahuddin-ayub/" target="_blank"&gt;NFC 'cowgate' investigation to be resumed says Salahuddin Ayub&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The Government will reopen the case of the cattle-breeding project under the National Feedlot Corporation (NFC), which is also known as "cowgate". The information was shared via the official Parti Amanah Negara Facebook page on Thursday morning (May 24) citing Agriculture and Agro-Based Industry Minister Salahuddin Ayub. Salahuddin is cited as saying that the reopening of the case is in line with the Pakatan Harapan manifesto to reexamine cases with alleged misappropriation. In a live broadcast on Astro Awani on the same day, Salahuddin, who is also Amanah deputy president, s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakatan leaders to fulfil all promises in manifesto - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/03/10/pakatan-leaders-to-fulfil-all-promises-in-manifesto/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJL0LI5M_VFSjJqt2ZuvTIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/03/10/pakatan-leaders-to-fulfil-all-promises-in-manifesto/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan leaders to fulfil all promises in manifesto&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KLANG: Pakatan Harapan leaders have pledged to fulfil all their promises unveiled in their manifesto for the 14th General Election including limiting the terms of its mentri besar and chief minister, abolishing the Goods and Services Tax (GST) and reforming federal institutions. Klang DAP MP Charles Santiago, who was among those who contributed towards the drafting of the manifesto, said Pakatan would carry this out from the general election onwards. “Pakatan will adhere to the provisions of its GE14 manifesto and limit the terms of its mentri besar and chief minister to two terms even if t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakatan convention: Amanah eyeing more Johor state seats - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/07/pakatan-convention-amanah-eyeing-more-johor-state-seats/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKlRreyu_P0WHgKYBIZ64iUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 05:25:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/07/pakatan-convention-amanah-eyeing-more-johor-state-seats/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan convention: Amanah eyeing more Johor state seats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SHAH ALAM: Parti Amanah Negara (Amanah) plans to ask for more state seats in Johor as it was given the least parliamentary seats to contest in the upcoming general election. Amanah deputy president Salahuddin Ayub (pic) said he acknowledged the dissatisfaction by state delegates who chose to boycott the ongoing Pakatan Harapan convention over the finalised parliamentary seat distribution. “We are willing to work for more state seats and we will continue to pursue this,” he said when met at the sidelines of the convention here at Ideal Convention Centre (IDCC) here Sunday. Pakatan had reache...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Palace-Mahathir feud a worry for Pakatan in Johor - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/palace-mahathir-feud-a-worry-for-pakatan-in-johor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFVqS7j0w6mjzNE3t5zpnnUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 09:39:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/palace-mahathir-feud-a-worry-for-pakatan-in-johor/" target="_blank"&gt;Palace-Mahathir feud a worry for Pakatan in Johor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s why PPBM is seeking dialogue with the Sultan of Johor. (FMT) – The influence of the palace among Johoreans is something Pakatan Harapan has to deal with as it gears itself for the next polls. It’s no secret that the royal household is not fond of former prime minister Mahathir Mohamad, who is the opposition alliance’s chairman. This is readily admitted by PPBM, the Pakatan party of which Mahathir is also chairman and the one seen as being at the forefront of a campaign to break Umno’s six-decade stranglehold on Johor. The party recently decided to engage the Johor sultan through a se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Amanah not attending Friday's Jerusalem rally - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/12/20/amanah-not-attending-friday-jerusalem-rally/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO4uMpOD5bcBa1rgThYH4JMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 15:04:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/12/20/amanah-not-attending-friday-jerusalem-rally/" target="_blank"&gt;Amanah not attending Friday's Jerusalem rally&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Parti Amanah Negara (Amanah) supports the Palestinian cause, but will not attend the upcoming rally on Jerusalem. Despite Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi having invited "everyone" including the Opposition to attend the event, Amanah deputy president Salahuddin Ayub claimed that the Friday (Dec 22) rally had been politicised. "If they (Umno) are serious (in having solidarity with all parties), they should invite us. Just like they did with PAS," he said. Salahuddin said that as far as he was aware, Amanah had received no formal invite from Umno to attend ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Mahfuz Omar and Salahuddin Ayub jailed for opposing Mahathir - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/mahfuz-omar-and-salahuddin-ayub-jailed-for-opposing-mahathir/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELnGCxHX54aXzvsnNSzPf9oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 09:19:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/mahfuz-omar-and-salahuddin-ayub-jailed-for-opposing-mahathir/" target="_blank"&gt;Mahfuz Omar and Salahuddin Ayub jailed for opposing Mahathir&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sentences come as Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad’s government prepares to prosecute more than 100 activists who participated in a rally on Sunday to demand the release of the jailed former Deputy Prime Minister Anwar Ibrahim. BBC, 9 November 2000 Three leaders of Malaysia’s largest opposition party, PAS, have been jailed for participating in an illegal anti-government protest three years ago. Mahfuz Omar, Salahuddin Ayub and Jalaluddin Abdul Manaf, senior leaders of the Parti Islam SeMalaysia (PAS), led a rally in 1997 against a planned visit by an Israeli cricket team to Malaysia, whe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item></channel></rss>