<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Bank Rakyat - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNR28yTW1ad2NoSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:27:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Noripah Kamso appointed new chairman of Bank Rakyat - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/06/noripah-kamso-appointed-new-chairman-of-bank-rakyat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780127926799</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/06/noripah-kamso-appointed-new-chairman-of-bank-rakyat/" target="_blank"&gt;Noripah Kamso appointed new chairman of Bank Rakyat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/116519" target="_blank"&gt;Noripah Kamso is new Bank Rakyat chairman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Malaysian Insight&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWlQOUpxbWpZQU1FWE45WnY1M3JVVlFLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/OJfnklP8MGmMj-5952m0yNzGwtJUyuW3BT25W-lckch91bKazij6XaNKj9AQ7l028vQ7f87VBQe9LM2nhBVRI5Zt6LdvPBOMHbzp-oTUT5mMdIHVoJcHj4eKtx2kPM4OIroxKtvubNbTpeqhwzrBuxVtmFiXWnazJm8sMIWK=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Bank Rakyat chairman candidate 'not a politician' - The Malaysian Insight</title><link>https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/115131</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiLGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZW1hbGF5c2lhbmluc2lnaHQuY29tL3MvMTE1MTMx0gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:17:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/115131" target="_blank"&gt;Bank Rakyat chairman candidate 'not a politician'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Malaysian Insight&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Entrepreneur development minister says candidate has long been involved in international banking sector.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com">The Malaysian Insight</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/G59X1yoNkStbnIz0HKYX7NVmdlrh-ViQ43xO2qZQwZVdF_DyrGAW5hssv4Un3SaxA7uSGhrTgnpF8JNXVdI-AcE_6bamwtC-tZFodwGId6_wnPOvXO8_EzQ5KCXC6qViQNjJuPJ5dFOkxhI5o1joncGxbw=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Bank Rakyat chairman sacked - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/26/bank-rakyat-chairman-sacked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiWWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZyZWVtYWxheXNpYXRvZGF5LmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yeS9uYXRpb24vMjAxOC8xMS8yNi9iYW5rLXJha3lhdC1jaGFpcm1hbi1zYWNrZWQv0gEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/26/bank-rakyat-chairman-sacked/" target="_blank"&gt;Bank Rakyat chairman sacked&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Putrajaya has sacked Bank Rakyat chairman Shukry Mohd Salleh effective immediately, saying the decision was due to his involvement in the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/1KQ4d4zNhZ4vDfcUJx8HsnrrATiVh_9P2LoIWcMqgUuavvZUVT78ltKfTHRL23hwPi9GYl14yk_t9aOLZR6F8bZ5IvhX5ahAGcxFv_4z5uzHQccQ47TF44Un87ETnNMqSz14kwRMAXTd4jmz6MOK0yBK=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>New Bank Rakyat chairman to be named by New Year - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/29/new-bank-rakyat-chairman-to-be-named-by-new-year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZyZWVtYWxheXNpYXRvZGF5LmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yeS9uYXRpb24vMjAxOC8xMS8yOS9uZXctYmFuay1yYWt5YXQtY2hhaXJtYW4tdG8tYmUtbmFtZWQtYnktbmV3LXllYXIv0gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/29/new-bank-rakyat-chairman-to-be-named-by-new-year/" target="_blank"&gt;New Bank Rakyat chairman to be named by New Year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The replacement for sacked Bank Rakyat chairman Shukry Mohd Salleh will be named before the end of the year, according to Entrepreneur ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/BKG-7lSt3CrFqOat9Jz41Yjr4HTJvDNBo3I2kWjFDftAynwnF_-qS3APvc1MVFJF0t5tnzILmW-UCxHC9KINfdqft6V9xHVshyVDl1acVU7hTksHTogCp9d9yVxIzymc9ACfsyQ5IT-tgFBf=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Noripah Kamso new chairman of Bank Rakyat - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/12/06/noripah-kamso-new-chairman-of-bank-rakyat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGBaPHp6781c1av3Q-AlF1UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:13:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/12/06/noripah-kamso-new-chairman-of-bank-rakyat/" target="_blank"&gt;Noripah Kamso new chairman of Bank Rakyat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Entrepreneur Development Minister has appointed Datuk Noripah Kamso as the new chairman of Bank Rakyat with effect from Thursday. Noripah, who was an advisor of CIMB Islamic, takes over from Tan Sri Shukry Mohd Salleh. Shukry was removed on Nov 26 due to his involvement in the original audit report of 1Malaysia Development Bhd (1MDB). The minister said Noripah was the chief executive of CIMB-Principal Islamic Asset Management Sdn Bhd and also of CIMB-Principal Asset Management Sdn Bhd. She is a member of the board of BIMB Investment Management Bhd and Top Glove Corporation...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bank Rakyat's new chairman not a politician - Redzuan - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPmiaMKQDkp-vlGziQgGEOQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:55:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new chairperson for Bank Kerjasama Rakyat Malaysia Bhd (Bank Rakyat) has been identified, and an announcement over the matter will be made soon, Entrepreneur Development Minister Mohd Redzuan Yusof said. According to Redzuan, the candidate is not a politician and has long been involved in the international banking sector. He said the ministry was waiting for an assessment on the candidate by Bank Negara Malaysia. "There is already a candidate; although the power of appointment lies with the ministry, we are taking the professional approach. "We need to follow the procedure from Bank Neg...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Minister: New Bank Rakyat chairman to be announced before year-end - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/29/minister-new-bank-rakyat-chairman-to-be-announced-before-yearend/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDgHXq13zmKSa8tboP9EwzoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:21:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/29/minister-new-bank-rakyat-chairman-to-be-announced-before-yearend/" target="_blank"&gt;Minister: New Bank Rakyat chairman to be announced before year-end&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Entrepreneur Development Ministry has identified a new candidate to be appointed as Bank Rakyat chairman and it will be announced soon. Entrepreneur Development Minister Datuk Seri Mohd Redzuan Md Yusof (pic) said that the candidate would not have any political affiliations and has been involved internationally with banking management. “It will be announced soon. If I could, I would have announced yesterday. But we need to adhere to the Bank Negara Malaysia (BNM)’s procedure. I don’t want to jump the gun. “I can guarantee that the new candidate is a professional who has be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Wahid urges more listings of Islamic financial institutions on Bursa - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/05/02/wahid-urges-more-listings-of-islamic-financial-institutions-on-bursa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM5Z_FWOdxqY-qIBWj52F_YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 05:52:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/05/02/wahid-urges-more-listings-of-islamic-financial-institutions-on-bursa/" target="_blank"&gt;Wahid urges more listings of Islamic financial institutions on Bursa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The listing of more Islamic financial institutions on Bursa Malaysia is needed to boost the Islamic fund and wealth management industry going forward. The Permodalan Nasional Bhd (PNB) group chairman Tan Sri Abdul Wahid Omar said this would also strengthen Malaysia's position as a global hub for such funds. He said that of the 672 syariah-compliant securities listed on the local bourse, only two were from the finance sector, namely, BIMB Hodings Bhd and Syarikat Takaful Malaysia Bhd. "The finance sector has thus the lowest number of syariah-compliant listed securities availabl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Ministry: Further research needed before deciding on action against MBI Group - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/05/hamzah-more-research-needed-before-action-taken/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGS5g0Y4V9nW7IfNPAeHVNYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 10:27:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/05/hamzah-more-research-needed-before-action-taken/" target="_blank"&gt;Ministry: Further research needed before deciding on action against MBI Group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Domestic Trade, Cooperatives and Consumerism Ministry (KPDNKK) has to carry out thorough research before any action can be taken against MBI Group International. "We can't simply accuse anyone despite receiving reports from several quarters. We have to carry out thorough research," said its Minister Datuk Seri Hamzah Zainuddin. He added that KPDNKK had to be "very sure" about the offence committed before proceeding with the next course of action. Hamzah also said that the task force was still gathering evidence to strengthen its case against MBI. "The investigation is not ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bank Rakyat announces 15% dividend payment for 2016 - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/05/06/bank-rakyat-announces-15-dividend-payment-for-2016/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELrcPp0ND8XTdXUZBt2PpPAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/05/06/bank-rakyat-announces-15-dividend-payment-for-2016/" target="_blank"&gt;Bank Rakyat announces 15% dividend payment for 2016&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Bank Kerjasama Rakyat Malaysia Bhd (Bank Rakyat) has announced a cash dividend payment of 15%, involving a payout of RM450mil for the financial year ended Dec 31, 2016, compared with 13% in 2015. The bank registered a profit before tax and zakat of RM1.74bil against RM2.01bil in 2015. Bank Rakyat chairman Tan Sri Shukry Mohd Salleh said the dividend payment was based on higher revenue of RM6.66bil recorded last year, compared to RM6.43bil achieved in 2015. “Despite the challenging environment, the bank’s income has increased, driven by financing and treasury activities,” he to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bank Rakyat appoints new MD and president - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/04/04/bank-rakyat-appoints-new-md-and-president/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAsIOcKweI3XZq3-fnMw4h4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/04/04/bank-rakyat-appoints-new-md-and-president/" target="_blank"&gt;Bank Rakyat appoints new MD and president&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former Affin Bank group CEO and managing director Datuk Zulkiflee Abbas Abdul Hamid has been appointed Bank Rakyat’s managing director and president effective since yesterday. Zulkiflee, who has also served on the board of directors of Maybank Islamic, held the role of group CEO and managing director of Affin Bank from 2009 to 2015. On his plans for Bank Rakyat, Zulklifee said:“Give me a chance to explore what is available in Bank Rakyat. I might be able to provide a more comprehensive action plan after that as I have just begun my role as managing director and president of Ba...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Syukry appointed chairman of Bank Rakyat - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/01/05/syukry-appointed-chairman-of-bank-rakyat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEExRv9UJKmxgEkMB3yQH0N8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 13:03:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/01/05/syukry-appointed-chairman-of-bank-rakyat/" target="_blank"&gt;Syukry appointed chairman of Bank Rakyat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Bank Rakyat has appointed former principal private secretary to the Prime Minister, Tan Sri Syukry Mohd Salleh, as its chairman effective Jan 3. Domestic Trade, Cooperatives and Consumerism Minister Datuk Seri Hamzah Zainudin said Syukry’s vast experience in security management, development and management at the state and federal levels would put him in good stead in his new role. “Hopefully, his experience can help strengthen Bank Rakyat’s position as the largest Islamic cooperative bank in the country,” Hamzah said in a statement. Among the posts Syukry held previously were hea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Ministry gets tough on traders - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/05/29/ministry-gets-tough-on-traders-more-than-1000-plainclothes-officers-appointed-to-ensure-traders-comp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGLXwuLxH7iA1cvwabz-9WoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/05/29/ministry-gets-tough-on-traders-more-than-1000-plainclothes-officers-appointed-to-ensure-traders-comp/" target="_blank"&gt;Ministry gets tough on traders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUCHING: The Domestic Trade, Cooperatives and Consumerism Ministry (MDTCC) has appointed over 1,000 price monitoring officers to check the price of goods and controlled items across the country. These plain-cloth officers, to complement some 2,000 MDTCC enforcement officers nationwide, would report to the ministry of any non-compliance among traders, said its deputy minister Datuk Henry Sum Agong. “The temporary officers, on a one-year contractual basis, will be mobilised discreetly to monitor the price of goods and sufficient supply of controlled items in the market. “This is one of the ac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>KAPB launches real estate private equity firm - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/08/16/kapb-launches-real-estate-private-equity-firm/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEImuuu8ZF4PwdO7wx6Vfz2cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 06:46:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/08/16/kapb-launches-real-estate-private-equity-firm/" target="_blank"&gt;KAPB launches real estate private equity firm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Hartanah AP Rakyat Bhd (HAPRB), a newly established real estate private equity firm led by Koperasi Amanah Pelaburan Bhd (KAPB) chairman Datuk Ilyas Mohamed and a team of real estate experts was introduced in Malaysia on Wednesday. An initiative of KAPB, HAPRB aims to grow its current global investment market in the best interest of its members and the local targeted community as a whole. According to a press release issued on Wednesday, HAPRB is backed by "solid and substantial funds" which allow purchasing of properties with readily accessible cash. KAPB’s newly appointed ad...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>How turkeys got their prices - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2016/12/22/how-turkeys-got-their-prices-fowl-among-items-on-ministrys-control-list-for-christmas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGUnbMm8iA79SX_DWoMm6l4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2016/12/22/how-turkeys-got-their-prices-fowl-among-items-on-ministrys-control-list-for-christmas/" target="_blank"&gt;How turkeys got their prices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TURKEY, a popular festive favourite has found its way on the Domestic Trade, Cooperatives and Consumerism Ministry’s price control list for Christmas which is effective until Dec 28. The other festive controlled price items include chicken (live and slaughtered; super or standard), eggs (grade A, B and C), local mutton, imported lamb (bone-in or boneless), imported bone-in lamb leg, green capsicum and tomato. The ministry’s Penang director Mohd Nawardi Saad said turkey was not a controlled item last year. “In Penang, turkeys are priced at RM27 per kg for wholesale and RM30 for retail. “The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bank Rakyat a takeover target - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/03/13/bank-rakyat-a-takeover-target/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPiLhaT_Z10SKrxSd1rHAFUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/03/13/bank-rakyat-a-takeover-target/" target="_blank"&gt;Bank Rakyat a takeover target&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PNB among institutions said to be exploring the profitable co-operative bank PETALING JAYA: Bank Rakyat, Malaysia’s profitable Islamic co-operative bank, has become a takeover target as part of Bank Negara’s bigger plan to consolidate the financial sector. According to sources familiar with the matter, the idea is being floated around and among the institutions exploring the takeover of Bank Rakyat is Permodalan Nasional Bhd (PNB). Local conventional banks are also said to be eyeing Bank Rakyat. “It is still at an infancy stage. It’s early days and remains an idea that is being explored,” s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Push for mergers among Islamic banks and non-bank lenders - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/06/10/push-for-mergers-among-islamic-banks-and-nonbank-lenders/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELe6NYai9KZgjK73caXqYTEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/06/10/push-for-mergers-among-islamic-banks-and-nonbank-lenders/" target="_blank"&gt;Push for mergers among Islamic banks and non-bank lenders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CONVENTIONAL banks aside, there is a push by industry players for mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;A) to take place in the crowded Islamic banking as well as the non-bank lender space. There are 16 Islamic banks in Malaysia. Two are full-fledged standalone banks: Bank Islam (M) Bhd and Bank Muamalat Malaysia Bhd. Eight more are subsidiaries of conventional banks, while the remaining are foreign banks. Non-bank lenders include entities such as the Government-owned Bank Kerjasama Rakyat Malaysia Bhd (Bank Rakyat), Bank Simpanan Malaysia, Bank Pertanian Malaysia Bhd and Malaysia Building Society Bh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Degrading BR1M an insult towards recipients, Dr M told - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/degrading-br1m-an-insult-towards-recipients-dr-m-told/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaKxBtBDFeTuUy9AfTi-XUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:01:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/degrading-br1m-an-insult-towards-recipients-dr-m-told/" target="_blank"&gt;Degrading BR1M an insult towards recipients, Dr M told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea was originally mooted by the former Bank Negara Malaysia’s Governor, Tan Sri Dr Zeti Akhtar Aziz during a budget briefing for the 2012 Budget (MMO) – Datuk Johari Abdul Ghani has accused the Opposition and Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad today of insulting the recipients of the Bantuan Rakyat 1Malaysia (BR1M) by attacking the financial aid initiative. Claiming the initiative is noble, the Finance Minister II said he hopes BR1M will not be exploited by “disgruntled politicians” for their own personal gain. “To exploit and demean BR1M as being illegal and being a form of bribery is not only ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>No, there’s no plastic in rice pack, says ministry - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/06/14/no-theres-no-plastic-in-rice-pack-says-ministry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHbTK5JJiQWkxMbLHkScttoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/06/14/no-theres-no-plastic-in-rice-pack-says-ministry/" target="_blank"&gt;No, there’s no plastic in rice pack, says ministry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOHOR BARU: There is no fake rice in Johor as an analysis on a Thai fragrant rice brand available in hypermarkets here found no foreign element as alleged. Johor Domestic Trade, Co-operatives and Consumerism Ministry (KPDNKK) director Khairul Anwar Bachok said the ministry took three samples of the rice for analysis following a 60-year-old man’s claim about buying “plastic-smelling” rice from a Kulai hypermarket. He said after the man’s claim went viral on social media, enforcement personnel collected samples of the rice from the hypermarket chain on June 7. Samples of the Thai fragrant ric...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Minister tells investors to be wary of JJPTR’s new offer - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/04/dont-get-bitten-twice-minister-tells-investors-to-be-wary-of-jjptrs-new-offer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMg0UV_SlbGOmqmxBwjCW8UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/04/dont-get-bitten-twice-minister-tells-investors-to-be-wary-of-jjptrs-new-offer/" target="_blank"&gt;Minister tells investors to be wary of JJPTR’s new offer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: If an offer is too good to be true, don’t take it up! Domestic Trade, Cooperatives and Consumerism Minister Datuk Seri Hamzah Zainudin has warned the public to be wary of unlicensed financial schemes. “If a company has cheated you before, and if you still want to believe in the company’s new offer ... well, that’s up to you. “But please, my advice is, do not fall for it,” he said at a special briefing on dodgy money games and illegal investment schemes at his ministry here yesterday. Hamzah also confirmed that investigations into the Penang-based JJPTR and individuals involved in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Ministry finds no plastic or artificial substance in rice - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/06/29/ministry-finds-no-plastic-or-artificial-substance-in-rice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJzDDhO0bmQUyLQgnvAopP4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/06/29/ministry-finds-no-plastic-or-artificial-substance-in-rice/" target="_blank"&gt;Ministry finds no plastic or artificial substance in rice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE Agriculture and Agro-based Ministry’s Perak Paddy Inspection Control Office has cleared the name of a rice brand, which was alleged to be selling plastic rice in a video that has gone viral on social media. The inspection control office found no artificial substance in the rice samples in the preliminary tests carried out. Its director Mohd Abdul Rahim Rashid said the examination and investigation were carried out on the brand’s distribution facility after the viral video was brought to their attention. However, he advised the public to report to the authorities if they came across plas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hamzah: All imported goods must meet safety standards – even fidget spinners - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/05/all-imported-goods-must-meet-safety-standards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEICCu0XMpGvmf1CGU0hneHkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 10:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/05/all-imported-goods-must-meet-safety-standards/" target="_blank"&gt;Hamzah: All imported goods must meet safety standards – even fidget spinners&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Domestic Trade, Cooperatives and Consumerism Ministry (KPDNKK) wants to ensure that all items entering the country, including fidget spinners, abide by set safety standards. Minister Datuk Seri Hamzah Zainuddin said all import and export items must be endorsed by KPDNKK, including the toy. Hamzah told reporters at the Bank Rakyat Twin Towers here Wednesday that the ministry had identified several types of fidget spinners that were dangerous and parents should practise discretion when purchasing the toy. However, Hamzah said there is no mechanism in place to track violation...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Stepping up checks on CNY essentials - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/01/26/stepping-up-checks-on-cny-essentials/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEII-JKXJQvxC25OQkSETEgMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/01/26/stepping-up-checks-on-cny-essentials/" target="_blank"&gt;Stepping up checks on CNY essentials&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The state Domestic Trade, Cooperatives and Consumerism Ministry has stepped up efforts to ensure prices of 13 controlled items are in check. State director Mohd Nawardi Saad said officers have been actively checking places such as mini markets, supermarkets and wet markets. “We have so far checked 65 places in Penang as part of the ministry’s nationwide effort to ensure that traders are selling according to the Chinese New Year Price Control Scheme. “The scheme started on Jan 23 and ends on Feb 3,” he said during an inspection at the Batu Lanchang wet market yesterday that saw 20 officers c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>KADS1M distribution will be done in phases - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/15/kads1m-distribution-will-be-done-in-phases/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI2P3PzzpWuqr8I6peezTYgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 14:42:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/15/kads1m-distribution-will-be-done-in-phases/" target="_blank"&gt;KADS1M distribution will be done in phases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The distribution of Kad Diskaun Siswa 1Malaysia (KADS1M) will be done in phases, said the Higher Education Ministry. The ministry said that the distribution would start with students who had applied for the debit card with Bank Rakyat, and it advised students who have yet to open an account with Bank Rakyat to do so via www.bankrakyat.com.my/bppt "Students who already have accounts with Bank Rakyat are still required to open a new account as this aid will only be channelled through the KADS1M debit account," the ministry said in a statement. As of May 9, 919, 628 students ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bank Rakyat eyes RM1bil credit card transactions in 2017 - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2016/12/20/bank-rakyat-eyes-rm1bil-credit-card-transactions-in-2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFIF5ot4iagYmmbFjXSCUxUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 09:57:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2016/12/20/bank-rakyat-eyes-rm1bil-credit-card-transactions-in-2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Bank Rakyat eyes RM1bil credit card transactions in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Bank Kerjasama Rakyat Malaysia Bhd (Bank Rakyat) is eyeing to sign up over 450,000 credit card holders with RM1bil transactions next year, with the introduction of the Muslimah Card. Chief operating officer Md Khairuddin Arshad said the introduction of the card was aimed at increasing Bank Rakyat’s overall proportion of female card holders from 50% to 55% within 12 months. “The female segment is very significant in the consumer market and we expect it to grow. Currently, we have 385,000 credit card holders with total transactions of around RM800mil,” he told reporters after la...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bank Rakyat picks Zulkiflee as new MD and president - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/04/03/bank-rakyat-picks-zulkiflee-as-new-md-and-president/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEKhuK6xu4NRGbgYSWobgdAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 04:46:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/04/03/bank-rakyat-picks-zulkiflee-as-new-md-and-president/" target="_blank"&gt;Bank Rakyat picks Zulkiflee as new MD and president&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Bank Rakyat has appointed former Affin Bank group CEO and managing director Datuk Zulkiflee Abbas Abdul Hamid as its new managing director and president. Zulkiflee, who has also served on the board of directors of Maybank Islamic, helmed the role of group CEO and managing director of Affin Bank from 2009 to 2015. In addition, he served on a number of industry committees, including council member of the Association of Banks Malaysia as well as chairman of the audit committee of Malaysian Electronic Payment System (MEPS). Zulkiflee holds a Master in Business Administration and a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Former Bank Rakyat MD, chairman acquitted of CBT over RM15mil book project - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/25/former-bank-rakyat-md-chairman-acquitted-of-cbt-over-rm15mil-book-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBEFq5wQk09taG65YqghjkYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 02:37:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/25/former-bank-rakyat-md-chairman-acquitted-of-cbt-over-rm15mil-book-project/" target="_blank"&gt;Former Bank Rakyat MD, chairman acquitted of CBT over RM15mil book project&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Sessions Court here has freed former Bank Rakyat managing director Datuk Mustafha Abd Razak and the bank’s former chairman Tan Sri Abdul Aziz Zainal for committing criminal breach of trust and abetment respectively involving near RM15mil. The case was in relation to a biography book on a prominent political figure project. Judge Madihah Harullah acquitted and discharged Mustafha, 50, and Abdul Aziz, 67, after the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) Deputy Public Prosecutor Afzainizam Abdul Aziz informed the court that they have withdrawn the charges against the two...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bank Rakyat declares 16% dividend payout - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/03/27/bank-rakyat-declares-bumper-dividend-payout/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECYZgdIgiYm1p_etRq66H3AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 11:48:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/03/27/bank-rakyat-declares-bumper-dividend-payout/" target="_blank"&gt;Bank Rakyat declares 16% dividend payout&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Bank Kerjasama Rakyat Malaysia Bhd (Bank Rakyat) has declared a dividend of 16% for financial year ended Dec 31, 2017 compared with 15% in the previous year. In announcing the bank's 2017 financial results, Domestic Trade, Cooperatives and Consumerism Minister Datuk Seri Hamzah Zainudin said this would involve a total payout amounting to RM480mil. He said 2% or RM39.97mil of Bank Rakyat's profit before taxation and zakat would be chanelled to the Co-operative Trust Fund, while another 1% or RM19.98mil to the Co-operative Development Provident Fund. Overall, the improved perf...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bank Rakyat cancels LoI with Microlink for banking system upgrade - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/02/19/bank-rakyat-cancels-loi-with-microlink-for-banking-system-upgrade/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGK0bCQOScO0EdPisGMH9dEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 10:25:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/02/19/bank-rakyat-cancels-loi-with-microlink-for-banking-system-upgrade/" target="_blank"&gt;Bank Rakyat cancels LoI with Microlink for banking system upgrade&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Bank Kerjasama Rakyat Malaysia has cancelled its non-binding letter of intent (LoI) with Microlink Solutions Bhd to improve the group's core banking system. Microlink said on Monday it had received a letter date Jan 5 from the bank about the latter's cancellation of the LoI which was issued on July 14, 2016. To recap, the LOI had invited Microlink to take part in detailed discussions to enhance the relating to the core banking system. “The cancellation letter thanks the company for attending the discussions and for providing its proposals on the project but advises that it wil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Budget 2018: Full speech - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/27/budget-2018-full-speech/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGF3YuDijE8JwdDZS-ht9aAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:56:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/27/budget-2018-full-speech/" target="_blank"&gt;Budget 2018: Full speech&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Budget 2018 speech by Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak, Prime Minister and Finance Minister: Prospering an Inclusive Economy, Balancing Between Worldly and Hereafter, For The Wellbeing of the Rakyat, Towards the TN50 Aspiration Mr Speaker Sir, I beg to move the Bill intituled "An Act to apply a sum from the Consolidated Fund for the service of the year 2018 and to appropriate that sum for the service of that year" be read a second time. In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful. INTRODUCTION 1. There is no God but Allah, and Muhammad is the messenger of Allah. Send your bless...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>