<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Fatwa - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNREpmZDIwU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:53:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>SIS' challenge to fatwa ruling to be heard in March - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/06/sis-challenge-to-fatwa-ruling-to-be-heard-in-march/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMicGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZyZWVtYWxheXNpYXRvZGF5LmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yeS9uYXRpb24vMjAxOC8xMi8wNi9zaXMtY2hhbGxlbmdlLXRvLWZhdHdhLXJ1bGluZy10by1iZS1oZWFyZC1pbi1tYXJjaC_SAQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:39:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/06/sis-challenge-to-fatwa-ruling-to-be-heard-in-march/" target="_blank"&gt;SIS' challenge to fatwa ruling to be heard in March&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This after the Federal Court ordered for the challenge to be heard in the High Court.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/qhtpmm0O37njeTSZgycnzmRhvEpKgZs__5jWmQoFQ0gBrQPsuYNZYYTmYHTmBn739ks3RtstuFy7OEgZ-W8a14BdpajAX6RGXFMZ-YzwZTqKqsgy2CetIMmT7XsM_31oaOrP7yHPe4WDa6oAM_3LakBH11Wc=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Chandra calls for annulment of anti-Shia fatwa - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/19/chandra-calls-for-annulment-of-anti-shia-fatwa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZyZWVtYWxheXNpYXRvZGF5LmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yeS9uYXRpb24vMjAxOC8xMS8xOS9jaGFuZHJhLWNhbGxzLWZvci1hbm51bG1lbnQtb2YtYW50aS1zaGlhLWZhdHdhL9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/19/chandra-calls-for-annulment-of-anti-shia-fatwa/" target="_blank"&gt;Chandra calls for annulment of anti-Shia fatwa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social activist Chandra Muzaffar says the religious elite must play a bigger role in stopping the hatred towards Shia Muslims. (Bernama pic). PETALING JAYA: ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/1_bfmTNFLiszioHA5uT2B5acnYPlRngfDNa7b761HrPWyzLbB-myy_HhEJxrFoXfGIP8-FPemaexHHQG3oAW6Q5J5MZYoxPt3GTSKRTc9cIEyPfEoQGugbRH6t-46I3DcJWoNrJM3UroOp-JqM1IOFq-m1uJ7g=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>March 13 court date for SIS' challenge against fatwa labelling it 'deviant' - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/march-13-court-date-for-sis-challenge-against-fatwa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPxVe1Anw8wEO1LCM493zQkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 07:59:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/06/march-13-court-date-for-sis-challenge-against-fatwa/" target="_blank"&gt;March 13 court date for SIS' challenge against fatwa labelling it 'deviant'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The High Court will hear a suit filed by Sisters in Islam (SIS) Forum (Malaysia) challenging a Selangor Fatwa Committee decision to label the organisation as "deviant". Selangor Islamic Religious Council's (Mais) lawyer Majdah Muda told reporters the date after meeting High Court (Appellate and Special Powers) judge Justice Nordin Hassan in chambers Thursday (Dec 6). Majdah said the court would decide whether a civil court has the jurisdiction to hear the judicial review application relating to fatwa (religious edicts). On Sept 25, the Federal Court's seven-man panel chaired b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Out-of-wedlock children’s names: NRD gets stay on order - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/08/21/out-of-wedlock-childrens-names-nrd-gets-stay-on-order/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFpHrmayMIlqaIqFiYbKoP8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 04:35:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/08/21/out-of-wedlock-childrens-names-nrd-gets-stay-on-order/" target="_blank"&gt;Out-of-wedlock children’s names: NRD gets stay on order&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The Apex Court here has granted an application by the National Registration Department (NRD) and two others to stay a Court of Appeal ruling that a Muslim child conceived out of wedlock can use his or her father's surname instead of “bin Abdullah.” Chief Justice Raus Sharif, who chaired a three-man panel of the Federal Court on Monday, allowed the application by Senior Federal Counsel Ahmad Terrirudin Mohd Salleh who acted for the NRD, its director-general, and the Government. Justice Md Raus later fixed Sept 8 for the hearing of the application for leave by the three appellants....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Fatwa: A non-binding viewpoint - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/sharing-the-nation/2017/08/06/fatwa-a-nonbinding-viewpoint-we-need-dynamism-and-compassion-in-islamic-law-juristic-opinion-in-the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMsjg4pgev_PmgXPFIn666QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/sharing-the-nation/2017/08/06/fatwa-a-nonbinding-viewpoint-we-need-dynamism-and-compassion-in-islamic-law-juristic-opinion-in-the/" target="_blank"&gt;Fatwa: A non-binding viewpoint&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juristic opinion in the Muslim legal tradition is human-made, changing over time and in different circumstances to ensure that justice is always done. THERE are hundreds, if not thousands of fatwas issued by the various State Fatwa Councils and the National Fatwa Council. And many of them differ from each other. Many states have declared smoking as haram; Selangor and Penang gazetted this fatwa which makes it then a criminal offence for any Muslim to smoke in those two states. I must say I haven’t heard of anyone being arrested and charged with the offence. The criminal justice system and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Apex court sets Feb 7 to hear NRD's appeal in 'bin Abdullah' case - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/10/apex-court-sets-feb-7-to-hear-nrds-appeal-in-bin-abdullah-case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMNm3UqPKbZpUgid0XE22mAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 06:59:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/10/apex-court-sets-feb-7-to-hear-nrds-appeal-in-bin-abdullah-case/" target="_blank"&gt;Apex court sets Feb 7 to hear NRD's appeal in 'bin Abdullah' case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Federal Court has set Feb 7 to hear an appeal by the National Registration Department (NRD) and two others over a ruling that a Muslim child conceived out of wedlock can use his or her father's surname instead of "bin Abdullah". Deputy Registrar Syahrin Jeli Bohari fixed the date during case management on Tuesday. Senior Federal Counsel Aida Nurdiana Che Kamarulzaman acted for the NRD, its director-general and the Government, counsel Haziq Othman appeared for the Johor Islamic Religious Council and counsel S. Kiattilin represented the parents and the child. On Sept 8, Chie...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>PAS to sue Penang over failure to gazette state fatwas, including on beauty pageants - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/pas-to-sue-penang-over-failure-to-gazette-state-fatwas-including-on-beauty-pageants/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEtORbMER_MbsMNSuSiq-WYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 06:54:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/pas-to-sue-penang-over-failure-to-gazette-state-fatwas-including-on-beauty-pageants/" target="_blank"&gt;PAS to sue Penang over failure to gazette state fatwas, including on beauty pageants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Penang PAS is planning legal action against the state government for allegedly failing to gazette four approved fatwas or religious edicts. Its Youth wing chief Afnan Hamimi Taib Azamudden said the party is consulting its lawyers and plan to take action soon, Umno-owned news outlet Utusan Malaysia reported on its website today. “This lawsuit is proof of the state PAS’ determination to protect Islamic interests. “The decision to not gazette an approved fatwa clearly goes against the Yang Di-Pertuan Agong who is the head of Islam in the state,” he was quoted telling reporters in Bukit...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>SIS: Decision on out-of-wedlock child in line with Islam - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGZ8vtEfVc_8FshxzTvKPNsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 13:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Court of Appeal decision stating that children conceived out of wedlock can be registered with their father's name is in line with Islam, says Sisters of Islam (SIS). SIS says the judgment written by Justice Abdul Rahman Sebli following the unanimous decision by the bench embodies the spirit of justice taught in Islam. "The decision by the Court of Appeal is within the pillars of Maqasid Syariah which is Daruriyyah (Necessity) which relates to the protection of life (nafs). "The Quran in Surah al-Ahzab 33:5 states “Call them by (the names of) their fathers: that is more just in the eyes...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The cleric who altered the course of modern history - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/19/opinions/9-11-spiritual-guide-dies-bergen/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE13QJBFhH-Yt3nS-v1QKN4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 18:17:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/19/opinions/9-11-spiritual-guide-dies-bergen/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The cleric who altered the course of modern history&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peter Bergen is CNN's National Security Analyst and the author of "The Osama bin Laden I Know," which this article draws upon in part. Omar Abdel-Rahman, the Egyptian cleric who inspired terrorist plots in New York during the early 1990s and who died in an American prison on Saturday, was also the spiritual guide of key 9/11 plotters. More specifically, he was the source of a laminated card of Arabic script that is critical to understanding why nearly 3,000 Americans lost their lives on the morning of September 11, 2001. The Arabic on the card reads: "A fatwa [religious ruling] of the capti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>PNB hopes to see boost in unit holders following nods from Selangor, Penang muftis - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/09/13/pnb-hopes-to-see-boost-in-unit-holders-following-nods-from-selangor-penang-muftis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPw36OfugXCIp1qEY6IgZwgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 07:52:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/09/13/pnb-hopes-to-see-boost-in-unit-holders-following-nods-from-selangor-penang-muftis/" target="_blank"&gt;PNB hopes to see boost in unit holders following nods from Selangor, Penang muftis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Permodalan Nasional Bhd (PNB) hopes to increase the number of unit holders from the current 13 million following the backing of the Selangor and Penang muftis who have issued a ‘harus’, or permissible status, for investments in the fund’s products Amanah Saham Bumiputera and Amanah Saham Nasional. PNB group chairman, Tan Sri Abdul Wahid Omar, said there were several cases where unit holders had requested to withdraw their investments, as their states had not issued the fatwas. “We have received positive feedbacks from both Selangor and Penang muftis, and our unit holders can i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Liberal mosque founder vows to keep it open despite Egyptian fatwa and death threats - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/liberal-mosque-founder-ibn-rushd-goethe-fatwa-berlin-seyran-ates-death-threats-egypt-turkey-islam-a7808106.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPJH7QVMD4UiBGfsBtamYIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/liberal-mosque-founder-ibn-rushd-goethe-fatwa-berlin-seyran-ates-death-threats-egypt-turkey-islam-a7808106.html" target="_blank"&gt;Liberal mosque founder vows to keep it open despite Egyptian fatwa and death threats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The founder of a new liberal mosque in Berlin has vowed to keep the building open in the face of death threats and heavy criticism from religious conservatives. Seyran Ates told The Guardian she was sent “3,000 emails a day full of hate” about the Ibn-Rushd-Goethe Mosque which allows men and women to pray side by side, instead of segregating them. But the 54-year-old remained defiant.“The pushback I am getting makes me feel that I am doing the right thing,” she said. Read more - Saudi Arabia says it has foiled Ramadan terror plot at Grand Mosque - Man charged with terrorism-related murder a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>U.N. experts urge Indonesia to overturn Jakarta governor's blasphemy conviction - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-politics-un-idUSKBN18I16L</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMrFX8cg5HziKgnsipXEhGEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 10:40:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-politics-un-idUSKBN18I16L" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. experts urge Indonesia to overturn Jakarta governor's blasphemy conviction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Tom Miles GENEVA (Reuters) - U.N. experts urged Indonesia on Monday to free Jakarta's Christian governor, who was jailed this month for blasphemy - a conviction that risks encouraging Islamists to challenge secularism in the world's largest Muslim-majority nation. Basuki Tjahaja Purnama, an ethnic Chinese popularly known as "Ahok", was jailed on May 9 for a longer-than-expected two years under a fatwa from Indonesia's highest Muslim clerical council and after aggressive media campaigns and violent protests. The government should have stood up to those pressures, the three U.N. experts sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Perlis goes the other way in conversion issue - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/perlis-goes-the-other-way-in-conversion-issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgCIs0j19ZX2wHw18gNTVMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 02:37:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/perlis-goes-the-other-way-in-conversion-issue/" target="_blank"&gt;Perlis goes the other way in conversion issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – Just weeks after a Bill was tabled in Parliament to prevent a parent from unilaterally converting a child, Perlis has gone the opposite way, passing a Bill that allows for such conversions. The Perlis legislative assembly also freed itself from being obligated to abide by decrees issued by the National Fatwa Council. The assembly passed amendments to the Administration of the Religion of Islam Enactment 2006 yesterday. Section 117 was changed, with the phrase in the Malay version reading “father and mother or guardian” to “father or mother or guardian” to give consent for child...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Indonesian Islamic council to issue fatwa against fake news - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/02/01/indonesian-islamic-council-to-issue-fatwa-against-fake-news/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENbfIfXlubVu1og-dFEP8SQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 08:01:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/02/01/indonesian-islamic-council-to-issue-fatwa-against-fake-news/" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian Islamic council to issue fatwa against fake news&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - Indonesia's highest Muslim clerical council is to issue an edict, or fatwa, declaring the spreading of fake news un-Islamic, the organisation's chairman said on Wednesday. Indonesia has one of the world's highest number of Facebook and Twitter users, and the biggest Muslim population, and concern is growing that fake news is fuelling religious and ethnic tension. "We will issue it as soon as possible, because the situation is worrying," said Maaruf Amin, chairman of the Indonesia Ulema Council. "Hopefully, at least Muslims won't be involved anymore in hoaxes." The counci...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Penang PAS wants state govt to stop meddling in Islamic affairs - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/16/penang-pas-wants-state-govt-to-stop-meddling-in-islamic-affairs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMTIp2zp3G7dAVH0uOuL0TUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 07:51:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/16/penang-pas-wants-state-govt-to-stop-meddling-in-islamic-affairs/" target="_blank"&gt;Penang PAS wants state govt to stop meddling in Islamic affairs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BUKIT MERTAJAM: Penang PAS has demanded that the state government apologise to Muslims for meddling in Islamic affairs. The party's state commissioner Muhammad Fauzi Yusof also urged the DAP-led state government to retract the issuance of fatwa in the state, saying it is a matter only for Muslims. "The state exco committee has 12 members, including the Chief Minister who is a non-Muslim. There are only three Muslims in the committee. “We want them to stop meddling in Islamic affairs and drop the state ruling that fatwa have to go through them first," he said at the Penang PAS convention at ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Zahid backs appeal against illegitimate kid’s case - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/31/zahid-backs-appeal-against-illegitimate-kids-case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDSOnuEAafdRQOil74qIYNQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/31/zahid-backs-appeal-against-illegitimate-kids-case/" target="_blank"&gt;Zahid backs appeal against illegitimate kid’s case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi agrees with the move made by the National Registration Department (NRD) to file an appeal against the case of an illegitimate Muslim child to the Federal Court. The Deputy Prime Minister said at the moment, the NRD was carrying out its tasks according to the Fatwa Committee of the National Council for Islamic Affairs’ ruling which did not allow children conceived out of wedlock to take the name of the father. “We know a law is a law. The Home Ministry, especially the NRD, should adhere to the decision of the National Fatwa Council and as such, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Party ulama chief: Changes to Marriage Act against Islam - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/28/party-ulama-chief-changes-to-marriage-act-against-islam-unilateral-conversion-of-minors-allowed-via/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG7u66nLD-CCjOuj2aAYIyAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/28/party-ulama-chief-changes-to-marriage-act-against-islam-unilateral-conversion-of-minors-allowed-via/" target="_blank"&gt;Party ulama chief: Changes to Marriage Act against Islam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ALOR SETAR: PAS is adamant that the proposed amendments to the Law Reform (Marriage and Divorce) Act, which prevents unilateral conversion, is against Islam. Party ulama chief Datuk Dr Mahfodz Mohamed said the rise of “liberal Islam” among Muslims and some leaders had led to such proposals being made. “The proposed amendments are against Islam and Article 12(4) of the Federal Constitution, which allows a parent to convert a child below 18 to Islam,” he said at the Dewan Ulama assembly yesterday. There was a fatwa (edict) and Federal Court decision, which allowed a Muslim parent to convert h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Amendments to Marriage and Divorce Act postponed - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/06/amendments-to-marriage-and-divorce-act-postponed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPg8OzOEzU2JFO5nY5zCyXMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 03:26:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/06/amendments-to-marriage-and-divorce-act-postponed/" target="_blank"&gt;Amendments to Marriage and Divorce Act postponed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The tabling of proposed amendments to the Law Reform (Marriage and Divorce) Act 1976 has been postponed. Announcing this, Datuk Seri Dr Zahid Hamidi (pic) said the decision was made after receiving feedback on the matter. "The Attorney-General has been asked to study the feedback and look into the proposed amendments together with religious experts. "This is to ensure the amendments will not be against Islamic fatwa or the Federal Constitution," said the Deputy Prime Minister. He said this should not be seen as the Government back-tracking on its assurance to non-Muslims that the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Iranian women get on their bikes to defy cycling fatwa - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/iran-women-defy-cycling-fatwa-tehran-religious-prohibitions-rights-traffic-a7787876.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA3SiasihNXG3bO7XXpPYqsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 15:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/iran-women-defy-cycling-fatwa-tehran-religious-prohibitions-rights-traffic-a7787876.html" target="_blank"&gt;Iranian women get on their bikes to defy cycling fatwa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An increasing number of women in Iran are getting on their bicycles to protest against a fatwa banning them from cycling in public. Hardline Iranian leaders believe women on bikes are a threat to morality and are strictly forbidden as a means of public transport. Women must also be completely veiled, even in the height of summer, when playing sport or driving. But a counter-movement, propelled by social media, has emerged over the last year. In a country of record-high air pollution and traffic congestion, more and more women are cycling. - Read more Iran 'bans female football player' photo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Saudi cleric declares war on birthdays - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/403462-saudi-cleric-birthday-fatwa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA8duKpAPY8BcPhG6Rpt4UsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 14:50:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/403462-saudi-cleric-birthday-fatwa/" target="_blank"&gt;Saudi cleric declares war on birthdays&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Saudi cleric has issued a fatwa on birthdays, claiming the celebrations are too costly. Advisor to the Royal Court Abdullah al-Mutlaq announced the ban on state television, blowing out the candles on those eager to mark their annual milestone. "We do not want to open up that door to ourselves because people do not have that kind of money to spend," he was cited as saying by local media, after a caller asked if it was ok to celebrate the birthdays of children and wives. "We want to save up for our households and they now want to destroy themselves with these parties… which are unbeneficial...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Harussani insists Muslims must follow Islamic laws - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/harussani-insists-muslims-must-follow-islamic-laws/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED4uplzKb5IURTk5Me0T_IgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 06:28:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/harussani-insists-muslims-must-follow-islamic-laws/" target="_blank"&gt;Harussani insists Muslims must follow Islamic laws&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Tan Sri Harussani Zakaria was outraged that the Court of Appeal had yesterday rejected a fatwa, and ruled that a child conceived out of wedlock may bear the father’s name. The Perak mufti also cautioned Muslims, saying that Islamic laws still apply and must be obeyed by adherents although they have been rejected by “worldly” laws. “Islamic laws remain Islamic laws, it is obligatory for all Muslims to obey, although worldly laws have rejected them,” Harussani was quoted saying by Islamist portal Ismaweb. “What has the court decided? Why is it opposed to the Constitution? It has alrea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>NRD: No father's surname for Muslim child born out of wedlock - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/28/nrd-father-surname-for-muslim-child-born-out-of-wedlock/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH9cAyGsjk7ew9Wn9Nra_nAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:35:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/28/nrd-father-surname-for-muslim-child-born-out-of-wedlock/" target="_blank"&gt;NRD: No father's surname for Muslim child born out of wedlock&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The National Registration Department (NRD)'s current system of registering a Muslim child born out of wedlock will continue. A Muslim child conceived out of wedlock will not be allowed to take his or her father's surname, said NRD director-general Datuk Yazid Ramli (pix). He said the NRD had filed an appeal to the Federal Court after the Court of Appeal ruled that a Muslim child who was born out of wedlock has the right the carry the father's name. He said any changes to the current NRD procedure of registering the births of Muslim children conceived out of wedlock will only...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Perak mufti: Allowing a Muslim child born out of wedlock to take father's name legitimises adultery - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/31/allowing-a-muslim-child-to-take-father-name-legitimises-adultery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECCtsHSMTXOwL2qbAsE83IMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 08:00:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/31/allowing-a-muslim-child-to-take-father-name-legitimises-adultery/" target="_blank"&gt;Perak mufti: Allowing a Muslim child born out of wedlock to take father's name legitimises adultery&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The "new view" to allow a Muslim child conceived out of wedlock to take the father's name would legitimise adultery, said the Perak mufti. Tan Sri Harussani Zakaria said this view goes against the teachings in the Quran, hadith, and ijmak ulamak (consensus decision by ulamak worldwide). "So why should we go against it? I hope some ulamak will be careful as the matter has been decided thousands of years ago based on the Quran and hadith. "Are we looking for publicity by going against the teachings?" Harussani said to reporters at the launch of Residensi RAH at Kampung Baru M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Perlis fatwa says vaccinations are obligatory - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/11/perlis-fatwa-says-vaccinations-are-obligatory/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPPz9j-YusrJWPCvz_TamtgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 13:43:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/11/perlis-fatwa-says-vaccinations-are-obligatory/" target="_blank"&gt;Perlis fatwa says vaccinations are obligatory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KANGAR: The Perlis Fatwa Committee has decided that vaccination is the most effective method to prevent diseases and thus obligatory (wajib) for Muslims. The decision was made during the 23rd meeting of the Perlis Fatwa Committee on Oct 3-4. "The negligence of parents in discharging this responsibility is sinful since it can endanger the lives of their children," said the Perlis Fatwa Committee in a statement Friday. "Therefore, the Muslim community in Perlis should not refuse vaccinations and the refusal to seek medical prevention is irresponsible. "Even if parents do not want the vaccinat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Federal Court grants NRD leave to appeal in father’s name issue - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/09/08/federal-court-grants-nrd-leave-to-appeal-in-fathers-name-issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFDoeN_RDDnZirTQxSWGQVsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 02:58:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/09/08/federal-court-grants-nrd-leave-to-appeal-in-fathers-name-issue/" target="_blank"&gt;Federal Court grants NRD leave to appeal in father’s name issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The Federal Court today granted the National Registration Department (NRD) leave to appeal against a ruling that allowed a Muslim child conceived out of wedlock to carry the father’s name instead of ‘Abdullah’. Chief Justice Tan Sri Md Raus Sharif, leading a three-man panel, allowed three of the seven questions put forward by the Government's lawyers. The first question was whether in carrying out the registration of Muslim children, the registrar of birth and death may refer to and rely on sources of Islamic Law on legitimacy. Second, whether the civil court may determine questi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>DPM agrees with appeal in illegitimate Muslim children case - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/30/dpm-agrees-appeal-federal-court-illegitimate-child-case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBp4cYVCcFsXasWVaBwAtcQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 01:03:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/30/dpm-agrees-appeal-federal-court-illegitimate-child-case/" target="_blank"&gt;DPM agrees with appeal in illegitimate Muslim children case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi (pix) agrees with the move taken by the National Registration Department (NRD) to appeal against the case of illegitimate Muslim children to the Federal Court. The Deputy Prime Minister said at the moment, the NRD was carrying out its tasks according to the Fatwa Committee of the National Council for Islamic Affairs' ruling which did not allow children conceived out of wedlock to take the name of the father. “We know a law is a law. The Home Ministry, especially the NRD, should adhere to the decision of the National Fatwa Council and as such, w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Female Islamic clerics declare rare fatwa against child marriage - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/female-islamic-clerics-child-marriage-fatwa-muslim-indonesia-java-a7707201.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENFSt8RaY15RzwLWIfOneAMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 10:49:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/female-islamic-clerics-child-marriage-fatwa-muslim-indonesia-java-a7707201.html" target="_blank"&gt;Female Islamic clerics declare rare fatwa against child marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Female scholars of Islam have decreed that child marriage should be banned after a rare congress held in Indonesia. Dozens of women from the Muslim-majority country as well as scholars from Saudi Arabia, India and Pakistan gathered for what is believed to be the first major meeting of female clerics in Cirebon, Java, issuing a raft of religious decrees on Thursday after three days of discussions. Among the most important was a fatwa calling on the government to raise the age of marriage for girls from 16 to 18. Mother and Daughter in video message defying fatwa on cycling in public in Iran ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Liberal Berlin mosque to stay open despite fatwa from Egypt - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jun/25/ibn-rushd-goethe-mosque-berlin-seyran-ates-egypt-fatwa-burqa-niqab</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-2WfUig-0OSlYpDDo5i_0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 10:30:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jun/25/ibn-rushd-goethe-mosque-berlin-seyran-ates-egypt-fatwa-burqa-niqab" target="_blank"&gt;Liberal Berlin mosque to stay open despite fatwa from Egypt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The founder of a new liberal mosque in Berlin that allows men and women to pray side by side has vowed to press on with her project even though the institution has been issued with a fatwa from Egypt and attacked by religious authorities in Turkey within a week of its opening. “The pushback I am getting makes me feel that I am doing the right thing,” said Seyran Ateş, a Turkish-born lawyer and women’s rights campaigner, who does not wear a hijab. “God is loving and merciful – otherwise he wouldn’t have turned me into the person I am.” Related: Zakat requires Muslims to donate 2.5% of their ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>PNB enhances syariah compliant in investments - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/09/22/pnb-enhances-syariah-compliant-in-investments/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM-JklUyYVmZaVf1KScPxS4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 13:00:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/09/22/pnb-enhances-syariah-compliant-in-investments/" target="_blank"&gt;PNB enhances syariah compliant in investments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Permodalan Nasional Berhad (PNB) will continue to improve its syariah compliance in its investments and enhancement of Islamic financial investment instruments to help the people to increase their investments. PNB Group chairman Tan Sri Abdul Wahid Omar, in a statement Friday, said he hoped that the Muslim community would continue to increase their investments in the various unit trusts managed by PNB. He said investment by the Muslim community in Amanah Saham Bumiputera (ASB) and Amanah Saham Nasional (ASN) was syariah-compliant. At a meeting held last Aug 14-15, the Penang F...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Penang CM's aide slapped by protester outside mosque - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/26/penang-cm-aide-slapped-by-protester-outside-mosque/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDQhkr7sGw6TsSWruT0VtMkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 11:36:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/26/penang-cm-aide-slapped-by-protester-outside-mosque/" target="_blank"&gt;Penang CM's aide slapped by protester outside mosque&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GEORGE TOWN: Chief Minister Lim Guan Eng's information officer Zaidi Ahmad was slapped by a protester outside the Simpang Enam mosque here during a commotion. Zaidi, 48, who is a former Royal Malaysian Air Force (RMAF) officer, is believed to have approached a group of protesters headed by Jalinin Muslimin Pulau Pinang chairman Mohamed Hafiz Mohamed Nordin, who was speaking to the crowd. The group was at the mosque at Macalister Road to protest against alleged interference of the state government in the issuance of fatwa by the state Fatwa Committee. A scuffle ensued when Zaidi approached M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Inside the ‘Curb Your Enthusiasm’ Premiere: Fatwas, Larry David, and Donald Trump - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-curb-your-enthusiasm-premiere-fatwas-larry-david-and-donald-trump</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA8x5FUwKOtRli2kozjaUqwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-curb-your-enthusiasm-premiere-fatwas-larry-david-and-donald-trump" target="_blank"&gt;Inside the ‘Curb Your Enthusiasm’ Premiere: Fatwas, Larry David, and Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a finicky shampoo bottle, a foisting, and even a fatwa, Curb Your Enthusiasm returned Sunday night after a seemingly interminable six-year absence. It was pretty, pretty, pretty good! As if we ever doubted it would be. Getting to the genesis of the genius behind HBO’s longest-running series ever—nine seasons over 17 years—is a reliably hilarious pursuit. Ask where ideas came from, what went into producing the episode, or even why they brought the show back now, and the answers from Larry David, his co-stars, and executive producer Jeff Schaffer are hysterically matter-of-fact. The last...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Dr Ahmad Zahid: Accept decision to amend Marriage and Divorce Act - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/05/nations-interest-comes-first-dr-ahmad-zahid-accept-decision-to-amend-marriage-and-divorce-act/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG8XrM1KGAdt9ktu0WtTBR0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/05/nations-interest-comes-first-dr-ahmad-zahid-accept-decision-to-amend-marriage-and-divorce-act/" target="_blank"&gt;Dr Ahmad Zahid: Accept decision to amend Marriage and Divorce Act&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The decision to amend the Law Reform (Marriage and Divorce) Act 1976 is in the interest of the nation and all groups are urged to accept it, said Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi. The Deputy Prime Minister said it has been the “Malaysian practice” to respect all religions and the rights of all races. “When we do things or make decisions, our target is that the people benefit from it. But the interest of the nation supersedes other interests. “When the Government decided to amend the Act, it was because we were looking at the interest of the country as a whole,” he said after visi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng sends legal notices to NST, Berita Harian over mufti issue - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/guan-eng-sends-legal-notices-to-nst-berita-harian-over-mufti-issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBaSxBMyOtMb3ds1JvlRbJsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 07:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/guan-eng-sends-legal-notices-to-nst-berita-harian-over-mufti-issue/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng sends legal notices to NST, Berita Harian over mufti issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Penang Chief Minister Lim Guan Eng said today he will sue the New Straits Times (NST) and Berita Harian (BH) for defamation if the dailies do not retract a report claiming he had removed a state mufti for banning non-Muslims from using the word “Allah”. The Penang lawmaker gave the two dailies 48 hours to retract the articles published on February 5 and to publish an apology, failing which he will file defamation suits against the newspapers. In the articles, both BH and NST reported that Lim had not renewed former mufti Datuk Seri Hassan Ahmad’s contract in 2014 after the ban on “A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Perlis fatwa: Wives can leave marital home if in danger - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/10/perlis-fatwa-women-leave-marital-home/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJs_4SfSCVsCJxKiqXnk7aYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 09:03:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/10/perlis-fatwa-women-leave-marital-home/" target="_blank"&gt;Perlis fatwa: Wives can leave marital home if in danger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Muslim wives can leave their homes without the permission of their husbands if they feel that they are being threatened, ruled the Perlis Fatwa Committee. The Committee was responding to cases where abused women did not leave their houses for fear of supposedly going against the religion. In the fatwa (edict) approved this month, the Perlis Fatwa committee ruled that the women can leave their homes if their lives if they strongly felt that their life, religion, honour, family or property is endangered. "This is the last resort and if the wife feels that there was no other way...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Call for open forum on ‘bin Abdullah’ rule - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/call-for-open-forum-on-bin-abdullah-rule/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJZtrQe21FUqbdGrZClNA7IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 04:19:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/call-for-open-forum-on-bin-abdullah-rule/" target="_blank"&gt;Call for open forum on ‘bin Abdullah’ rule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – Khalid Samad says changed circumstances require a revisit of fatwas that are based on the opinions of ulama of the past. Amanah communications director Khalid Samad has called for open discussions on a religious edict forbidding Muslims conceived out of wedlock from carrying their fathers’ names. This follows a South China Morning Post (SCMP) report that quoted several Muslims born out of wedlock as saying they faced numerous problems due to the social alienation and stigma growing up with “bin Abdullah” attached to their names. Stressing that he neither agreed nor disagreed with th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Liberal mosque founder who banned burqas defies death threats and vows to continue - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/liberal-mosque-seyran-ates-founder-lawyer-burqa-ban-death-threats-islam-muslim-a7861461.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMldbdYWyFV6yGmWqlMuas4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 14:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/liberal-mosque-seyran-ates-founder-lawyer-burqa-ban-death-threats-islam-muslim-a7861461.html" target="_blank"&gt;Liberal mosque founder who banned burqas defies death threats and vows to continue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seyran Ates has been beaten up in the street, received death threats and had fatwas issued against her since she opened her mosque in Berlin where men and women can pray together and explore a liberal version of Islam. But the Turkish born lawyer and human rights campaigner has stuck to her beliefs and she is now in Britain to promote a campaign for tolerance and dialogue and fight aggressive extremism in religion and politics. She will, in the course of this, meet Muslim imams and community leaders and seek to help set up mosques where worshippers are not segregated by their gender. “There...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Constitutional view on Bin Abdullah case - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/reflecting-on-the-law/2017/08/03/constitutional-view-on-bin-abdullah-case-islam-is-like-a-mansion-with-many-rooms-and-diversity-aboun/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOKFwAYEbGAMwOuCYJBrsIEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/reflecting-on-the-law/2017/08/03/constitutional-view-on-bin-abdullah-case-islam-is-like-a-mansion-with-many-rooms-and-diversity-aboun/" target="_blank"&gt;Constitutional view on Bin Abdullah case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islam is like a mansion with many rooms, and diversity abounds in Islamic jurisprudence. COURT of Appeal judges Datuk Abdul Rahman Sebli, Datuk Tengku Maimun Tuan Mat and Puan Sri Zaleha Yusof must be congratulated for their courageous and principled decision in the “Bin Abdullah” case. Their verdict is based on sound principles of administrative law and has far-reaching, positive implications for our constitutional system. The issue, in this case, was whether an illegitimate Muslim child can carry the name of his father. The child was conceived out of wedlock but the parents had married. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘Curb Your Enthusiasm’ Returns With a Vengeance—And a Fatwa - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/curb-your-enthusiasm-returns-with-a-vengeanceand-a-fatwa</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGef97WPs6KcxI07HgBU99sqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 02:40:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/curb-your-enthusiasm-returns-with-a-vengeanceand-a-fatwa" target="_blank"&gt;‘Curb Your Enthusiasm’ Returns With a Vengeance—And a Fatwa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who had money on the Season 9 premiere of Curb Your Enthusiasm, the first new episode in six years, beginning with a Larry David nude scene? The anticipation for a new season of Curb Your Enthusiasm has been so fevered that HBO promoted the return with tongue-in-cheek commercials positing Larry as “the hero we need.” The world is bleak right now, a toxic cauldron of massive political and social issues about to boil over. Someone’s got to focus on the little, petty things that need fixing. That man, as he has been for the last 17 years, is Larry David. In fact, hype for the premiere was so l...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Mahathir and Islam are not compatible - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/mahathir-and-islam-are-not-compatible/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEApoImrFhTcHWbMEBMR3ngsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMOvrnwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 10:57:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/mahathir-and-islam-are-not-compatible/" target="_blank"&gt;Mahathir and Islam are not compatible&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;2015 and 2016 were disaster years for Mahathir. Mahathir wanted us to hate Najib by hating 1MDB. Now Mahathir has brought in a new dimension, which is 1MDB is abusing taxpayers’ money by helping Muslims to perform their pilgrimage, and hence Allah will not accept their Haj. This is Mahathir’s new fatwah, just like his earlier fatwah that Muslims should not ape the Prophet by sporting beards. NO HOLDS BARRED Raja Petra Kamarudin Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad is worried. It has just been revealed that 1MDB has embarked upon many worthy causes, one of which is to help those who do not have enough mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>NRD stands its ground on Muslim child’s name - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/29/nrd-stands-its-ground-on-muslim-childs-name-dept-well-register-as-usual-until-federal-court-ruling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBoHkHLD7P8ZEQ1k0hmho0UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/29/nrd-stands-its-ground-on-muslim-childs-name-dept-well-register-as-usual-until-federal-court-ruling/" target="_blank"&gt;NRD stands its ground on Muslim child’s name&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The National Registration Department (NRD) will continue to register the births of Muslim children conceived out of wedlock as usual, pending an appeal against the Court of Appeal’s decision to allow these children to take the name of their fathers. Any changes to the current procedures will only come after the Federal Court rules on the appeal filed by the Attorney-General’s Chambers, said NRD director-general Datuk Mohd Yazid Ramli. “NRD would like to clarify the decision by the Court of Appeal which stated that a Muslim child who is conceived out of wedlock can take his or...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Indonesia prepares to to issue a fatwa against fake news - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/01/31/indonesia-prepares-issue-fatwa-against-fake-news/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN5T5Y7HxyQbnWhGMjskBC0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 23:46:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/01/31/indonesia-prepares-issue-fatwa-against-fake-news/" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia prepares to to issue a fatwa against fake news&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesian clerics are preparing to issue a fatwa against “fake news” after a series of damaging hoaxes on social media which targeted the Chinese and Christian minorities. The move follows growing concern in the world’s most populous Muslim nation about the spread of fake news – a phenomenon that has been credited with fuelling recent ethnic and political tensions. Some of the spurious items in recent months include a claim that China was using contaminated chilli seeds to wage biological warfare against Indonesia, a claim that the design of new monetary notes contains an image of the com...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Saudi top prosecutor summons Twitter users for harming public order - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/08/14/saudi-top-prosecutor-summons-twitter-users-for-harming-public-order/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENVn9hhug_By3iuLYIbEx-EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 19:51:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/08/14/saudi-top-prosecutor-summons-twitter-users-for-harming-public-order/" target="_blank"&gt;Saudi top prosecutor summons Twitter users for harming public order&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RIYADH (Reuters) - A group of Twitter users will be indicted in Saudi Arabia on charges of harming public order for threatening the "safety and moderate ideology of society" through extremism, according to a statement on state news agency SPA. The country's chief prosecutor summoned the Twitter users on Sunday, the statement said, without naming them or specifying how many were accused. A spokesman for the Ministry of Culture and Information had earlier tweeted that a radical Sunni cleric, Ali al-Rabieei, had been referred to a "publication crimes" committee for unspecified violations. Mini...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Court: NRD chief not bound by fatwa on child conceived out of wedlock - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/28/muslim-kid-can-take-dads-surname-court-nrd-chief-not-bound-by-fatwa-on-child-conceived-out-of-wedloc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEmjCY1dbyyw22y8-C4r-3IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/28/muslim-kid-can-take-dads-surname-court-nrd-chief-not-bound-by-fatwa-on-child-conceived-out-of-wedloc/" target="_blank"&gt;Court: NRD chief not bound by fatwa on child conceived out of wedlock&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A Muslim child conceived out of wedlock can now take his or her father’s surname following the Court of Appeal’s latest landmark decision. The appellate court ruled that the National Registration Department (NRD) director-general is not bound by a fatwa or religious edict issued by the National Fatwa Committee to decide on the surname of a Muslim child conceived out of wedlock. In the judgment, Justice Abdul Rahman Sebli said the director-general’s jurisdiction was a civil one and was confined to determining whether the child’s parents had fulfilled the requirements under the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>In Indonesia, an Islamic Edict Seeks to Keep Santa Hats Off Muslims - The New York Times</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/12/23/world/asia/indonesia-fatwa-christmas.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAl_vG-gfTotuTqeA-QjWBIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 12:53:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2016/12/23/world/asia/indonesia-fatwa-christmas.html" target="_blank"&gt;In Indonesia, an Islamic Edict Seeks to Keep Santa Hats Off Muslims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA, Indonesia — Apit Abdullah does not believe in Santa Claus. That is not surprising, considering that he is 18 years old. But Mr. Apit, a Muslim, was wearing a red Santa hat at the cafe where he works, inside the largest upscale shopping mall in Jakarta, the Indonesian capital. “It’s showing respect for the holiday,” he said of his Christmas-themed hat as he cleaned a window. “It’s no problem.” Others, however, are trying to make it one. This month, the Indonesian Ulema Council, the country’s largest body of Islamic clerics, issued a religious edict barring Muslims from wearing Chris...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>PAS blames rise of 'liberal Islam' for Law Reform Act amendments - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/27/pas-blames-rise-of-liberal-islam-for-law-reform-act-amendments/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPvwpoUGIoCNmpdyMCZlsdMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 07:29:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/27/pas-blames-rise-of-liberal-islam-for-law-reform-act-amendments/" target="_blank"&gt;PAS blames rise of 'liberal Islam' for Law Reform Act amendments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ALOR SETAR: PAS is adamant that proposed amendments to the Law Reform (Marriage and Divorce) Act against unilateral conversion is against Islam. Its ulama chief Datuk Dr Mahfodz Mohamed (pic) said the rise of "liberal Islam" among Muslims and some leaders has led to the proposal being made. "The proposed amendments to the Law Reform Act are against Islam and Article 12(4) of the Constitution which allows a parent to convert a child below 18 to Islam," he said in his keynote address at 56th Dewan Ulama Assembly here Thursday. He added that there is even a national fatwa (edict) and Federal C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Indonesia's highest Islamic council to issue fatwa against 'fake news' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/indonesia-fake-news-fatwa-islam-council-spreading-alternative-facts-jakarta-elections-ahok-religious-a7556406.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBir3r9A1BEJMHdNZm7sulwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 08:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/indonesia-fake-news-fatwa-islam-council-spreading-alternative-facts-jakarta-elections-ahok-religious-a7556406.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia's highest Islamic council to issue fatwa against 'fake news'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia’s highest Muslim authority is to issue a fatwa declaring the spread of “fake news” to be un-Islamic amid concern over sectarian tensions. The Indonesia Ulema Council’s chairman, Maaruf Amin, said: “We will issue it as soon as possible, because the situation is worrying. “Hopefully, at least Muslims won't be involved anymore in hoaxes.” Trump calls leak "fake news" and "something that Nazi Germany would have done" The religious edict, which is not legally binding, is expected to be issued before the elections for the governor of Jakarta on 15 February, which have been rife with rel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>IGP: Raja Bomoh to be summoned by police - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/19/igp-raja-bomoh-to-be-summoned-by-police/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEclxkb0CxLpwhrd0e09K00qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 08:07:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/19/igp-raja-bomoh-to-be-summoned-by-police/" target="_blank"&gt;IGP: Raja Bomoh to be summoned by police&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MALACCA: Ibrahim Mat Zin (pic), popularly known as “Raja Bomoh Sedunia,” will be summoned to give a statement after police reports were lodged against him, says Inspector-General of Police Tan Sri Khalid Abu Bakar. He said police will summon him under Section 111 of the Criminal Procedure Code (CPC), and would track him down if he does not comply. The controversial shaman recently made headlines when he resurfaced to conduct his signature rituals to ostensibly “protect” Malaysia from North Korea, as diplomatic ties between the two countries soured with the murder on Kim Jong-nam at Kuala Lu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>As a taxpayer, I don’t want to fund religious bodies - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/as-a-taxpayer-i-dont-want-to-fund-religious-bodies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMeHqeHP081jK8nk648onGQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 04:11:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/as-a-taxpayer-i-dont-want-to-fund-religious-bodies/" target="_blank"&gt;As a taxpayer, I don’t want to fund religious bodies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Muslims get to have a say, through their pockets, on how exactly they want Shariah legislation to work in Malaysia for their community. This will also lead to greater accountability by religious departments. Non-Muslims are also less likely to scrutinise the actions of religious departments and Shariah courts since none of their tax monies are used. When I used to go to church, I would regular give the church tithes, or 10 per cent of my monthly income. The funds would be used to run the church’s programmes and pay the staff and there would be an annual report explaining where the m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>A Dictator’s Mindset - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/a-dictators-mindset/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA70loslek3DmdfjXsBqk4sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMPrpnwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 04:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/a-dictators-mindset/" target="_blank"&gt;A Dictator’s Mindset&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;They want BN to stop PAS because they believe the law would affect non-Muslims but they defend their own government’s amendment because they say it doesn’t affect non-Muslims. Mak Khuin Weng DAP appears incessant with their demand that it is BN’s responsibility to stop PAS from tabling the Syariah Courts Act (RUU 355) amendment. Is such a demand or expectation of BN fair? Principled Democracy PAS parliamentarians are democratically elected representatives of their constituents. They have publicly declared that they would pursue an Islamic state, and the proposed amendments to RUU 355 is par...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Look to compassionate side - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2017/08/10/look-to-compassionate-side/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMx29J5d2tzJUT2TJVy825wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2017/08/10/look-to-compassionate-side/" target="_blank"&gt;Look to compassionate side&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AN approach to Syariah that lacks “a just balance” and “compassion” has triumphed yet again. By withdrawing a clause that would have put an end to the unilateral conversion of children by the parent who has converted to Islam, the Government has failed to prioritise the wellbeing of the child which is an important principle of Islamic jurisprudence. Since unilateral child conversions have generated so much friction and caused so much pain for so many years, the new Bill presented to Parliament on Tuesday which legitimises such acts is a huge disappointment. To be fair to the Government, as ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘We reject the headscarf’: Austrian politicians blast Islamic leaders’ recommendations to women - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/379651-austrian-politicians-reject-headscarf/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBMA0QRgoF5Ts-UYmkAmdEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 21:06:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/379651-austrian-politicians-reject-headscarf/" target="_blank"&gt;‘We reject the headscarf’: Austrian politicians blast Islamic leaders’ recommendations to women&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Austrian government officials have sharply criticized a recommendation by the Islamic Religious Community in Austria (IGGO) that Muslim women start wearing a headscarf from the onset of puberty, describing it as an attack on integration and women’s freedom. "As an integration minister, I have to say clearly: we reject an obligation to [wear] the headscarf,” Sebastian Kurz, the Austrian Minister for Foreign Affairs and Integration, told the daily newspaper Österreich on Sunday. “I urge the IGGO to say whether the recommendation will remain on their website.” “Such a position is an attack on ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Egypt's Top Islamic Scholars Work to Promote Moderate Vision of Islam - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/egypt--top-islamic-scholars-work-to-promote-moderate-vision-of-islam/3996281.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEArLgl7oNiuBEeN27iwgvsAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 19:41:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/egypt--top-islamic-scholars-work-to-promote-moderate-vision-of-islam/3996281.html" target="_blank"&gt;Egypt's Top Islamic Scholars Work to Promote Moderate Vision of Islam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Al Azhar University, Egypt's venerable seat of Islamic law, has been working to project a more modern image of Islam to counter the violent versions being espoused by Islamic State, al-Qaida and other militant groups. Efforts by Al Azhar religious authorities to control the tenor of Islamic religious edicts or “fatwas” are part of the strategy that moderate forces are using to battle clerics espousing death and violence. Egypt has been plagued by the efforts of militant Islamic terrorists and their “spiritual guides” to sow turmoil in the country in recent years, leaving a bloody trail of d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Protesters tell Guan Eng to skip ‘buka puasa’ events - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/protesters-tell-guan-eng-to-skip-buka-puasa-events/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN3EkZFTuAndb3WzNecw9hEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 12:03:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/protesters-tell-guan-eng-to-skip-buka-puasa-events/" target="_blank"&gt;Protesters tell Guan Eng to skip ‘buka puasa’ events&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Penang chief minister’s information officer shoved and allegedly slapped during protest over claims that state government interfered in issuance of fatwas. (FMT) – Protesters who accused Penang Chief Minister Lim Guan Eng and his state executive council of interfering in the issuance of fatwa (religious decrees for Muslims) have told the CM not to join “buka puasa” (breaking of fast) gatherings this coming fasting month. Jaringan Muslimin Pulau Pinang chairman Mohd Hafiz Noordin said if Lim wanted to break fast with Muslims during Ramadan, he should convert to Islam. “We do not want a kafir...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>NRD D-G not bound by fatwa to decide surname of illegitimate Muslim child - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/27/nrd-dg-not-bound-by-fatwa-to-decide-surname-of-illegitimate-muslim-child/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ2KaDXEhtqkVXbTfOg3fQ8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 05:12:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/07/27/nrd-dg-not-bound-by-fatwa-to-decide-surname-of-illegitimate-muslim-child/" target="_blank"&gt;NRD D-G not bound by fatwa to decide surname of illegitimate Muslim child&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The National Registration Department (NRD) director-general is not bound by fatwa or religious edict issued by the National Fatwa Committee to decide on the surname of a Muslim child conceived out of wedlock. In a 29-page landmark judgment, Justice Datuk Abdul Rahman Sebli said the director-general's jurisdiction was a civil one and confined to determining whether the child's parents had fulfilled the requirements under the Births and Deaths Registration Act 1957 (BDRA) which covered all illegitimate children, Muslim and non-Muslim. He said the director-general was guided by proc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Sabah authorities waiting for go-ahead to crack down on deviant religious group - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/19/sabah-authorities-waiting-for-go-ahead-to-crack-down-on-deviant-religious-group/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF6lj9FGcif_tcofq7ryOkoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 07:14:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/04/19/sabah-authorities-waiting-for-go-ahead-to-crack-down-on-deviant-religious-group/" target="_blank"&gt;Sabah authorities waiting for go-ahead to crack down on deviant religious group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KOTA KINABALU: Islamic authorities here are waiting for a state Cabinet decision as to whether Indonesia-based deviant religious group Milah Abraham will be banned in Sabah, said assistant minister to the Chief Minister Datuk Mohd Arifin Mohd Arif. He said at a meeting last May, the religious authorities discussed the activities of Milah Abraham and decided that it was deviant to true Islamic teachings. "We have issued a fatwa on Milah Abraham and the proposal for the ban has been submitted to the state cabinet," said Mohd Arifin after presenting excellence performance awards to the Sabah I...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>CM’s officer denies provoking crowd to earn slap - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/27/cms-officer-denies-provoking-crowd-to-earn-slap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKsJiUEL0ie4HjalYZyItEEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/27/cms-officer-denies-provoking-crowd-to-earn-slap/" target="_blank"&gt;CM’s officer denies provoking crowd to earn slap&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GEORGE TOWN: The ‘indelible ink’ ex-Royal Malaysian Air Force (RMAF) major Zaidi Ahmad (pic), who was publicly slapped by a PAS supporter, maintained that he did not provoke the incident. He said he was trying to clarify something with former Penang PAS Youth chief Mohamed Hafiz Mohamed Nordin, who was giving a speech. Zaidi, 48, an information officer in the Chief Minister’s office, said he went to the Simpang Enam mosque in Macalister Road for Friday prayers yesterday. “I came out from the mosque around 2.30pm and saw people demonstrating,” he said. Videos on social media show Zaidi walki...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Perlis conversion law clashes with state fatwa - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/09/perlis-conversion-law-state-fatwa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgutC2a3HYsF3feiAUETnAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 04:19:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/09/perlis-conversion-law-state-fatwa/" target="_blank"&gt;Perlis conversion law clashes with state fatwa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KANGAR: The passing of a Bill by Perlis which allows for the unilateral conversion of children by a parent has caused confusion, not least because it goes against a state fatwa. On top of conflicting with a Bill in Parliament which seeks to prevent unilateral conversions, it appears that the enactment also goes against the state Fatwa Committee's 2015 decision on the matter. Perlis mufti Datuk Dr Mohd Asri Zainul Abidin, who is overseas currently, said he did not have the details on the passing of the Bill and would seek clarification from the state government. He, however, shared a copy of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng interfered in appointment of Penang mufti, PAS Youth claims - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/guan-eng-interfered-in-appointment-of-penang-mufti-pas-youth-claims/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQfrfh1L4hTnXD9N_2SQC4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 06:03:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/guan-eng-interfered-in-appointment-of-penang-mufti-pas-youth-claims/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng interfered in appointment of Penang mufti, PAS Youth claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Penang PAS Youth has accused Lim Guan Eng of “political interference” in the appointment of the state mufti, and that the Penang chief minister had a hand in ensuring that the former state mufti’s contract was not renewed. New Sunday Times, the Sunday edition of New Straits Times (NST) reported today Penang PAS Youth chief Afnan Hamimi Taib Azamudden saying that Lim was responsible for the non-renewal of state mufti Datuk Seri Hassan Ahmad’s contract when it expired in June 2014. According to the report, Afnan said Hassan’s contract was not renewed because the latter had objected to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>‘Footloose’ Fatwas in the U.K. - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2017/03/13/drawing-the-line-against-footloose-fatwas-in-the-u-k.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMG_SVw1pmeun7tCLXYGSvIqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLzdlwI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2017/03/13/drawing-the-line-against-footloose-fatwas-in-the-u-k.html" target="_blank"&gt;‘Footloose’ Fatwas in the U.K.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON—A Muslim girl wearing a headscarf was filmed dancing in the streets of Birmingham, U.K.—twerking, in fact—and the smartphone video soon went viral, viewed over a million times. Ironically, it was popularized in no small part by outraged Muslim men. The fundamentalist Muslim backlash directed at this anonymous 17-year-old girl’s innocuous behavior was instant, personal, and severe. Amid threats in comment threads such as, “Fu**ing sl*t someone give me her address I will kill her,” and “Stupid b**ch needs to be killed,” the young girl issued a tearful, pitiful public apology that was b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>There’s good news and there’s bad news - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/brave-new-world/2017/08/02/theres-good-news-and-theres-bad-news-first-came-a-surprise-ban-but-it-was-followed-by-an-inspiring-h/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJV64ub4vLncU7SG2UiYlPMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/brave-new-world/2017/08/02/theres-good-news-and-theres-bad-news-first-came-a-surprise-ban-but-it-was-followed-by-an-inspiring-h/" target="_blank"&gt;There’s good news and there’s bad news&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;First came a surprise ban, but it was followed by an inspiring, heartwarming Court of Appeal decision. THE banning of the book Breaking the Silence: Voices of Moderation – Islam in a Constitutional Democracy came as a surprise to me. I wasn’t surprised that it was banned. The Government has banned around 2,000 books since 1960. It’s not exactly a bestseller. Full disclosure here folks: I have a chapter in this book. I can hardly remember what I wrote, but it was about fundamental liberties in the Federal Constitution. Anyway, the point I am trying to make is that the book is a collection of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Sisters in Islam's case against fatwa back to High Court - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/02/sisters-in-islam-allowed-appeal-against-deviasion-ruling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELLoFyujujV78z7Y536a9nIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 06:31:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/02/sisters-in-islam-allowed-appeal-against-deviasion-ruling/" target="_blank"&gt;Sisters in Islam's case against fatwa back to High Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The Court of Appeal has allowed Sisters in Islam (SIS) to challenge a gazetted fatwa (edict) in Selangor that declared the Muslim women’s rights group as deviating from Islam. Justice Tengku Maimun Tuan Mat ordered the merits of the judicial review bid by SIS to be heard by another High Court judge. "We disagreed with the High Court judge in upholding the preliminary objection on the issue of jurisdiction," she said in packed courtroom. In unanimously allowing the appeal by SIS, Justice Tengku Maimun did not make any order as to costs and set March 9 for mention at the High Court...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Muslim feminist plans to open liberal mosque in Britain - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jul/26/seyran-ates-muslim-feminist-liberal-mosque-london-britain</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECJ9gJlryI-3oDRDxKd8eToqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 11:20:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jul/26/seyran-ates-muslim-feminist-liberal-mosque-london-britain" target="_blank"&gt;Muslim feminist plans to open liberal mosque in Britain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Muslim feminist who founded a liberal mosque in Berlin, triggering death threats and fatwas, is planning to open an inclusive place of worship in the UK, saying a revolution in Islam is under way. Seyran Ates, a Turkish-born lawyer and human rights campaigner, visited London this week to investigate potential sites for a liberal mosque open to men, women and LGBT Muslims on an equal basis, and people from all strands of Islam. Related: Liberal Berlin mosque to stay open despite fatwa from Egypt She hopes to establish such a mosque within a year, and says her aim is to create similar place...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Go beyond current mindsets - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/26/go-beyond-current-mindsets-if-pas-president-datuk-seri-hadi-awangs-motion-to-amend-the-syariah-court/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHkMs9D-EH8QHfEwsaY-xdsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/26/go-beyond-current-mindsets-if-pas-president-datuk-seri-hadi-awangs-motion-to-amend-the-syariah-court/" target="_blank"&gt;Go beyond current mindsets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If PAS president Datuk Seri Hadi Awang’s motion to amend the Syariah Courts (Criminal Jurisdiction) Act is approved by Parliament, what impact will the enhanced punishments have on syariah offences like expressing an opinion contrary to a state fatwa or discussing Islam with non-family members – including friends – without getting a tauliah (credentials) from the state’s religious body? IF you hold a breastfeeding clinic, tell mothers to breastfeed their newborn for two years, and quote the Quran as the source of that advice, can you be charged by the state Islamic religious authorities? Mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Chandra calls for annulment of anti-Shia fatwa - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/19/chandra-calls-for-annulment-of-anti-shia-fatwa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPVIKgJbBUNJeO_m6-vBbsAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 04:40:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/19/chandra-calls-for-annulment-of-anti-shia-fatwa/" target="_blank"&gt;Chandra calls for annulment of anti-Shia fatwa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – Social activist Chandra Muzaffar has called for the setting aside of a 1996 fatwa declaring Shi’ism as a deviant expression of Islam. He told FMT he believed the fatwa was misconceived and that Shia Muslims were not beyond the pale of Islam since they, like Sunnis, accept the Quran as revelation and believe in the absolute oneness of God. The issue of religious persecution came up again recently when Islamic Renaissance Front chief Ahmad Farouk Musa complained about continued demonisation of Shia Muslims in Friday sermons and remarked that “nothing has changed with respect to Islam”...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Hate speech is wrong, even against ‘deviant’ Shias, says Mujahid - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/12/hate-speech-is-wrong-even-against-deviant-shias-says-mujahid/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEINng9FQd66YyLxWg6urYO0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 04:40:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/12/hate-speech-is-wrong-even-against-deviant-shias-says-mujahid/" target="_blank"&gt;Hate speech is wrong, even against ‘deviant’ Shias, says Mujahid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – Mujahid Yusof Rawa, the minister in charge of Islamic affairs, agrees that no one should be persecuted for their beliefs, including Muslims who follow Shia teachings, which Islamic authorities in Malaysia label as “deviant”. The Amanah leader said the debate on Shia Muslims in Malaysia was made complicated by those who put forward a narrative that borders on hate speech. Mujahid said the line must be drawn when it came to hate speech against Shias, despite a 1996 fatwa banning Muslims from practicing the second biggest denomination in Islam. “I can call on people to accept Sunni Isl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>The Satanic Verses sowed the seeds of rifts that have grown ever wider - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/29/satanic-verses-sowed-seeds-of-rift-grown-ever-wider</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBgNic6I4qUk95trk9xh-JMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 17:00:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/29/satanic-verses-sowed-seeds-of-rift-grown-ever-wider" target="_blank"&gt;The Satanic Verses sowed the seeds of rifts that have grown ever wider&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thirty years ago last week, Salman Rushdie’s The Satanic Verses was published. Rushdie was then perhaps the most celebrated British novelist of his generation. His new novel, five years in the making, had been expected to set the world alight, though not quite in the way that it did. The novel was, Rushdie suggested, both about “migration, metamorphosis, divided selves, love, death” and “a serious attempt to write about religion and revelation from the point of view of a secular person”. At its heart was a clash of race, religion and identity that, ironically, prophesied the controversy tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>High Court to decide on MAIS declaration that Sisters in Islam is 'deviant' - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/02/high-court-to-decide-on-mais-declaration-that-sisters-in-islam-is-deviant/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG73wJhe96l46Ka2JCn_uekqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 06:47:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/02/high-court-to-decide-on-mais-declaration-that-sisters-in-islam-is-deviant/" target="_blank"&gt;High Court to decide on MAIS declaration that Sisters in Islam is 'deviant'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: In a suit filed by Sisters in Islam (SIS) against an Islamic fatwa (ruling or edict) labelling the organisation as "deviant", the High Court will examine whether civil courts have the power to rule over what seems to be a religious matter. The case began in 2014, when it declared that any individual or groups which adopted the ideologies of "liberalism" and "pluralism", including SIS, were Islamic "deviants", as decided by the Selangor Fatwa Committee and Selangor Islamic Religious Council (Majlis Agama Islam Selangor or MAIS). MAIS' Counsel Majdah Muda told reporters that amo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>SIS challenge against fatwa declaring it a deviant group sent back to High Court - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/25/sis-challenge-against-fatwa-declaring-it-a-deviant-group-sent-back-to-high-court/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMFbVeEMFW1G-EyGTkQaHKYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 08:45:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/25/sis-challenge-against-fatwa-declaring-it-a-deviant-group-sent-back-to-high-court/" target="_blank"&gt;SIS challenge against fatwa declaring it a deviant group sent back to High Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The legal challenge by Sisters in Islam (SIS) against a fatwa declaring it a "deviant group" will return to the High Court to be heard. The Federal Court on Tuesday (Sept 25) decided that the judicial review application filed by SIS' corporate body SIS Forum (Malaysia) challenging the Selangor Fatwa Committee's order will be remitted back to the High Court to decide the merits, which included whether a non-syariah court had jurisdiction over the matter. A seven-man bench chaired by Chief Justice Tan Sri Richard Malanjun and six other judges said parties were free to argue on the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Activist warns Mujahid against repeating ‘hate mantra’ against Shias - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/27/activist-warns-mujahid-against-repeating-hate-mantra-against-shias/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJiRZlkyYspNFAZk9AY-UeMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 04:28:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/27/activist-warns-mujahid-against-repeating-hate-mantra-against-shias/" target="_blank"&gt;Activist warns Mujahid against repeating ‘hate mantra’ against Shias&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vocal activist Dr Ahmad Farouk Musa has warned the Pakatan Harapan government against falling into the “hate mantra of the past” in dealing with the diversity of Muslims, following remarks by a minister that Shia Islam would not be tolerated. (FMT) – “At a time when we are celebrating the new dawn of Malaysia, he is repeating the hate mantra of the previous regime,” Farouk, who heads the Islamic Renaissance Front, told FMT. “It now seems that nothing has changed with this new government with respect to Islam.” He said mosques in Selangor continue to invoke anti-Shia sentiments during Friday...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Suspected pro-Syiah leaflets at MRT in KL are illegal, being monitored, says Jawi - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/24/suspected-pro-syiah-leaflets-at-mrt-in-kl-are-illegal-being-monitored-says-jawi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKKCzYz8_5gBvQAYDuYzancqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/24/suspected-pro-syiah-leaflets-at-mrt-in-kl-are-illegal-being-monitored-says-jawi/" target="_blank"&gt;Suspected pro-Syiah leaflets at MRT in KL are illegal, being monitored, says Jawi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Only one school of Muslim thought is allowed in Malaysia and the propagation of anything other than the Sunni Islam teachings known as “ahli Sunnah Wal Jamaah” is forbidden, said Federal Territory Islamic Religious Department (Jawi) director Mohd Ajib Ismail. This is following the distribution of doughnuts and leaflets believed to be by the pro-Syiah “Who is Hussain?” movement at the Bukit Bintang monorail station in Kuala Lumpur. (The Muslim world is split into Sunni and Syiah schools of thought, and the latter is illegal in Malaysia.) Mohd Ajib said that Jawi was aware of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>