<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Hannah Yeoh - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRFJqY3pRemVCSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:24:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Hannah Yeoh: Child marriages cannot be solved without solving teen pregnancies - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/24/hannah-yeoh-child-marriages-cannot-be-solved-without-solving-teen-pregnancies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELCZ0iNd-mzTyxt0dv1YfbYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/24/hannah-yeoh-child-marriages-cannot-be-solved-without-solving-teen-pregnancies/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah Yeoh: Child marriages cannot be solved without solving teen pregnancies - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Child marriages cannot be solved without solving the issue of teen pregnancies, says Deputy Women, Family and Community Development ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>40,923 women registered for I-Suri: Hannah Yeoh - thesundaily.my</title><link>https://www.thesundaily.my/local/40-923-women-registered-for-i-suri-hannah-yeoh-ED207969</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiWGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZXN1bmRhaWx5Lm15L2xvY2FsLzQwLTkyMy13b21lbi1yZWdpc3RlcmVkLWZvci1pLXN1cmktaGFubmFoLXllb2gtRUQyMDc5NjnSAQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thesundaily.my/local/40-923-women-registered-for-i-suri-hannah-yeoh-ED207969" target="_blank"&gt;40,923 women registered for I-Suri: Hannah Yeoh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;thesundaily.my&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A total of 40,923 women have registered under the Employees Provident Fund (EPF)'s Suri Incentive (i-Suri) voluntary contribution scheme as ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thesundaily.my">thesundaily.my</source></item><item><title>Hire more people from OKU community, says Yeoh - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/18/hire-more-people-from-oku-community-says-yeoh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZXN0YXIuY29tLm15L25ld3MvbmF0aW9uLzIwMTgvMTEvMTgvaGlyZS1tb3JlLXBlb3BsZS1mcm9tLW9rdS1jb21tdW5pdHktc2F5cy15ZW9oL9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/18/hire-more-people-from-oku-community-says-yeoh/" target="_blank"&gt;Hire more people from OKU community, says Yeoh - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUBANG JAYA: All ministries should have at least 1% of their staff from the OKU community, says Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/ML35ciK_nGGE2ZsWi0H3OIDSxprn0gBj_25Li1q4K5KicUdbuWT_ukiLl9NeQhbtPGEY3_p2K4_67ykgM6HFHWCI2uuWoy9UStMCEcvQgBcotMczVG_VuPoEQ_Pc9wmvDsMjBAnrOubag_h5WG01B0BpALHAkFVzk4jj061Qo3l2wAfl60WUfUNfP6eimyFr2-GjOoC_xdx-TXUUoTinbG41M4IqqJxqDG555Pg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Snoring, shopping and night-time laundry behind some divorces in Malaysia, says Yeoh - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/13/snoring-shopping-and-night-time-laundry-behind-some-divorces-in-malaysia-says-yeoh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMikAFodHRwczovL3d3dy5mcmVlbWFsYXlzaWF0b2RheS5jb20vY2F0ZWdvcnkvbmF0aW9uLzIwMTgvMTEvMTMvc25vcmluZy1zaG9wcGluZy1hbmQtbmlnaHQtdGltZS1sYXVuZHJ5LWJlaGluZC1zb21lLWRpdm9yY2VzLWluLW1hbGF5c2lhLXNheXMteWVvaC_SAQA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/13/snoring-shopping-and-night-time-laundry-behind-some-divorces-in-malaysia-says-yeoh/" target="_blank"&gt;Snoring, shopping and night-time laundry behind some divorces in Malaysia, says Yeoh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: More than one-third of marriages in the country end within the first five years, Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/bvNW8vLARZMDHaoD9i7BG0BMaIbLoACEmy79yYXHSJGxc5NY_GVitO_Ggx4KCcmgPJ783mOLQY3a9zwwFx4LFJMHbzubUEtdWXB5Bx10rQkRcm79HobkbTzHtRc6x0uEGF9GCXjyVwQ6eTJOpZPTuBMLOfnDlg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Too early to decide whether to charge parents of dead baby: Hannah Yeoh - New Straits Times</title><link>https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/430484/too-early-decide-whether-charge-parents-dead-baby-hannah-yeoh</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIYbT1eEs0waltajhSVox6MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow9sveCjC0m9YBMJHSoQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/430484/too-early-decide-whether-charge-parents-dead-baby-hannah-yeoh" target="_blank"&gt;Too early to decide whether to charge parents of dead baby: Hannah Yeoh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: It is too early to decide whether a married couple should be charged with negligence over the death of their 11-month-old baby who was ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nst.com.my">New Straits Times</source></item><item><title>Hannah lodges MACC report over 29 violations of KL City Plan in Segambut - Metro News - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/11/10/hannah-lodges-macc-report-over-29-violations-of-kl-city-plan-in-segambut/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPWjAly_VLNt6rmqricrPiwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/11/10/hannah-lodges-macc-report-over-29-violations-of-kl-city-plan-in-segambut/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah lodges MACC report over 29 violations of KL City Plan in Segambut - Metro News&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEGAMBUT MP Hannah Yeoh has lodged a report with the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission (MACC) over the 29 violations of the recently gazetted Kuala ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hannah Yeoh: Use referrals, don't look for babysitters online - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/23/hannah-yeoh-use-referrals-dont-look-for-babysitters-online/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBdqVSOclkI27QHr8SGixXkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:01:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/23/hannah-yeoh-use-referrals-dont-look-for-babysitters-online/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah Yeoh: Use referrals, don't look for babysitters online&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Hannah Yeoh (pic) has urged parents not to search for babysitters on the Internet but to rely on referrals instead. The Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister said parents should be wary of leaving their children in the care of strangers. "Please do not look for babysitters online. Please do not let strangers – people you don't know – look after your children. "Go with personal recommendation from friends or relatives or you could also consult the ministry or agencies like the Association of Registered Childcare Providers (PPBM) and the Early Childhood Care and E...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Many suicide cases in Selangor go unreported - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/04/15/many-suicide-cases-in-selangor-go-unreported/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBwwhDLMGL-RUufqQAVjG1UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 05:35:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/04/15/many-suicide-cases-in-selangor-go-unreported/" target="_blank"&gt;Many suicide cases in Selangor go unreported&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A TOTAL of 122 suicide cases have been reported in Selangor between Jan to Dec last year. This alarming number of cases was recorded by the Criminal Investigation Department of Selangor Police Contingent Headquarters and shared with Subang Jaya assemblyman Hannah Yeoh. Citing records obtained from IPD Subang Jaya, Hannah said 65 suicide cases were reported in Subang Jaya from 2011 and 2015. “In Subang Jaya, records show that 81 percent of the suicide cases comprised of male victims. “There is also a recent pattern of suicide cases among senior citizens and this is just reported cases, "Ther...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>New outdoor gym equipment for PJS 9 residents - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2016/11/01/new-outdoor-gym-equipment-for-pjs-9-residents/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELtZaEX2AH9p8oJPoABy3EsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2016/11/01/new-outdoor-gym-equipment-for-pjs-9-residents/" target="_blank"&gt;New outdoor gym equipment for PJS 9 residents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;RESIDENTS of PJS 9 can now enjoy exercising in the outdoors with new gym equipment installed in their park in Jalan PJS 9/14. Four types of equipment were installed, namely a double leg press, double sky walker, body row and double hip swing. PJS 9 resident of 24 years, Sitha Chelliah said she was looking forward to using the gym set. "I will find the time to use it during off-peak hours. The playground is usually packed from 6.30am to 9am and 5pm to 7.30pm," she said. PJS 9 Rukun Tetangga deputy chairman Mohamad Nor Ahmad said the equipment were selected to make the exercise area resemble ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng speaks up in defence of Hannah Yeoh - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/17/lim-guan-eng-speaks-up-in-defence-of-hannah-yeoh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHFTvt-cDupGDEQK9RYKDoAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 10:58:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/17/lim-guan-eng-speaks-up-in-defence-of-hannah-yeoh/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng speaks up in defence of Hannah Yeoh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GEORGE TOWN: DAP secretary-general Lim Guan Eng has defended Subang Jaya assemblyman Hannah Yeoh, whose autobiography is currently in the spotlight. "I want to question why is Hannah Yeoh being persecuted for talking about her faith. Is it wrong for non-Muslims to talk about their faith. She is not preaching," said Lim. Lim said if his administration had wanted to "Christianise" Penang, why would they increase the allocation for Muslims by 84 percent or RM450mil. "Why is PAS accusing us of trying to Christianise Penang?" he added at a press conference in Komtar on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Women march to Parliament ‘for Maria’ - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/24/women-march-to-parliament-for-maria/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOc2gScXlBaVo0aLmAgngagqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/24/women-march-to-parliament-for-maria/" target="_blank"&gt;Women march to Parliament ‘for Maria’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A group of women rights activists submitted a petition to the Government to demand the immediate release of Bersih chairman Maria Chin Abdullah. The group of about 300 activists called “Women for Maria” yesterday walked from Padang Merbok to Parliament to submit the petition. They marched along Jalan Parlimen but were stopped by a police barricade halfway to Parliament guardhouse. A few representatives, including former Bersih co-chairman Datuk S. Ambiga, former Women’s Aid Organisation head Ivy Josiah and G25 spokesman Datuk Noor Farida Ariffin, were allowed in to submit the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘Speakers should not take sides’ - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/14/speakers-should-not-take-sides-sultan-wants-rules-and-standards-of-house-upheld/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDxZIvTZR2pATWL-ZF5qqIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/14/speakers-should-not-take-sides-sultan-wants-rules-and-standards-of-house-upheld/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Speakers should not take sides’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SHAH ALAM: Speakers are the key pillars in the democratic process and should be politically impartial, says the Selangor state Ruler. Sultan Sharafuddin Idris Shah said a Speaker has to be fair, mature, honest and knowledgeable with high integrity. “Speakers should never take sides, be it the ruling party or the opposition. “Hence, they have to uphold the rules and standards of the assembly and ensure that all members adhere to them,” he said at the opening of the three-day 2017 Conference of Parliamentary and State Assembly Speakers of Malaysia at a hotel here yesterday. Sultan Sharafuddin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Moving beyond tolerance - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/28/moving-beyond-tolerance-for-the-country-to-be-happy-whole-and-accepting-we-need-to-not-just-tolerate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEARWOvUbeRup75OXhFmiNMQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/05/28/moving-beyond-tolerance-for-the-country-to-be-happy-whole-and-accepting-we-need-to-not-just-tolerate/" target="_blank"&gt;Moving beyond tolerance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF the state of Malaysian society could be likened to a set of traffic lights, it’s the yellow caution light that is blinking now, says Dr Shahreen Mat Nayan, 42. “I don’t see a red or green light but a yellow one, and that is a warning sign if we don’t nip things in the bud. It means we can still live in this environment but we shouldn’t let it get worse,” says the Universiti Malaya senior lecturer who teaches journalism, rhetoric, and current issues and does research on inclusivity, diversity, and women activism. She says Malaysians need to work harder at being civil to each other. Civili...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Whither go the nons? - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/whither-go-the-nons/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBpemhqRAPDVvRMmLVitKHEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 05:00:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/whither-go-the-nons/" target="_blank"&gt;Whither go the nons?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Does proselytization mean we cannot talk about our beliefs in any way, shape, or form? Scott Ng, Free Malaysia Today The uncomfortable tension between Malaysia’s religious majority and the various minorities is once again threating to come to a head, this time over the accusation by UUM lecturer Kamarul Zaman Yusoff that Selangor Speaker Hannah Yeoh’s autobiography contains elements of proselytisation for her Christian faith. Yeoh, well known among her constituents as an avid churchgoer, released her biography back in 2014 and the authorities placed no restrictions on the sale of book. Kama...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Bebas: Lecturer’s proselytisation claim feeds Muslim paranoia - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/bebas-lecturers-proselytisation-claim-feeds-muslim-paranoia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA3-vB9xkDezKs0T036tIaYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 04:39:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/bebas-lecturers-proselytisation-claim-feeds-muslim-paranoia/" target="_blank"&gt;Bebas: Lecturer’s proselytisation claim feeds Muslim paranoia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – They should not accuse Christians of criminal acts, simply when they sing praises of their own religion. A university lecturer’s claim that Selangor Speaker Hannah Yeoh was attempting to proselytise the Muslims by speaking of her personal religious experience is “absurd”, said rights group Bebas. The group’s spokesperson Azrul Mohd Khalib said the arguments put forward by the lecturer, Kamarul Zaman Yusoff, “feeds into the paranoia that Muslims, in a Muslim majority country, should forever feel insecure, afraid and suspicious of those of other faiths”. “Such arguments use fear, bigo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>UUM don rails against Yeoh, now wants DAP deregistered - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIelB4EwHfOjEoq272xEg4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 01:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After lodging a police report against DAP assemblyperson Hannah Yeoh, Universiti Utara Malaysia (UUM) lecturer Kamarul Zaman Yusoff has now trained his guns on DAP itself. Kamarul Zaman, who lodged a report on May 17 against Yeoh for allegedly "proselytising" in her biography, now intends to urge the Registrar of Societies (ROS) to cancel DAP's registration as a political party. "To all academicians working in local universities, it is my pleasure to inform you that I have started an initiative to prepare a memorandum to urge the ROS to send a show-cause letter to DAP (to explain) why their...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Selangor State Assembly to have sign language interpreter - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2016/11/09/selangor-state-assembly-to-have-sign-language-interpreter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELyMXBespxU47nqZhO9yVJgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 08:40:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2016/11/09/selangor-state-assembly-to-have-sign-language-interpreter/" target="_blank"&gt;Selangor State Assembly to have sign language interpreter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SIGN language interpreter will be included throughout the live telecast of the Selangor Legislative Assembly sitting in 2017. Selangor Speaker Hannah Yeoh said the initiative had been on a trial run since Tuesday and will go on until the sitting ends on Friday. “We have set aside a budget together with TVSelangor for this. “We will have this feature included throughout the sitting starting next year so that the hearing-impaired community, who are also tax payers, can follow the telecast. “We urge our friends with disability to log on and watch it in the next few days and give us feedback ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Outdoor equipment upgrade for USJ 1 field - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2016/12/03/outdoor-equipment-upgrade-for-usj-1-field-xxxx/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIRIrTINMgkIuyS3JBHp_R8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2016/12/03/outdoor-equipment-upgrade-for-usj-1-field-xxxx/" target="_blank"&gt;Outdoor equipment upgrade for USJ 1 field&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIVE new outdoor gym sets have been added to the USJ 1 recreational field. A trio station, beam jump, ostrich ride, double mirage walker and knee lift, which cost RM29,400, were installed by the Subang Jaya Municipal Council. Another RM3,700 was also spent on a see-saw. The area, known as Padang Cegas on Jalan USJ 1/2, already has facilities such as tennis, basketball, skating and futsal courts, slides and monkey bars. During the launch on Dec 1, students of Excel Education International were already there bright and early to utilise the equipment. Lai Sue Ann, 13, said her school did not h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>School gets funds to repair its walkway - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/08/22/school-gets-funds-to-repair-its-walkway/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhfK7vY69j79xxPxtRx3iMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/08/22/school-gets-funds-to-repair-its-walkway/" target="_blank"&gt;School gets funds to repair its walkway&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SJK(C) Lick Hung in Subang Jaya has finally got half of its damaged walkway repaired. Its Parent-Teacher Association (PTA) chairman Lim Kok Sang said students kept tripping over broken pieces of the concrete pavement in the past and it badly needed repairs. He said the school received RM20,000 from Subang Jaya assemblyman Hannah Yeoh and would get another RM50,000 from the state government. The RM20,000, he said, was used to repair half of the damaged walkway which was about a 162 sq m area while the other half would be repaired with the state government allocation later. “The state’s alloc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>A public park by the people and for the people - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/03/31/a-public-park-by-the-people-and-for-the-people/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELylLYjraHf0KE3GuWWDipEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/03/31/a-public-park-by-the-people-and-for-the-people/" target="_blank"&gt;A public park by the people and for the people&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR THE next six months, the public will have the chance to give suggestions and vote for the amenities they want at the Millennium Park in SS13, Subang Jaya. Located along Jalan SS13/1a and SS13/2, the park has several prototypes of amenities for park-goers to choose from. At the launch on Sunday, Subang Jaya assemblyman Hannah Yeoh, who allocated RM20,000 for the project, said it would re-energise and re-imagine the Millennium Park. “It was abandoned for years. In 2008, the Subang Jaya Municipal Council cleared the area and on World Environment Day, we planted some trees. It was also gaze...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hannah Yeoh files report over ‘biggest hypocrite’ article - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/hannah-yeoh-files-report-over-biggest-hypocrite-article/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN7RPlD2sb_dylDYmsKV9wIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 03:53:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/hannah-yeoh-files-report-over-biggest-hypocrite-article/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah Yeoh files report over ‘biggest hypocrite’ article&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – I was sharing my journey and it was not easy. I was a nobody. But if you want to twist, you can take any angle to twist. The Selangor assembly speaker says article by UUM lecturer, based on her book, ‘Becoming Hannah’, is defamatory in nature. Selangor speaker Hannah Yeoh today lodged a police report against a lecturer over an essay she claims is defamatory in nature. The essay — titled “Hannah Yeoh contoh hipokrasi terbesar DAP” (“Hannah Yeoh is the biggest hypocrite in DAP”) — by Kamarul Zaman Yusoff alleged that the Subang Jaya assemblyperson had mixed politics with her Christian...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Women's groups march to Parliament to demand Maria Chin's release - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/23/womens-groups-march-to-parliament-to-petition-for-maria-chins-release/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMqwyZDOE1cAuHUewJbmRU8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 04:23:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/11/23/womens-groups-march-to-parliament-to-petition-for-maria-chins-release/" target="_blank"&gt;Women's groups march to Parliament to demand Maria Chin's release&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A group of protesters walking towards Parliament to demand the release of Bersih 2.0 chairman Maria Chin Abdullah were prevented from entering the building. They started their march from Padang Merbok at 10.30am on Wednesday. The participants, who represented various women's rights groups, had encountered a police barricade on the bridge of Jalan Parlimen leading up to the Parliament guardhouse. They were meant to hand over a petition to the Prime Minister or relevant Ministers to release Maria, who is being detained under the Security Offences (Special Measures) Act (Sosma). ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>I didn’t start fight with Hannah Yeoh, says UUM lecturer - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/i-didnt-start-fight-with-hannah-yeoh-says-uum-lecturer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPgWVOOxp-7s0ZpyiH0BGWkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 06:02:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/i-didnt-start-fight-with-hannah-yeoh-says-uum-lecturer/" target="_blank"&gt;I didn’t start fight with Hannah Yeoh, says UUM lecturer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kamarul Zaman Yusoff says Selangor state speaker should have engaged him in a debate about the book instead of filing a police report, and have DAP attack him. (FMT) – The lecturer who had accused Selangor state assembly speaker Hannah Yeoh of trying to proselytise the public with her personal autobiography, said he was a victim of DAP’s “hypocrisy”. Offering his side of the story, Universiti Utara Malaysia’s (UUM) lecturer Kamarul Zaman Yusoff said he had never intended to start a war with DAP. Neither did he expect that what started off as a personal academic analysis of Yeoh’s book, woul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Candlelight vigils held around the country for missing pastor - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/05/candlelight-vigils-held-around-the-country-for-missing-pastor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBACg3pBfzV5xn01IDQOBqsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 14:00:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/03/05/candlelight-vigils-held-around-the-country-for-missing-pastor/" target="_blank"&gt;Candlelight vigils held around the country for missing pastor&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SHAH ALAM: Hundreds of Malaysians gathered at a candlelight vigil Sunday to stand in solidarity with the family of missing pastor Raymond Koh. There was a heavy police presence as the crowd gathered at some shophouses, after they were prevented from gathering front of the Selangor police headquarters here. The crowd were seen holding placards that read "Where is Pastor Raymond" and "Let Raymond go". The vigil was organised by a fellow pastor S.M. Yee. Also sighted at the vigil was DAP's Subang Jaya assemblyman Hannah Yeoh, Amanah president Mohammad Sabu and Selangor Ikram chairman Norazmi M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>What the public have to say - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/focus/2017/01/04/what-the-public-have-to-say/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB5emNzr1jLOOpdiRse9hW4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/focus/2017/01/04/what-the-public-have-to-say/" target="_blank"&gt;What the public have to say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Kow Cheong Wei Puchong People Service Centre chief Dr Kow Cheong Wei was one of the pioneer councillors for MPSJ, serving as a councillor from 1998 to 2008. “We were the first batch and went through hardcore years. “With areas such as Seri Kembangan, which was a new village, the main task was to strike a balance between developed areas and places left out by history. “I do not think a council can go far if councillors just go for meeting and approve minutes. We have to brainstorm for ideas,” he said. He is proud that MPSJ is an award-winning council. “We won the top three council award t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Speaker rejects motion on Syariah court, BN reps cry foul - Malaysiakini</title><link>http://www.malaysiakini.com/news/362180</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBTG50uZcGfIETJ55KHHWBYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysiakini.com/news/362180" target="_blank"&gt;Speaker rejects motion on Syariah court, BN reps cry foul&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selangor Barisan Nasional assemblypersons have expressed regret over the speaker's rejection of the proposed motion to empower the Syariah court institution in the state during the state legislative assembly last week. Permatang assemblyperson Sulaiman Abdul Razak, who represented the group, said the proposal was submitted to the assembly on Oct 13, but was rejected by speaker Hannah Yeoh in chambers on Nov 2, on the grounds that Syariah courts were under the judiciary, and not subject to legislative jurisdiction. "We regret the rejection as the issue needs to be discussed to empower Syaria...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysiakini.com">Malaysiakini</source></item><item><title>Resist the attempt to stifle academic freedom - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/resist-the-attempt-to-stifle-academic-freedom/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILbJXw6_09ZC5smRw4evyUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMPrpnwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 16:28:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/resist-the-attempt-to-stifle-academic-freedom/" target="_blank"&gt;Resist the attempt to stifle academic freedom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CENTHRA, CLJ, MLC, PPMM, iPeguam and YP We, the Centre for Human Rights Research and Advocacy (CENTHRA), Concerned Lawyers for Justice (CLJ), Malaysian Lawyears Circle (MLC), Muslim Lawyers Association Malaysia (PPMM), iPeguam and Young Professionals (YP), strongly protest and condemn the police report lodged by Speaker of the Selangor State Legislative Assembly and Subang Jaya assemblywoman Hannah Yeoh, and her subsequent public statement against Universiti Utara Malaysia academician and professor Dr Kamarul Zaman Yusoff. On 10th May 2017, Dr Kamarul, who is the UUM’s Malaysian Institute f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Nursing room set up at state secretariat building - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2017/09/21/nursing-room-set-up-at-state-secretariat-building/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEInrYFU2p2FYIJ3cJTPkjQYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2017/09/21/nursing-room-set-up-at-state-secretariat-building/" target="_blank"&gt;Nursing room set up at state secretariat building&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A nursing room for mothers has been set up at the Selangor secretariat building (SUK) in Shah Alam. The room at SUK foyer that will cater to female visitors and employees was launched by Selangor health, welfare, women and family affairs committee chairman Dr Daroyah Alwi yesterday. Dr Daroyah said the initiative was to provide mothers with a conducive and comfortable environment to nurse their child. “There is also another nursing room at Dewan Negeri office that was opened by state assembly speaker Hannah Yeoh,” she said. She said the facilities were added after a study on women-friendly ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>USJ 13 RT area members focus on keeping their neighbourhood safe - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2017/09/11/usj-13-rt-area-members-focus-on-keeping-their-neighbourhood-safe/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJUIuC-Jave_o11wdqDzsn0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2017/09/11/usj-13-rt-area-members-focus-on-keeping-their-neighbourhood-safe/" target="_blank"&gt;USJ 13 RT area members focus on keeping their neighbourhood safe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USJ 13 Kawasan Rukun Tetangga (KRT) members patrol their neighbourhood on bicycles, three times a week, to keep the area safe. Nick Loong, who heads the KRT cycling patrol, said there were 10 regulars in the patrolling unit. “Initially some members borrowed bicycles, donated by Subang Jaya assemblyman Hannah Yeoh, but once they got into cycling, they bought their own gear. “Our focus is on neighbourhood safety and promoting a healthy lifestyle,” he said. In line with their goal to promote health and fitness among residents, a line dance group is currently recruiting members. Residents c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>What residents have to say - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/02/23/what-residents-have-to-say/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE-owMP9m1F2N4JT8Fg6s_4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2017/02/23/what-residents-have-to-say/" target="_blank"&gt;What residents have to say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE standards MPSJ maintained now are certainly befitting that of a city. In fact, I think that it is better than most cities. Council officers are quick to respond to any complaints, especially via WhatsApp chat groups. MPSJ needs to improve the parking system, making sure that the machines are properly maintained and in working order. More parking lots are required, to solve parking issues, especially haphazard parking in commercial areas. MPSJ should also keep to its 40% greenery target and ensure developers adhere to the master plans submitted.” – Putra Heights resident Adrian Looi I HO...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>War of words over insensitive remarks - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2016/11/11/war-of-words-over-insensitive-remarks-reps-argue-following-reference-to-may-13-riot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH9ohyRVoVIcmZondHHBLzgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/metro/community/2016/11/11/war-of-words-over-insensitive-remarks-reps-argue-following-reference-to-may-13-riot/" target="_blank"&gt;War of words over insensitive remarks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE calm and order of the current state assembly sitting was disrupted on the ninth day yesterday following a series of heated arguments involving the assemblymen from both sides of the political divide. Barisan Nasional and Pakatan Harapan assemblymen were involved in a shouting match for 15 minutes over the use of word bodoh (stupid) at the state assembly. In the incident, State Investment Committee chairman Datuk Teng Chang Khim demanded Datuk Sulaiman Abdul Razak (BN-Permatang) to withdraw his statement that DAP caused the May 13 racial riot in 1969. Teng said it was a provocative state...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘Making DAP the bogeyman will fail’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/22/making-dap-the-bogeyman-will-fail-yeoh-pushing-a-racist-agenda-has-been-tried-before-and-didnt-work/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHpack-fUBgmISAYSY_JqRQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/22/making-dap-the-bogeyman-will-fail-yeoh-pushing-a-racist-agenda-has-been-tried-before-and-didnt-work/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Making DAP the bogeyman will fail’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Making DAP the bogeyman to push a racist agenda would surely fail, says a DAP leader and deputy minister. DAP Segambut MP and Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister Hannah Yeoh said for years Umno made DAP the bogeyman to forward its racist agenda, only to be rejected by Malaysians during the last general election after decades in power. “The Gagasan Kuasa 3 (G3) which vows to destroy DAP is similar to the Umno movement which all these years made DAP the bogeyman,” she said. “But Malaysians are smarter nowadays and voted Umno out. Today, DAP is in power in Put...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hannah Yeoh: Offenders can slip through cracks in Child Registry - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/12/hannah-yeoh-offenders-can-slip-through-cracks-in-child-registry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN5jeWUbAWWdu1BbmVf4z1UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 06:39:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/12/hannah-yeoh-offenders-can-slip-through-cracks-in-child-registry/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah Yeoh: Offenders can slip through cracks in Child Registry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister Hannah Yeoh says that they will not encourage the public to use the recently-created Child Registry to screen for child abusers as it has shortcomings that could see them slip through. "Promotion to encourage the use of the registry for screening purposes will not be expanded as there are worries that some individuals that may slip through the screening due to incomplete information," she said. Since its creation last year, Yeoh said that 536 convicted child offenders were registered with the Registry. However, she said o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>MCA: Ministry should focus on bigger issues than divorce - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/14/mca-ministry-should-focus-on-bigger-things-than-divorce/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMPmldKzqTokTMbAtYqWQYcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 12:24:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/14/mca-ministry-should-focus-on-bigger-things-than-divorce/" target="_blank"&gt;MCA: Ministry should focus on bigger issues than divorce&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: MCA has criticised the Women, Family and Community Development Ministry for focusing on divorce cases instead of more pertinent issues such as child marriage and other social ills affecting the country. "More pertinent attention by the federal government should be paid on the devastating issues of child marriage, abandoned babies, domestic violence and child abuse. These social problems must be addressed. "Marriage and divorce are personal matters. Once the romance has died down, reasons cited for marital break-down can verge on unusual. "The government should refrain from in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Trivial reasons given for divorce - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/14/trivial-reasons-given-for-divorce-counselling-plus-pre-and-postmarriage-courses-in-the-wo-snoring-an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM1tvXZBLtF8daOfuYC4m7QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/14/trivial-reasons-given-for-divorce-counselling-plus-pre-and-postmarriage-courses-in-the-wo-snoring-an/" target="_blank"&gt;Trivial reasons given for divorce&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Marriages are supposedly made in heaven but when things don’t go well even a spouse’s snoring is grounds for divorce. Other reasons that made couples abandon their vows include wives who go on trips with friends too often or those who do their laundry at night. Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister Hannah Yeoh, referring to a media report that quoted the Selangor Syariah Judiciary Department, said these were among reasons for divorce among couples who had been married less than five years. “Even I wash my clothes at night but this is (apparently) among the re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Activists and school students gather at Parliament urging end to child marriage - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/13/activists-and-school-students-gather-at-parliament-urging-end-to-child-marriage/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAGJoME38CsKIHlHbbNaurwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 08:38:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/13/activists-and-school-students-gather-at-parliament-urging-end-to-child-marriage/" target="_blank"&gt;Activists and school students gather at Parliament urging end to child marriage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A group of civil society activists and school students staged a peaceful demonstration in front of Parliament to urge the government to ban child marriages. The gathering, which began at 8am, saw the attendance of about 70 protestors, consisting of activists, and students clad in school or girl guide uniforms. They were seen holding placards that read #SchoolNotSpouse, #PelajarBukanPengantin, 18 for all. No exceptions”, “#wheniwas11, #igotmarriedat11, #endchildmarriages”. The placards also bore the logos of Sisters in Islam, Women’s Aid Organisation, and The Body Shop. The pea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>TTDI residents gear up for zero waste - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/11/12/ttdi-residents-gear-up-for-zero-waste/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHHaaerxwJVKXaOnKSnuy2UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/11/12/ttdi-residents-gear-up-for-zero-waste/" target="_blank"&gt;TTDI residents gear up for zero waste&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A GROUP of like-minded residents in Taman Tun Dr Ismail (TTDI) started a Zero Waste Initiative and, to their surprise, they managed to recycle about 50% of their waste. The initiative comprised 22 households and they separated their waste for three months, between October and December last year. The residents were part of the Transition TTDI group which focuses on environmental related activities. They hosted a community environmental educational event on waste separation which was attended by Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister Hannah Yeoh. Khoo Zhao Phin from Transitio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘Will action be taken against parents of dead baby?’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/13/will-action-be-taken-against-parents-of-dead-baby/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEKIxD5rraD7YPOY0uxaaLQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/13/will-action-be-taken-against-parents-of-dead-baby/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Will action be taken against parents of dead baby?’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: An Opposition lawmaker has raised the question on whether action should be taken against the parents of 11-month-old infant Nur Muazara Ulfa Mohammad Zainal who died from alleged physical and sexual abuse. “As what was said, there were early symptoms of child abuse. “I wish to know if the government will take action against the parents as this is considered a form of negligence towards the safety of their children,” Datuk Jalaluddin Alias (BN-Jelebu) said when raising a supplementary question during Question and Answer Time in Parliament yesterday. Women, Family and Community ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakatan govt should protect wives from abusive or sex maniac husbands says Wanita MCA - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/pakatan-govt-should-protect-wives-from-abusive-or-sex-maniac-husbands-says-wanita-mca/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHVx7HyI5x8MLEtKymBgpecqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:02:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/pakatan-govt-should-protect-wives-from-abusive-or-sex-maniac-husbands-says-wanita-mca/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan govt should protect wives from abusive or sex maniac husbands says Wanita MCA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Wanita MCA says the Pakatan Harapan government should protect wives from abusive or sex maniac husbands. As such, Wanita MCA chief Datuk Heng Seai Kie (pic) has challenged the Minister and Deputy Minister of the Women, Family and Community Development to state their stand on whether the government will or will not criminalise marital rape She said the Minister, Datin Seri Dr Wan Azizan Wan Ismail, and her deputy, Hannah Yeoh, should both state the ministry’s stand on the Parliamentary reply by Mohamed Hanipa Maidin, which was that the government has no plans to amend laws to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Cops to probe sexual assault claim on ex-minister despite retraction - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/30/cops-to-probe-sexual-assault-claim-on-ex-minister-despite-retraction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENYRiESw0ikDWm32qebs4N4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 05:22:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/30/cops-to-probe-sexual-assault-claim-on-ex-minister-despite-retraction/" target="_blank"&gt;Cops to probe sexual assault claim on ex-minister despite retraction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – The police today said they would investigate a complaint by a 15-year-old girl who claimed to have been molested by a senior politician and former minister, just hours after saying they would not pursue the case as the complainant had retracted her report. In a short texted reply to FMT, Perlis police chief Noor Mushar Mohd said the case would be investigated under Section 14 (a) of the Sexual Offences Against Children Act 2017. However, he declined to divulge further details in the interest of protecting the complainant’s identity. Section 14 of the act states that any person who t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Christian lawmakers pledge to combat graft - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/christian-lawmakers-pledge-to-combat-graft/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPFxDqA59CHJWJYNOtRDH_8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/christian-lawmakers-pledge-to-combat-graft/" target="_blank"&gt;Christian lawmakers pledge to combat graft&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysian Christian lawmakers and church leaders pledged to combat corruption and act justly. The MPs include Works Minister Baru Bian, Primary Industries Minister Teresa Kok, Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Datuk Liew Vui Keong, Deputy Women, Family and Community Develop­ment Minister Hannah Yeoh and Deputy Youth and Sports Minister Steven Sim. The MPs and church leaders signed a pledge at the parliamentary prayer and worship meet at Royal Lake Club yesterday. Liew said that the last day for MPs to file their declaration of assets would be today and that their ass...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Don’t mess with me, Guan Eng tells DAP leaders who applied for and accepted titles - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/28/dont-mess-with-me-guan-eng-tells-dap-leaders-who-applied-for-and-accepted-titles/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECAkuqSvBrcCDAAZFocdovEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 07:47:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/28/dont-mess-with-me-guan-eng-tells-dap-leaders-who-applied-for-and-accepted-titles/" target="_blank"&gt;Don’t mess with me, Guan Eng tells DAP leaders who applied for and accepted titles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAP people are not to apply for and accept titles and awards from the Raja-Raja Melayu (FMT) – DAP secretary-general Lim Guan Eng today issued a stern warning to DAP’s elected representatives and councillors who accepted titles and awards. He threatened to take stern action against those who do. In a fiery speech, Lim said these DAP representatives should not challenge the party or leadership. “Some people think that if they become a state Exco member, they can become a Datuk; they feel it’s their right. That is not right. “Don’t mess with me. Regardless of your position, I will take action...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Politician lambasted for suggesting Indonesia quake disaster was god’s wrath against gay people - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/442054-malaysia-politician-gay-earthquake/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBW9M3bvIsmG7X-LH6jM0DwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 16:34:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/442054-malaysia-politician-gay-earthquake/" target="_blank"&gt;Politician lambasted for suggesting Indonesia quake disaster was god’s wrath against gay people&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;With money laundering charges pending, the president of Malaysia’s main opposition party stoked outrage among ministers by suggesting natural disasters are god’s punishment for transgender and homosexual communities. Last month, around 2,000 people were killed when a powerful 7.5 magnitude earthquake struck the Indonesian island of Sulawesi and triggered a devastating tsunami. READ MORE: Powerful tsunami strikes Indonesian island after huge quake – geophysics agency (VIDEO) Opposition leader Ahmad Zahid Hamidi inferred to the Malaysian Parliament that the neighboring state’s recent disaster...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Ministers, activists criticise Zahid's LGBT remark (Updated) - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/23/govt-ministers-criticise-zahid-s-lgbt-remark/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOTVqziAkDyfd9_D9lfBMlAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 07:29:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/23/govt-ministers-criticise-zahid-s-lgbt-remark/" target="_blank"&gt;Ministers, activists criticise Zahid's LGBT remark (Updated)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Ministers and social advocates have criticised Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi for suggesting that the activities of the Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender (LGBT) community might incur God's wrath. They said the focus should instead be on pressing issues such as corruption. Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister Hannah Yeoh said instead of LGBT, corruption was the "biggest social ill and immoral activity" in Malaysia. "Of all the pressing issues the Opposition leader @Zahid_Hamidi could have raised, he chose this. "Corruption is the biggest social ill an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Many defend Zahid’s grandchild, saying she is too young to be involved - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/22/many-defend-zahids-grandchild-saying-she-is-too-young-to-be-involved/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEORibyl6I4FcEU0_q_uNDLkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/22/many-defend-zahids-grandchild-saying-she-is-too-young-to-be-involved/" target="_blank"&gt;Many defend Zahid’s grandchild, saying she is too young to be involved&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Large sections of society have come to the defence of the granddaughter of Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi after the nine-year-old’s viral video backing the latter ended up attracting severe criticism. The video recording of the girl “warning” those responsible for her grandfather’s arrest was first posted on her mother’s Instagram account on Saturday. It quickly went viral on social media, irking Malay­sians who starting hurling insulting comments directed at the girl. In the comment section of one news portal that featured the video, readers made disparaging remarks agains...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Cyberbullies told to lay off Zahid's 9-year-old granddaughter over Instagram post - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/21/cyberbullies-told-to-lay-off-zahids-9yearold-granddaughter-over-instagram-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM9kotnQc9EJm12vXo6b2WYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 09:29:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/21/cyberbullies-told-to-lay-off-zahids-9yearold-granddaughter-over-instagram-post/" target="_blank"&gt;Cyberbullies told to lay off Zahid's 9-year-old granddaughter over Instagram post&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Stop the verbal harassment against a nine-year-old girl who didn't know better - that's the message from politicians and activists after Datuk Seri Dr Ahmad Zahid Hamidi's granddaughter became a target of cyberbullying over a viral video of her defending him. The video recording of the girl "warning" those responsible for her grandfather's arrest was first posted on her mother's Instagram page on Saturday (Oct 21). It quickly went viral over several social media platforms, irking Malaysians who starting hurling insulting comments directed at the girl. In the comments section ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Many not fit to be parents, says Hannah Yeoh on child abuse issue - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/06/many-not-fit-to-be-parents-says-hannah-yeoh-on-child-abuse-issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPv__eYXkyyHUzuLZUVDkzEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 05:46:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/06/many-not-fit-to-be-parents-says-hannah-yeoh-on-child-abuse-issue/" target="_blank"&gt;Many not fit to be parents, says Hannah Yeoh on child abuse issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Many parents are not fit to be parents, says deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister Hannah Yeoh (pic) in relation to cases of child abuse. She said the protection of a child’s welfare should start with the parents. “If you want to talk about child protection and child safety, statistics show that they are not just abused by nannies or homes; parents also abuse their children,” she said at BFM’s Health and Living Jr fair by AIA Vitality. On child marriage, she said ministry officials were going on the ground to educate parents on the issue. “Our officers have t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hannah defends views after getting roasted in Sarawak - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/01/hannah-defends-views-after-getting-roasted-in-sarawak/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECO8YoO_kLw03uV_083iq9oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 08:34:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/10/01/hannah-defends-views-after-getting-roasted-in-sarawak/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah defends views after getting roasted in Sarawak&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – Hannah Yeoh, the deputy minister for women’s affairs, has defended her criticism of the “Sarawak for Sarawakians” sentiments, saying Malaysians do not need to be divided by yet another factor. “Malaysians have long been divided by race, religion and now region with sentiment such as Sarawak for Sarawakians only,” the DAP MP said today, responding to angry comments in the Sarawak media over her remarks at a forum in Kuching last week. “We need a Malaysia Baru that focuses on us being one. The local media in Sarawak has attacked me for not respecting Sarawak. This is far from the trut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Hannah Yeoh: Stop blaming and shaming woman victim in autism molest case - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/19/hannah-yeoh-stop-blaming-shaming-woman-victim-in-autism-molest-case/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC2yzzfTCx7KufHtKl_u3i8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:23:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/19/hannah-yeoh-stop-blaming-shaming-woman-victim-in-autism-molest-case/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah Yeoh: Stop blaming and shaming woman victim in autism molest case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Members of the public need to stop “nasty comments” on the 23-year-old victim in the molest case involving a 22-year-old autistic man, said Hannah Yeoh. The Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister said she met with the victim, whom she said was “very traumatised” by the incident. “I urge the public to stop condemning the victim. “This young woman who is the victim in this case was very traumatised by the incident. I have seen the police report and she was actually touched in the private parts. “I have seen online comments. The victim shaming and victim blaming has...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Khairy has been critical of Umno, let's see if he will rebel, says Hannah Yeoh - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/19/khairy-has-been-critical-of-umno-lets-see-if-he-will-rebel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0SqnyV6OHs0dIZ2FiC6EUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:45:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/19/khairy-has-been-critical-of-umno-lets-see-if-he-will-rebel/" target="_blank"&gt;Khairy has been critical of Umno, let's see if he will rebel, says Hannah Yeoh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: All eyes will be on Khairy Jamaluddin after several senior Umno leaders announced their departure from the party, says Hannah Yeoh. The Wanita DAP vice-chairman said the Rembau MP and former Umno Youth Chief was “the only one in Umno who talks sense” and therefore could be the next one to rebel. “Now, everybody is waiting to see what KJ will do next. As we have seen, he has been very critical of Umno. "Recently, there was a parliament walkout but only Khairy and Anifah stayed,” said Yeoh to reporters, when asked about the recent exodus of Umno leaders. On Wednesday (Sept 19), sen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Wanita MCA slams Wan Azizah, says federal govt must make child marriage a crime - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/19/wanita-mca-slams-wan-azizah-federal-govt-must-make-child-marriage-crime/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB9ZXpXKwGzuW-vnu4wicP8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 09:54:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/19/wanita-mca-slams-wan-azizah-federal-govt-must-make-child-marriage-crime/" target="_blank"&gt;Wanita MCA slams Wan Azizah, says federal govt must make child marriage a crime&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Wanita MCA has urged the Government to make child marriages a criminal offence under Federal law. Wanita chief Datuk Heng Seai Kie said irrespective of race or religion, child marriages must be strictly prohibited as a way to demonstrate the nation’s determination to defend children’s safety and rights. Heng also lambasted Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Dr Wan Azizah Wan Ismail's handling of the issue of child marriage cases in Kelantan, adding that it was regrettable and disappointing that the Government has not increased the minimum legal marriage age to 18. Heng said a c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Being Hannah - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/16/being-hannah-from-an-accidental-politician-to-selangor-state-assembly-speaker-and-now-deputy-women-f/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJqiN4bxknuG1ESQhSm09PcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/16/being-hannah-from-an-accidental-politician-to-selangor-state-assembly-speaker-and-now-deputy-women-f/" target="_blank"&gt;Being Hannah&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;HANNAH Yeoh Tseow Suan is a household name these days. When she made the move from Subang Jaya to contest Segambut’s parliamentary seat, she found herself treated like a celebrity. And her meteoric rise continued with a thumping 82% win in GE14 and her appointment as Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister. The journey has come with some changes. “In Subang Jaya for the last 10 years, I was able to walk around malls and public places without being recognised. But now I find that it’s quite a problem to go out without being stopped for photographs. We are all learning to cope...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hannah striving to change mindset of civil servants for an inclusive M'sia - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/31/hannah-striving-to-change-mindset-of-civil-servants-for-an-inclusive-msia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKEoNcBEyE00IsRlCtJGzowqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 09:44:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/31/hannah-striving-to-change-mindset-of-civil-servants-for-an-inclusive-msia/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah striving to change mindset of civil servants for an inclusive M'sia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Changing the mindset of Malaysians to rebuild a new inclusive Malaysia is difficult, and that is why Hannah Yeoh wants to start with the civil service. "Changing government is the easy part, changing mindset is the hardest," said the Women, Family and Community deputy minister during a Merdeka Day celebration held by Malaysians for Malaysia on Thursday (Aug 31). Yeoh said the new mould for Malaysia should be not divisive or tear people down, and she aimed to achieve this by first changing the mindset of the civil service. "I'm trying to better them, challenge them to think out...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hannah Yeoh, Syahredzan condemn attacks on transgenders after vicious attack in Seremban - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/19/hannah-yeoh-syahredzan-condemn-attacks-on-transgenders-after-vicious-attack-in-seremban/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKMYbVWbwaxvgDrJfZOIJEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 12:56:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/19/hannah-yeoh-syahredzan-condemn-attacks-on-transgenders-after-vicious-attack-in-seremban/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah Yeoh, Syahredzan condemn attacks on transgenders after vicious attack in Seremban&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Physical and verbal attacks against the transgender community must stop, say DAP leaders Hannah Yeoh and Syahredzan Johan. In a joint statement, the Segambut MP and the lawyer, who is also Lim Kit Siang’s political secretary, said any such attacks were gross violations of human rights. They underlined that members of the transgender community should enjoy the same fundamental liberties as any other Malaysian citizen. “We believe that the wanton disregard for the lives of the transgender community is the result of the constant demonisation of the community by certain quarters....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hannah Yeoh: Ministry looking to amend Child Act to allow automatic registration of sex offenders - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/20/hannah-yeoh-ministry-looking-to-amend-child-act-to-allow-automatic-registration-of-sex-offenders/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDN-j-SSm4O-EhLvlledefoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 06:59:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/20/hannah-yeoh-ministry-looking-to-amend-child-act-to-allow-automatic-registration-of-sex-offenders/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah Yeoh: Ministry looking to amend Child Act to allow automatic registration of sex offenders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Child Act will be amended to ensure a more effective Child Registry that will, among others, provide for automatic registration of child sex offenders in the future. “Based on our findings, the registry is not comprehensive and checks revealed that it only contains the names of about 300 sexual offenders,” said Women, Family and Community Development Deputy Minister Hannah Yeoh. She cited delays in getting details of convicted paedophiles from the courts and police as a factor for this. She said that most of the information on child sex offenders are manually keyed into th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hannah Yeoh: Sexual harassment probe of KL hospital doctor to wrap up next week - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/16/sexual-harassment-probe-of-kl-hospital-doctor-to-wrap-up-next-week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP9ZfRZf_psCK8ZEM3O2dTgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 10:01:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/16/sexual-harassment-probe-of-kl-hospital-doctor-to-wrap-up-next-week/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah Yeoh: Sexual harassment probe of KL hospital doctor to wrap up next week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Investigations into the case of a senior doctor alleged to have sexually harassed female housemen in his hospital will be completed next week, says Women, Family and Community Development Deputy Minister Hannah Yeoh. She said the independent body looking into the case had launched a two-week investigation and would conclude their findings soon. As there is no Sexual Harassment Act in place yet, she said, the case needed to be investigated under the Penal Code and according to the 2005 civil service guidelines relating to sexual harassment in the workplace. “For now the enquiry...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hannah stands up for Dr Wan Azizah amidst child bride criticisms - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/hannah-stands-up-for-dr-wan-azizah-amidst-child-bride-criticisms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFt6qCB6smDD1-rryrNRZ50qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 07:39:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/hannah-stands-up-for-dr-wan-azizah-amidst-child-bride-criticisms/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah stands up for Dr Wan Azizah amidst child bride criticisms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: In response to criticism of Datuk Seri Dr Wan Azizah Wan Ismail on the 11-year-old child bride issue, Deputy Minister of Women, Family and Community Development Hannah Yeoh shared a heartfelt post about her time working under the Deputy Prime Minister’s leadership. In a Tuesday (Aug 7) update on her official Facebook page, she revealed that her experience with Dr Wan Azizah is “not just a process of learning about issues involving the ministry alone”, but also her partnership with other leaders. Calling the Deputy Prime Minister “Kak Wan”, she cited an anecdote of Dr Wan Aziz...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Yeoh lauds Selangor Sultan for initiating efforts to raise minimum age to 18 - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/07/yeoh-lauds-selangor-sultan-for-initiating-efforts-to-raise-minimum-age-to-18/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFy-TILLKJ4FAsY0_9mGk6IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:30:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/07/yeoh-lauds-selangor-sultan-for-initiating-efforts-to-raise-minimum-age-to-18/" target="_blank"&gt;Yeoh lauds Selangor Sultan for initiating efforts to raise minimum age to 18&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister Hannah Yeoh has lauded Selangor Ruler Sultan Sharafuddin Idris Shah's effort to raise the minimum age for marriage to 18 in Selangor. Yeoh, who had an audience with Sultan Sharafuddin at Istana Bukit Kayangan on Monday (Aug 6) morning, said she was happy to be back at the palace to thank the Selangor Ruler for initiating the effort. "I have enjoyed every conversation with Tuanku, understanding the whys behind Tuanku's decrees. "Here is a Ruler who is concerned about the best interest of children. Proud to be a Selangoria...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hannah Yeoh 'thorough investigation' needed for hospital sexual abuse claims - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/29/hannah-yeoh-thorough-investigation-needed-for-hospital-sexual-abuse-claims/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIQsHj6f_WROjlujC0Rm9FMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 13:36:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/29/hannah-yeoh-thorough-investigation-needed-for-hospital-sexual-abuse-claims/" target="_blank"&gt;Hannah Yeoh 'thorough investigation' needed for hospital sexual abuse claims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The allegations of sexual abuse against house officers (doctors) by a department head at a Klang Valley hospital are "very serious", said Hannah Yeoh. The Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister said that she has received an e-mail detailing the allegations from one of the house officers on Sunday (July 29). "I have read the email and the allegations are very serious," Yeoh said when contacted, adding that she will discuss the allegations with Women, Family and Community Development Minister Datuk Seri Wan Azizah Wan Ismail and Health Minister Dr Dzulkefly Ahm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Health and Women Ministries to discuss hospital sex predator issue - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/30/health-women-ministries-to-discuss-hospital-sex-predator-issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAxB-BLWgCzVzdoNkH38xmwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 04:42:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/30/health-women-ministries-to-discuss-hospital-sex-predator-issue/" target="_blank"&gt;Health and Women Ministries to discuss hospital sex predator issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Health Minister Dr Dzulkefly Ahmad will meet with the Women, Family and Community Development Ministry Monday (July 30), following The Star's front page expose of a sex predator in a Klang Valley hospital. "(Deputy Minister) Hannah Yeoh said she is ready to meet with me and Datuk Seri Dr Wan Azizah Wan Ismail. "We will meet soon, in fact today if I'm not mistaken, to discuss this. We are conducting a detailed investigation to get to the bottom of this. "It is not something we are unaware of, but there has been no concrete action so far. "We are looking at sending a stern warni...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Urgent need for laws against sexual harassment at workplace, says Yeoh - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/04/urgent-need-for-laws-against-sexual-harassment-at-workplace-says-yeoh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKBZ7RGIekrux03qGa_v77kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 04:05:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/04/urgent-need-for-laws-against-sexual-harassment-at-workplace-says-yeoh/" target="_blank"&gt;Urgent need for laws against sexual harassment at workplace, says Yeoh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: There is an "urgent" need to put in place legislation to prevent sexual harassment at the workplace, says Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister Hannah Yeoh. This comes in the wake of allegations of sexual harassment against female housemen at a Klang Valley hospital. "In this particular case, it is about who covered up (the complaints). "The victims said they had reported to the authorities, but there was no action," she told reporters at a Bukit Kiara Hikers group picnic on Saturday (Aug 4). Although there were laws under the Penal Code and a circular in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Workplace sexual harassment goes unreported due to fear, ignorance: Hannah Yeoh - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/01/workplace-sexual-harassment-goes-unreported-due-to-fear-ignorance-hannah-yeoh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO0nA-482OesivfUXUyB-_UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 05:27:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/01/workplace-sexual-harassment-goes-unreported-due-to-fear-ignorance-hannah-yeoh/" target="_blank"&gt;Workplace sexual harassment goes unreported due to fear, ignorance: Hannah Yeoh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Fear and ignorance are among the reasons why sexual harassment cases against women at the workplace go unreported, says Women, Family and Community Development Deputy Minister Hannah Yeoh. Between 2015 and 2017, there were a total of 47 cases of sexual harassment reported out of 1.6 million civil servants in the public sector. "I feel this may not be a real reflection of the situation at the respective ministries, as we get a lot of feedback from officers," she said when replying a supplementary question raised by Siti Zailah binti Mohd Yusoff (PAS-Rantau Panjang) in Parliamen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Register with welfare department to be eligible for benefits, urges deputy minister - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/07/24/record-on-the-disabled-inaccurate-register-with-welfare-department-to-be-eligible-for-benefits-urges/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGeJev5vIci9eDnlPJAsTBEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/07/24/record-on-the-disabled-inaccurate-register-with-welfare-department-to-be-eligible-for-benefits-urges/" target="_blank"&gt;Register with welfare department to be eligible for benefits, urges deputy minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PEOPLE with disabilities are encouraged to register with the Social Welfare Department to reap the benefits. Deputy Women, Family and Community Development Minister Hannah Yeoh said the numbers in the register were inaccurate because registration was not compulsory. “Resistance is an issue and because of social stigma within society, some families refuse to label their disabled children as differently-abled. “Recent statistics show that the number of registered disabled people in Kuala Lumpur is 31,750, while in Selangor it is 75,337,” said Yeoh at a charity carnival to raise funds for the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Who Is Hannah Yeoh, Deputy Women, Community and Family Development Minister? - CLEO Malaysia</title><link>http://cleo.com.my/who-is-hannah-yeoh-deputy-women-community-and-family-development-minister/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAcB_0utPCj2xXQlt637Oh8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowjLjeCjCS9NUBMIXynwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 11:27:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://cleo.com.my/who-is-hannah-yeoh-deputy-women-community-and-family-development-minister/" target="_blank"&gt;Who Is Hannah Yeoh, Deputy Women, Community and Family Development Minister?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CLEO Malaysia&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been following the elections and all its exciting developments, then you must have heard of Hannah Yeoh. She’s certainly been one of the stars of GE14, with her enthusiastic speeches and approachable demeanour. [caption id="attachment_53785" align="aligncenter" width="459"] DAP women who were sworn in today. From left: Teresa Kok (Primary Industries), Teo Nie Ching (Education), Hannah Yeoh (Women, Community &amp; Family), and Yeo Bee Yin (Energy, Green Technology, Science and Climate Change).[/caption] Recently sworn in as Deputy Women, Community and Family Development Minster, Hannah...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://cleo.com.my">CLEO Malaysia</source></item><item><title>Rumblings in DAP about jobs for Guan Eng’s clique - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/07/09/rumblings-in-dap-about-jobs-for-guan-engs-clique/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHrtkHco7ny9jOcTYH4n-xgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 04:56:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/07/09/rumblings-in-dap-about-jobs-for-guan-engs-clique/" target="_blank"&gt;Rumblings in DAP about jobs for Guan Eng’s clique&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior party official says there is unhappiness about senior members being sidelined, and that nominations based on party heirarchy are not being followed. (FMT) – A senior DAP politician says there is unhappiness within the party, particularly among some strongmen, about allies of party secretary-general Lim Guan Eng being appointed to the Cabinet. The politician, who asked to remain anonymous, told FMT that the DAP’s leadership had previously stated that the party’s Cabinet nominations for consideration by Prime Minister Dr Mahathir Mohamad would be based on positions held in the party ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Fiery start for Subang Jaya rep - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/focus/2018/06/26/fiery-start-for-subang-jaya-rep-legal-background-comes-in-handy-for-assemblyman/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJrGD5n3HX7Awm56ooKay6kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/focus/2018/06/26/fiery-start-for-subang-jaya-rep-legal-background-comes-in-handy-for-assemblyman/" target="_blank"&gt;Fiery start for Subang Jaya rep&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MICHELLE Ng had a fiery start in her very first week as Subang Jaya assemblyman when a fire broke out in her constituency. About 100 motorcycles were destroyed in the raze at the Angsana low-cost flats in USJ 1, Subang Jaya, in the wee hours of May 16. Michelle said someone even joked that she was “thrown into the fire in the very first week”. Michelle garnered 55,354 votes in GE14, winning with a 48,272-vote majority. “I was surprised with the results. As a newcomer, we have to win the people’s trust,” she said. Her new role has shifted from being a litigation lawyer to the people’s repres...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Javanese-speaking rep voted as new Speaker - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/06/27/javanesespeaking-rep-voted-as-new-speaker-ng-promises-fair-and-orderly-selangor-state-assembly-sitti/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9dt6FSOo1rUMrb6VgU1AsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/06/27/javanesespeaking-rep-voted-as-new-speaker-ng-promises-fair-and-orderly-selangor-state-assembly-sitti/" target="_blank"&gt;Javanese-speaking rep voted as new Speaker&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEKINCHAN assemblyman Ng Suee Lim, known for his witty Javanese comebacks and hearty laughs during debates in the Selangor State Assembly, will turn down a notch for his new role as Speaker. The four-term assemblyman has a following among fellow assemblymen including representatives from the opposition – Barisan Nasional and PAS – who enjoyed watching and hearing him speak. “The state assembly Speaker is an important and serious role and I know I will have to adapt and change my style to ensure the sitting is conducted in an orderly and fair manner,” said Ng, who is a former businessman. A ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>PH split over Dewan Speaker post? - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/21/ph-split-over-dewan-speaker-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECSAp9EDSIOIks7YELQJXroqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 04:58:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/21/ph-split-over-dewan-speaker-post/" target="_blank"&gt;PH split over Dewan Speaker post?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IS there a tussle between opposing camps in Pakatan Harapan (PH) concerning the appointment of the new Dewan Rakyat speaker? (NST) – Sources from within the ruling coalition and word on the ground reveal disagreements over candidates for the all-important post, which will become the face of Malaysia’s legislature in this brand new term. One name being bandied about is Tan Sri Dr Rais Yatim, a former Barisan Nasional cabinet minister who broke ranks with the party when he openly supported PH in the 14th General Election. Rais, 76, has held ministerial portfolios under five prime ministers, i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Three names being bandied for Dewan Rakyat Speaker’s post - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/22/three-names-being-bandied-for-dewan-rakyat-speakers-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOf_UE8ZBAia1enCQkgryJkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/22/three-names-being-bandied-for-dewan-rakyat-speakers-post/" target="_blank"&gt;Three names being bandied for Dewan Rakyat Speaker’s post&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: While some names have cropped up for the post of Speaker in the new Parliament that will start on July 16 – the first to be held since Pakatan Harapan formed the government – there is no formal discussion yet among the coalition partners on who this will be. Among the names mentioned are former minister Tan Sri Rais Yatim, social activist and lawyer S. Ambiga and former Selangor Speaker Han­nah Yeoh. Ambiga, who was formerly Bersih 2.0 chairman, is said to be the forerunner for the post – due to her being legally trained as well as hints dropped by Human Resources Minister M....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Award winner wants equal education rights for 40,000 refugee children - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/20/award-winner-wants-equal-education-rights-for-40000-refugee-children/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDJDz7siQTYwS8y1D8wPwegqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 04:08:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/20/award-winner-wants-equal-education-rights-for-40000-refugee-children/" target="_blank"&gt;Award winner wants equal education rights for 40,000 refugee children&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The sole Malaysian winner of the 2017 Queen's Young Leaders Award, Heidy Quah, wants some 40,000 refugee children here to have equal access to education. "I definitely want to be more involved in policy making and legislation, as that has always be the dream of Refuge for Refugees (RFTR) when we first started it," she told reporters after handing over her membership form to DAP adviser Lim Kit Siang here on Wednesday (June 20). Quah noted that she would like to see a policy in place that allows equal education opportunities for the 40,200 refugee children here who are younger...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>