<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Papua - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRE40Y25FU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:36:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>'Kill or be killed' says rebel group behind Papua massacre - The Sun Daily</title><link>https://www.thesundaily.my/world/kill-or-be-killed-says-rebel-group-behind-papua-massacre-BY230838</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZXN1bmRhaWx5Lm15L3dvcmxkL2tpbGwtb3ItYmUta2lsbGVkLXNheXMtcmViZWwtZ3JvdXAtYmVoaW5kLXBhcHVhLW1hc3NhY3JlLUJZMjMwODM40gEA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:14:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thesundaily.my/world/kill-or-be-killed-says-rebel-group-behind-papua-massacre-BY230838" target="_blank"&gt;'Kill or be killed' says rebel group behind Papua massacre&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Sun Daily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SORONG: Construction workers massacred at a remote jungle work camp in Papua were legitimate military targets, a rebel group said Friday, as authoriti...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpxa2NLbWpZQU1FVnVmWFZWSHJFNkhLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thesundaily.my">The Sun Daily</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/fnF_ON8ISVEhK2y5_Jks90nRxFkQ7LahyHMYlFlpSlt0kXyPlwNJtYgXpuWaPO9oYVDfXCPg9smS4GW3yUGgHnCXHb14Q6rm0SqAxuFsCz9hDKUeLKRTdDXl0IPZZXvCdkr5QANcMufaGw3E1bfjZWs7qLBhzROYcl7VilOxy9QKbkc-ekX1E8MRe9FNtZm6IYkTryhKF4Do4RSG=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Indonesia hunts suspects in alleged Papua mass killing - Asean Plus - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2018/12/05/indonesia-hunts-suspects-in-alleged-papua-mass-killing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780125183989</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 08:03:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2018/12/05/indonesia-hunts-suspects-in-alleged-papua-mass-killing/" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia hunts suspects in alleged Papua mass killing - Asean Plus&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thesundaily.my/world/indonesia-hunts-suspects-in-alleged-papua-mass-killing-YD216331" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia hunts suspects in alleged Papua mass killing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Sun Daily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/indonesia-hunts-suspects-papua-mass-killings-181205084835789.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia hunts suspects after Papua mass killings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWoxdl9Pa2pZQU1FVjY4Y2ZrZmg2Y3VLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/wergbw94kJG2_2aEPtglHgjkjKg2-JZZz8wECPMK82I-DA_ECQUO17aGUlx9Kpnv-9e4QbQoWmpw_trJS5Kj_kiDiTlmKQPq--AJ8Sg5Yamvn3PviOXHZx_anHfiCTJ000RNWPnc3fu8lkFVeGqPIyRwuLhu4O5SBKIFlg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Australian among hundreds of Papuan activists arrested in Indonesia - Channel NewsAsia</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/australian-among-hundreds-of-papuan-activists-arrested-in-indonesia-10991792</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMid2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNoYW5uZWxuZXdzYXNpYS5jb20vbmV3cy93b3JsZC9hdXN0cmFsaWFuLWFtb25nLWh1bmRyZWRzLW9mLXBhcHVhbi1hY3RpdmlzdHMtYXJyZXN0ZWQtaW4taW5kb25lc2lhLTEwOTkxNzky0gEA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 06:20:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/australian-among-hundreds-of-papuan-activists-arrested-in-indonesia-10991792" target="_blank"&gt;Australian among hundreds of Papuan activists arrested in Indonesia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Channel NewsAsia&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA: An Australian was among hundreds of pro-Papuan independence activists arrested across Indonesia at the weekend, police and rights groups ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.channelnewsasia.com">Channel NewsAsia</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/NDwuJ3jrf57R-sErJTF8tOuFeaaj75f5K76gzpOdwn-GvbEQSaOKuOGQs8yWVgL_z--55nbGjnVXQvDT404CBhxgLpjDJ-VFJmBprTrPoEMMH94d9mLmzQACFlayMa8WJatN01LBp8qI9fA99CEDrn9K55ATCjCF23is03v1ngZtX4kGnuFpl3s0NQkPj6_5femeQLEApHheRQnOirVZBwk4BNXTWDXHzl4BepNKjbKm9Kdf5kq0QE2JusGgYTRQhckver-BPT4FPDexfbyvdceaMb8Jishhn3gLXm169I5_jV3x1TCCJ18VCPQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>16 bodies found after attack in Indonesia's Papua - Channel NewsAsia</title><link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/16-bodies-found-after-attack-in-indonesia-s-papua-11002824</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiZGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNoYW5uZWxuZXdzYXNpYS5jb20vbmV3cy9hc2lhLzE2LWJvZGllcy1mb3VuZC1hZnRlci1hdHRhY2staW4taW5kb25lc2lhLXMtcGFwdWEtMTEwMDI4MjTSAQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:59:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/16-bodies-found-after-attack-in-indonesia-s-papua-11002824" target="_blank"&gt;16 bodies found after attack in Indonesia's Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Channel NewsAsia&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesian security forces have retrieved the bodies of 16 people in the aftermath of a massacre by suspected separatist rebels in restive Papua ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.channelnewsasia.com">Channel NewsAsia</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/iWx7hXbbpFKXR0SLEugarwgC57k-J5hHlo8r7Q8AUG4YD3OtAB4qQvhsc6SAo46Hs_qocSCdJab4k_kiE30uSI4yjh-0M4m3fNs5jXd4YevuOfY_Wece3fCalZp7B_qy0m0fiwBByPt4tFC6puQg5AbJB5hvHfBpaiktx7NQvdsCAOYOgwq0gjTT8wYBerh5KJYzUb9DmOZAEVBZ_FmEu7b7o4kqVhM3TNLJOJjJrkyHnM1gg9B3KhRztvSnbpffyTR8kA8fV442SwNssR6iEPz2kwEGRU9g4ncNqLN-vuR4Kenzyc9qeR0-ZQ_-uIyGOqDDKw=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Rebels Demand Indonesia Negotiate on Papua Independence - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/rebels-demand-indonesia-negotiate-on-papua-independence/4690843.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_xJ5OOo03iGAveBBjRBhwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:12:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/rebels-demand-indonesia-negotiate-on-papua-independence/4690843.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rebels Demand Indonesia Negotiate on Papua Independence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rebels in Indonesia's troubled Papua province demanded Friday that the government hold negotiations on self-determination for the province and warned of more attacks. Sebby Sambom, spokesman for the West Papua National Liberation Army, the military wing of the Free Papua Movement, said in a telephone interview they attacked a government construction site last weekend because they believe the project is conducted by the military. "Trans-Papua road projects are being carried out by Indonesian military and that is a risk they must bear," Sambom said. "We want them to know that we don't need de...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indonesia halts search for Papua dead after clash with separatists - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua/indonesia-halts-search-for-papua-dead-after-clash-with-separatists-idUSKBN1O516M</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEW0V90YsH_kgKRzOuok-38qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 11:32:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua/indonesia-halts-search-for-papua-dead-after-clash-with-separatists-idUSKBN1O516M" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia halts search for Papua dead after clash with separatists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesian soldiers on Thursday retrieved the bodies of nine construction workers killed by separatists in the province of Papua, where fresh fighting halted a search for the remaining dead, a military spokesman said. Colonel Muhammad Aidi said efforts to retrieve more bodies from the weekend attack on a Papua construction site were halted after soldiers clashed with fighters from the separatist Free Papua Movement (OPM). "We still haven't been able to recover another seven because there was a shootout between the military and the separatist group," Aidi said, adding that the bodies of 16 o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>West Papua independence leader urges calm after killings - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/06/west-papua-independence-leader-urges-calm-after-killings</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJKtIvCxem8UT6KLuySQngUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:17:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/06/west-papua-independence-leader-urges-calm-after-killings" target="_blank"&gt;West Papua independence leader urges calm after killings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exiled leader of the West Papuan independence movement has called for calm after independence fighters attacked and killed up to 31 people in a remote West Papuan district on Sunday. On Thursday the Indonesian military said it had retrieved 16 of the bodies from the district of Nduga, which would be sent to the main town of Timika. None were identified. Benny Wenda, the chair of the United Liberation Movement for West Papua (ULMWP), said it was hard to know exactly what happened at Nduga, amid conflicting reports on the long-running tensions, and without free access for media or human r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Army vows to hunt killers of 31 labourers in Indonesia's Papua province - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/army-vows-hunt-killers-31-labourers-indonesias-papua-province/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED97nvka9vchKssPIExHP-YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:21:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/05/army-vows-hunt-killers-31-labourers-indonesias-papua-province/" target="_blank"&gt;Army vows to hunt killers of 31 labourers in Indonesia's Papua province&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Indonesian authorities have vowed to hunt down the killers of 31 construction workers who were building a major road in the restive Papua province. The men were murdered in the remote mountainous district of Nduga, allegedly by members of the Free Papua Movement, reported the Associated Press. Most of the victims were shot at their construction site, while seven attempted to hide at the residence of a local councillor before being tracked there and massacred. The incident was described by Ryamizard Ryacudu, the defence minister, as one of the worst attacks in the country in recent years...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>West Papua: conflicting reports surround attack that killed up to 31 - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/west-papua-fears-of-spiralling-violence-after-attack-leaves-up-to-31-dead</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECweYT8MW0wpwrGGF59XSD4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:44:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/west-papua-fears-of-spiralling-violence-after-attack-leaves-up-to-31-dead" target="_blank"&gt;West Papua: conflicting reports surround attack that killed up to 31&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deadly violence has escalated in West Papua following the shooting deaths of up to 31 construction workers in a central district of the region and the reported killing of an Indonesian investigator. The West Papuan liberation army has claimed responsibility for the attack – the deadliest in many years in the ongoing independence conflict – but there are otherwise differing versions of events from Indonesian authorities. There are fears of reprisals and violent crackdowns. There were mass arrests of hundreds of West Papuan protesters across the region who were marking the 1 December “indepen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Indonesia probes mass suspected killings in Papua - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/indonesia-probes-mass-suspected-killings-papua-181204234322758.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFhE3Q44yNVClwcY9zYQMzQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:09:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/indonesia-probes-mass-suspected-killings-papua-181204234322758.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia probes mass suspected killings in Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indonesian soldier has been killed while investigating reports that more than two dozen construction workers were shot dead by separatist rebels in the far-east province of Papua, officials said Tuesday. If confirmed, the killings would mark the deadliest bout of violence in years to hit a resource-rich but impoverished region wracked for decades by a low-key armed battle for independence. Citing local police, Indonesian media reported late on Monday that the workers were shot dead on Sunday in Nduga, a district in the centre of the region on the western half of New Guinea island, just n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Indonesian Public and Human Rights Groups Decry West Papuan Arrests - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/west-papuan-arrests/4687497.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIkFUhwZVaNhil2UJAmUc4IqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 10:24:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/west-papuan-arrests/4687497.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian Public and Human Rights Groups Decry West Papuan Arrests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesian human rights groups decried the arrests made of West Papuan students and pro-independence activists after they staged peaceful rallies across Indonesian cities on Saturday. Benny Wenda, chairman of the United Liberation Movement for West Papua (ULMWP), demanded accountability from the Indonesian law enforcers, writing, “in the strongest possible terms, the ULMWP condemns the Indonesian government for the arrest and brutal treatment of over 500 West Papuan people and Indonesians in solidarity, who were targeted on 1st December simply for peaceful commemorating West Papua National ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Gunmen Said to Kill 31 Construction Workers in Remote Indonesian Province - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/04/world/asia/indonesia-papua-construction-workers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKhJgEz0yasVVmGcj5BMRWYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 13:42:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/04/world/asia/indonesia-papua-construction-workers.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen Said to Kill 31 Construction Workers in Remote Indonesian Province&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA, Indonesia — Gunmen in the remote Indonesian province of Papua have killed as many as 31 construction workers who were brought from a distant island to help build a major highway, officials said Tuesday. The police attributed the attacks to separatists who have long pushed for an independent Papua, The Associated Press reported. But there were few details of the killings, which were said to have begun on Sunday with the shooting of 24 workers. Indonesia’s public works minister, Basuki Hadimuljono, told reporters on Tuesday that work on the highway would be halted while the authoriti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Separatist gunmen kill 31 workers in Papua region: Indonesian officials - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/west-papua-separatists-allegedly-kill-workers-indonesia/10582480</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFMuskDrqkda1zYA0GcBjL8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 08:03:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/west-papua-separatists-allegedly-kill-workers-indonesia/10582480" target="_blank"&gt;Separatist gunmen kill 31 workers in Papua region: Indonesian officials&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesian authorities say independence supporters in the restive province of Papua have slaughtered up to 31 people who were working at a state-owned construction company. Key points: - The alleged separatist attack is the worst for many years in Indonesia's Papua region - The violence reportedly flared after migrant workers photographers a pro-independence rally - A low-level insurgency has plagued the mineral-rich but impoverished region for decades Papua police spokesman Suryadi Diaz said 24 workers were killed when gunmen stormed a government bridge construction project in a remote mou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Indonesia says Papua separatists suspected of killing at least 24 workers - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2018/12/04/indonesia-says-papua-separatists-suspected-of-killing-at-least-24-workers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN_KeUE00WXNWYpUN950OjgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 06:07:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2018/12/04/indonesia-says-papua-separatists-suspected-of-killing-at-least-24-workers/" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia says Papua separatists suspected of killing at least 24 workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - Security forces in Indonesia's easternmost province of Papua are hunting for a separatist group suspected of killing at least 24 construction workers building a bridge in a remote district, a military spokesman said on Tuesday. Papua has suffered a simmering separatist conflict since it was incorporated into Indonesia after a widely criticised U.N.-backed referendum in 1969 and remains one of its poorest regions. Colonel Muhammad Aidi said security forces were trying to confirm a report from a priest that 24 men from the construction company PT Istaka Karya working in th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Passenger removed from Garuda flight over bomb joke - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/07/12/passenger-removed-from-garuda-flight-over-bomb-joke/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI_ca8tk90Mrk5NZ3ukPsN0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 01:47:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/07/12/passenger-removed-from-garuda-flight-over-bomb-joke/" target="_blank"&gt;Passenger removed from Garuda flight over bomb joke&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA: A Garuda Indonesia passenger was removed from a Timika-Denpasar flight on Monday after a flight attendant heard him joke to another passenger that his heavy bag contained a bomb. The man, identified only by his initials WH, was removed before the aircraft took off at Timika Airport in Papua at around 2:30 p.m., local time. The incident happened when a passenger named Parlindungan Tambunan asked WH what he was carrying in his bag because it looked heavy. Spontaneously, WH jokingly replied that he was carrying “a bomb”. Parlindungan was not shocked by the response because he knew WH ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Freeport Indonesia mine workers extend strike for fourth month - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-freeport-mcmoran-indonesia-strike-idUSKBN1A61VJ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBrxLA020uF_WpUEmSMKPzoqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 14:39:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-freeport-mcmoran-indonesia-strike-idUSKBN1A61VJ" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport Indonesia mine workers extend strike for fourth month&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Wilda Asmarini and Susan Taylor JAKARTA/TORONTO (Reuters) - An estimated 5,000 workers at the giant Grasberg copper mine operated by Freeport-McMoRan Inc's (FCX.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) Indonesian unit will extend their strike for a fourth month, a union official said on Friday, in an ongoing dispute over layoffs and employment terms. The escalating labor issue comes as Freeport, the world's largest publicly traded copper miner, is snarled in a lengthy and costly dispute with Indonesia's government over rights to the Grasberg copper and gold mine. Freeport resumed copper ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Banned West Papua independence petition handed to UN - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/sep/27/banned-west-papua-independence-petition-un</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK1_28cPuLjUTu0OtSniuEIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 05:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/sep/27/banned-west-papua-independence-petition-un" target="_blank"&gt;Banned West Papua independence petition handed to UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A petition banned by the Indonesian government, but bearing the signatures of 1.8 million West Papuans – more than 70% of the contested province’s population – has been presented to the United Nations, with a demand for a free vote on independence. Exiled West Papuan independence campaigner Benny Wenda presented the bound petition to the UN’s decolonisation committee, the body that monitors the progress of former colonies – known as non-self-governing territories – towards independence. Related: Melanesian leaders condemn UN for turning 'a deaf ear' to West Papua atrocities The petition was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Magnitude 7.9 quake strikes off Papua New Guinea - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/01/22/asia/papua-new-guinea-quake/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJzCdxYOTIAEZyYf20SwjOsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 07:52:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/01/22/asia/papua-new-guinea-quake/" target="_blank"&gt;Magnitude 7.9 quake strikes off Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A magnitude 7.9 earthquake has struck west of Papua New Guinea. The quake was 153 kilometers (95.5 miles) deep and centered 40 kilometers (24 miles) west of the town of Panguna, according to the US Geological Survey. The Pacific Tsunami Warning Center has advised that tsunami waves of up to a meter above the tide level are possible for some coasts of Papua New Guinea and nearby Solomon Islands. Preliminary reports said the earthquake, which occurred at 2:30 p.m. local time Sunday (11:30 p.m. Saturday ET) measured 8.0 but USGS later downgraded its magnitude. The USGS estimates that 72,000 pe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Showdown in Indonesia Brings World’s Biggest Gold Mine to Standstill - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/showdown-in-indonesia-brings-gold-mine-to-standstill/3741401.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIms2EAGZQYPyj1-U_JV3zEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 12:57:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/showdown-in-indonesia-brings-gold-mine-to-standstill/3741401.html" target="_blank"&gt;Showdown in Indonesia Brings World’s Biggest Gold Mine to Standstill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American mining company Freeport-McMoRan has brought the world's biggest gold mine, in the Indonesian province of West Papua, to a standstill. The corporation is butting heads with the Indonesian government over protectionist mining regulations. And now that Freeport has started to dismiss tens of thousands of workers, the local economy is poised to take a huge hit. In Mimika Regency, the West Papua province containing the Grasberg gold mine, 91 percent of the Gross Domestic Product (GDP) is attributed to Freeport. Freeport Indonesia abruptly stopped production on February 10 and lai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indonesia strikes deal with Freeport over copper mine - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/8441a589-616b-3684-b9cc-0cfe0243a0f0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECwLCL5qNhu4WjeIP-jey7oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 08:42:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8441a589-616b-3684-b9cc-0cfe0243a0f0" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia strikes deal with Freeport over copper mine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia has reached an agreement with US copper miner Freeport-McMoran to allow the company to keep operating its giant Grasberg mine in the country. Phoenix-based Freeport has agreed to give a 51 per cent ownership in the mine to Indonesia and build smelters in the country, according to a statement by the Ministry of Energy and Mineral Resources. It will be allowed to operate the mine until 2041 under a special licence, it said. Freeport had been embroiled in a bitter dispute with the government in Jakarta over its contract to operate Grasberg, the world’s second-largest copper mine. Tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Freeport Indonesia CEO resigns after force majeure on copper exports - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/02/18/freeport-indonesia-ceo-resigns-after-force-majeure-on-copper-exports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO-64eeOfQtmqxMsrEbYC6kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 13:06:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2017/02/18/freeport-indonesia-ceo-resigns-after-force-majeure-on-copper-exports/" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport Indonesia CEO resigns after force majeure on copper exports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA: Chappy Hakim, the chief executive of miner Freeport-McMoran Inc's Indonesian unit, has resigned, the company said on Saturday, after the parent firm declared force majeure on copper concentrate shipments from its Grasberg mine in Papua. Freeport, which has been negotiating with the Indonesian government after halting exports due to new mining rules, said on Friday it could not meet contractual obligations for copper concentrate shipments from the giant mine following a five-week export stoppage. All work has stopped at the mine, the world's second largest for copper, a union leader...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Cargo aircraft skids off runway in Indonesia - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/07/19/cargo-aircraft-skids-off-runway-at-wamena-airport/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGklZbs4EAX5FRaQCRNt--YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 02:45:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/07/19/cargo-aircraft-skids-off-runway-at-wamena-airport/" target="_blank"&gt;Cargo aircraft skids off runway in Indonesia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA: For the umpteenth time, a plane has experienced an accident at Wamena Airport in Jayawijaya, Papua. On Tuesday a cargo aircraft belonging to Tri MG veered off the runway for almost a kilometer when it landed at 12:30 p.m. local time. The left wheel and undercarriage of the aircraft had fallen off when the plane touched down. “The Boeing 737-301 aircraft carried five people, comprising pilot, co-pilot, crew members and a passenger. The plane skidded off [the runway] about 100 meters from its landing point,” Jayawijaya Police chief Adj. Sr. Comr. Yan Piet Reba told The Jakarta Post o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Japanese documentary makers deported from Indonesia - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/05/12/japanese-documentary-makers-deported-from-indonesia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFljMVRflDLNBUtjPPp5OYIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 10:25:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/05/12/japanese-documentary-makers-deported-from-indonesia/" target="_blank"&gt;Japanese documentary makers deported from Indonesia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAYAPURA: Six Japanese documentary makers have been deported from Indonesia after being caught trying to make a film in the sensitive province of Papua without the correct visas, an immigration official said. The men, who were working for Nagano Production House, were flown out of the country Thursday after being arrested while filming a documentary about tribes people in the town of Wamena, said local immigration chief Yopie Watimena. Indonesia is deeply sensitive about journalists covering the easternmost province, where a low-level insurgency against the central government has simmered f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Indonesian air force plane crashes in Papua killing 13, official says - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2016/12/18/indonesian-air-force-plane-crashes-in-papua-killing-13-official-says/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKaXhjU4YXxFa6t7pth__gIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 03:15:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2016/12/18/indonesian-air-force-plane-crashes-in-papua-killing-13-official-says/" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian air force plane crashes in Papua killing 13, official says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - An Indonesian air force transport plane has crashed into a mountain, killing all 13 people board, during a training exercise in the remote region of Papua, a search and rescue agency official said on Sunday. The Hercules C130 plane had taken off from the city of Timika before crashing near its destination of Wamena at around 6.15 a.m. local time (2315 GMT), said Ivan Ahmad Riski Titus, operational director of Indonesia's Search and Rescue Agency. The crash site on Lisuwa mountain had been found and the bodies of the victims were being brought back to Wamena, he said. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Indonesian police kill civilian, injure others in Papua - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/08/02/indonesian-police-kill-civilian-injure-others-in-papua/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPleCTx89Z_FCpHxg6YmQQYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 12:36:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/08/02/indonesian-police-kill-civilian-injure-others-in-papua/" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian police kill civilian, injure others in Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAYAPURA: Indonesian police said Wednesday they shot dead one man and injured several other people during a clash in Papua sparked by a worker’s refusal to take a dying man to hospital. A confrontatation broke out in Deiyai district in Indonesia’s easternmost province on Tuesday when a villager asked a group of workers at a company’s construction site to take the person to hospital. A worker denied the request, fearing he would blamed if the patient died en route. This angered locals, who gathered at the site to confront the workers after the patient passed away. Police deployed to handle t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>England beats Samoa, rugby league world is still three countries - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-05-06/england-samoa-fiji-tonga-papua-new-guinea-cook-islands-rl-tests/8503562</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDTCD8HWAqAeskj47iWygOkqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 11:43:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-05-06/england-samoa-fiji-tonga-papua-new-guinea-cook-islands-rl-tests/8503562" target="_blank"&gt;England beats Samoa, rugby league world is still three countries&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rugby league world remains, for all intents and purposes, just three countries wide after England beat Samoa in Campbelltown. After the Kangaroos' dominant performance against the Kiwis on Friday night, the international league scene could have used a shake-up, but none was forthcoming. A Samoan side brimming with NRL talent could not match it with the Englishmen, who ran out 30-10 victors. The win wrapped up a three-Test Saturday, during which Papua New Guinea beat the Cook Islands 32-22 and Tonga scored a last-gasp 26-24 victory over Fiji. Ultimately, Samoa ran out of puff in the last...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Plane tips over on runway after cooking oil spill makes cargo slip to its tail - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/indonesia/articles/plane-tips-onto-its-tail-after-cooking-oil-spillage-slump/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED4wku-Q5nYUF3-PDKaB568qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/indonesia/articles/plane-tips-onto-its-tail-after-cooking-oil-spillage-slump/" target="_blank"&gt;Plane tips over on runway after cooking oil spill makes cargo slip to its tail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A plane ended up sat on its haunches after a cooking oil spillage in the hold meant that all its cargo slipped to the back of the aircraft, raising its nose into the air. The mishap took place at Wamena Airport in Papua, Indonesia, as the Tri-MG plane that had arrived from Timika was being unloaded. Among its cargo was a shipment of Indonesian Bimoli oil which was somehow breached, allowing its contents to grease the floor of the fuselage. Thanks to the shifting balance of weight, the aircraft see-sawed on its wheels, only coming to a stop when its tail was touching the tarmac. A post share...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>West Papuans Protest Against Indonesian Rule - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/ap-west-papuans-protest-against-indonesian-rule/3618542.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEXdm3SBYVtn3fladcbZJ7cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 04:49:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/ap-west-papuans-protest-against-indonesian-rule/3618542.html" target="_blank"&gt;West Papuans Protest Against Indonesian Rule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;West Papuan protesters faced off with police in the Indonesian capital on Thursday in a demonstration calling for the remote region's independence. Organizers had promised protests in other cities and said police had denied them permission to march in central Jakarta. The dozens of demonstrators were blocked from marching onto a busy traffic circle in the capital by several hundred police who fired water cannons and dragged men from the crowd into waiting police vans. “Don't hinder our right to voice our aspirations. Papuans are demanding the truth of our history,” a speaker standing atop a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indonesia, Australian military officials meet over Papua row - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/02/09/indonesia-australian-military-officials-meet-over-papua-row/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHB5OvqTfqRgq5KCLmdcvJQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 17:16:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/02/09/indonesia-australian-military-officials-meet-over-papua-row/" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia, Australian military officials meet over Papua row&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - Australia's army chief has apologised for comments deemed insulting to Indonesia that were contained in teaching material found at an Australian military base, Indonesia's armed forces chief said on Wednesday. However, no decision has yet been made on fully restoring defence ties, General Gatot Nurmantyo said. The material in question referred to Indonesia's eastern province of Papua needing to be independent and "discredited the TNI, the nation of Indonesia and even the ideology of Indonesia," Nurmantyo had said previously. Papua province forms part of the island of New...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>6.0-magnitude quake hits off Papua New Guinea - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/09/26/60-magnitude-quake-hits-off-papua-new-guinea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJ6yMyxM9iFOD6lP3Uj1CwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 01:40:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/09/26/60-magnitude-quake-hits-off-papua-new-guinea/" target="_blank"&gt;6.0-magnitude quake hits off Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sydney (AFP) - A 6.0-magnitude earthquake struck off Papua New Guinea on Tuesday, according to the United States Geological Survey, but no Pacific-wide tsunami warning was issued. The tremor hit at a depth of five kilometres (three miles) near the sparsely-populated East New Britain region, some 210 kilometres southeast of the town of Kokopo, the USGS said. The Hawaii-based Pacific Tsunami Warning Center did not issue a tsunami warning. Earthquakes are common near Papua New Guinea, which lies on the 4,000-kilometre-long Pacific Australia plate. It forms part of the “Ring of Fire”, a hotspot...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>13 people killed when Indonesian C-130 cargo plane hits mountain (PHOTOS) - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/370654-indonesian-hercules-plane-crash/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKa--DEQPwlMc5B-Ifp3ufQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 05:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/370654-indonesian-hercules-plane-crash/" target="_blank"&gt;13 people killed when Indonesian C-130 cargo plane hits mountain (PHOTOS)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All 13 people on board a Hercules C-130 plane owned by the Indonesian Air Force died after it crashed into a mountain near the town of Wamena in the eastern Papua province not far from the airport on Sunday. The US-made transport plane departed from the city of Timika at 22:35 GMT and was set to arrive at Wamena airport at 23:13 GMT. However, contact with the aircraft was lost some ten minutes before the scheduled landing, and search and rescue crews were dispatched to the area. Puing puing Pesawat Hercules C-130 HS milik TNI AU yang jatuh di Pegunungan Wamena pagi ini, 3 Pilot dan 10 Awak ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Foreigners Have Long Mined Indonesia, but Now There’s an Outcry - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/31/business/energy-environment/indonesia-gold-mine-grasberg-freeport-mcmoran.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBAAa87tvhvx0BAKHg-8bJUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwlqlf</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 02:00:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/31/business/energy-environment/indonesia-gold-mine-grasberg-freeport-mcmoran.html" target="_blank"&gt;Foreigners Have Long Mined Indonesia, but Now There’s an Outcry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protesters are pressing the government to push back against Freeport-McMoRan, a U.S. mining giant, and to regain control of natural resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Freeport cuts copper production targets after Indonesia spat - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/612cb890-41c5-3501-8917-a06e430f6713</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK72j0tOe3ID9ULkvylFz_oqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 12:57:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/612cb890-41c5-3501-8917-a06e430f6713" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport cuts copper production targets after Indonesia spat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freeport-McMoRan, the world’s largest publicly traded copper company, has cut its production forecasts following a stand-off with the Indonesian government stop exports from its Grasberg mine banned. The Arizona-based miner company had previously expected to sell 4.1bn pounds of copper this year, a figure it has now revised to 3.9bn after Jakarta banned shipments from Grasberg, the world’s second biggest copper mine. The new guidance was revealed in a trading update that saw Freeport report net income of $228m for the three months to the end of March, against a loss of $4.2bn a year ago whe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Asylum seekers in Papua New Guinea fear they will be put at risk by relocation - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/16/asylum-seekers-in-papua-new-guinea-fear-they-will-be-put-at-risk-by-relocation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAFhyVOijyUqMPRWyd5h9wYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 06:43:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/05/16/asylum-seekers-in-papua-new-guinea-fear-they-will-be-put-at-risk-by-relocation/" target="_blank"&gt;Asylum seekers in Papua New Guinea fear they will be put at risk by relocation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SYDNEY (Reuters) - Papua New Guinea's decision to relocate hundreds of men held in an Australian-run detention centre to a nearby town soon exposes them to violence and inadequate medical care, asylum seekers and human rights groups said on Tuesday. Papua New Guinea immigration officials told asylum seekers on Monday that an area of the controversial Manus Island camp north of the PNG mainland would close on May 28, with the rest of the compound to shut on June 30. Those eligible for resettlement to the United States, under a deal that U.S. President Donald Trump has described as "dumb", wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Indonesia takes majority stake in Freeport-McMoRan copper mine - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9c6614d4-8c94-11e7-a352-e46f43c5825d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJL1vMv5vw7GP5zJKML_QcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 13:40:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9c6614d4-8c94-11e7-a352-e46f43c5825d" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia takes majority stake in Freeport-McMoRan copper mine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia will take a majority stake in US miner Freeport-McMoran’s group Grasberg copper and gold mine as part of an agreement that will allow the mine to keep operating after months of bitter dispute. Phoenix-based Freeport has agreed to give a 51 per cent ownership in the mine to Indonesia and build a smelter in the country within five years, according to the country’s Ministry of Energy and Mineral Resources. The company will be allowed to operate the mine until 2041 under a special licence, it said. Freeport had been embroiled in a dispute with the government in Jakarta over its contra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Britain has the chance to bring a brutal colonial occupation to an end - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/21/britain-west-papua-colonial-occupation-geoge-monbiot</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENvlhmzCwE7gkWTjQSQTTg4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 06:00:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/21/britain-west-papua-colonial-occupation-geoge-monbiot" target="_blank"&gt;Britain has the chance to bring a brutal colonial occupation to an end&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every colonial enterprise pretends to be inspired by something other than theft. The General Act of the Berlin Conference in 1885, under which the European powers carved Africa into formal colonial possessions, claimed that their purpose was “furthering the moral and material wellbeing of the native populations … and bringing home to them the blessings of civilisation”. Similar rhetoric has attended all such seizures. To save native people from their enslavement to the Devil, or the Arabs, or each other, they had to be forced into general servitude, while their land and natural wealth were ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Freeport-McMoRan boosted by higher copper price - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/feb60078-7154-11e7-aca6-c6bd07df1a3c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC1dgMWC9uOT8s3jTFlvBv4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 17:51:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/feb60078-7154-11e7-aca6-c6bd07df1a3c" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport-McMoRan boosted by higher copper price&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Freeport-McMoRan, the world’s biggest listed copper company, jumped by the most in 16 months on Tuesday as a higher copper price and news of constructive discussions with the Indonesian government over its operating licence helped offset the sting of a guidance cut. The stock rose as much as 13.4 per cent to a five-month high of $14.70 after Freeport’s chief executive Richard Adkerson said he was optimistic of reaching an agreement with Jakarta over its contract to operate in the country and run the giant Grasberg copper deposit. The move is the stock’s biggest one-day rise since ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Earthquake hits off Papua New Guinea - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/09/17/earthquake-hits-off-papua-new-guinea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJAbl9MeE9aRLlXEbbrXJesqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 14:53:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/09/17/earthquake-hits-off-papua-new-guinea/" target="_blank"&gt;Earthquake hits off Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON (Reuters) - A magnitude 5.9 earthquake hit off the coast of Papua New Guinea in the early hours of Monday local time, the Pacific Tsunami Warning Center said. The quake struck at a depth of 37 km (23 miles), in the sea southwest of Kandrian soon after midnight (1426 GMT Sunday), the centre added. (Reporting by Andrew Heavens)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>How I ended up in the jungle with deadly hornets in my hair - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/dec/28/giant-hornets-antidote-west-papua-vicks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK4OwvAqwtgWnFQyBmVdbmgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 07:30:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/dec/28/giant-hornets-antidote-west-papua-vicks" target="_blank"&gt;How I ended up in the jungle with deadly hornets in my hair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story has no message or purpose. It is one of the winter’s tales – accounts of the many bizarre incidents that have marked my life – that I tell at this time of year. For once, I am not trying to make a point. In 1987, I was working with the photographer Adrian Arbib in the occupied territory of West Papua. Annexed by Indonesia in 1963, it was being governed with characteristic brutality by the Suharto regime. The indigenous people were being forced off their land and replaced, in a programme sponsored by the World Bank, by migrants from Java and Bali. Many had been tortured and killed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Indonesian provincial government says Freeport loses $188 million tax appeal - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-freeport-tax-idUSKBN1591SI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMgObayER4Wd9K2k4cKDIlwqFAgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMOpn</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 15:03:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-freeport-tax-idUSKBN1591SI" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian provincial government says Freeport loses $188 million tax appeal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - Indonesia's Papua province, home of the giant Grasberg copper mine operated by the local unit of Freeport McMoRan Inc (FCX.N: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz), said it has won a court battle in a claim against the company for 2.51 trillion rupiah ($188 million) in outstanding surface water taxes. According to Papua's local government Indonesia's Tax Court has rejected a lawsuit lodged by PT Freeport Indonesia over the claim for taxes on water the company used from the Aghawagon and Otomona rivers between 2011 and mid-2015. Freeport, which used the water to suspend i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Freeport-McMoRan threatens to sue Indonesia over mine dispute - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9ba0b210-f776-11e6-9516-2d969e0d3b65</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELj9o6_oZQfUtiI_I7gfhCUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 17:23:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9ba0b210-f776-11e6-9516-2d969e0d3b65" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport-McMoRan threatens to sue Indonesia over mine dispute&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freeport-McMoRan on Monday warned the Indonesian government it was prepared to sue Jakarta if it could not resolve an increasingly bitter dispute that has slashed production at its flagship copper deposit in the country. Richard Adkerson, chief executive of the US mining company, said Jakarta had been notified of what he characterised as violations of its contract to mine copper at the giant Grasberg deposit in the eastern province of Papua. The two sides have 120 days to resolve the issues, which was triggered by changes to Indonesia’s mining laws — otherwise Freeport will launch arbitrati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Papua New Guinea hit by earthquake measuring 6.2 - USGS - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/06/03/papua-new-guinea-hit-by-earthquake-measuring-62--usgs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFvxGhCmh4Rl46nzF3ZTkmAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 00:16:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/06/03/papua-new-guinea-hit-by-earthquake-measuring-62--usgs/" target="_blank"&gt;Papua New Guinea hit by earthquake measuring 6.2 - USGS&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SYDNEY (Reuters) - A magnitude 6.2 earthquake struck in Papua New Guinea on Saturday, the U.S. Geological Survey reported. The quake was at a depth of 118 miles (190.3 km) and centered 68 miles (109 km) west of Madang province. No tsunami warning was issued. (Reporting by Harry Pearl; Editing by Cynthia Osterman)&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Solidarity with the West Papua people’s struggle for self-determination - Malaysiakini</title><link>http://www.malaysiakini.com/letters/364796</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOs9WQXEV8CcEqQGChZBY78qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPTirwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 05:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysiakini.com/letters/364796" target="_blank"&gt;Solidarity with the West Papua people’s struggle for self-determination&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We, the undersigned organisations, express our support to the struggle of the people of West Papua for self-determination. Dec 1 marks West Papua’s Independence Day for Papuans when the Morning Star flag was raised in 1961 before annexed by Indonesia. The flag symbolised the aspiration of many Papuans for a Free West Papua. Yet, it is still illegal to raise the Morning Star flag in West Papua and people who do that might face arrest and persecution from the authorities. On Dec 1 this year, the people of West Papua will continue this tradition of struggle for self-determination through mass ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysiakini.com">Malaysiakini</source></item><item><title>Freeport shares jump after CEO signals progress on Indonesia mine talks - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e568ae24-fec9-3e63-a133-6b8268ec9e01</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIXuweQSSWnlWWDU6aBIIS4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 15:19:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e568ae24-fec9-3e63-a133-6b8268ec9e01" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport shares jump after CEO signals progress on Indonesia mine talks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares in Freeport-McMoran, the world’s biggest listed copper company, jumped in morning trading in New York as a higher copper price and news of constructive discussions with the Indonesian government over its operating license offset revised sales guidance. The stock rose as much as 12.5 per cent to a five-month high of $14.58 after Freeport’s chief executive Richard Adkerson said he was optimistic of reaching an agreement with Jakarta over its contract to operate in the country and run the giant Grasberg copper deposit. “We are now approaching a stage where both parties have expressed an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Dingo relative rediscovered in New Guinea Highlands - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-30/dingo-relative-rediscovered-in-papua-new-guinea-highlands/8463208</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKPCrNNqwPS54OoZbRYSPpEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 23:57:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-04-30/dingo-relative-rediscovered-in-papua-new-guinea-highlands/8463208" target="_blank"&gt;Dingo relative rediscovered in New Guinea Highlands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have confirmed the existence of an ancient dog species in one of the world's most remote places — the mountains of Papua New Guinea and Indonesia's Papua provinces. Key points: - The discovery is the first sighting of the dogs in more than 40 years - They are among the oldest and most primitive canines in the world - Analysis of the species could help explain dog and human co-evolution The international team led by scientists from Indonesia's University of Papua captured evidence of the New Guinea highland wild dog during a 2016 expedition to an austere, high-altitude region near...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Indonesian police name six suspects after labour unrest at Freeport's Grasberg mine - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/08/21/indonesian-police-name-six-suspects-after-labour-unrest-at-freeports-grasberg-mine/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECmLbUc1o9pIj-KEAYpJIwUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 10:26:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/08/21/indonesian-police-name-six-suspects-after-labour-unrest-at-freeports-grasberg-mine/" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian police name six suspects after labour unrest at Freeport's Grasberg mine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - Police in the eastern Indonesian province of Papua have named six people as suspects out of 17 arrested on Saturday after a violent demonstration by former mine workers at Freeport McMoRan Inc's Grasberg copper mine, a police spokesman said. Trouble erupted at the mine, the world's second-biggest copper mine, when demonstrators blocked an access road in a protest over employment terms. At least seven people were injured and dozens of vehicles and buildings torched, and access to Grasberg was restricted amid safety concerns. The six people were named as suspects for carry...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Water, power supply to largest compound in PNG detention centre cut off - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/07/31/water-power-supply-to-largest-compound-in-png-detention-centre-cut-off/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPZOMN3i2A8GjsuRzLT14mkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 06:42:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/07/31/water-power-supply-to-largest-compound-in-png-detention-centre-cut-off/" target="_blank"&gt;Water, power supply to largest compound in PNG detention centre cut off&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SYDNEY (Reuters) - Water and power supplies were cut off on Monday at the largest compound at an Australian-run camp for asylum seekers in Papua New Guinea, detainees said, as officials tried to force them to move to a nearby transit centre. Australia wants to close its controversial detention centre, which has drawn sharp criticism from the United Nations and domestic and international human rights groups, on Papua New Guinea's remote Manus Island on Oct. 31. However, efforts to relocate the 800 men held there have stalled after a U.S. relocation swap deal was suspended and almost all the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>British cruise ship crashes into one of world's most spectacular coral reefs - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/british-cruise-ship-crashes-coral-reef-indonesia-papua-raja-ampat-a7629061.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG0IYbTR7El2D4YRs-bPQbgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 14:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/british-cruise-ship-crashes-coral-reef-indonesia-papua-raja-ampat-a7629061.html" target="_blank"&gt;British cruise ship crashes into one of world's most spectacular coral reefs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A British-owned cruise ship carrying hundreds of tourists has crashed into one of the world’s most spectacular coral reefs, sparking outrage from locals. The 4,290-tonne Caledonian Sky caused "irreparable damage" in Raja Ampat, an idyllic island chain in the west of Indonesia’s Papua province. The ship, owned by British company Noble Caledonia, was hosting a bird-watching trip on earlier this month when it veered off course, running aground during low tide and ploughing into the coral. Roughly 1,600 square meters of the “underwater Amazon” is thought to have been damaged in the incident. Re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Swimming with jellyfish: a Pacific paradise in the Raja Ampat islands - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/jan/26/indonesia-pacific-misool-island-new-guinea-raja-ampat</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKcvGXqti6YmtwWXrKHSUlsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCw3Gc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 10:38:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/travel/2017/jan/26/indonesia-pacific-misool-island-new-guinea-raja-ampat" target="_blank"&gt;Swimming with jellyfish: a Pacific paradise in the Raja Ampat islands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Raja Ampat archipelago, off the Indonesian province of West Papua, is famed for its whale sharks, manta rays and diverse coral. But I’m here to witness another natural phenomenon – a lake that’s home to thousands of giant golden medusa jellyfish. And, what’s more, I’m going for a swim. Some jellyfish can kill people, but the species here are unarmed. Bobbing around in the lake, gelatinous blobs collide with me, tentacles wrap gently around my legs and torso, their bulbous bodies pulse like beating hearts in an oddly therapeutic dance of the deep. Misool island. Photograph: Alamy There a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Papuan separatists to petition U.N. against Indonesian rule - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/09/06/papuan-separatists-to-petition-un-against-indonesian-rule/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJYCd2OUOEnsTvDD-Su1JdAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 13:09:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/09/06/papuan-separatists-to-petition-un-against-indonesian-rule/" target="_blank"&gt;Papuan separatists to petition U.N. against Indonesian rule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (Reuters) - The people of West Papua are facing a "slow motion genocide" and demand independence from Indonesia, separatist leaders told Reuters after a march in Geneva, adding they would press their case with a petition to the United Nations in New York. Benny Wenda, international spokesman for the United Liberation Movement for West Papua (ULMWP), said the human rights situation had worsened under Indonesian President Joko Widodo, with estimates of up to 8,000 people arrested last year. "They look at West Papua differently, as subhuman, and as a colony. We are not equal. That’s why...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Papua New Guinea Parliament Re-elects Prime Minister - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/papua-new-guinea-parliament-re-elects-prime-minister/3969132.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEHFAnJ5V8GiCs4FZVkgojYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 15:07:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/papua-new-guinea-parliament-re-elects-prime-minister/3969132.html" target="_blank"&gt;Papua New Guinea Parliament Re-elects Prime Minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incumbent Peter O'Neill has been re-elected as prime minister of Papua New Guinea, following a chaotic, violence-plagued campaign marred by allegations of voting irregularities. O'Neill was sworn in Wednesday to a second five-year term to lead the South Pacific island nation after his People's National Congress formed a coalition government with other minor parties, giving O'Neill 60 votes with 46 votes against him. The weeks-long election process struggled because of poor organization and accusations by opposition candidates of vote rigging. Papua New Guinea has been plagued for decades by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indonesian Military Plane Crashes, Killing All 13 Aboard - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/indonesia-plane-crash/3640781.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPzzRGOpqcnIvZrJzefGjcIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 04:38:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/indonesia-plane-crash/3640781.html" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesian Military Plane Crashes, Killing All 13 Aboard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indonesian military plane crashed into a mountain near Wamena, Papua, Sunday, killing all 13 people on board. The statement from the Indonesian Air Force sent to VOA said that the Hercules C-130 plane was carrying 12 tons of food supplies from Timika to Wamena, a distance of about 200 kilometers (125 miles), and some other areas (Jayapura, Merauke, Biak) when it crashed. The plane left Timika around 5:45 a.m. local time and was to arrive in Wamena around 6:15 a.m. local time. Just before it landed, the control tower lost contact with the plane. The plane was carrying three pilots and 10 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Indonesia rights body urges end to abuses in Papua after police shooting - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua-idUSKBN1AJ1F2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELCDNoMn_Z36mCwU4ERV8eMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 10:41:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-indonesia-papua-idUSKBN1AJ1F2" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia rights body urges end to abuses in Papua after police shooting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA (Reuters) - Indonesia's human rights commission on Thursday urged President Joko Widodo to end rights violations in the easternmost province of Papua after police were alleged to have killed one person and wounded 16 others while trying to quell a protest. The incident started on Tuesday when workers at a construction site in the province's Deiyai district refused to transport a man who had nearly drowned in a river to a hospital, according to local media Tabloid Jubi. Residents were angry when the man eventually died and attacked the workers' camp and assaulted police officers who ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Marathon Election Starts in Papua New Guinea - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/marathon-election-starts-in-papua-new-guinea/3915885.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGY2iWOkz3G0xJg1HD3vZl0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 09:09:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/marathon-election-starts-in-papua-new-guinea/3915885.html" target="_blank"&gt;Marathon Election Starts in Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voting has begun in Papua New Guinea's marathon national elections as the Prime Minister faces an arrest warrant for corruption. Peter O’Neill’s People’s National Congress won the last poll in 2012, but critics are accusing him of “burying” the economy in debt. Papua New Guinea, or PNG, is a South Pacific nation of almost 7 million and lies to the north of Australia. About 5 million voters will elect members of Papua New Guinea’s 111-seat parliament. Occupying the eastern half of the island of New Guinea and numerous islands, PNG is a land of rugged terrain and voting will last for two we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Copper concentrate supply hit by disputes in Chile and Indonesia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/5db10156-0713-11e7-97d1-5e720a26771b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHoRfegtZ98PoAs55HUnLWAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 02:34:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5db10156-0713-11e7-97d1-5e720a26771b" target="_blank"&gt;Copper concentrate supply hit by disputes in Chile and Indonesia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supply disruptions at two large mines in Chile and Indonesia are spurring a global shortfall in copper concentrate according to the chairman of China’s second-largest copper refiner. Disputes at the Escondida and Grasberg mines were having “a big effect on global supplies of copper concentrate”, Jiangxi Copper chairman Li Baomin told the Financial Times in Beijing, adding: “It’s the first time in 15 years that copper concentrate is not overproduced.” Copper concentrate — a dry grey powder — is a feedstock used by smelters to create molten copper that is cast into anodes. Annual production i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Outlawed West Papua independence petition presented to the UN - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-27/west-papua-independence-petition-handed-to-un/8994400</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHL1L-HB-wDsj6FP9dg--FwqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 10:12:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-27/west-papua-independence-petition-handed-to-un/8994400" target="_blank"&gt;Outlawed West Papua independence petition presented to the UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A secret petition demanding a new independence referendum for West Papua has been presented to the United Nations. The Indonesian Government banned the petition in the provinces of West Papua and Papua, threatening that those who signed it will be arrested and face jail. But the document was smuggled between villages where it has been signed by 1.8 million West Papuans, more than 70 per cent of the province's population. Advocates argue that West Papuans have been denied a legitimate self-determination process, since it was incorporated into Indonesia in 1969. The petition demands a free vo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Freeport-McMoran lowers sales guidance after industrial action - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/90b50edb-6673-31a1-a559-2b8c9a9a0497</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIEoTs9yQeBJ9E_Ixhjnd-cqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 12:44:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/90b50edb-6673-31a1-a559-2b8c9a9a0497" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport-McMoran lowers sales guidance after industrial action&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freeport-McMoran, the world’s biggest publicly listed copper miner, has lowered it sales guidance because of industrial action at its giant Grasberg pit in Indonesia. The New-York-listed company now expects to produce 3.7bn pounds (1.68m tonnes) of copper this year, down 150m pounds on its previous forecast. Freeport blamed the the shortfall on lower mining rates and reduced “manpower levels” at the Grasberg open pit and the slower development of a nearby underground expansion project. “These shortfalls are expected to be recovered in future periods,” the company said. The revised guidance ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>UN rejects reports of petition for West Papua independence vote - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-29/west-papua-independence-petition-reports-false-say-un/9001538</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOB74puQeKCsKX9owcsWusUqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-09-29/west-papua-independence-petition-reports-false-say-un/9001538" target="_blank"&gt;UN rejects reports of petition for West Papua independence vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The head of the United Nation's decolonisation committee has rejected reports of a secret petition demanding a free vote for independence in West Papua. Exiled West Papuan independence campaigner Benny Wenda had told the press 1.8 million West Papuans had signed the secret petition that was passed between homes and villages across provinces. In the reports, Mr Wenda said he presented the petition to the UN Special Committee on Decolonisation. But from New York, the chairman of the committee said no petition had been received and the report, which first appeared in The Guardian newspaper, wa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Freeport fights for future of Grasberg mine - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9ab702a4-30b1-11e7-9555-23ef563ecf9a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOYGhXp9Pccw3AZjsm1duYAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 04:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9ab702a4-30b1-11e7-9555-23ef563ecf9a" target="_blank"&gt;Freeport fights for future of Grasberg mine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richard Adkerson, chief executive of Freeport-McMoRan, has six months to thrash out a deal with Indonesia to assure the future of Grasberg, the world’s second-biggest copper deposit. The main open pit at Grasberg sits more than 4,000 metres above sea level among snow capped mountains in a remote and restless part of Indonesia. Continually shrouded in fog and soaked by heavy rains, conditions at the pit are among the toughest in the mining industry. But government interference in the lucrative mine has proven more difficult to deal with than even the harshest of conditions. Freeport, the Pho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Global union heads to Indonesia to defend Freeport workers - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-08-11/global-union-heads-to-indonesia-to-defend-freeport-workers/8795584</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK4Jife81A0-FtRFuLKAt70qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 21:48:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-08-11/global-union-heads-to-indonesia-to-defend-freeport-workers/8795584" target="_blank"&gt;Global union heads to Indonesia to defend Freeport workers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fight between West Papuan workers and mining giant Freeport-McMoRan has intensified with the US-owned company accused of denying health care for striking workers and education for their children. Key points: - Workers have been on strike for over four months - The unions say the workers were sacked for taking part in legal strike action - Australia's CFMEu says "a very tragic set of circumstances… occurring as a result of this labour dispute" A global trade union is in Jakarta to lobby the Indonesian Government to help solve the ongoing dispute between Freeport and an estimated 4,000 wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>US, Allies to ‘Transform’ Papua New Guinea With Electricity - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-allies-to-transform-papua-new-guinea-with-electricity/4663416.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ-926ByS0JTl5pjNk3yZLQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 04:01:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-allies-to-transform-papua-new-guinea-with-electricity/4663416.html" target="_blank"&gt;US, Allies to ‘Transform’ Papua New Guinea With Electricity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S., Japan, New Zealand and Australia said they’ll bring electricity to 70 percent of Papua New Guinea’s people by 2030, boosting the West’s response to growing Chinese influence in the South Pacific. The four countries and Papua New Guinea signed the electrification agreement Sunday at the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation meeting behind held in the capital Port Moresby. U.S. Vice President Mike Pence said it shows how strongly the U.S. and its allies are committed to the region. “The commitment of the United States of America to this region of the world has never been stronger,” he s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>APEC is being held by the member country that can least afford it - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/13/asia/papua-new-guinea-apec-summit-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJjAuiebOw82Jx3AJXskxEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:27:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/13/asia/papua-new-guinea-apec-summit-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;APEC is being held by the member country that can least afford it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Port Moresby doesn't know what's about to hit it. The Papua New Guinean capital, a tiny cluster of high rise and residential buildings housing some 300,000 people on the Pacific nation's southern coast, has been preparing all year for the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) summit, which begins on November 17. But for months, experts have been warning the city isn't ready, and concerns remain over costs, infrastructure and security. This is the first time Papua New Guinea (PNG), the poorest of the 21 countries in APEC, has hosted the summit. PNG ranks 110th worldwide for GDP, with an e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Papua New Guinea Is Rich in Resources but Poor in Health - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/13/world/asia/papua-new-guinea-apec-polio-health-crisis.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF5iDjKEQPXOebZFNlNkEbMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 18:00:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/13/world/asia/papua-new-guinea-apec-polio-health-crisis.html" target="_blank"&gt;Papua New Guinea Is Rich in Resources but Poor in Health&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PORT MORESBY, Papua New Guinea — Polio was vanquished by the Pacific nation of Papua New Guinea 18 years ago. Now, as world leaders gather there for the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation summit meeting this week, polio has returned — on top of raging drug-resistant epidemics of tuberculosis, malaria and H.I.V., and deadly flash points of preventable diseases like whooping cough and measles. All over the country, there are symptoms of a profound public health emergency; young and old are getting sick and dying unnecessarily, while facilities lack basic medicines and equipment. Doctors and ex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Coming to Papua New Guinea: World Leaders (and 40 Maseratis) - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/12/world/asia/papua-new-guinea-apec-conference.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBzzMpdZPPFq-u_BHAbL9p4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 02:51:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/12/world/asia/papua-new-guinea-apec-conference.html" target="_blank"&gt;Coming to Papua New Guinea: World Leaders (and 40 Maseratis)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PORT MORESBY, Papua New Guinea — The Maseratis and Bentleys have been delivered. Laborers from China have repaired roads and installed bus stop shelters with signs saying “China Aid.” Three cruise ships will serve as temporary hotels. The Pacific island nation of Papua New Guinea is in the global spotlight as some of the world’s most powerful leaders gather here this week for the annual Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation summit meeting. Some say hosting the annual Asia-Pacific leaders forum will be Papua New Guinea’s biggest event since it gained independence in 1975. For the country’s scand...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>'Can they really pull it off?': the Apec summit comes to Papua New Guinea - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/12/can-they-really-pull-it-off-the-apec-summit-comes-to-papua-new-guinea</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0AaMhH_MBSJ4dc4epPF78qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 23:44:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/12/can-they-really-pull-it-off-the-apec-summit-comes-to-papua-new-guinea" target="_blank"&gt;'Can they really pull it off?': the Apec summit comes to Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is likely to end, as all Apec leaders summits do, with world leaders, including Xi Jinping, Mike Pence, Shinzo Abe, Justin Trudeau and Australian prime minister Scott Morrison, donning matching shirts and posing awkwardly for a photo op. But this week world leaders will arrive in Port Moresby, the capital of Papua New Guinea, for an Apec unlike any other. This is the first time Papua New Guinea, the poorest country among the 21 countries of the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation (Apec) bloc, has hosted the summit. PNG ranks around 130th worldwide for GDP and 135th in the corruption percep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>First Maseratis, now Bentleys for Apec in Papua New Guinea - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/16/first-maseratis-now-bentleys-for-apec-in-papua-new-guinea</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIAZwBjFFh8cxLzFg-BiDbsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 06:03:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/16/first-maseratis-now-bentleys-for-apec-in-papua-new-guinea" target="_blank"&gt;First Maseratis, now Bentleys for Apec in Papua New Guinea&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Papua New Guinea has reportedly added three Bentleys to its controversial fleet of luxury cars purchased for the upcoming Apec leaders’ summit in November. Papua New Guineans reacted with outrage to the news that the PNG government had bought 40 Maseratis for the summit despite the country struggling with a nationwide polio outbreak, increased rates of tuberculosis and chronic funding shortages for health, education and other services. Opposition MPs called for a nationwide strike over the purchase, which cost millions of dollars, calling it “blatant fraud”. The anger looks set to continue ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Papua New Guinea imports 40 Maseratis to transport Apec delegates - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/12/papua-new-guinea-imports-40-maseratis-to-transport-apec-delegates</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAOWboSDTDwt4_bxRg-G1bEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 03:33:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/12/papua-new-guinea-imports-40-maseratis-to-transport-apec-delegates" target="_blank"&gt;Papua New Guinea imports 40 Maseratis to transport Apec delegates&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Papua New Guineans have reacted with anger at its government importing a fleet of Maseratis to drive international delegates around the Apec conference next month, amid a health and poverty crisis, struggling economy, and ongoing efforts after a devastating earthquake. The PNG government has defended its decision, expressing confidence that all 40 luxury cars will be bought by the “private sector” after the two-day event, leaving the government with no financial burden. The cars, which cost between $200,000 and $350,000 each in Australia, were flown in from Milan on two Boeing 747-8F charte...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Papua New Guinea hit by 7 magnitude earthquake - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/11/papua-new-guinea-hit-by-7-magnitude-earthquake</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPY6dMmOZMt6i5RdXSXWdIIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 22:00:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/11/papua-new-guinea-hit-by-7-magnitude-earthquake" target="_blank"&gt;Papua New Guinea hit by 7 magnitude earthquake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A magnitude 7.0 earthquake has struck remote New Britain island in Papua New Guinea, the United States Geological Survey said, though there were no immediate reports of damage. The quake hit about 200km (125 miles) south-west of the town of Rabaul at a depth of almost 40km, just before 7am local time (2100 GMT Wednesday). “We felt the earthquake a bit, but it was not too strong,” constable Roy Michael told Reuters by phone from Rabaul police station. Related: 'A lurking beast': polio casts shadow over Papua New Guinea independence day He said there was no damage in the town, but officers ha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Indonesia accuses Vanuatu of 'inexcusable' support for West Papua - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/03/indonesia-accuses-vanuatu-of-inexcusable-support-for-west-papua</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDLKryRudNcx3ONtQWzMdwgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 18:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/03/indonesia-accuses-vanuatu-of-inexcusable-support-for-west-papua" target="_blank"&gt;Indonesia accuses Vanuatu of 'inexcusable' support for West Papua&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indonesia has accused Vanuatu of challenging “friendly relations” between the two countries and supporting separatist movements, after it offered support to West Papua at the United Nations. Vanuatu has long been a supporter of the rights of West Papuans in their movement for independence from Indonesia. On Monday Indonesia used its second right of reply at the 73rd UN general assembly to mount an excoriating attack on Vanuatu over its support for West Papuan self-determination, calling it “clueless”. “Although being disguised with flowery human rights concern, Vanuatu’s sole intention and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Polish globe-trotter blunders into Indonesia-Papua conflict - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/2361971b0e0a474386e6047d3ab0cd58</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHSZWfJyzh_im4aPbGe1VEMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 02:16:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/2361971b0e0a474386e6047d3ab0cd58" target="_blank"&gt;Polish globe-trotter blunders into Indonesia-Papua conflict&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA, Indonesia (AP) — To the Indonesian government, the 39-year-old factory worker and globe-trotting Polish traveler is a danger to the state, a man who plotted with shadowy gunmen to foment revolt in isolated eastern jungles. But to his supporters, Jakub Skrzypski is just an idealistic tourist with no money to his name, a man with an oddball combination of sympathies for right-wing and liberation causes. Even Indonesian police say it's unlikely Skrzypski could have arranged the arms deal they say he promised to make with rebels. But Skrzypski, who is charged with treason, still faces ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item></channel></rss>