<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Mohamed Hanipa Maidin - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyY3ZNVEl5WXpGaWNEY1NBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:02:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Former AG Apandi may be charged in court, says Hanipa - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/05/former-ag-apandi-may-be-charged-in-court-says-hanipa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780126632493</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/05/former-ag-apandi-may-be-charged-in-court-says-hanipa/" target="_blank"&gt;Former AG Apandi may be charged in court, says Hanipa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0kUtVkDCXzA" target="_blank"&gt;Not right time to to table separation of powers law, says Hanipa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWl0OU11bGpZQU1FZXhjUjlJSVN1WExLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/hpi3TNzUEYngSsxroSlNZ4zoCncfWlAqeuBcj4UDd-v8rhhFg9n-4kY5r8LHj0wdft_LODRXBcds0NoUWTj0Qu96YvHzNk3yUwIZUTYwNszUgbXEgjLcGszYBRJWqEPe9FbK9lq8GHO_Q6bc=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Hanipa: Govt to put an end to Amanah Ikhtiar Malaysia - New Straits Times</title><link>https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/438001/hanipa-govt-put-end-amanah-ikhtiar-malaysia</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENI3Y-hcKzJjDKT4aUbxOdUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow9sveCjC0m9YBMJHSoQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/438001/hanipa-govt-put-end-amanah-ikhtiar-malaysia" target="_blank"&gt;Hanipa: Govt to put an end to Amanah Ikhtiar Malaysia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department Mohamed Hanipa Maidin says Amanah Ikhtiar Malaysia had gone against regulations by setting up ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nst.com.my">New Straits Times</source></item><item><title>Easier to charge offenders under Sexual Offences Against Children Act, says Hanipa - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/26/easier-to-charge-offenders-under-sexual-offences-against-children-act/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEOGJ3s68wdRsBAJPJ6GMeMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/26/easier-to-charge-offenders-under-sexual-offences-against-children-act/" target="_blank"&gt;Easier to charge offenders under Sexual Offences Against Children Act, says Hanipa - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Sexual Offences Against Children Act 2017 has made it relatively easier to charge perpetrators who are accused of sexual crimes against ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Go ahead with anti-ICERD rally, Hanipa tells Umno-PAS - The Malaysian Insight</title><link>https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/113303</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiLGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZW1hbGF5c2lhbmluc2lnaHQuY29tL3MvMTEzMzAz0gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 05:12:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/113303" target="_blank"&gt;Go ahead with anti-ICERD rally, Hanipa tells Umno-PAS&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Malaysian Insight&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pakatan Harapan has no issues with the December 8 protest as long as it is done responsibly.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com">The Malaysian Insight</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/ErdLhIG16TiRKHitOZ4wCehlcKGEW5sm1U7sz_Q9zEav33Fgf2b0b2itPTWonw4kHgeBwXkZxMQLyRd6jX8AKlXxbHavYAbvFEmjWCRDXQcijTMAG92uPFkbsADSDJlXii1wPcwNrXMF9tSUTr_KNlyOLdbA92ygM1KVCBh-b8zpo7ipRCeojmdvDYPSpW3t4w=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Reform of AG's powers needs two-third support in Parliament - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/22/reform-of-ag-powers-needs-two-third-support-in-parliament/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELpMPzvYNxISL14U3Z3Gcx8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/22/reform-of-ag-powers-needs-two-third-support-in-parliament/" target="_blank"&gt;Reform of AG's powers needs two-third support in Parliament - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The powers and duties of the Attorney General and Public Prosecutor can only be separated once the Government has two-thirds support of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>New act to ensure information obtained from credible, valid sources: Hanipa - The Sun Daily</title><link>https://www.thesundaily.my/local/new-act-to-ensure-information-obtained-from-credible-valid-sources-hanipa-GX198239</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMic2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZXN1bmRhaWx5Lm15L2xvY2FsL25ldy1hY3QtdG8tZW5zdXJlLWluZm9ybWF0aW9uLW9idGFpbmVkLWZyb20tY3JlZGlibGUtdmFsaWQtc291cmNlcy1oYW5pcGEtR1gxOTgyMznSAQA</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 06:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thesundaily.my/local/new-act-to-ensure-information-obtained-from-credible-valid-sources-hanipa-GX198239" target="_blank"&gt;New act to ensure information obtained from credible, valid sources: Hanipa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Sun Daily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The country needs a Freedom of Information Act to ensure that the information disseminated to the public comes from credible and valid s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thesundaily.my">The Sun Daily</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/PGVUg-bPfpzcNRes4B0JUspjbLFP8-7rEd4vMyNxyQ68q5ljppEEdM4lUz599pZBM4gXCEl8XZ2gTfBrlzCS91H-1KDoLHXbZijZqXFKQP44kVnHRnrp0eiz6Gym4mRSFGg-9Zft-m1XDizC8w9Uw6wA_BTXgdoYI4SkCIgb9VuLkQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>No selective prosecution in withdrawal of graft case against Lim Guan Eng: Hanipa - New Straits Times</title><link>https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/432678/no-selective-prosecution-withdrawal-graft-case-against-lim-guan-eng</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFm8sZwGBbuYu_t-61HHHwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow9sveCjC0m9YBMPDtoQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/432678/no-selective-prosecution-withdrawal-graft-case-against-lim-guan-eng" target="_blank"&gt;No selective prosecution in withdrawal of graft case against Lim Guan Eng: Hanipa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: There is no selective prosecution in the withdrawal of the graft case against Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng, said deputy Minister in the Prime ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nst.com.my">New Straits Times</source></item><item><title>Govt must wait till 2026 before carrying out next redelineation exercise, says Hanipa - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/21/govt-must-wait-till-2026-before-carrying-out-next-redelineation-exercise-says-hanipa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBmYT744QlHUyoP_DobpIWsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/21/govt-must-wait-till-2026-before-carrying-out-next-redelineation-exercise-says-hanipa/" target="_blank"&gt;Govt must wait till 2026 before carrying out next redelineation exercise, says Hanipa - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Government has to wait till 2026 or make constitutional amendments if the Election Commission (EC) is to make changes to the electoral ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Gather but keep it peaceful, Hanipa tells anti-Icerd assembly - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM6aDIYvGldrLNlPfvqtV7gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants of the rally against the International Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Racial Discrimination (Icerd) in Kuala Lumpur have been told to maintain peace and keep it clean. Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department Hanipa Maidin said each Malaysian has the right to hold peaceful assembly according to law, but the gathering should be under control and not to create any provocations. “I am repeating what has been said by the Prime Minister (Dr Mahathir Mohamad)... if they want to gather, want to carry out thanksgiving... it is their right, if they promise not t...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Former AG Apandi may be charged in court, says Hanipa - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/12/05/former-ag-apandi-may-be-charged-in-court-says-hanipa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF5_OdwIlG9ipqmDoEPmIigqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:44:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/12/05/former-ag-apandi-may-be-charged-in-court-says-hanipa/" target="_blank"&gt;Former AG Apandi may be charged in court, says Hanipa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year Apandi Ali had declared war on Raja Petra Kamarudin when Malaysia Today revealed his links to Tabung Haji’s Abdul Azeez Rahim (FMT) – Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Hanipa Maidin today hinted that former attorney-general (AG) Mohamed Apandi Ali may be charged in court. “We (lawyers) often asked if the AG would be charged, but I feel now it is possible. “He may be charged,” Hanipa said in the Dewan Rakyat, adding however that political will would be needed to do so. Apandi was appointed as AG on July 27, 2015. He replaced Abdul Gani Patail, who was reportedly re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Barisan, PAS lawmakers willing to amend Constitution to separate AG's powers - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/barisan-pas-lawmakers-willing-to-amend-constitution-to-separate-ag-powers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGKBZ-asV7aC3oiAlqKM00sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 06:02:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/barisan-pas-lawmakers-willing-to-amend-constitution-to-separate-ag-powers/" target="_blank"&gt;Barisan, PAS lawmakers willing to amend Constitution to separate AG's powers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Opposition lawmakers from Barisan Nasional and PAS will support a Pakatan Harapan amendment of the Federal Constitution to separate the powers of the Attorney General (AG) and the Public Prosecutor. The assurance was given by senior Umno and PAS lawmakers when Hanipa Maidin, the Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department in charge of law, told Parliament there are no plans at the moment to separate the powers. "At the moment, there is no Cabinet decision to implement the separation of the powers of the AG as the Government needs a two-thirds majority (in Parliament) to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Dr M: Repeal NSC and gangsters will run wild - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/22/dr-m-repeal-nsc-and-gangsters-will-run-wild/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFhlNF9_AlNw-9Cn6IfpzW4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 13:32:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/22/dr-m-repeal-nsc-and-gangsters-will-run-wild/" target="_blank"&gt;Dr M: Repeal NSC and gangsters will run wild&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – Gangsters and criminals will be free to do whatever they want if the National Security Council (NSC) Act 2016 is repealed, says Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad. “As a democratic nation, we the government have to listen to the people. There is worry that if we repeal the NSC (Act), the gangsters and criminals will be free to do what they like,” said Dr Mahathir. He was commenting on a written statement by Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Hanipa Maidin in Parliament, that stated that the NSC will be amended, not repealed. On Monday (Nov 19), the Pakatan H...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Economist: Why is PH tiptoeing on political financing law? - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/04/economist-why-is-ph-tiptoeing-on-political-financing-law/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELWWv8SfyKShF1d1h81h-kQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 09:16:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/04/economist-why-is-ph-tiptoeing-on-political-financing-law/" target="_blank"&gt;Economist: Why is PH tiptoeing on political financing law?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – A political economist has questioned the government’s commitment to ensuring transparency in political funding, saying it has shown it doesn’t consider it urgent to introduce the relevant law. Edmund Terence Gomez, a Universiti Malaya professor, said Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Hanipa Maidin appeared evasive when he spoke to him on the issue last Tuesday at the venue of an anti-corruption conference, where both had earlier addressed the audience. He told FMT he didn’t get clear answers from Hanipa when he asked him at what stage Pakatan Harapan was in its deli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Mohamed Hanipa urges victims of marital rape to lodge reports - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/mohamed-hanipa-urges-victims-of-marital-rape-to-lodge-reports/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECXijW1-gRl-rSxLCozpXcYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 07:33:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/mohamed-hanipa-urges-victims-of-marital-rape-to-lodge-reports/" target="_blank"&gt;Mohamed Hanipa urges victims of marital rape to lodge reports&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Following backlash from women's groups, Mohamed Hanipa Maidin is now encouraging women to lodge police reports on any form of domestic violence, including marital rape. The Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department said at present there was a scarcity of such police reports to substantiate such unfortunate incidents. According to Mohamed Hanipa, there is only one case under Section 375(A) of the Penal Code, which makes it an offence for a man to use fear or violence against his wife for sexual intercourse. However, it does not cover non-consensual sex in a marriage. "...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hanipa: Political financing law not priority, will be enacted within Pakatan govt's term - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/30/hanipa-political-financing-law-not-priority-will-be-enacted-within-pakatan-govts-term/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG9bks9ktF492WmhKQ4t8MkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 09:19:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/30/hanipa-political-financing-law-not-priority-will-be-enacted-within-pakatan-govts-term/" target="_blank"&gt;Hanipa: Political financing law not priority, will be enacted within Pakatan govt's term&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Hanipa Maidin (pic) says no timeframe is given as to when the legislation on political funding will be enacted although it will be within this government’s term. “I don’t want to speculate, but I believe they (government) is going to present it within this term,” the Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department told reporters on the sidelines of the Anti-Corruption Summit at a hotel here on Tuesday (Oct 30). He said this when asked if political financing legislation would be in place before the next general election. “We have agreed in principle to have this legislation,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>No plans to make marital rape a crime, says Hanipa Maidin - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/30/no-plans-to-make-marital-rape-a-crime-says-hanipa-maidin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDpVwaLtItdtcAYIoulXIHMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 03:57:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/30/no-plans-to-make-marital-rape-a-crime-says-hanipa-maidin/" target="_blank"&gt;No plans to make marital rape a crime, says Hanipa Maidin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: There are no plans to make martial rape a crime, says Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department Hanipa Maidin. "There is no decision to amend the law to make marital or spousal rape a crime," he said when answering a question raised by Maria Chin Abdullah (PH-Petaling Jaya) in Parliament today (Oct 30). He said the proposal was considered in 2006, but was rejected due to religious and evidentiary factors. Instead, Hanipa said that Section 375A of the Penal Code was amended to make it an offence for a spouse to put fear or to use violence against his wife. More to come&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakatan govt should protect wives from abusive or sex maniac husbands says Wanita MCA - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/pakatan-govt-should-protect-wives-from-abusive-or-sex-maniac-husbands-says-wanita-mca/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHVx7HyI5x8MLEtKymBgpecqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:02:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/pakatan-govt-should-protect-wives-from-abusive-or-sex-maniac-husbands-says-wanita-mca/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan govt should protect wives from abusive or sex maniac husbands says Wanita MCA&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Wanita MCA says the Pakatan Harapan government should protect wives from abusive or sex maniac husbands. As such, Wanita MCA chief Datuk Heng Seai Kie (pic) has challenged the Minister and Deputy Minister of the Women, Family and Community Development to state their stand on whether the government will or will not criminalise marital rape She said the Minister, Datin Seri Dr Wan Azizan Wan Ismail, and her deputy, Hannah Yeoh, should both state the ministry’s stand on the Parliamentary reply by Mohamed Hanipa Maidin, which was that the government has no plans to amend laws to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Shouting match erupts in Parliament after MP says BN will sabotage election reforms - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/shouting-match-erupts-in-parliament-after-mp-says-bn-will-sabotage-election-reforms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENplDWKGekX3hqm0_P9sGQUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 07:01:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/shouting-match-erupts-in-parliament-after-mp-says-bn-will-sabotage-election-reforms/" target="_blank"&gt;Shouting match erupts in Parliament after MP says BN will sabotage election reforms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A shouting match erupted in Parliament after a deputy minister claimed it would be hard for the government to do election reforms for fear of sabotage by the opposition Barisan Nasional. Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Mohamed Hanipa Maidin (PH-Sepang) said the government’s attempt to reduce the voting age to 18 and to introduce automatic voters registration required two-thirds support in the Dewan Rakyat to amend the Federal Constitution. “Whatever we are doing (for election reforms) need amendments to the Constitution. "The problem is the Pakatan Harapan g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Mujahid not encouraging vice, says Anwar - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/08/mujahid-not-encouraging-vice-says-anwar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJGJn1KWF5ckFzAkQcN1uqgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/08/mujahid-not-encouraging-vice-says-anwar/" target="_blank"&gt;Mujahid not encouraging vice, says Anwar&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The remarks by Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Datuk Dr Mujahid Yusof Rawa (pic) on khalwat raids must be seen in a larger context, says PKR president-elect Datuk Seri Anwar Ibrahim. He said the minister was merely referring to how enforcement should be carried out. “He did not encourage khalwat. He was only talking about the legal action. We do not encourage it (khalwat). Vice is vice,” he told reporters at Padang Merdeka in Sri Tanjung, Port Dickson yesterday. Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Mohamed Hanipa Maidin said the issue of Dr Mujahid s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hanipa: Govt to review landmark judgment allowing individuals to be sued for defamation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/28/hanipa-govt-to-review-landmark-judgment-allowing-individuals-to-be-sued-for-defamation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECWBgGgqWjXFkMuAopjynJoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 08:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/28/hanipa-govt-to-review-landmark-judgment-allowing-individuals-to-be-sued-for-defamation/" target="_blank"&gt;Hanipa: Govt to review landmark judgment allowing individuals to be sued for defamation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Pakatan Harapan government will review the Federal Court’s landmark judgment allowing the government to sue individuals for defamation, says Mohamed Hanipa Maidin. “We are going to have a meeting and form a committee to study the matter. “This includes taking into consideration recommendations made on the issue and the Derbyshire principle, which is based on sound judgment,” the Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department told reporters at the launching of the International Sports Law Conference at the Asian International Arbitration Centre (AIAC) on Friday (Sept ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hanipa: Govt committed to ensure racial balance in civil service - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/03/govt-committed-to-ensure-racial-balance-in-civil-service-says-hanipa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBRTKDF1qA4HJM5jrgtSN9kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 10:21:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/03/govt-committed-to-ensure-racial-balance-in-civil-service-says-hanipa/" target="_blank"&gt;Hanipa: Govt committed to ensure racial balance in civil service&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR (Bernama): The Pakatan Harapan (PH) government is committed to ensuring racial balance in the civil service, said Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department Mohamed Hanipa Maidin. However, he said, the appointment of an individual into the civil service was based on the merits of qualification under the Public Service Commission (SPA). “The government appointed a non-Malay as the finance minister based on merit and credibility. The appointments of the Attorney-General, Chief Justice ... all these are examples of what the government is doing to create an environment wher...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>AG mulls amending charges against Sosma detainees, says Hanipa - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/29/ag-mulls-amending-charges-against-sosma-detainees-says-hanipa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELxfcIUXNJKtclB-VuL9ZN4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 04:40:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/29/ag-mulls-amending-charges-against-sosma-detainees-says-hanipa/" target="_blank"&gt;AG mulls amending charges against Sosma detainees, says Hanipa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR (Bernama): The Attorney General (AG), in his capacity as the Public Prosecutor, is considering amending the charges against the 442 people remanded under the Security Offences (Special Measures) Act 2012 (Sosma), says Mohamed Hanipa Maidin. The Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department said the process would take some time as it had to be done on a case-by-case basis. "The Criminal Procedure Code (and not Sosma) will govern the procedural aspects if the charges are so amended. "The Public Prosecutor will give priority to female offenders and juveniles. Likewise, sick o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Sosma detainees in Sg Buloh prison end hunger strike - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/26/sosma-detainees-in-sg-buloh-prison-end-hunger-strike/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELQOuTT8KNZzmECSNkW0XUYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 09:15:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/26/sosma-detainees-in-sg-buloh-prison-end-hunger-strike/" target="_blank"&gt;Sosma detainees in Sg Buloh prison end hunger strike&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUNGAI BULOH (Bernama): A total of 118 detainees held under the Security Offences (Special Measures) Act (Sosma) 2012 at the Sungai Buloh Prison have agreed to end their hunger strike. Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department Mohamed Hanipa Maidin said an agreement was reached after he a two-hour meeting with representatives of the detainees. "They (detainees) agreed to end the hunger strike and have started to eat and drink. Their health is also good," he told reporters at the Sungai Buloh Prison here Sunday (Aug 26). Earlier, he met with the detainees' family members who had gat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakatan wants to end bribery, injustice, discrimination and inequality - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/26/pakatan-wants-to-end-bribery-injustice-discrimination-and-inequality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIJGixEbNgqKs2dWvUsSVI0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMOvrnwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 08:56:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/26/pakatan-wants-to-end-bribery-injustice-discrimination-and-inequality/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan wants to end bribery, injustice, discrimination and inequality&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anwar Ibrahim was pardoned and allowed to go home. And he is a convicted criminal. Another 118 others have not been pardoned and allowed to go home. And they have never been tried or convicted of any crime. NO HOLDS BARRED Raja Petra Kamarudin This was what Free Malaysia Today reported today: Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Hanipa Maidin said the 118 Sosma detainees have agreed to end their hunger strike, which they started on Friday. Attorney-General Tommy Thomas said yesterday that the law would “go soon” and it was subject to consultation with many ministries. In July,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Parliament passes bill to repeal Anti-Fake News law - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/16/parliament-passes-bill-to-repeal-anti-fake-news-law/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOO2Apx2Am1_33BGnDz3IRwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 09:43:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/16/parliament-passes-bill-to-repeal-anti-fake-news-law/" target="_blank"&gt;Parliament passes bill to repeal Anti-Fake News law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Anti-Fake News Act, which was passed about five months ago, has been repealed with a simple voice vote. Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department Mohamed Hanipa Maidin in his winding-up speech said there were sufficient laws to deal with fake news. "We don't need new legislations. We already have existing laws, such as the Communications and Multimedia Act 1998 and others that can deal with this phenomenon," he told lawmakers on Thursday. Mohamed Hanipa also said the police and other enforcement agencies should be empowered further to deal with the emergence of fa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>We are committed to abolishing Sosma, says Mohamed Hanipa - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/19/we-are-committed-to-abolishing-sosma-says-mohamed-hanipa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFUMPPDGtNYvNO3oxYSnhEcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 06:26:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/19/we-are-committed-to-abolishing-sosma-says-mohamed-hanipa/" target="_blank"&gt;We are committed to abolishing Sosma, says Mohamed Hanipa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Government remains committed to abolishing the controversial Security Offences (Special Measures) Act 2012 (Sosma), which allows for detention without trial. Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister's Department Mohamed Hanipa Maidin (pic) gave his assurance that the Government would repeal such laws, but could not commit to when it would be done. “We have received a memorandum from a non-governmental organisation, comprising more than 400 families of those who have been detained under Sosma. “The Government wants to abolish Sosma, but it will take time. “I will bring this ma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hanipa in stable condition after fainting - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/10/hanipa-in-stable-condition-after-fainting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOGhAkHI1mSxamWAV3ReDXEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/10/hanipa-in-stable-condition-after-fainting/" target="_blank"&gt;Hanipa in stable condition after fainting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Mohamed Hanipa Maidin is in stable condition at the hospital here after fainting during the monthly assembly. He is expected to be discharged today. Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad, who was addressing the assembly when Hanipa suddenly slumped and fell off the stage, said he “was found to be okay now”. Hanipa’s media officer Anas As-Said Zaharuddin said the 49-year-old Sepang MP was still being treated at the Putrajaya Hospital. “Doctors are still examining him to determine why he fainted and collapsed,” he said. During the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Hanipa Maidin collapses while attending Putrajaya monthly assembly - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/07/09/hanipa-maidin-collapses-while-attending-putrajaya-monthly-assembly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBJzFlbut3Gno1w6vEaJa54qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 06:58:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/07/09/hanipa-maidin-collapses-while-attending-putrajaya-monthly-assembly/" target="_blank"&gt;Hanipa Maidin collapses while attending Putrajaya monthly assembly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – Deputy Minister in the Prime Minister’s Department Hanipa Maidin today collapsed while attending the monthly civil servants’ assembly in Putrajaya. Hanipa, the Amanah MP for Sepang who took his oath of office last week, underwent surgery at the Kuala Lumpur Hospital for a brain haemorrhage in 2016 after collapsing in the middle of a Dewan Rakyat debate. He was out of action for six months, returning to Parliament in October that year. He lost consciousness today as Prime Minister Dr Mahathir Mohamad was delivering a speech at Dataran Perdana. Hanipa, who was there together with Depu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Deputy Minister suffers fainting spell at monthly gathering - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/09/deputy-minister-suffers-fainting-spell-at-monthly-gathering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAEceWocR6vdvqqJvLteSegqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 01:05:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/09/deputy-minister-suffers-fainting-spell-at-monthly-gathering/" target="_blank"&gt;Deputy Minister suffers fainting spell at monthly gathering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Deputy Minister In the Prime Minister's Department Mohamed Hanipa Maidin suffered from a fainting spell while attending the department 's monthly gathering. This caused him to fall from the temporary stage while Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad was addressing the crowd. Dr Mahathir stopped his speech for several minutes while Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Dr Wan Azizah Wan Ismail came down from stage to check on Hanipa. Those present were shocked and staff on duty immediately attended to him. A doctor on standby provided Hanipa with medical attention before he was taken ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakatan’s Hanipa Maidin says Najib is guilty even if not proven guilty - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/17/pakatans-hanipa-maidin-says-najib-is-guilty-even-if-not-proven-guilty/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIcAoCBuiUJ4wpdleZav3PgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 08:52:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/06/17/pakatans-hanipa-maidin-says-najib-is-guilty-even-if-not-proven-guilty/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan’s Hanipa Maidin says Najib is guilty even if not proven guilty&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Malaysiakini) – After attendees to Najib Abdul Razak’s Hari Raya open house said that the former premier should be presumed innocent until proven guilty, Sepang MP Hanipa Maidin says that the maxim should only apply in certain contexts, specifically during the judicial process. “I am not saying that the principle or maxim is wrong. It is just that when it is being used frivolously, without context of the place, time and situation, it turns out funny. “There is nothing wrong with that principle if we use it in the context of a trial in court. But if you want to use it in an unqualified mann...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Amanah appalled PAS making AG appointment a racial issue - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/04/amanah-appalled-pas-making-ag-appointment-a-racial-issue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKSWxXk8Rm-1TW1rpjSxtNQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/04/amanah-appalled-pas-making-ag-appointment-a-racial-issue/" target="_blank"&gt;Amanah appalled PAS making AG appointment a racial issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: While PAS is against Tommy Thomas as candidate for the Attorney General (AG) post, its offshoot Parti Amanah Negara is “disgusted and tired” that the candidacy is being turned into a racial issue. PAS information chief Nasrudin Hassan has come out insisting that the AG must be a person capable of protecting Islam. “Islam is the religion of the federation. The appointment of the AG must be based on that,” Nasrudin said in a statement yesterday. Amanah legal bureau chief Hanipa Maidin said: “Frankly, I am really disgusted and tired with such racial issues. “With respect, I feel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakatan wins all seats in Sepang - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/05/11/pakatan-wins-all-seats-in-sepang/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI-wk6CstuB6jK5WvEUg4jcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/05/11/pakatan-wins-all-seats-in-sepang/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan wins all seats in Sepang&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAKATAN Harapan has made a clean sweep in Sepang by winning all the parliamentary and state seats in the constituency. Borhan Aman Shah, from PKR, who won the Tanjung Sepat state seat, said he had earlier received a congratulatory call from PKR deputy president Datuk Azmin Ali, but as results were not official yet, he chose to sit outside the tallying centre, surrounded by friends for moral support. Sharing the same initial trepidations was Adhif Syan Abdullah, from Pribumi, who won the Dengkil seat after beating his former boss Shahrum Mohd Sharif from Barisan Nasional and PAS’ Yusmi Hanif...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Colourful affair at Sepang nomination centre - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/04/28/colourful-affair-at-sepang-nomination-centre/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA-1YOAdl4VOs-7z6mfijAsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 08:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/04/28/colourful-affair-at-sepang-nomination-centre/" target="_blank"&gt;Colourful affair at Sepang nomination centre&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHOOPS, cries and chants pierced the quiet morning air at Bandar Baru Salak Tinggi multipurpose hall as processions of supporters accompanying the candidates for the Sepang parliamentary and state constituencies arrived to register their names at the nomination centre. Attracting the attention of the newspeople who had been waiting at the entrance hall as early as 7.30am was a team of female officers from the police light strike force team. Corporal Nor Zihan Amran (pic below), who unwittingly found herself the centre of attraction, refused to comment for security reasons but a police spoke...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Amanah MP under fire after ‘if I were God’ remark - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/03/30/amanah-mp-under-fire-after-if-i-were-god-remark/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPx_Od88GYSvqZ7FemKNCrgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 11:44:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/03/30/amanah-mp-under-fire-after-if-i-were-god-remark/" target="_blank"&gt;Amanah MP under fire after ‘if I were God’ remark&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Muslims must refrain from likening themselves to God as it degrades the latter, Perlis mufti Datuk Mohd Asri Zainul Abidin warned today, following a controversial remark by an MP in Parliament yesterday. Asri said any Muslim who likens him or herself to God “was indirectly debasing Him and denying His creation”, adding that the act could be dangerous to the person’s faith. “If you say ‘if I were God, I wouldn’t have done this or that’… then you may have indirectly denied His creation and debased its significance,” Asri wrote on his Facebook page. “This is dangerous to the faith of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Mat Sabu cleared over Bukit Kepong remarks - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/19/mat-sabu-cleared-over-bukit-kepong-remarks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAOG5kIqwFoFAzuk45TZTKMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 05:03:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/19/mat-sabu-cleared-over-bukit-kepong-remarks/" target="_blank"&gt;Mat Sabu cleared over Bukit Kepong remarks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Amanah president Mohamad Sabu has walked free of defamation charges over remarks about the 1950 Bukit Kepong incident, after the Court of Appeal here upheld his acquittal. The three person panel led by Justice Tengku Maimun Tuan Mat unanimously found there was no reason to challenge the High Court's findings that the prosecution failed to raise a prima facie case. The panel which also included Justices Ahmadi Asnawi and Rhodzariah Bujang also agreed that the charge was defective. Mohamad, popularly known as Mat Sabu, was charged with defaming policemen and their family members wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>