<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Circumcision - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNREY2YTNrU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:16:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Two government hospitals, three others seek to strike out negligence suit over botched circumcision - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/two-government-hospitals-three-others-seek-to-strike-out-negligence-suit-over-botched-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDhBaT42D-OmI4afMiWf0UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:43:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/two-government-hospitals-three-others-seek-to-strike-out-negligence-suit-over-botched-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Two government hospitals, three others seek to strike out negligence suit over botched circumcision - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Two government hospitals and three others are seeking to strike out a negligence suit filed by a teenager, who suffered permanent disability ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Female circumcision part of Malaysian culture, says DPM - New Straits Times</title><link>https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/431411/female-genital-mutilation-part-malaysian-culture-says-dpm</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE-2oLrw4VFWZJfvfm6yzzYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow9sveCjC0m9YBMPDtoQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/431411/female-genital-mutilation-part-malaysian-culture-says-dpm" target="_blank"&gt;Female circumcision part of Malaysian culture, says DPM&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Deputy Prime Minister Datuk Seri Wan Azizah Wan Ismail has reiterated the government's stand on female circumcision, calling it a part of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nst.com.my">New Straits Times</source></item><item><title>Teenager files suit after suffering from botched circumcision - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/30/teenager-files-suit-after-suffering-from-botched-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDft4qadPr27OgVYTXEUzdcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 08:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/30/teenager-files-suit-after-suffering-from-botched-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Teenager files suit after suffering from botched circumcision - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A teenager who suffered permanent disability after a circumcision procedure went awry eight years ago, has filed a suit against two ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Suhakam slams 'misleading' comment on female circumcision at UN event - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/14/suhakam-slams-misleading-comment-on-female-circumcision-at-un-event/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMigQFodHRwczovL3d3dy5mcmVlbWFsYXlzaWF0b2RheS5jb20vY2F0ZWdvcnkvbmF0aW9uLzIwMTgvMTEvMTQvc3VoYWthbS1zbGFtcy1taXNsZWFkaW5nLWNvbW1lbnQtb24tZmVtYWxlLWNpcmN1bWNpc2lvbi1hdC11bi1ldmVudC_SAQA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/14/suhakam-slams-misleading-comment-on-female-circumcision-at-un-event/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam slams 'misleading' comment on female circumcision at UN event&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suhakam chairman Razali Ismail says the claim that female circumcision is a 'cultural obligation' will damage Malaysia's stand on human rights.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/gZhmh606-dZuRHFg5ErDiMAInequ5Z1FQw16KXpbzFocUT4SniNxET8Ti7sXbk3Wa4Bl2RKaNUi0cc7X4TF4Fios0NvK6vgEy03beiRjMgxsrIlQTJmWItjPMvIT67xnSIWHCE83iRAFYGCtEMIlhJF2Hj8=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Defending female circumcision in Malaysia - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/16/defending-female-circumcision-in-msia-dpm-says-only-accredited-medical-professionals-can-perform-the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDg1CxCmhK3wbB8HAEIbu3EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/16/defending-female-circumcision-in-msia-dpm-says-only-accredited-medical-professionals-can-perform-the/" target="_blank"&gt;Defending female circumcision in Malaysia - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Putrajaya has affirmed its stand that female circumcision is part of the Malaysian culture.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Botched circumcision: Five defendants apply to strike out suit - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDe7UTBzHC2IMflF-KkyldYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 09:33:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government and four others, who were named defendants in a negligence suit filed by a man over a circumcision that went awry when he was 10 years old, have applied to strike out the suit. Besides the government, the other defendants are Kuala Lipis Hospital medical officer and its director, as well as a specialist doctor and director of Selayang Hospital. They were named the second to sixth defendants in the suit. A medical assistant at Kuala Lipis Hospital, who was named the first defendant, had filed an application to strike out the suit, but later withdrew the application. Lawyer Moh...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>FGM: Number of child victims and girls at risk doubles in year in England and Wales - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/fgm-female-genital-mutilation-uk-girls-number-doubles-year-england-wales-a8660036.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIzEfK_C07FptayNQiWu2-IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/fgm-female-genital-mutilation-uk-girls-number-doubles-year-england-wales-a8660036.html" target="_blank"&gt;FGM: Number of child victims and girls at risk doubles in year in England and Wales&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of girls identified as victims of female genital mutilation (FGM) or being at risk has more than doubled in a year as campaigners warn the practice is significantly under-reported. New figures show that FGM was listed in 1,960 social work assessments by councils in 2017/18, compared to 970 cases the previous year. Possible cases of child abuse linked to faith or belief, such as fears of spirit possession or witchcraft, rose by 12 per cent to 1,630 in the same period. Read more - MP who blocked upskirting bill sparks outrage for blocking FGM bill - FGM orders granted to protect Ro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Police arrest 6 after a teenage boy died in an adulthood initiation ritual in Kenya - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/27/africa/kenya-teenager-dies-after-ritual-circumcision-int/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGBA7C2XfiokZLjO0OKvaw8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 13:04:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/27/africa/kenya-teenager-dies-after-ritual-circumcision-int/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Police arrest 6 after a teenage boy died in an adulthood initiation ritual in Kenya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six people have been arrested after a teenage boy died in an adulthood initiation ritual that went wrong in Kenya. Juliano Kanyonyo, 15, died Wednesday morning after being sent to a camp to join other teenage boys in a traditional ceremony designed to teach him the customary values of his people. Days after returning from the trip and recovering from a circumcision that is part of the ritual, Kanyonyo was found dead by his sister at their home in Kandara, central Kenya. "I went to serve him tea, we are not allowed in that house as females but he would pick it from outside but that morning h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Teen sues over botched op - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/01/teen-sues-over-botched-op-circumcision-procedure-leaves-youth-with-permanent-disability/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKoOP-tEaWMteGN8OR16UncqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/01/teen-sues-over-botched-op-circumcision-procedure-leaves-youth-with-permanent-disability/" target="_blank"&gt;Teen sues over botched op&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A teenager, who suffered permanent disability after a circumcision procedure went awry eight years ago, has filed a suit against two government hospitals and four others for negligence. The 18-year-old, who filed the lawsuit via his mother, has named a medical assistant, a doctor at Kuala Lipis Hospital, the director of Kuala Lipis Hospital, a doctor at Selayang Hospital, the director of Selayang Hospital and the government as the defendants. In the lawsuit filed on July 19, it said that on Dec 13, 2010, at about 10am, the first defendant carried out the circumcision surgery, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Judge's Decision Dismissing Female Genital Mutilation Charges Sparks Concern - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/judges-decision-dismissing-fgm-charges-sparks-concern-among-activists_us_5bf57f02e4b03b230f9db168</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG0t6HhJ4eDZt6Ml8vTlAFgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 22:09:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/judges-decision-dismissing-fgm-charges-sparks-concern-among-activists_us_5bf57f02e4b03b230f9db168" target="_blank"&gt;Judge's Decision Dismissing Female Genital Mutilation Charges Sparks Concern&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A federal judge has dismissed key charges against a Michigan doctor accused by prosecutors of performing female genital mutilation (FGM) on young girls ― a decision that has prompted some concern among activists against the practice. On Tuesday, U.S. District Judge Bernard Friedman dismissed conspiracy and mutilation charges against Dr. Jumana Nagarwala, a Detroit physician accused of performing the surgery on nine minor girls, and Dr. Fakhruddin Attar, who reportedly allowed the procedures to take place in his Livonia clinic. The same charges were also dismissed against two women who repor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Law which bans female genital mutilation ruled as unconstitutional by US federal judge - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/female-genital-mutilation-michigan-doctor-unconstitutional-us-a8645091.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIHTIL0S35EzXWNJsCoF-L0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/female-genital-mutilation-michigan-doctor-unconstitutional-us-a8645091.html" target="_blank"&gt;Law which bans female genital mutilation ruled as unconstitutional by US federal judge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US law banning female genital mutilation has been ruled unconstitutional by a federal judge. Judge Bernard Friedman dropped almost all charges against a Michigan doctor accused of performing the procedure on several underage age girls. The judge wrote in the decision: "Congress overstepped its bounds by legislating to prohibit [female genital mutilation]” and said it was a “local criminal activity" for states to figure out. - Read more FGM in England and Wales 'not being properly investigated' “As despicable as this practice may be, it is essentially a criminal assault...FGM is not part...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Another botched circumcision emerges - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/08/another-botched-circumcision-emerges-third-of-such-case-prompts-calls-for-legal-action-by-govt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK2RVz0s0-OxTcHcJpJvU5IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/08/another-botched-circumcision-emerges-third-of-such-case-prompts-calls-for-legal-action-by-govt/" target="_blank"&gt;Another botched circumcision emerges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEGAMAT: A third case of a circumcision gone wrong has come to light, prompting the Health Ministry to urge victims to take such cases to court. The victim, a 10-year-old boy, has to use a catheter and a urine bag after severe damage to his penis. Health Minister Datuk Seri Dr S. Subramaniam said parents of victims of botched circumcisions should file civil suits to get compensation. “The ministry can suspend the licences of medical practitioners if they are found to be negligent by the Malaysian Medical Council,” he said during a visit to Pekan Batu Anam here yesterday. Dr Subramaniam said...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Complications of circumcision - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/ask-dr-g/2016/12/11/complications-of-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhu60SWDrOqTz4Vo7ibWysqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 04:45:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/ask-dr-g/2016/12/11/complications-of-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Complications of circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the school holidays, parents are taking the opportunity to schedule health care appointments for their children. This includes fathers bringing their sons to see the urologists. This week, we address the issues relating to circumsion of children. Dear Dr G, I am a concern father who has two boys. My elder one is now 9 years old and the younger one is only seven. When my older boy was born, I accepted the proposal of the paediatrician to let him undergo a circumcision. Although the operation was uneventful, my son began to have a band that bridged across the penile shaft and glans. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘Please help my only child’ - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/31/please-help-my-only-child-father-pleads-for-medical-aid-to-treat-son/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0Vf9qjwPLk41VCbDde7xUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/31/please-help-my-only-child-father-pleads-for-medical-aid-to-treat-son/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Please help my only child’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: It’s a living nightmare for the father of a nine-year-old boy who had part of his penis severed during a botched circumcision. Fighting back tears, the boy’s father – who wanted to be known only as Ali – issued a plea to medical experts and authorities to help his only child. “Please help us. We don’t know what to do. It has been 16 days since this happened and it has been 16 days of torture for us,” he said at a press conference at Hospital Kuala Lumpur (HKL). The boy’s case is the first of two botched circumcisions that have been reported in the past two weeks. On Dec 15, Al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Doctor accidentally cut off boy's penis during circumcision procedure - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/doctor-cut-off-boy-penis-circumcision-geneva-switzerland-procedure-muslim-a7658361.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGMsDdAm1jviLGcrKYf0Ex0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 17:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/doctor-cut-off-boy-penis-circumcision-geneva-switzerland-procedure-muslim-a7658361.html" target="_blank"&gt;Doctor accidentally cut off boy's penis during circumcision procedure&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A doctor who allegedly cut off a boys penis during his circumcision, has been accused of causing serious body harm by negligence. Swiss prosecutor Judith Levy Owczarczak accused the medic of trying to cover up the 2014 incident, which took place at his surgery. Instead of sending the four-year-old boy straight to hospital, she said he spent four hours “running around Geneva trying to find a catheter” according to La Tribune de Genève newspaper. Read more - Herpes cases in babies linked to ultra-Orthodox circumcision ritual - Doctors in Denmark want to stop circumcision for under-18s - Teena...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Preventing The Spread Of HIV With One Simple Gadget - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/leebelltech/2017/06/28/prepex-the-simple-gadget-preventing-the-spread-of-hiv/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGvt8ypHzSd9g4W1sLVeEXoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 14:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/leebelltech/2017/06/28/prepex-the-simple-gadget-preventing-the-spread-of-hiv/" target="_blank"&gt;Preventing The Spread Of HIV With One Simple Gadget&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2007, the World Health Organization (WHO) and UNAIDS cited that Voluntary Medical Male Circumcision can reduce the risk of HIV infection by approximately 60 percent in high risk areas such as Sub Saharan Africa. So to save millions of lives and billions of dollars in long-term HIV/AIDS healthcare costs, UNAIDS is leading a campaign that involves the circumcision of 27 million men. But how do you get million so men to willingly opt into such a personal and potentially dangerous procedure? You invent a device that makes it easy, painless and cheap, that’s how. Enter a startup called Circ M...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Boy loses penis in second botched circumcision - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/29/boy-loses-penis-botched-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGQdoxS0DjIl13TcbImC9NQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 12:12:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/29/boy-loses-penis-botched-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Boy loses penis in second botched circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A nine-year-old boy has lost his penis after a failed reattachment, in the second botched circumcision case in a span of a week. According to Hindraf lawyer P Uthayakumar, a nine-year-old boy had the head of his penis completely severed during a circumcision procedure using scissors at a Jalan Ipoh clinic on Dec 15. Uthayakumar said the boy was then sent to Hospital Kuala Lumpur (HKL) to try and reattach the penis. However, the reattachment failed and the penis blackened, leaving the doctor no choice but to amputate the boy's penis. "It is so unfortunate that this had happened...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Genital piercings – to do or not to do - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/putting-dr-g-on-the-spot/2017/08/20/genital-piercings-to-do-or-not-to-do/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGbS0sKccCJ6RZqdrCWl9KIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 04:32:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/putting-dr-g-on-the-spot/2017/08/20/genital-piercings-to-do-or-not-to-do/" target="_blank"&gt;Genital piercings – to do or not to do&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dear Dr G, I am a 24-four-year old university student who reads your column on a regular basis and I hope you can help me to answer some "strange" questions. My girlfriend recently talked to me about a "Prince Albert piercing", and mentioned how sexy she finds it. Following the initial conversation, she has asked me to think about doing this myself. I know nothing about genital piercings and am rather horrified at the thought of some jewellery hanging on my manhood. However, since I love my girlfriend a lot, I will consider the piercing. What is a "Prince Albert piercing", what is the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Jeremy Hunt 'googled FGM survivor and asked her if she could have orgasms' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/jeremy-hunt-fgm-survivor-nimco-ali-google-orgasm-female-genital-mutilation-health-secretary-a7652521.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB-6sxww1gQ9E2Msthwor74qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 16:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/jeremy-hunt-fgm-survivor-nimco-ali-google-orgasm-female-genital-mutilation-health-secretary-a7652521.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jeremy Hunt 'googled FGM survivor and asked her if she could have orgasms'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jeremy Hunt has been accused of asking a Female Genital Mutilation (FGM) campaigner whether “girls like you” can still have an orgasm. Nimco Ali claimed the Health Secretary found her via a Google search and that he had no idea about FGM at the time. The former civil servant, who is the director of the Daughters of Eve non-profit organisation, told the News Roast podcast that the pair met at his Whitehall office four years ago. “This man is the Secretary of State for Health but he has no idea about FGM and I don’t think he even reads his briefings,” said Ms Ali, recalling her thoughts at th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Photo of 'pierced' baby sparks outrage - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/health/2017/07/07/facebook-baby-piercing-enedina-vance-orig-vstop.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPwTqI557bWDtZbG3mOu1FcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 17:13:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/health/2017/07/07/facebook-baby-piercing-enedina-vance-orig-vstop.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Photo of 'pierced' baby sparks outrage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mother's Facebook post showing her baby daughter with a pierced cheek sparked a debate over piercing and circumcising children. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Danish Doctors’ Group Wants to End Circumcision for Boys - The New York Times</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/12/08/world/europe/circumcision-boys-babies.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFThnaQRdyZEJbwd683_N8AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 19:49:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2016/12/08/world/europe/circumcision-boys-babies.html" target="_blank"&gt;Danish Doctors’ Group Wants to End Circumcision for Boys&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A major doctors association in Denmark has recommended ending circumcisions for boys, saying the procedure should be “an informed personal choice” that young men make for themselves when they reach adulthood. But the Danish Medical Association stopped short of calling for a legal ban, saying it would be difficult to predict the consequences. “This area is ethically, culturally and religiously complex, and we worry whether a legal ban might result in unauthorized circumcisions,” said Lisa Moller, the president of the association’s ethics committee, which released the new policy statement las...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Family of boy with severed penis hopes for help from specialists - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/30/boy-with-severed-penis-hopes-for-help-from-specialists/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH_YaZDPpRfMpeUXE4j88CIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 15:09:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/30/boy-with-severed-penis-hopes-for-help-from-specialists/" target="_blank"&gt;Family of boy with severed penis hopes for help from specialists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The family of a nine-year-old boy, whose penis was severed during a circumcision, hopes to get help from specialists to reattach the part. Lawyer P.Uthayakumar, who is representing the parents, Ali Akhbar Pakkeer Mohamad and Rodziah Abdul Razak, said the family wants immediate action since it is a sensitive issue and involves the boy's future. "A private health centre has referred the case to HKL (Hospital Kuala Lumpur) since they do not have specialists to reattach the severed part. "If HKL does not have specialists to help his son, I urge HKL, Pusat Zakat or Baitulmal to get...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Bangladesh family arrested over fake penis scam - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/02/08/bangladesh-family-arrested-over-fake-penis-scam/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFeh4U0rPRSM9aXUV5_aIXUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 09:45:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2017/02/08/bangladesh-family-arrested-over-fake-penis-scam/" target="_blank"&gt;Bangladesh family arrested over fake penis scam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DHAKA: A family in Bangladesh has been arrested after using a fake penis to trick villagers into believing a genie had performed a sex change on their teenage daughter, police said Wednesday. Villagers in southern Bangladesh rushed to the family’s home seeking miracle cures after hearing the genie had changed the girl’s sex and performed a circumcision as proof. But police smelled a scam, and took the 15-year-old to a hospital for an examination. “A doctor examined the teenager and discovered a fake penis tied to her waist,” Monzur Murshed, the local police chief, told AFP. “The girl and he...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Two more charged in first US female genital mutilation case - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/fgm-female-genital-mutilation-jumana-nagarwala-fakhruddin-attar-farida-attar-michigan-dawoodi-bohra-a7698106.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENngpX5x9l2VwoBWX3CugtUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 21:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/fgm-female-genital-mutilation-jumana-nagarwala-fakhruddin-attar-farida-attar-michigan-dawoodi-bohra-a7698106.html" target="_blank"&gt;Two more charged in first US female genital mutilation case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more people have been charged in connection with the female genital mutilation (FGM) of two seven-year-olds in the first ever federal case in the US. The defendants are part of a religious and cultural community called Dawoodi Bohra, an Islamic sect based in India, which is alleged to practise FGM. The procedure has been condemned by the United Nations and is banned in the US. Detroit Physician Jumana Nagarwala, 44, has been accused of cutting two Minnesota girls, leaving them with scars and lacerations. Read more - Officials hint that Trump's wall could lead to government shutdown - No...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>A debate over circumcision - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/ask-dr-g/2016/12/25/a-debate-over-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPTNW1OhC_-rgIun55HOPs8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 03:51:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/ask-dr-g/2016/12/25/a-debate-over-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;A debate over circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christmas is a season to rejoice. While celebrating the festivity with friends and family, I often reflect on the events in the last twelve months, focusing on all the ups and downs. When it comes to all the articles that had been published this year, I also look back on the emails that I responded to, and reflecting on sexual health issues that concern many of the readers. This week, I would like to discuss the point of contention a reader raised. When reading the email from David, I realised he "cut to the chase" and did not hold back on issues related to the preservation of the foreskin....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Ministry begins probe on botched circumcision - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/28/health-ministry-investigations-boy-penis-cut-off/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFEWDYyTdRqgggLLhCjbhA4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 09:54:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/28/health-ministry-investigations-boy-penis-cut-off/" target="_blank"&gt;Ministry begins probe on botched circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Health Ministry has begun its investigations into the botched circumcision incident involving a 10-year-old boy at a clinic in Taman Cheras Utama. Ministry director-general Datuk Dr Noor Hisham Abdullah said a police report has been made on the matter. “A report has been made and we will let the investigation progress. The ministry is also conducting its own investigations,” he said when contacted on Wednesday. It was reported that a routine circumcision for the boy went horribly wrong when his penis was severed during a laser-based procedure at a clinic in Taman Cheras Ut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Girls in Kenya are hiding in school over Christmas for fear of FGM at home - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/kenya-girls-fgm-hiding-school-fear-christmas-home-female-genital-mutilation-a7489801.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ_LRu-nKHdFOpgNuXnQRPwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 22:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/kenya-girls-fgm-hiding-school-fear-christmas-home-female-genital-mutilation-a7489801.html" target="_blank"&gt;Girls in Kenya are hiding in school over Christmas for fear of FGM at home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some Kenyan schools will stay open throughout the Christmas holidays to accommodate hundreds of girls who are scared their family will force them to undergo female genital mutilation (FGM) if they go home. Schools that would have closed more than a month ago for the Christmas break are staying open for the girls, with head teachers being told to make the buildings available and ensure they attend classes. The danger of female circumcision becomes more acute around Christmas, which is a time for initiation rituals in many communities, the BBC reported. Read more - FGM 'parties' taking place ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Campaigners call for 'barbaric' male circumcision to be treated the same as female genital mutilation - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/male-circumcision-female-genital-mutilation-fgm-treated-the-same-campaigners-a7765126.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOh5qhpyKybIJuVZZAC5qroqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 14:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/male-circumcision-female-genital-mutilation-fgm-treated-the-same-campaigners-a7765126.html" target="_blank"&gt;Campaigners call for 'barbaric' male circumcision to be treated the same as female genital mutilation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Campaigners are calling for “barbaric” male circumcision to be treated like the illegal practice of female genital mutilation (FGM). Based in the US state of Michigan, anti-circumcision NoCirc group held a protest outside the Henry Ford Hospital in Detroit over the weekend, calling for an end to removing the foreskin of baby boys. The hospital has recently made headlines because it used to employ Dr Jumana Nagarwala, who has been accused of performing FGM on young girls. - Read more Herpes cases in babies linked to ultra-Orthodox circumcision ritual NoCirc mocked a statement put out by the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Man urged to have more surgery in middle of circumcision - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2016/12/26/man-urged-to-have-more-surgery-in-middle-of-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEXeOUYSyH81Y07sv-YSdq4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 06:28:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2016/12/26/man-urged-to-have-more-surgery-in-middle-of-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Man urged to have more surgery in middle of circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEIJING: A young man from western China was urged to have more surgery while he was in the middle of a circumcision and his treatment ended up costing him eight times more than he had originally agreed, according to a newspaper report. The man, whose full name was not given, was undergoing the procedure at a hospital in Chengdu earlier this month when the doctor said he needed more surgery, the Chengdu Commercial Daily said. “I was laying on the bed. I was not willing to have the additional surgery, but the doctor insisted ,” said the patient, who is 20. The man said he did not have the med...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Tribal circumcision ritual becomes Africa's latest tourist attraction - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-12-31/tribal-circumcision-becomes-africas-latest-tourist-attraction/8154314</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMohcRleNVQIdQcH6a78XwAqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 18:51:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-12-31/tribal-circumcision-becomes-africas-latest-tourist-attraction/8154314" target="_blank"&gt;Tribal circumcision ritual becomes Africa's latest tourist attraction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a small dusty village fringed by brooding blue mountains, Sullaih Kyalo is bracing himself as he is about to become a man of the Bamasaaba tribe. The 19-year-old stands opposite the traditional surgeon, who clutches a 12-centimetre blade. Sullaih doesn't look at the blade, but into the distance with a trance-like resolve. Relatives, friends and neighbours surge round, anticipating the centuries-old circumcision ritual. Sullaih's foreskin will be sliced off without anaesthetic, with the cheering crowd goading him on. He must endure the pain without tearing, wincing, flinching or falling. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>A Catholic reads the Bible, Week 50: Walking in St. Paul's sandals - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/10/living/catholic-bible-50/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED2fGykbGDu7PYim7Xg49bcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 18:54:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/10/living/catholic-bible-50/" target="_blank"&gt;A Catholic reads the Bible, Week 50: Walking in St. Paul's sandals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is week 50 of a yearlong series. Laura Bernardini is director of coverage in CNN's Washington Bureau. The views expressed in this column belong to Bernardini. Spreading the word has got to be hard. St. Paul had it rough. As someone who has logged a lot of miles covering the world as a journalist, I empathize with the apostle. I can almost feel the sores on his sandal-covered feet. My imagination ran wild about what Paul's life was like. When plotted on a map, Paul visited more places than most people get to today. Reading through his letters to the Ephesians, Colossians and Thessalonia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Woman waits for man accused of hurting her after his release on bail - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/true-or-not/2017/01/06/woman-greets-man-accused-of-hurting-after-his-release/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELGN2f3X4ORe4-kmFY-VjDIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 04:11:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/true-or-not/2017/01/06/woman-greets-man-accused-of-hurting-after-his-release/" target="_blank"&gt;Woman waits for man accused of hurting her after his release on bail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A jobless man charged with hurting his girlfriend was greeted by her after he was released on bail. The accused, Alan Lim, 30, was released on Thursday after his father posted bail granted by the George Town magistrate's court. His girlfriend, Tan Hui Yih, 20, was seen waiting for Lim with his father outside the court. On Dec 30, Lim, who is unemployed, was charged with voluntarily hurting Tan at 10pm on Dec 23 in a house in Jalan Rawang. He had claimed trial to the offence which carries a maximum jail sentence of 10 years, whipping or a fine, or any two of the punishments. &gt; Catheter inser...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>These Gay Men Got Naked To Help Demystify The Uncircumcised Penis - The Huffington Post</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/demystify-the-uncircumsized-penis_us_588f67a1e4b0176377958d37</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHiF-XTVf5Zo_0qM5jIxjocqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJ2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 16:48:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/demystify-the-uncircumsized-penis_us_588f67a1e4b0176377958d37" target="_blank"&gt;These Gay Men Got Naked To Help Demystify The Uncircumcised Penis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Huffington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest video from popular lesbian vlogger Arielle Scarcella tackles a topic that should hit close to home for anyone with a penis: circumcision. After setting up her trusty video camera, Scarcella asked a gay couple ― one partner circumcised, the other uncircumcised ― to get naked and then talk about their experiences and thoughts surrounding the procedure, during which the foreskin is removed from the shaft of the penis. Scarcella told The Huffington Post that she finds the cultural stigma surrounding uncircumcised penises in America parallel to what she thinks people with vaginas some...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">The Huffington Post</source></item><item><title>Boy loses penis during botched laser circumcision - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/27/boy-loses-penis-during-botched-laser-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENVFmsJeQeWpCKCBXLSnWIoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 00:46:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/27/boy-loses-penis-during-botched-laser-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Boy loses penis during botched laser circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KAJANG: A routine circumcision for a 10-year-old boy went horribly wrong when his penis was severed during a laser-based procedure at a clinic in Taman Cheras Utama here. It is learnt that the incident occurred at about 8.15pm on Dec 20 at the clinic during the surgery, which was performed using a laser scalpel. Soon after the procedure, the doctor told the father of the boy that he had accidentally cut off the head of his son's penis. The boy was rushed to the Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia Hospital (HUKM), which then referred him to the Kuala Lumpur Hospital (HKL) for surgery to reattach ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘Good Example of Profanity Use: Stepping on a Lego Brick’ - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/07/29/insider/good-example-of-profanity-use-stepping-on-a-lego-brick.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ5loygfir-I874XVLreYk0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwt4QY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 09:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/07/29/insider/good-example-of-profanity-use-stepping-on-a-lego-brick.html" target="_blank"&gt;‘Good Example of Profanity Use: Stepping on a Lego Brick’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Top 10 Comments of the Week: Readers debate the power of a good curse, transgender people in the military and the fate of the “skinny repeal.”&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Detroit doctor faces life in prison for 'carrying out female genital mutilation on young girls' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/detroit-doctor-jumana-nagarwala-life-prison-carrying-out-female-genital-mutilation-young-girls-a7683476.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdfvLeMSGpTA7C0doSk1IoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 10:07:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/detroit-doctor-jumana-nagarwala-life-prison-carrying-out-female-genital-mutilation-young-girls-a7683476.html" target="_blank"&gt;Detroit doctor faces life in prison for 'carrying out female genital mutilation on young girls'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Detroit doctor is facing life in prison after being charged with performing female genital mutilation (FGM) on two young girls. Dr Jumana Nagarwala, 44, is alleged to have performed the “horrifying” practice on young children for 12 years. The federal case is the first of its kind in the US, where FGM was banned in 1996. Anti-FGM campaigner interview - London Live An investigation began after the authorities were informed of Dr Nagarwala’s alleged activities. Dr Nagarwala has denied the charges but was remanded in custody after a court appearance. If found guilty, she could be given a max...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Woman shares photo of baby daughter's 'pierced' cheek to make point about circumcision - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/woman-baby-daughter-pierced-cheek-dimple-cheek-mother-circumcision-male-fgm-childrens-rights-a7824136.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKyJoEsDQRNw9Lph0mksqqoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 07:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/woman-baby-daughter-pierced-cheek-dimple-cheek-mother-circumcision-male-fgm-childrens-rights-a7824136.html" target="_blank"&gt;Woman shares photo of baby daughter's 'pierced' cheek to make point about circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mother has outraged parents by posting a photo of her baby daughter with a dimple 'piercing' – but all was not as it seemed. In a Facebook post, Enedina Vance, from Ohio, wrote: "So I got the baby girl's dimple pierced. It looks so cute, right? I just know she's gonna love it. She'll thank me when she's older lol. "If she decides she doesn't like it, she can just take it out, no big deal. I'm the parent, she is my child, I will do whatever I want. I made her, I own her." The image was shared 12,000 times and received more than 100 comments – and many of those who thought it was real were ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Boy forced to use urine bag after botched circumcision - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/07/boy-forced-to-use-urine-bag-after-botched-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKzLRmz7fRMVt6HDhZH5jGUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 03:47:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/07/boy-forced-to-use-urine-bag-after-botched-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Boy forced to use urine bag after botched circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEGAMAT: Another case of botched circumcision was reported on Jan 5 after a 10-year-old boy had part of his penis severed following a mass circumcision ceremony at a surau in Sg Buloh. The boy was rushed to Hospital Selayang after the bleeding in his penis failed to stop following the Nov 25 procedure which was performed by an assistant medical officer. After doctors failed to reattach the blackened penis head, he was sent to a private hospital to undergo three more surgeries. As a result, the boy now has to urinate using a catheter and carries around a urine bag on his body. On Dec 15, a n...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Help boys lead a normal life - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2017/01/10/help-boys-lead-a-normal-life/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIRkpi6Ao-KewpVhiT921GUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2017/01/10/help-boys-lead-a-normal-life/" target="_blank"&gt;Help boys lead a normal life&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LAST month, we were shocked by the reports of the botched circumcision cases involving two boys aged nine and 10. As I went about my daily chores, including driving my children to and from school, I couldn’t help thinking about the boys’ condition and praying for them too. My heart broke upon reading that the nine-year-old boy had asked his mother why he was still in hospital. His innocent question must have put a heavy burden on his parents’ shoulders and even I, an outsider who doesn’t know the boys, felt so sad and wanted to help in any way I could. What I would like to say is that as mu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>FGM clinic hailed as 'life-changing' to close after losing funding - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/fgm-clinic-closed-west-london-funding-cuts-loss-a7542356.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFk--VJSUQaUf11X1B_gWgYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 16:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/fgm-clinic-closed-west-london-funding-cuts-loss-a7542356.html" target="_blank"&gt;FGM clinic hailed as 'life-changing' to close after losing funding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A “life changing” clinic which helps women and girls subjected to female genital mutilation (FGM) could be forced to close in March after losing its council funding. The Acton FGM Community Clinic in West London – where FGM figures are the highest in the country - is the only facility in the country to offer reversal of the practice. Ealing Council and Imperial NHS Trust have funded the service for the past decade, but the council is withdrawing money for rent of the space and other costs - and health commissioners have refused to plug the gap. The procedure, also known as female circumcisi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Health Ministry: SOP for clinics providing circumcision service - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/09/health-ministry-sop-for-clinics-providing-circumcision-service/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELIEKCxlPJtx6iADhcydvKYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 10:42:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/09/health-ministry-sop-for-clinics-providing-circumcision-service/" target="_blank"&gt;Health Ministry: SOP for clinics providing circumcision service&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BALIK PULAU: The Health Ministry will establish a standard operating procedure (SOP) for government and private clinics providing circumcision service to prevent untoward incidents. Deputy Health Minister Datuk Seri Dr Hilmi Yahaya (pic) said the ministry would also supervise the equipment used at the clinics to ensure there were no side effects. "Some private clinics use electric tools to cut the skin. A slip can cut the penis itself. The penis is blackened and scorched when the victim is taken to hospital. Definitely, cannot do anything then. "Takes time to reconstruct, to redo...needs tw...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Subra: Doctors in botched circumcisions referred to MMC - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/06/subra-doctors-in-botched-circumcisions-referred-to-mmc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIg1ZkoXjWfixyC1vA6hChAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 06:17:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/01/06/subra-doctors-in-botched-circumcisions-referred-to-mmc/" target="_blank"&gt;Subra: Doctors in botched circumcisions referred to MMC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SELAYANG: The two doctors involved in two cases of botched circumcisions have been referred to the Malaysian Medical Council (MMC) for investigation, says Health Minister Datuk Seri Dr S. Subramaniam. He said that the decision was made during the Ministry's post-Cabinet meeting on Wednesday. "I have ordered for the two doctors that carried out the surgeries to be referred to the MMC for investigation," he said during the launch of the angiography and angio-CT hybrid unit at Hospital Selayang Friday. Dr Subramaniam said that if the doctors were found to be professionally negligent, action co...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Woman charged with child abuse for circumcising her 4-year-old son - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/circumcision-child-abuse-charge-israel-jewish-eritrean-tradition-legal-case-asylum-seeker-a7662636.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELMPmOr2qDmNXUDsG0GshT8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 09:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/circumcision-child-abuse-charge-israel-jewish-eritrean-tradition-legal-case-asylum-seeker-a7662636.html" target="_blank"&gt;Woman charged with child abuse for circumcising her 4-year-old son&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Eritrean asylum seeker in Israel is facing a charge of child abuse and 14 years behind bars after she performed a circumcision on her four-year-old son. The unnamed woman, who works as a hotel cleaner and has been in Israel for over a decade, carried out the circumcision at her home in March 2016 and did not use the traditional instruments used in Jewish rituals. The woman, known only as “A”, told the court: "This is my son, my baby. After so many requests I made to all sorts of places about how to do it, I took it upon myself and cut. In Ethiopian culture, Eritrean culture, anyone who k...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Female genital mutilation - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/ask-dr-g/2017/03/12/female-genital-mutilation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8kqv3upzTcWPzPAhq3IDgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 01:58:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/ask-dr-g/2017/03/12/female-genital-mutilation/" target="_blank"&gt;Female genital mutilation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dear Dr G, I am really sorry to put you on the spot, but I am quite interested to find out about the practice of female circumcision and what harm is it to women. In conjunction with the International Women’s Day recently, I have come across an article condemning the practice of female circumcision. I am just curious to find what exactly is female circumcision and how is it different from male circumcision? How common is such a practice? What exactly is done for this procedure and is it just a simple ritual? I look forward to hearing from you. Regards Les Female circumcision is a pra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Herpes cases among babies linked to ultra-Orthodox Jewish circumcision ritual - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/herpes-babies-jewish-circumcision-ritual-link-rabbis-infants-a7620446.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXT21LBlFSZWTrmxLaDGuQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 11:23:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/herpes-babies-jewish-circumcision-ritual-link-rabbis-infants-a7620446.html" target="_blank"&gt;Herpes cases among babies linked to ultra-Orthodox Jewish circumcision ritual&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A baby boy was rushed to hospital when he developed herpes following a controversial ancient circumcision ritual, it has been reported. The New York health department alerted doctors to the case of a newborn who fell ill after undergoing the ultra-Orthodox Jewish practice in which the circumcision wound is cleaned by mouth. A rash is said to have spread across the child’s genitals, buttocks, inner thighs and ankle two weeks after the procedure. Read more - Doctors in Denmark want to stop circumcision for under-18s - Circumcision does not reduce penis sensitivity, research finds - Muslim man...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>New York Times refuses to use term 'female genital mutilation' for being 'culturally loaded' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/new-york-times-female-genital-mutilation-culturally-loaded-response-a7702221.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELjs6QlRIGadDMjmzVo6o_QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 22:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/new-york-times-female-genital-mutilation-culturally-loaded-response-a7702221.html" target="_blank"&gt;New York Times refuses to use term 'female genital mutilation' for being 'culturally loaded'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several conservative news outlets have criticised the New York Times for their use of the term “genital cutting” rather than “female genital mutilation” (FGM), after the newspaper said it would stop .using the latter term because it is "culturally loaded". FGM is defined by UNICEF as “all procedures involving partial or total removal of the female external genitalia or other injury to the female genital organs for non-medical reasons.” Fox News, The Blaze, Daily Caller, and several other right-wing news sites have jumped on the story of New York Times Health and Science editor Celia Dugger ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Another case of a penis lost in circumcision - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/30/another-case-of-a-penis-lost-in-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPsj5KQhCszzwUcoptAkpCsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/30/another-case-of-a-penis-lost-in-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Another case of a penis lost in circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Days after a 10-year-old boy had part of his penis severed during a botched circumcision, the story of another nine-year-old who lost his penis in a failed circumcision has surfaced. While the boy in the first case had the severed part reattached, the other case ended with a failed reattachment. According to Hindraf lawyer P. Uthaya­kumar, the nine-year-old boy had the front of his penis completely severed during a circum­cision procedure using scissors at a Jalan Ipoh clinic on Dec 15. Uthayakumar said the boy was then sent to Hospital Kuala Lumpur (HKL) to try and have his p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Circumcised men who want their foreskins back - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/ask-dr-g/2017/03/05/circumcised-men-who-want-their-foreskins-back/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJrx3tW9QCHVSamNhyVo0YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 02:17:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/ask-dr-g/2017/03/05/circumcised-men-who-want-their-foreskins-back/" target="_blank"&gt;Circumcised men who want their foreskins back&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dear Dr. G, My name is James and I am 26 years old. I have a very embarrassing issue that has been troubling me for years. My father "forced" my brother and I to have circumcision when we were teenagers because of hygiene reasons. I was scared and not keen for the operation, but I guess it was a bit of a family tradition as my father was also circumcised. The problem is, after the operation, I realised the skin is so tight that I get pain when I have an erection. Besides, I also experienced loss of sensation. I have made several attempts at intercourse and have been finding it difficult! Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Boys have no problem urinating, says Dr Noor Hisham - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/31/boys-have-no-problem-urinating-says-dr-noor-hisham/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDFygc7O17_UuQgrzBB_SA4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/31/boys-have-no-problem-urinating-says-dr-noor-hisham/" target="_blank"&gt;Boys have no problem urinating, says Dr Noor Hisham&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The two boys who suffered from botched circumcision procedures can urinate normally. But it is too early to predict other physiological disabilities they may face in adulthood, said Health director-general Datuk Dr Noor Hisham Abdullah. He said the boys were referred to the Hospital Kuala Lumpur (HKL) after the earlier procedure at two private clinics. “The timing of presentation to our health facility for treatment is vital, as late presentation is asso­ciated with lesser favourable outcomes,” he said in a statement. The first case involved a nine-year old boy on Dec 15. “Ap...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>When Jewish Parents Decide Not to Circumcise - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/07/25/well/family/cutting-out-the-bris.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOKHqLJWsulZe819nuK-iHoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwqIQY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 10:00:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/07/25/well/family/cutting-out-the-bris.html" target="_blank"&gt;When Jewish Parents Decide Not to Circumcise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;If parents skip the bris, can a son still be Jewish?&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>To cut or not to cut? - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/ask-dr-g/2016/11/20/to-cut-or-not-to-cut/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOCO2OtOa4kE3DNO7WVX1ekqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 01:53:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/ask-dr-g/2016/11/20/to-cut-or-not-to-cut/" target="_blank"&gt;To cut or not to cut?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children’s Day is recognised in many nations around the world to honor children globally. Although many countries mark the day on different occasions, the Universal Children’s Day on Nov 20 is celebrated by the United Nations to highlight important issues affecting children. The Universal Children’s Day dedicates in promoting the well-being and rights of the world’s children, especially those suffering the impact of poverty, discrimination and exploitation. On the Universal Children’s Day today, I intend to explore the rights of infants who “cannot really fight back” and issues surrounding ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Lesotho taxi drivers help lead fight against HIV - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/05/lesotho-taxi-drivers-lead-fight-hiv-170529104750993.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBooHOgIpUbeg_WaJ_eD-AqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 08:38:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2017/05/lesotho-taxi-drivers-lead-fight-hiv-170529104750993.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lesotho taxi drivers help lead fight against HIV&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maseru, Lesotho - Tsitso Mokale drives down Moshoeshoe Road in his black taxi with a yellow stripe, scanning the pavement for potential passengers. The taxi driver in Lesotho's capital, Maseru, is on a mission not just to find new customers, but to start a conversation about the benefits of male circumcision and HIV prevention. It is a daunting task in a country with the second-highest HIV prevalence rate in the world and where social norms and cultural restraints often prevent men from accessing health services. "It's sometimes difficult to talk to the older [male passengers]," Tsitso says...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>'Pierced' baby picture sparks outrage among parents - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/07/06/health/photoshopped-baby-picture-with-piercing-trnd/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEERxh7XGzRpZjPOAfPpoC4cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMLrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:01:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/07/06/health/photoshopped-baby-picture-with-piercing-trnd/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Pierced' baby picture sparks outrage among parents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enedina Vance was fed up. She felt like other parents didn't understand her message. She felt like they weren't listening to her. So she got on her phone, found a picture of her 6-month-old daughter and pasted a diamond stud over the infant's dimple to make it look like she had a piercing. Vance, a strong advocate against piercing or circumcising children, posted the edited picture to Facebook, where it had more than 13,000 shares as of Thursday afternoon. "I make all of her decisions until she's 18, I made her, I own her!!" she wrote. What Vance didn't expect was the reaction she'd get fro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The practice of autocircumcision - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/putting-dr-g-on-the-spot/2017/05/07/the-practice-of-autocircumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEONhLHi37DJiM-LtZjhN8Y8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 01:48:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/putting-dr-g-on-the-spot/2017/05/07/the-practice-of-autocircumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;The practice of autocircumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dear Dr G, I'm in my early 20s, and I have a question that needs a solution. I'm uncircumcised and I'm aware of the hygiene and long-term benefits of circumcision. I recently came across some information regarding a practice called "autocircumcision". Can you elaborate what this is? From what I understand, this is a situation when the male who is uncut can try to manually retract his foreskin behind the glans to reduce the sensitivity of the head of penis, without requiring any circumcision. Is it a safe practice to retract the foreskin for 24 hours? Will this result in any unwanted c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Swiss court acquits doctor who cut off 4yo’s penis in botched circumcision - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/385325-doctor-circumcision-switzerland-ruling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO1eg02uxhCYJWicfNnQlk8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 16:50:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/385325-doctor-circumcision-switzerland-ruling/" target="_blank"&gt;Swiss court acquits doctor who cut off 4yo’s penis in botched circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Swiss doctor who cut off a young boy's penis during a circumcision operation has been acquitted of causing bodily harm through negligence. In the Tuesday ruling, a court in Geneva said the factors involved in the incident had made the accident "unforeseeable," Le Temps newspaper reported. That remark is in reference to the fact that the four-year-old boy's father was taking photos during the July 2014 operation. At one point, the boy turned to look at his father as he prepared to take a picture. In doing so, the boy moved his pelvis, causing the surgeon to sever the penis, which fell to t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Boy loses more in botched circumcision - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/27/boy-loses-more-in-botched-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-8PNNyvkQS03hyCFbmIQIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/27/boy-loses-more-in-botched-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Boy loses more in botched circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KAJANG: A circumcision surgery for a 10-year-old boy went horribly wrong when a doctor allegedly sliced off the tip of his penis by accident at a clinic in Taman Cheras Utama here. It is learnt the clinic was not re­­gistered with the health authorities. The incident was said to have occurred at about 8.15pm on Dec 20 for the surgery that was carried out using a laser. His father then rushed him to the Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia Medical Centre. The boy was later referred to Kuala Lumpur Hospital to undergo a surgery to reattach the head of the penis. Kajang OCPD Asst Comm Othman Nanyan ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Doctor faces trial for cutting off 4yo boy's penis during circumcision - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/382693-swiss-doctor-circumcision-trial/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMJZP72HGjNdY4WeOIrn5ngqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 13:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/382693-swiss-doctor-circumcision-trial/" target="_blank"&gt;Doctor faces trial for cutting off 4yo boy's penis during circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A doctor is facing trial in Switzerland after severing a four-year-old's penis during a circumcision operation and ‘wasting time’ before sending him to hospital. The medico is accused of inflicting serious bodily harm through negligence. The tragic incident occurred on July 2014, when the boy's parents took him to the doctor's office in Geneva. The parents had confidence in the physician, who had at the time performed 700 circumcisions, according to Le Matin newspaper. Once the procedure was underway, the boy's father, an Algerian refugee, began taking photos of the event, which many famili...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Doc claims ignorance - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/31/doc-claims-ignorance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO0vzPuN-lUt7-ZL7pPUgukqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2016/12/31/doc-claims-ignorance/" target="_blank"&gt;Doc claims ignorance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: An old, unassu­ming cli­nic, facing busy Jalan Ipoh, sits sandwiched between motorcycle workshops and empty coffee shops. Outside, a worn-out black plastic sign with letters missing shows a list of treatments and services such as blood test and medical treatments. While it doesn’t state so, this cli­nic also does circumcisions. More specifically, this is where a nine-year-old boy had his penis severed during a bungled circumcision. So far, it appears to be business as usual for this clinic. The Star went to see the doctor at the clinic for an eye ailment. On the pretext of mak...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Mother opened nappy to find three-month-old son had been circumcised - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/06/29/mother-opened-nappy-find-three-month-old-son-had-circumcised/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEObdRODnSCoKthSW1luWDXYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 07:10:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/06/29/mother-opened-nappy-find-three-month-old-son-had-circumcised/" target="_blank"&gt;Mother opened nappy to find three-month-old son had been circumcised&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mother has told how she opened her three-month-old baby's nappy to find he had been circumcised without her consent. The woman, from Nottingham, said she was so distraught she had to leave the room. Three suspects, including a family GP, have now been arrested over the incident. "I opened the nappy and I ended up having to leave the room because I felt hysterical," the mother, who did not want to be identified, told the BBC. A family GP has been arrested over the incident (stock picture)Credit: Andrew Matthews/PA Wire "It was just awful really, it wasn't very nice, there was all blood the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>One female genital mutilation case reported every hour in the UK - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/female-genital-mutilation-fgm-case-per-hour-uk-nhs-circumcision-a7564571.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJQWuhzSHHELDlbHDgSIEcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 08:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/health-news/female-genital-mutilation-fgm-case-per-hour-uk-nhs-circumcision-a7564571.html" target="_blank"&gt;One female genital mutilation case reported every hour in the UK&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A case of female genital mutilation (FGM) is either discovered or treated at a medical appointment in England every hour, according to analysis of NHS statistics by a charity. Between April 2015 and March 2016 there were 8,656 times when women or girls attended doctors' surgeries or hospitals and the problem was assessed — the equivalent of one every 61 minutes. Among those who attended, a case of FGM is newly recorded every 92 minutes on average. This means a woman or girl has their case recorded by the NHS for the first time, although in many cases they will have been cut some years befor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ban on young boys’ circumcision proposed in Norway - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/387732-norway-ban-boys-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEILGtHEwvUO6n2-PkpbhWXQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 13:50:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/387732-norway-ban-boys-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Ban on young boys’ circumcision proposed in Norway&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Norway’s Progress Party (FrP), the country’s third largest party and known for its anti-immigration policies, has supported a bill outlawing ritual circumcision of boys aged under 16, a common practice among Jewish and Muslim communities. The draft law was passed at the party’s weekend national convention after the rejection of a compromise proposal to prevent state funding of the procedure rather than ban it altogether. Its proponents claim the religious rite causes mental and physical harm to children and constitutes a serious violation of children’s rights. Progress Party leader Siv Jens...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Doctors in Denmark want to ban circumcision for under-18s - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/denmark-considering-banning-circumcision-for-children-under-18s-a7459291.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDBPbVIjbNHxPKxnA88MxFgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 08:18:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/denmark-considering-banning-circumcision-for-children-under-18s-a7459291.html" target="_blank"&gt;Doctors in Denmark want to ban circumcision for under-18s&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boys should not be circumcised until they are old enough to choose for themselves, doctors in Denmark have said. The Danish Medical Association said it had considered suggesting a legal ban on the procedure for children under the age of 18, because it believed circumcision should be “an informed, personal choice” that young men make for themselves. When parents have their sons circumcised, it robs boys of the ability to make decisions about their own bodies, and choose their cultural and religious beliefs for themselves, the organisation said. Read more - Denmark deports woman for begging f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Ban the Ritual That Can Kill Jewish Newborns - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2017/04/22/ban-the-ritual-that-can-kill-jewish-newborns.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMWfn3azWhQbGap48KDS-T8qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 04:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2017/04/22/ban-the-ritual-that-can-kill-jewish-newborns.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ban the Ritual That Can Kill Jewish Newborns&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On March 29, 2017, the mayor of New York, Bill de Blasio, admitted defeat. “We tried a new policy,” he said. “It didn’t work, which I’m very unhappy about.” During the previous two years, six newborns in New York City had suffered severe infections with herpes simplex virus (HSV)—a situation de Blasio had been hoping to avoid. Adults infected with HSV typically develop ulcers in their mouth or blisters in their anal and genital areas. For newborns, however, it’s a different story. In babies, HSV can enter the bloodstream and infect the liver (causing hepatitis) or the lungs (causing pneumon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Female genital mutilation: Young Kenyan girls take part in tribal ceremony - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/life/female-genital-mutilation-young-kenyan-girls-take-part-tribal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEtELCyqLn6UImWQuGFpf2MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDqy7cF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/women/life/female-genital-mutilation-young-kenyan-girls-take-part-tribal/" target="_blank"&gt;Female genital mutilation: Young Kenyan girls take part in tribal ceremony&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;06 Feb 2017 Female genital mutilation: Young Kenyan girls take part in tribal ceremony Previous slideNext slide1 of 15View AllSkip Ad WARNING: Graphic images February 6 is the annual International Day of Zero Tolerance for female genital mutilation, or FGM. Despite being banned in 2011, the tradition of circumcising girls is still practiced in many rural parts of Kenya. Reuters photographer Siegfried Modola captured these pictures of four girls taking part in a ceremony in the village of Pokot, 80 kilometres from the town of Marigat in Baringo County, in 2014. REUTERS/Siegfried Modola Back...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Law in a Female Genital Cutting Case - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/06/12/opinion/the-law-in-a-female-genital-cutting-case.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBuPlmnUecWMDXxa6ORJteoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwpoIY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 18:42:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/06/12/opinion/the-law-in-a-female-genital-cutting-case.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Law in a Female Genital Cutting Case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lawyer Alan Dershowitz writes about his efforts at a compromise.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Botched circumcisions - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/putting-dr-g-on-the-spot/2017/01/01/botched-circumcisions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECghHLVN86rwZBx87zXEXE4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 03:02:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/online-exclusive/putting-dr-g-on-the-spot/2017/01/01/botched-circumcisions/" target="_blank"&gt;Botched circumcisions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TIME flies. I find it difficult to believe it has been nearly four years since I met up with Philip Golingai in a café in Hartamas and planned to set up a column in The Star Online. Our goal was to deal with sexual issues faced by readers which were permissible to be discussed within the context of Malaysian sensitivities. I will never forget the day I was introduced to Twitterjaya at The Star headquarters. I must admit, I was terrified of the “live bombardment” of questions from readers. I was not sure whether I was frightened of the handling Twitter for the first time, or providing instan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>'My daughter started crying': Culture and religion sees millions of girls undergo circumcision - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-13/female-circumcision-is-still-happening-in-malaysia/10473640</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELyX6a7E63MrNEwN3w_yPgkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 19:12:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-13/female-circumcision-is-still-happening-in-malaysia/10473640" target="_blank"&gt;'My daughter started crying': Culture and religion sees millions of girls undergo circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fa Abdul was nine years old when she found out she had been circumcised when she was just a baby. Key Points - A 2012 study found 93 per cent of Muslim women in Malaysia have been circumcised - Female circumcision is not prescribed in the Koran or Hadiths, women's advocates say - One mother says Malaysia's culture and society "expected us to do it" She was among the millions of girls across Malaysia whose families believe that female circumcision protects young girls from committing "sins". "Many Muslims in Malaysia will tell you that circumcision will protect girls from growing up and beco...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Female circumcision: Culture and religion in Malaysia see millions of girls undergo cut - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/13/female-circumcision-culture-and-religion-in-malaysia-see-millions-of-girls-undergo-cut/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDuf7L1iF3TVvSeqFt3edaIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 04:56:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/13/female-circumcision-culture-and-religion-in-malaysia-see-millions-of-girls-undergo-cut/" target="_blank"&gt;Female circumcision: Culture and religion in Malaysia see millions of girls undergo cut&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Society often does a lot of things that copies behaviours from African and Arab countries and defend it as having a religious origin. “We are confusing it with Islam and we think whatever they do is Islamic” (ABC) – Fa Abdul was nine years old when she found out she had been circumcised when she was just a baby. Key Points - A 2012 study found 93 per cent of Muslim women in Malaysia have been circumcised - Female circumcision is not prescribed in the Koran or Hadiths, women’s advocates say - One mother says Malaysia’s culture and society “expected us to do it” She was among the millions of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Suhakam calls out DPM’s ministry for ‘misleading’ response to UN on female circumcision - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/14/suhakam-calls-out-dpms-ministry-for-misleading-response-to-un-on-female-circumcision/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN0Ygmkm_Hk3npJzBxzCU3MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 03:51:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/14/suhakam-calls-out-dpms-ministry-for-misleading-response-to-un-on-female-circumcision/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam calls out DPM’s ministry for ‘misleading’ response to UN on female circumcision&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Human Rights Commission (Suhakam) today accused Putrajaya of misleading the United Nations Periodic Review about the practice of female circumcision in the country — considered female genital mutilation (FGM) worldwide. (MMO) – The commission said the representative Ministry of Women, Family and Community gave an “unconvincing and misleading” explanation when they defended the practice before the International Community in Geneva, Switzerland, five days ago. Suhakam added that the move could potentially damage the country’s global standing on women’s rights issue. “Suhakam was ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item></channel></rss>