<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Universal Declaration of Human Rights - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRGQyT1c0U0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:08:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>At 70, universal human rights declaration facing uncertain future - New Straits Times Online</title><link>https://www.nst.com.my/world/2018/12/438141/70-universal-human-rights-declaration-facing-uncertain-future</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5zdC5jb20ubXkvd29ybGQvMjAxOC8xMi80MzgxNDEvNzAtdW5pdmVyc2FsLWh1bWFuLXJpZ2h0cy1kZWNsYXJhdGlvbi1mYWNpbmctdW5jZXJ0YWluLWZ1dHVyZdIBbWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LW5zdC1jb20tbXkuY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3Yvcy93d3cubnN0LmNvbS5teS9ub2RlLzQzODE0MS9hbXA_YW1wX2pzX3Y9MC4xI3dlYnZpZXc9MSZjYXA9c3dpcGU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/world/2018/12/438141/70-universal-human-rights-declaration-facing-uncertain-future" target="_blank"&gt;At 70, universal human rights declaration facing uncertain future&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA: As the Universal Declaration of Human Rights turns 70, there are signs that the goals outlined in the text are facing unprecedented threats, from rising ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nst.com.my">New Straits Times Online</source></item><item><title>Human rights for the 21st century: by Margaret Atwood, Reni Eddo-Lodge, Dave Eggers and more - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2018/dec/08/universal-declaration-human-rights-turns-70</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELkzrJ_gHA95tVwZUlEEZVQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:00:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/books/2018/dec/08/universal-declaration-human-rights-turns-70" target="_blank"&gt;Human rights for the 21st century: by Margaret Atwood, Reni Eddo-Lodge, Dave Eggers and more&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The right to be a person, not a thing Margaret Atwood People, we have a problem. Or rather two problems. The first is a matter of definition: who or what is a human being, entitled to the rights spelled out in the Universal Declaration of Human Rights? The second is the old mind-body split: what if these two components have different wills? I illustrate by means of the Ohio Republicans, who have recently moved to declare motherhood mandatory, and also to define any fertilised egg – whether in a woman’s body or in a Petri dish – a person under the law. Causing a non-living condition in such ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Affirm Human Dignity For Everyone Everywhere And Stand Up For Human Rights - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewelinaochab/2018/12/07/affirm-human-dignity-for-everyone-everywhere-and-stand-up-for-human-rights/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMJgemvfqpFpOnphaTKDMw0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewelinaochab/2018/12/07/affirm-human-dignity-for-everyone-everywhere-and-stand-up-for-human-rights/" target="_blank"&gt;Affirm Human Dignity For Everyone Everywhere And Stand Up For Human Rights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations observes Human Rights Day on December 10, the day the United Nations General Assembly adopted the Universal Declaration of Human Rights (UDHR). This year’s celebration of the day is even more special as it will be the 70th anniversary of this important document. Eleanor Roosevelt, one of the drafters of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, displays a Spanish language version of the document which is the most translated document in the world. (Photo credit: Universal History Archive/UIG via Getty Images) The legacy of the UDHR can never be underestimated. It is a lan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>UN: Populist Nationalism Threatens Human Rights Declaration - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-populist-nationalism-threatens-human-rights-declaration/4687896.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN93S2olXnIivbEu_sx5BGkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 16:37:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-populist-nationalism-threatens-human-rights-declaration/4687896.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN: Populist Nationalism Threatens Human Rights Declaration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N.'s top human rights official warned that the rise of populist nationalism threatens many of the freedoms, rights and protections enshrined in the 1948 Universal Declaration of Human Rights. Born out of the devastation of two world wars, the Great Depression of the 1930s, and the Holocaust, the seminal document is geared toward preventing similar disasters from happening. December 10 marks the 70th anniversary of the declaration, which U.N. High Commissioner for Human Rights Michelle Bachelet said has withstood the test of time. She said its fundamental principles can be applied to m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Two big rallies set on same day - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/12/06/two-big-rallies-set-on-same-day/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEApy_ELz1bSlykXlsIwseBMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 03:33:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/12/06/two-big-rallies-set-on-same-day/" target="_blank"&gt;Two big rallies set on same day&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – This weekend, two major gatherings will take place in the Klang Valley, with both sides rallying to uphold human rights in their own context. As the anti-Icerd (International Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Racial Discrimination) protesters gather in downtown Kuala Lumpur at Dataran Merdeka to celebrate the non-ratification of the United Nations covenant, in Padang Timur, Petaling Jaya, Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad will be the chief guest in a celebration of universal human rights. The event in Petaling Jaya, which the organisers contend was planned thre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>PM to launch Suhakam's human rights rally on same day as anti-Icerd rally - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/pm-to-launch-suhakams-human-rights-rally-on-same-day-as-antiicerd-rally/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHfrkqVu0QKXwnriIXYD4DMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 07:45:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/05/pm-to-launch-suhakams-human-rights-rally-on-same-day-as-antiicerd-rally/" target="_blank"&gt;PM to launch Suhakam's human rights rally on same day as anti-Icerd rally&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Prime Minister Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad will be launching a pro-human rights rally on the same day as the anti-Icerd rally. The two opposing rallies are scheduled for Saturday (Dec 8), with the Human Rights Commission (Suhakam) is holding its first pro-human rights rally themed "Stand Up 4 Human Rights". The rally will be held from 9am to 3pm at Padang Timur in Petaling Jaya, while the rally against the International Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Racial Discrimination (Icerd) will be held about 10km away at Dataran Merdeka, Kuala Lumpur. Dr Mahathir is also sch...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Impact Investing and Human Rights: Can We Talk? - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/morgansimon/2018/11/30/impact-investing-and-human-rights-can-we-talk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH1jTyu53e4gsGM3boQRQBsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLKAAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/morgansimon/2018/11/30/impact-investing-and-human-rights-can-we-talk/" target="_blank"&gt;Impact Investing and Human Rights: Can We Talk?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Impact investors are good talkers. We talk about economic empowerment, sustainability, “doing well by doing good,” and in general the idea that our work can create opportunities for others. Creating opportunity, that we can talk about all day. What we don’t talk much about? Rights. These are extremely different concepts, and it’s important to be clear just what we are trying to achieve. What’s the difference between an opportunity and a right? The concept of opportunity often means that you have to work for something in order to deserve it — it’s not a “given” but rather contingent on circ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>For the ICERD to work non-Muslims must also come under Sharia laws - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/24/for-the-icerd-to-work-non-muslims-must-also-come-under-sharia-laws/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOPyMGsyyHfqFxr6ofP5PdkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 10:05:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/24/for-the-icerd-to-work-non-muslims-must-also-come-under-sharia-laws/" target="_blank"&gt;For the ICERD to work non-Muslims must also come under Sharia laws&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other Muslim countries, non-Muslims also get punished under Sharia laws and they are beheaded for certain crimes, just like the Muslims are. So, either abolish the Sharia or make non-Muslims subjected to the Sharia and Hudud as well. Then the ICERD can be ratified because only then will all Malaysians be equal before the law. NO HOLDS BARRED Raja Petra Kamarudin There are many who support or oppose the International Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Racial Discrimination or the ICERD but do not really know what the whole issue is about. It is like those non-Muslims who oppose...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Release Siti Noor Aishah Atam from Poca restrictions - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHgPW757jqyV6GJIcLnSeUcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPTirwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 04:29:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We, the 36 undersigned civil society organisations, trade unions and groups, are appalled to hear about the case of Siti Noor Aishah Atam, a 29-year-old Malaysian woman, who was arrested for the alleged possession of 12 books, detained, tried and acquitted by the court, and thereafter re-arrested and detained under the Prevention of Crime Act 1959 (Poca). We are shocked that Siti Noor Aishah, despite being acquitted and released by the court, which also denied the prosecution’s application to continue to detain her under the Security Offences (Special Measures) Act 2012 (Sosma) pending appe...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Abide by laws during protest, Rohingya refugees told - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/09/03/suhakam-refugees-right-to-protest-adhere-to-laws/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHrTKdlW7owE2xIaEbgZiG8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 11:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/09/03/suhakam-refugees-right-to-protest-adhere-to-laws/" target="_blank"&gt;Abide by laws during protest, Rohingya refugees told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Rohingya refugees in Malaysia have the right to protest but they must adhere to the laws of the country, the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) said. Its chairman Tan Sri Razali Ismail (pix) said Article 20 of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights (UDHR) states that every human being, wherever they are, has the right to freedom of peaceful assembly. "However, violent protesters lose their protection under the right to peaceful assembly, and the police shall act against those breaking the law," he said in a statement on Sunday. "The instincts of compassion and h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>What happens in December 2016? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2016/11/december-2016-161116154016918.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC7ci4LBDbecqoLNEIhVkv0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 07:48:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2016/11/december-2016-161116154016918.html" target="_blank"&gt;What happens in December 2016?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it is difficult to predict what will be the breaking news of the upcoming month, the United Nations, and various communities around the world have marked their calendars in December to remember, and in some occasions, celebrate a number of recurring events and anniversaries. Here are a few of them. World days On Wednesday, December 2 , the UN marks the Day for the Abolition of Slavery. Although slavery was officially abolished worldwide in 1981, millions of people around the world still suffer. Modern slavery today is manifested in the form of forced prostitution, human trafficking,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Three mass graves discovered in central Congo - U.N. - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/03/08/three-mass-graves-discovered-in-central-congo--un/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAtRes87Yuli3gHBwQLq_aEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 13:18:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/03/08/three-mass-graves-discovered-in-central-congo--un/" target="_blank"&gt;Three mass graves discovered in central Congo - U.N.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KINSHASA (Reuters) - Three mass graves have been discovered in central Democratic Republic of Congo, where hundreds have been killed since July in clashes between security forces and a local militia, the top U.N. rights official said on Wednesday. At least 400 people have died and 200,000 have been displaced since the fighting broke out with the Kamuina Nsapu militia. Police killed its leader, Kamuina Nsapu, last August, causing the violence to swiftly escalate. U.N. High Commissioner for Human Rights Zeid Ra'ad al-Hussein urged the U.N. human rights council in Geneva to set up an inquiry "...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Kyrgyzstan defies U.N., upholds life sentence for dissident - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-kyrgyzstan-rights-idUSKBN1581MR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAQPeOcHLI1sa8HQBlEoWJEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 12:59:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-kyrgyzstan-rights-idUSKBN1581MR" target="_blank"&gt;Kyrgyzstan defies U.N., upholds life sentence for dissident&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BISHKEK (Reuters) - A court in Kyrgyzstan upheld a life sentence on Tuesday for a prominent dissident accused of "inciting inter-ethnic hatred" in the former Soviet republic, defying U.N. calls for his release. Azimjon Askarov, a 65-year-old ethnic Uzbek, was convicted of "organizing mass disturbances" and stirring up ethnic hatred leading to the killing of a policeman during clashes in southern Kyrgyzstan in June 2010, when more than 400 people were killed. His imprisonment has been widely criticized by human rights groups and sparked a political spat with the United States in 2015. Kyrgyz...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>On Human Rights Day, UN Urges Everyone to Stand Up for Universal Rights - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/human-rights-day-stand-up-for-universal-rights/3630859.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGbNFqKrX94WC7N-UQM77rEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 08:42:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/human-rights-day-stand-up-for-universal-rights/3630859.html" target="_blank"&gt;On Human Rights Day, UN Urges Everyone to Stand Up for Universal Rights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Countries around the world mark International Human Rights Day December 10. As disrespect for basic human rights continues to be widespread in many parts of the globe, the United Nations is calling on everyone to stand up for universal rights. “The time for this is now. We the peoples can take a stand for rights. And together, we can take a stand for more humanity,” the world body said in a statement. “Upholding human rights is in the interest of all. Respect for human rights advances well-being for every individual, stability for every society, and harmony for our interconnected world,” U....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>U.S. seeks end to U.N. rights council's 'obsession' with Israel - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-un-rights-usa-idUSKBN1683V7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECXENF-ESNKzScV2GjGqDXcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 10:29:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-un-rights-usa-idUSKBN1683V7" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. seeks end to U.N. rights council's 'obsession' with Israel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Stephanie Nebehay GENEVA (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump's administration is reviewing its participation in the U.N. Human Rights Council, seeking reform of its agenda and an end to its "obsession with Israel", a senior U.S. official said on Wednesday. Washington has long argued that the Geneva forum unfairly focuses on Israel's alleged violations of human rights, including war crimes against Palestinian civilians in the occupied West Bank and Gaza Strip. The United States "remains deeply troubled by the Council’s consistent unfair and unbalanced focus on one democratic country, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>The Real Reason Behind Saudi Arabia's Election To UN Rights Panel - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2016/10/31/the-real-reason-behind-saudi-arabias-election-to-un-rights-panel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMfZSy4hB91dg7ciPJ4mJ3gqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/panosmourdoukoutas/2016/10/31/the-real-reason-behind-saudi-arabias-election-to-un-rights-panel/" target="_blank"&gt;The Real Reason Behind Saudi Arabia's Election To UN Rights Panel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil may be heading below $50, again, but the Saudi Kingdom is on the rise. In the UN, that is, which elected the kingdom to be part of its Human Rights panel last week. This honor gave investors in Saudi equities another reason to cheer, sending the major market average soaring for the week. Saudi equities have been rallying, following Riyadh’s successful international bond sale, which eased concerns about the government’s ability to close the gap opened in its fiscal and social budget by lower oil prices. ETF 5-day 1-year iShares MSCI Saudi Arabia (NYSE:KSE) 2.11% -12.58% iShares Emerg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>The One-Armed Orphan Who Brought Human Rights To The World - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/the-one-armed-orphan-who-brought-human-rights-to-the-world</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGCCqxSORdde2Rn1IsBu2S0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/the-one-armed-orphan-who-brought-human-rights-to-the-world" target="_blank"&gt;The One-Armed Orphan Who Brought Human Rights To The World&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The human wrongs many experienced during the twentieth century—individually and collectively—spawned today’s human rights movement. Even the Thomas Jefferson of human rights, John Peters Humphrey, was a one-armed orphan bullied in private school. After working in the United Nations for twenty years, he concluded that this hope of humanity had become an “organization of shame.” His greatest achievement, drafting the 1948 Universal Declaration of Human Rights, was ignored for decades as the movement’s George Washington—Rene Cassin—won the Noble Prize and its Paul Revere—Eleanor Roosevelt—beca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>U.N. experts slam Ecuador over forced closure of land rights group - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-un-ecuador-landrights-idUSKBN14J1TW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPqL_GvZR4hb372naBc4ARUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 20:35:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-un-ecuador-landrights-idUSKBN14J1TW" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. experts slam Ecuador over forced closure of land rights group&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Sebastien Malo NEW YORK (Thomson Reuters Foundation) - The United Nations criticized the government of Ecuador on Friday for ordering the closure of a land rights advocacy group that supports an indigenous community protesting mining plans in land they claim as their ancestral home. The crackdown by Ecuadorian authorities on Quito-based Accion Ecologica was part of a pattern that threatened freedom of association in the country, a group of six U.N. rights experts said in a statement. Accion Ecologica has been working for 30 years to protect land whose natural environment is threatened, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>U.N. rights office decries Israeli sentence as 'excessively lenient' - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/02/24/un-rights-office-decries-israeli-sentence-as-excessively-lenient/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEButrGbRdLKH4WDaAlFoRX0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 11:16:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/02/24/un-rights-office-decries-israeli-sentence-as-excessively-lenient/" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. rights office decries Israeli sentence as 'excessively lenient'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (Reuters) - The United Nations' human rights office said on Friday that an 18-month sentence handed down to an Israeli soldier for killing a wounded Palestinian was "excessively lenient" and "unacceptable". The soldier, who shot Abdel Fattah al-Sharif Elor in the head after he was incapacitated following a knife attack in March 2016, was sentenced to 18 months' imprisonment on Tuesday. The show of leniency drew Palestinian outrage. "We are deeply disturbed at the lenient sentence given by the Tel Aviv Military Court earlier this week to an Israeli soldier convicted of unlawfully kill...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘Double standard in respect for free speech, assembly a cause for concern’ - Malaysiakini</title><link>http://www.malaysiakini.com/letters/363365</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGX1SrUqRkTMW5lWOx_GaN4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPTirwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 10:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysiakini.com/letters/363365" target="_blank"&gt;‘Double standard in respect for free speech, assembly a cause for concern’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Centre for Human Rights Research and Advocacy (Centhra) is deeply disturbed by reports that the head of the red-shirts, Jamal Md Yunos, was allegedly punched in a scuffle with police at Ampang Point Mall in Ampang, Kuala Lumpur recently as well as the reactions of various quarters towards this incident. Centhra understands that Ampang MP and Wanita PKR chief Zuraida Kamaruddin has threatened him with legal action over the incident, and Wanita MCA in particular have released a statement condoning the police action as well-deserved. Meanwhile, commentators in news portals such as Ravinder...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysiakini.com">Malaysiakini</source></item><item><title>UN denounces Trump's travel ban as 'mean-spirited' and illegal under human rights law - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/donald-trump-muslim-travel-ban-illegal-un-rights-chief-a7552986.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFyMcu-LPUErUrlHq5Qo18AqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 12:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/donald-trump-muslim-travel-ban-illegal-un-rights-chief-a7552986.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN denounces Trump's travel ban as 'mean-spirited' and illegal under human rights law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump's ban on travel to the US from some Muslim-majority countries has been denounced by the UN's rights chief as "mean-spirited" and illegal under international human rights law. Zeid Ra'ad al Hussein said: "Discrimination on nationality alone is forbidden under human rights law. "The US ban is also mean-spirited, and wastes resources needed for proper counter-terrorism." More follows ]]&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>It will take more than tolerance to protect human rights - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/dec/10/tolerance-protect-human-rights-migration</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHD7aVtp6VMN2cD6xNP1W5gqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 06:00:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/dec/10/tolerance-protect-human-rights-migration" target="_blank"&gt;It will take more than tolerance to protect human rights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have always considered “tolerance” a highly problematic concept: it is today considered to describe a positive attribute, when in fact it refers to a rather negative one. This ambivalence was succinctly put by Goethe, who, in one of his Maxims and Reflections, stated: “Tolerance should really only be a passing attitude: it should lead to appreciation. To tolerate is to offend.” Related: Why does music give us chills? You asked Google – here’s the answer | David Shariatmadari Merely tolerating someone is ultimately an act of condescension, whereas actual appreciation results in seeing the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UN Rights Chief Wants Duterte's Murder Claims Investigated - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/un-rights-chief-wants-to-investigate-duterte/3643594.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMogRwi0HnamCZeno_zab8wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 15:13:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/un-rights-chief-wants-to-investigate-duterte/3643594.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Rights Chief Wants Duterte's Murder Claims Investigated&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The top human rights official at the United Nations on Tuesday called for an investigation of Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte after Duterte claimed he personally killed several alleged criminals. UN Human Rights Commissioner Zeid Ra’ad al-Hussein called on Philippine authorities to launch a murder investigation into claims Duterte made Friday in which he said he shot and killed “about three” men while serving as mayor of the city of Davao. It's “unthinkable for any functioning judicial system not to launch investigative and judicial proceedings when someone has openly admitted being a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>UN Official: Human Rights at Risk from “Political Profiteers” - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/human-rights-at-risk-from-political-profiteers/3741574.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIjs7GU6F8N08M2wZgxUfmQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 15:03:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/human-rights-at-risk-from-political-profiteers/3741574.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Official: Human Rights at Risk from “Political Profiteers”&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.N. Human Rights chief Zeid Ra’ad al-Hussein has warned world peace and stability based on fundamental human rights are under threat by so-called reckless political profiteers. The high commissioner told delegates attending the opening session Monday of the month-long meeting of the U.N. Human Rights Council many of the achievements that have been made in stabilizing the world order since the end of World War II are at risk of being lost by growing populism. He said durable peace in many parts of the world and success in development during the seven decades following this shattering war we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Ultimatum on Qatar is 'violation of human rights': NHRC - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/ultimatum-qatar-violation-human-rights-nhrc-170623215645625.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEInotIz2alT-0Uel4NEznywqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 22:42:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/06/ultimatum-qatar-violation-human-rights-nhrc-170623215645625.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ultimatum on Qatar is 'violation of human rights': NHRC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qatar National Human Rights Committee (NHRC) has called on Doha not to accept a list of demands submitted by four Arab countries, stating that it contains conditions that violate human rights conventions and other international and regional agreements. "By accepting those demands and conditions Qatar will be subject to international accountability and violating its commitments regarding human rights conventions," NHRC said in a statement on Friday. Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Bahrain, and the United Arab Emirates - which cut ties with Qatar - issued an ultimatum on Friday to Doha to close Al Jazee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>U.N. rights chief warns Aleppo "slaughter" could happen elsewhere - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2016/12/13/un-rights-chief-warns-aleppo-slaughter-could-happen-elsewhere/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECbxoneyE5aJK5id_khp9X4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 12:53:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2016/12/13/un-rights-chief-warns-aleppo-slaughter-could-happen-elsewhere/" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. rights chief warns Aleppo "slaughter" could happen elsewhere&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (Reuters) - U.N. human rights chief Zeid Ra'ad al Hussein called on Tuesday on the international community to demand Syria allow monitoring of its treatment of people fleeing eastern Aleppo, warning that populations of other rebel-held towns could face the same fate. “The crushing of Aleppo, the immeasurably terrifying toll on its people, the bloodshed, the wanton slaughter of men, women and children, the destruction – and we are nowhere near the end of this cruel conflict," Zeid said in a statement. "What is happening with Aleppo could repeat itself in Douma, in Raqqa, in Idlib. We ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>SIS: Where is public caning commanded in the Quran? - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/sis-where-is-public-caning-commanded-in-the-quran/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDeZAYajow3bknp1e9Obap4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 06:24:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/sis-where-is-public-caning-commanded-in-the-quran/" target="_blank"&gt;SIS: Where is public caning commanded in the Quran?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – The Kelantan government should point out the section in the Quran that allows for public caning, Sisters in Islam (SIS) demanded today. The Muslim women’s rights group said shaming and punishment would only create an increasingly repressive environment that would affect women and the poor disproportionately as in Acheh, pointing out that the Indonesian province’s Shariah laws have extended to non-Muslims too. “Do not deceive the Muslim population here by brandishing the holy religion of Islam to justify these deplorable actions,” said SIS in a statement. “As Malaysians, we demand th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Human rights under increasing attack worldwide - Malaysiakini</title><link>http://www.malaysiakini.com/letters/365830</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPqxj6F4hioAahUYAqgJhqsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPTirwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 08:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysiakini.com/letters/365830" target="_blank"&gt;Human rights under increasing attack worldwide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking ahead of Human Rights Day on Saturday Dec 10, the largest body of independent experts of the United Nations Human Rights system urges all governments around the world to stand up for human rights. The greatest achievement of the international community since the end of World War II has been the construction of an international human rights system based upon the Universal Declaration of Human Rights which was adopted 68 years ago. Since that time, enormous strides have been made in establishing universal standards, encouraging the very widespread domestic adoption of those standards...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysiakini.com">Malaysiakini</source></item><item><title>Trump torture remarks 'lay down gauntlet' for other states: U.N. expert - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-un-torture-idUSKBN16A1MI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4huDzKtt2l3gNDthKvpYYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 20:22:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-un-torture-idUSKBN16A1MI" target="_blank"&gt;Trump torture remarks 'lay down gauntlet' for other states: U.N. expert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Stephanie Nebehay GENEVA (Reuters) - A U.N. human rights expert voiced alarm on Friday that U.S. President Donald Trump might allow torture in interrogations, warning that it "lays down the gauntlet" for other countries to follow suit. Trump said in late January he felt "absolutely" that the practice of waterboarding - a form of simulated drowning - worked as an intelligence-gathering tool. He also said he would defer on the issue to Defense Secretary Jim Mattis, who disagrees with him about its usefulness. U.N. special rapporteur on protecting human rights Ben Emmerson told the U.N. Hum...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Turkey’s Future Is Moving Backward - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/09/19/opinion/turkey-islamism.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHI42RAta7UmlspNhJ8pLPIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwpoIY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 12:16:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/09/19/opinion/turkey-islamism.html" target="_blank"&gt;Turkey’s Future Is Moving Backward&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turks once saw themselves as a people who could merge Muslim culture with Western democracy and secularism. Nobody believes that anymore.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Boise's Anne Frank Memorial Vandalized With Swastika, Racial Slur - HuffPost</title><link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/boises-anne-frank-memorial-vandalized-with-swastika-racial-slur_us_591429c7e4b030d4f1efd250</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKIvrGZZHK_fTeXvEoXKYe8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMK2HuAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 10:19:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/boises-anne-frank-memorial-vandalized-with-swastika-racial-slur_us_591429c7e4b030d4f1efd250" target="_blank"&gt;Boise's Anne Frank Memorial Vandalized With Swastika, Racial Slur&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Anne Frank Human Rights Memorial in Boise, Idaho, has been repeatedly defaced with anti-Semitic and racial slurs this week. On Tuesday, a visiting tour group found part of the memorial was defaced with anti-Semitic and racial slurs. And officials at the organization say they found new graffiti on the memorial Wednesday ― this time, a swastika. The site opened in 2002 as a park that’s “designed to engage visitors to reflect, think and engage one another on human rights issues.” In middle of the memorial stands a life-size bronze statue of Anne Frank, the German-born 15-year-old diarist w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>U.N. rights envoy visits Myanmar amid border violence, report of abuse - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/01/09/un-rights-envoy-visits-myanmar-amid-border-violence-report-of-abuse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOtkJPsex2-AfNN4kk_WPtsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 06:45:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/01/09/un-rights-envoy-visits-myanmar-amid-border-violence-report-of-abuse/" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. rights envoy visits Myanmar amid border violence, report of abuse&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;YANGON (Reuters) - U.N. human rights envoy Yanghee Lee has arrived in Myanmar on a 12-day visit amid growing concern about reports of abuse of members of the Rohingya Muslim minority in a government security crackdown. Attackers killed nine police officers on Oct. 9 in a coordinated assault on posts near Myanmar's border with Bangladesh. Authorities say members of the Rohingya minority carried out the attacks and launched a security sweep. Since then, at least 86 people have been killed and the United Nations says about 34,000 civilians have fled across the border to Bangladesh. Residents a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>US Envoy Blasts UN Rights Council for ‘Unfair’ Treatment of Israel - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/us-envoy-blasts-un-rights-council-for-unfair-treatment-of-israel/3745459.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO4rEcGnqnf9vYTqVw7Z1SwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 21:00:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/us-envoy-blasts-un-rights-council-for-unfair-treatment-of-israel/3745459.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Envoy Blasts UN Rights Council for ‘Unfair’ Treatment of Israel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A United States envoy to the U.N. Human Rights Council called out the panel for what she called “unfair” treatment of Israel, which has been targeted by the council’s resolutions more than any other country. In a speech during the council’s main general session in Geneva Wednesday, U.S. envoy Erin Barclay accused the HRC of having “an obsession” with Israel and said it was hurting the council’s credibility. "When it comes to human rights no country should be free from scrutiny, but neither should any democratic country be regularly subjected to unfair, unbalanced and unfounded bias,'' she s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Rights groups accuse Saudi Arabia of crackdown after two activists arrested - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/01/11/rights-groups-accuse-saudi-arabia-of-crackdown-after-two-activists-arrested/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJkcEWlYkoVxeZC5kQD0SgMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 09:07:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/01/11/rights-groups-accuse-saudi-arabia-of-crackdown-after-two-activists-arrested/" target="_blank"&gt;Rights groups accuse Saudi Arabia of crackdown after two activists arrested&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DUBAI (Reuters) - Human Rights Watch and Amnesty International said Saudi Arabia had arrested two rights activists in the first ten days of this year and accused Riyadh of a crackdown on dissent. The organisations said in press releases that Essam Koshak in Mecca and Ahmed al-Mushaikhass in the eastern city of Dammam were summoned for questioning by police last week but have yet to be released. Koshak is being questioned about his tweets on human rights issues, Amnesty said, and al-Mushaikhass has advocated on behalf of relatives of detainees in the kingdom's Eastern Province - home to the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Duterte slams UN rights exec, calls him ‘idiot’ - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2016/12/23/duterte-slams-un-rights-exec-calls-him-idiot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPZRUrJdRAJXEnpjjlO6aFAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 08:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/regional/2016/12/23/duterte-slams-un-rights-exec-calls-him-idiot/" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte slams UN rights exec, calls him ‘idiot’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA: President Rodrigo Duterte (pic) erupted in anger over the comments of United Nations High Commissioner on Human Rights Executive Zeid Ra’ad Al Hussein that he should be held accountable for murder. “I think there is one United Nations official, human rights. He said Duterte is a murderer, should be charged for murder. I should be slapped with a case. This guy is either the joker or a little crazy,” Duterte said in his speech on Thursday at the Convergence of Nanay Volunteers as Community Drugwatch in Angeles City, Pampanga. “Whoever that idiot is, please tell that to him. Kindly te...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Iran’s Holding of 2 Americans Is Illegal, U.N. Experts Find - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/09/18/world/middleeast/iran-prisoners-namazi.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM3_n1zMCjDSZ4Ay842H8joqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 09:00:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/09/18/world/middleeast/iran-prisoners-namazi.html" target="_blank"&gt;Iran’s Holding of 2 Americans Is Illegal, U.N. Experts Find&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The opinion on Baquer and Siamak Namazi by the Working Group on Arbitrary Detention may embarrass Iran’s president as he attends the General Assembly.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Human Rights Day: US and EU call on China to release political prisoners - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/law/2016/dec/10/human-rights-day-us-and-eu-call-on-china-to-release-political-prisoners</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELvCfWVB-oLae2cb-AocOGAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 05:09:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/law/2016/dec/10/human-rights-day-us-and-eu-call-on-china-to-release-political-prisoners" target="_blank"&gt;Human Rights Day: US and EU call on China to release political prisoners&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than half a dozen political prisoners in China should freed, the United States and European Union have said, citing a deteriorating human rights situation that has seen hundreds lawyers and activists detained in the past year. Since coming to power in 2012 the Chinese president, Xi Jinping, has presided over a wide-ranging crackdown on freedom of expression, rights lawyers, feminists, activists and religion. About 250 lawyers and activists were detained by police starting in July last year in what some have called a “war on law”. Related: Salman Rushdie leads World Human Rights Day pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Envoy blasts OSCE resolution targeting Russian media as discriminatory - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/politics/368135-envoy-blasts-osce-resolution-targeting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHwJBJwEd1U9LXib1cQLRmYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhwwnoQo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 10:05:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/politics/368135-envoy-blasts-osce-resolution-targeting/" target="_blank"&gt;Envoy blasts OSCE resolution targeting Russian media as discriminatory&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia’s envoy to the Organization for Security and Cooperation in Europe (OSCE) has branded the group’s resolution on countering the Russian mass media a discriminatory document that contradicts basic international agreements on human rights. “Apart from its openly Russophobic orientation, the resolution is an appalling example of discrimination of the Russian media. It contradicts not only the key international standards on freedom of expression, including the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights and the OSCE obligations, but also...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>African states bid to stop work of U.N. gay rights investigator - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-un-rights-lgbt-idUSKBN12Z2OK</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGIyKK9R4vXFsxC-lkD9VBIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 20:50:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-un-rights-lgbt-idUSKBN12Z2OK" target="_blank"&gt;African states bid to stop work of U.N. gay rights investigator&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Michelle Nichols UNITED NATIONS (Reuters) - African states launched a bid at the United Nations on Friday to halt the work of the first U.N. independent investigator appointed to help protect gay and transgender people worldwide from violence and discrimination. The 47-member U.N. Human Rights Council, based in Geneva, created the position in June and in September appointed Vitit Muntarbhorn of Thailand, who has a three-year mandate to investigate abuses against lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender and intersex (LGBTI) people. In an unusual move, African states circulated a draft resoluti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Hadhari, human rights, hypocrisy - Malaysiakini</title><link>http://www.malaysiakini.com/columns/90543</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMUWYtk0ZCxTG-c1heKk3HgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMITjrwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 07:17:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysiakini.com/columns/90543" target="_blank"&gt;Hadhari, human rights, hypocrisy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The General Assembly proclaims this Universal Declaration of Human Rights (UDHR) as a common standard of achievement for all peoples and all nations, to the end that every individual and every organ of society, keeping this Declaration constantly in mind, shall strive by teaching and education to promote respect for these rights and freedoms and by progressive measures, national and international, to secure their universal and effective recognition and observance, both among the peoples of Member-States themselves and among the peoples of territories under their jurisdiction.- Universal Dec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysiakini.com">Malaysiakini</source></item><item><title>Congo forces killed 40, arrested 460 in Kabila protests: U.N. - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-congo-politics-casualties-idUSKBN14C126</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHncSYp1fkGrBe0hrR6v9soqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 10:53:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-congo-politics-casualties-idUSKBN14C126" target="_blank"&gt;Congo forces killed 40, arrested 460 in Kabila protests: U.N.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (Reuters) - The head of the U.N. human rights agency said on Friday that Congolese security forces had killed at least 40 people and arrested 460 in protests against President Joseph Kabila this week. "Such high casualty figures suggest a serious disregard ... of the need to exercise restraint in policing demonstrations," U.N. High Commissioner for Human Rights Zeid Ra'ad al-Hussein said in a statement. Protests erupted against Kabila when he failed to step down despite his mandate expiring on Tuesday. "Not only are soldiers participating in law enforcement operations, but all the fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>NGOs should condemn terrorists in Syria, not Russia fighting them – Foreign Ministry - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/364242-human-rights-un-russia-syria/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH2NOI9TKmF54n3rv4zhkNkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 22:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/364242-human-rights-un-russia-syria/" target="_blank"&gt;NGOs should condemn terrorists in Syria, not Russia fighting them – Foreign Ministry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NGOs that demanded Russia’s removal from UN Human Rights Council lack impartiality as they ignore terrorist activities as well as violations by the US-led coalition in Syria, the Russian Foreign Ministry's Commissioner for Human Rights told RT. Targeting Russia was “a gross misstep on the part of the human rights defenders,” Konstantin Dolgov said. “If they call themselves [human rights defenders] they have to be objective. Al least, they have to try to be impartial. How can they assess the human rights situation in Syria in this one-sided manner? Just to join the chorus of Western gove...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>U.S. signals that reviewing role in top U.N. rights body - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/03/01/us-signals-that-reviewing-role-in-top-un-rights-body/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN1wAB3qCFCs5wqGvNJ4dS8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 09:42:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/03/01/us-signals-that-reviewing-role-in-top-un-rights-body/" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. signals that reviewing role in top U.N. rights body&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (Reuters) - The U.S. Trump administration is reviewing its participation in the top United Nations human rights body, with an eye to reform and a balanced agenda that ends the forum's "obsession with Israel", a senior U.S. official said on Wednesday. "In order for this Council to have any credibility, let alone success, it must move away from its unbalanced and unproductive positions," Erin Barclay, U.S. deputy assistant secretary of state, told the U.N. Human Rights Council. "As we consider our future engagements, my government will be considering the Council's actions with an eye t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Liu Xiaobo’s Unflappable Optimism - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2017/07/13/opinion/liu-xiaobos-unflappable-optimism.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4WSXgBFwU9uU8L_Ge7nrwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwpoIY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 16:13:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/07/13/opinion/liu-xiaobos-unflappable-optimism.html" target="_blank"&gt;Liu Xiaobo’s Unflappable Optimism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chinese dissident didn’t let repression cloud his vision for a democratic China.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>U.N. rights expert criticises Myanmar over Rohingya crackdown - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/01/20/un-rights-expert-criticises-myanmar-over-rohingya-crackdown/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKnilUj4n8poIn1M6fVnaUkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:57:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/01/20/un-rights-expert-criticises-myanmar-over-rohingya-crackdown/" target="_blank"&gt;U.N. rights expert criticises Myanmar over Rohingya crackdown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;YANGON (Reuters) - A United Nations human rights investigator on Friday criticised Myanmar's crackdown on the Rohingya Muslim minority and urged the military to respect the law and human rights. Authorities say the military launched a security sweep in response to what they say was an attack in October by Rohingya insurgents on border posts near Myanmar's border with Bangladesh in which nine police officers were killed. Since then, at least 86 people have been killed and the United Nations says at least 65,000 Rohingya have fled to Bangladesh. Residents and refugees accuse the military of k...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Donald Trump's torture comments 'enough to make my blood run cold', says UN human rights expert - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/donald-trump-torture-comments-un-rights-expert-ben-emmerson-jim-mattis-a7609986.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB4FwQftrrcA5G0v-a2vJrgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:53:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/donald-trump-torture-comments-un-rights-expert-ben-emmerson-jim-mattis-a7609986.html" target="_blank"&gt;Donald Trump's torture comments 'enough to make my blood run cold', says UN human rights expert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A UN human rights expert voiced alarm on Friday that US President Donald Trump might allow torture in interrogations, and called for senior officials from George W Bush's administration to be prosecuted for allowing the illegal practice. US officials responsible for the secret detention, rendition and torture programmes run by the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) included "those in the most senior positions" under Bush, said Ben Emmerson, UN special rapporteur on protecting human rights while countering terrorism. "To hear President Trump, in the first days after his inauguration, glibly e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>‘Islamophobia is becoming institutionalized,’ Muslim nations tell UN - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/379243-islamophobia-human-rights-un/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHqp4-cVpM5pusslAjWgLTQqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 18:41:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/379243-islamophobia-human-rights-un/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Islamophobia is becoming institutionalized,’ Muslim nations tell UN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ascent of far-right politics has split the world, and discrimination against Muslims is becoming enshrined in law, says Yousef Al-Othaimeen, Secretary-General of the Organisation of Islamic Cooperation (OIC), which comprise 57 nations with Islamic majorities. “Far-right politics is on the rise, strengthening the narrative of ‘us’ against ‘them’,” said Al-Othaimeen, during an official session of the UN Human Rights Council in Geneva on Wednesday. “This is a scary scenario for an intolerant world that none of us would like our children to live in. We, therefore, need to play our role.” Al...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Philippines to defend Duterte's drug war at U.N. rights body - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/02/23/philippines-to-defend-dutertes-drug-war-at-un-rights-body/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOra0jln80hP83nWyuN1BEoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 11:41:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/02/23/philippines-to-defend-dutertes-drug-war-at-un-rights-body/" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines to defend Duterte's drug war at U.N. rights body&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA (Reuters) - The Philippine foreign minister on Thursday said he would tell a United Nations rights body that the killings in President Rodrigo Duterte's war on drugs were not state-sponsored. More than 7,700 people have been killed since Duterte unleashed the drugs war in June, about 2,500 in what police say are shootouts during raids and sting operations. Most of the rest are under investigation and activists believe many were extrajudicial killings. Police blame the killings on vigilante groups over which they have no control. Perfecto Yasay said he would address the Geneva-based U...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Court decision on PAA challenge another blow for freedom of assembly - Malaysiakini</title><link>http://www.malaysiakini.com/letters/358770</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEplj7M7HEWidrBRW6WzplcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPTirwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 05:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysiakini.com/letters/358770" target="_blank"&gt;Court decision on PAA challenge another blow for freedom of assembly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amnesty International is gravely concerned with the decision of the Federal Court on Oct 10, which ordered seven human rights activists and parliamentarians from an opposition party to face trial for participating in peaceful protests in 2015. The decision, which has happened in response to a constitutional challenge of several provisions of the Peaceful Assembly Act (PAA) 2012, highlights the ongoing pattern of repression against government critics in the country. Opposition parliamentarians Chong Chieng Jen and Julian Tan Kok Ping were charged with participating in a Bersih 4 rally on Aug...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysiakini.com">Malaysiakini</source></item><item><title>Hundreds of men from east Aleppo missing - U.N. rights office - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2016/12/10/hundreds-of-men-from-east-aleppo-missing--un-rights-office/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBLquZkqDKKSFYJChnLu9zEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 16:22:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2016/12/10/hundreds-of-men-from-east-aleppo-missing--un-rights-office/" target="_blank"&gt;Hundreds of men from east Aleppo missing - U.N. rights office&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (Reuters) - Hundreds of Syrian men from eastern Aleppo have gone missing after leaving rebel-held areas amid reports of reprisals by soldiers including executions of people suspected of supporting the opposition, the United Nations said on Friday. The U.N. human rights office voiced deep concern that government forces could be mistreating the missing men and said that some 150 activists feared detention if they left remaining rebel-controlled pockets of Syria's largest city. U.N. human rights spokesman Rupert Colville also said there were reports that two rebel militias - Jabhat Fata...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Congo must investigate credible reports of atrocities - U.N.'s Zeid - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/02/21/congo-must-investigate-credible-reports-of-atrocities--uns-zeid/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDlg7__3KJ5KfBs2HJ7qgJYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 17:25:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/world/2017/02/21/congo-must-investigate-credible-reports-of-atrocities--uns-zeid/" target="_blank"&gt;Congo must investigate credible reports of atrocities - U.N.'s Zeid&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GENEVA (Reuters) - Democratic Republic of Congo must investigate "multiple, credible allegations of massive human rights violations" including summary executions by the armed forces, U.N. human rights chief Zeid Ra'ad al Hussein said on Monday. “It is time to stop a blunt military response that does nothing to tackle the root causes of the conflict between the Government and local militias but instead targets civilians on the basis of their presumed links to the militias,” Zeid said in a statement after a video that appeared to show Congolese troops shooting dead a group of apparent militia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Philippines to Defend Duterte's Drug War at UN Rights Body - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/philippines-to-defend-duterte-drug-war-at-un-rights-body/3736649.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELoMOyGYaK-hz76EQbjpN38qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 14:48:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/philippines-to-defend-duterte-drug-war-at-un-rights-body/3736649.html" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines to Defend Duterte's Drug War at UN Rights Body&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Philippine foreign minister on Thursday said he would tell a United Nations rights body that the killings in President Rodrigo Duterte's war on drugs were not state-sponsored. More than 7,700 people have been killed since Duterte unleashed the drugs war in June, about 2,500 in what police say are shootouts during raids and sting operations. Most of the rest are under investigation and activists believe many were extrajudicial killings. Police blame the killings on vigilante groups over which they have no control. Perfecto Yasay said he would address the Geneva-based United Nations Human...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Human rights now face their gravest threat – Trumpism - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/jan/23/human-rights-threat-trumpism-white-house</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIS_fvuGiq6SG8r2ERS7GBoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 06:00:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/jan/23/human-rights-threat-trumpism-white-house" target="_blank"&gt;Human rights now face their gravest threat – Trumpism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember the 1990s? Anyone who cares about human rights must now recall the era with a knot in their stomach. Compared with what’s happening today, that decade feels like a lost era of Enlightenment. Donald Trump’s installation in the White House is not just a threat to global alliances, international trade or even fact-based discussion – it risks unleashing a tsunami that could sweep away the human rights movement as it has so far existed. Related: UN human rights boss says Trump would be a global danger as president It’s not just western democracies that are shaken by the inauguration of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Stand in solidarity with the Rohingyas - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2016/12/07/stand-in-solidarity-with-the-rohingyas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC-ao1brfkqFeYT-iRyYNI8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2016/12/07/stand-in-solidarity-with-the-rohingyas/" target="_blank"&gt;Stand in solidarity with the Rohingyas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;UNITED Nations secretary-general Ban Ki-moon once said the Rohingyas are “the world’s most persecuted minority.” These stateless Muslim people may constitute up to 7% of Myanmar’s population of nearly 60 million but their exact numbers are not known because the government has refused to include them on the national census. There are more than one million Rohingyas in Rakhine State on the western coast of Myanmar, nearly all of whom are denied citizenship and are stateless. For decades, the government of Myanmar has strictly restricted their freedom of movement, preventing them from moving b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>ICERD means Muslims can leave Islam - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/08/icerd-means-muslims-can-leave-islam/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFvK98BwGBaQZLKtDZPu0pMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:12:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/08/icerd-means-muslims-can-leave-islam/" target="_blank"&gt;ICERD means Muslims can leave Islam&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, the ICERD must be read alongside the Universal Declaration of Human Rights — which, I believe, Malaysia has also not ratified. If Malaysia ratifies the ICERD will that also mean the Universal Declaration of Human Rights will also apply to Malaysia? NO HOLDS BARRED Raja Petra Kamarudin We are hearing many debates for and against the ICERD (International Convention on the Elimination of All Forms of Racial Discrimination) but I fear many do not actually know what it means. Since Pakatan Harapan has announced Malaysians now live in a ‘new’ Malaysia, the ICERD would fit in nicel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Why Anti-Semitic Attacks Are Human Rights Violations -- And Should Be Treated That Way - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelposner/2018/10/28/why-anti-semitic-attacks-are-human-rights-violations-and-should-be-treated-that-way/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPEkXLe3J-S65cg8Ec_OfKMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 00:54:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaelposner/2018/10/28/why-anti-semitic-attacks-are-human-rights-violations-and-should-be-treated-that-way/" target="_blank"&gt;Why Anti-Semitic Attacks Are Human Rights Violations -- And Should Be Treated That Way&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;People mourn in Soldiers &amp; Sailors Memorial Hall &amp; Museum during a community gathering held in the aftermath of Saturday’s deadly shooting at the Tree of Life Synagogue in Pittsburgh, Sunday, Oct. 28, 2018. (AP Photo/Matt Rourke) The mass murder of 11 Jewish worshippers in a Pittsburgh synagogue has brought home to America the scourge of anti-Semitic violence. For decades, European countries from France to Denmark and from Hungary to Greece have experienced violent extremist attacks on Jews. But now Americans also must come to terms with a rising tide of anti-Semitic rhetoric and action her...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Man Armed With Hammer Tries To Steal Original Copy Of Magna Carta - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/man-steal-magna-carta-salisbury-cathedral_us_5bd329e4e4b0d38b5882c791</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ-i8wxs0Ze3kwN1dC2oD18qFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 16:45:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/man-steal-magna-carta-salisbury-cathedral_us_5bd329e4e4b0d38b5882c791" target="_blank"&gt;Man Armed With Hammer Tries To Steal Original Copy Of Magna Carta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police in Salisbury, England, have arrested a 45-year-old man they say tried to steal an original copy of the Magna Carta from Salisbury Cathedral late Thursday. The unnamed suspect used a hammer to smash holes in the protective glass box surrounding the 803-year-old document, but was unsuccessful in reaching the document itself. The Wiltshire police said the would-be thief was detained after alarms sounded and he attempted to flee. “He walked out of the Chapter House and tried to leave the cathedral via our work yard and he was detained there and restrained until the police arrived,” the V...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Climate Justice by Mary Robinson review – power to the people - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2018/oct/14/climate-change-hope-resilience-fight-for-sustainable-future-mary-robinson-review</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVgBKewFrs2zNmcAlafNfsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 08:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/books/2018/oct/14/climate-change-hope-resilience-fight-for-sustainable-future-mary-robinson-review" target="_blank"&gt;Climate Justice by Mary Robinson review – power to the people&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past few decades, Mary Robinson has relentlessly promoted gender equality, human rights and social justice across the globe, both in her role as the former president of Ireland, and as the United Nations’ high commissioner for human rights. But as she admits in the opening pages of Climate Justice, she came relatively late to the public conversation on global warming and environmental sustainability. That changed in 2002 when she set up Realising Rights. The project sought to advance economic, social and cultural rights for developing nations, making sure that fundamental human rig...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UAE rights activist Ahmed Mansoor appeals 10-year sentence - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/uae-rights-activist-ahmed-mansoor-appeals-10-year-sentence-181001193856134.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJc-pd6oZ5O_7G_9k7bo01gqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 20:10:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/uae-rights-activist-ahmed-mansoor-appeals-10-year-sentence-181001193856134.html" target="_blank"&gt;UAE rights activist Ahmed Mansoor appeals 10-year sentence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prominent Emirati rights activist Ahmed Mansoor has filed a Supreme Court appeal in a bid to overturn a 10-year prison sentence handed to him earlier this year over several Twitter posts. Mansoor was sentenced in May by Abu Dhabi's Federal Appeals Court for "defaming the UAE through social media channels". A father of four, Mansoor was also fined 1 million Dirhams ($270,000) for insulting the status and prestige of the UAE and its symbols, including its leaders. Several international rights groups, including a number of United Nations human rights bodies, the EU Parliament's subcommittee on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Gay Rights Activists Hail UN Chief's Support for LGBT Community - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/gay-rights-activists-hail-un-chief-s-support-for-lgbt-community/4588672.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ9KbGlvgfrpBzoI0fKfKhEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 20:51:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/gay-rights-activists-hail-un-chief-s-support-for-lgbt-community/4588672.html" target="_blank"&gt;Gay Rights Activists Hail UN Chief's Support for LGBT Community&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gay rights campaigners on Wednesday hailed a speech by U.N. chief Antonio Guterres in support of the LGBT community but said words must be followed by action. In the first address by the head of the United Nations to the U.N. LGBTI Core Group — which was established in 2008 to oversee gay rights globally — Guterres said the multinational body would boost efforts to end anti-LGBT+ abuse and violence. Concerns are rising about a possible rollback of hard-won LGBT+ rights worldwide — from a U.S. partial ban on transgender individuals serving in the military to a recent first punishment of a Ru...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>International Peace Day: 10 inspirational quotes from history on the ideal and its true meaning - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/international-peace-day-2018-un-general-assembly-universal-declaration-human-rights-a8548786.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGCPbj3NYICNT00Ouo0xougqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 15:08:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/international-peace-day-2018-un-general-assembly-universal-declaration-human-rights-a8548786.html" target="_blank"&gt;International Peace Day: 10 inspirational quotes from history on the ideal and its true meaning&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations (UN) observes International Peace Day this Friday. First held on 21 September 1982 following a resolution sponsored by the UK and Costa Rica, the occasion was inaugurated by the UN General Assembly as a moment “devoted to strengthening the ideals of peace, both within and among all nations and peoples”. In 1999, British documentary filmmaker Jeremy Gilley formed Peace One Day, an organisation campaigning for the existing day to be institutionalised around the world, ensuring that all countries honour ceasefires on 21 September. Giley appealed directly to the General Assem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Suhakam schools PM, says it doesn’t want same-sex marriage, just human rights - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/22/suhakam-schools-pm-says-it-doesnt-want-same-sex-marriage-just-human-rights/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKCVw8s9jsJGUj6bbiDDU7UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 11:38:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/22/suhakam-schools-pm-says-it-doesnt-want-same-sex-marriage-just-human-rights/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam schools PM, says it doesn’t want same-sex marriage, just human rights&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Mkini) – The Human Rights Commission (Suhakam) has denied assertions by Prime Minister Dr Mahathir Mohamad that it is pushing Putrajaya to allow same-sex marriages. Rather, commission chairperson Razali Ismail says Suhakam only wants the government to ratify international human rights treaties to give fair treatment and protect the basic rights of all Malaysians, including the LGBT community. “Suhakam does not support same-sex marriages in Malaysia… Suhakam is unaware of any international human rights treaty that if ratified, would oblige the government to legalise same-sex marriage,” he s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Conference on human rights and peace in Tunis - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/09/13/conference-on-human-rights-and-peace-in-tunis_74a2a9a6-9466-4d56-8d0c-c76c859e0d31.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELS26UfnvavkgkyN4OgSi-kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMIWA0QU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 07:45:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansamed.info/ansamed/en/news/sections/politics/2018/09/13/conference-on-human-rights-and-peace-in-tunis_74a2a9a6-9466-4d56-8d0c-c76c859e0d31.html" target="_blank"&gt;Conference on human rights and peace in Tunis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSAmed) - TUNIS, SEPTEMBER 13 - The Tunisian National Human Rights Committee (NHRC) will organize an international conference on ''Issues of Peace'' in Tunis from 26 to 29 September. Organized by NHRC in Tunis in cooperation with the Arab Institute for Human Rights, the United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) and the NGO-NESCO Liaison committee, more than 120 organizations, 250 participants and observers, and UNESCO Member States will attend the four-day conference as part of the celebration of the 70th anniversary of the Universal Declaration of Human Ri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansamed.info">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Suhakam deplores caning of women, says corporal punishment must end - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/04/suhakam-deplores-caning-of-women-says-corporal-punishment-must-end/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDen6DoRKPLMu3aXeTHUBiYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 10:09:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/04/suhakam-deplores-caning-of-women-says-corporal-punishment-must-end/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam deplores caning of women, says corporal punishment must end&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) has joined the chorus of voices demanding an end to corporal punishment, following the caning of two women in Terengganu on Monday (Sept 3) for attempting to have same-sex relations. In a statement Tuesday (Sept 4), commission chairman Tan Sri Razali Ismail said Suhakam deplores the decision of the Terengganu Shariah court, which not only imposed a cruel, inhuman and degrading punishment on the two women, but further humiliated them by executing the caning publicly, and in the presence of the media. “While Suhakam is aware that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Rights groups alarmed over Thai detention of asylum seekers - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/89d1dda9855943e997a299175bf6c682</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMSiH9bAxoxtstqPcmBi3YMqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 01:10:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/89d1dda9855943e997a299175bf6c682" target="_blank"&gt;Rights groups alarmed over Thai detention of asylum seekers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Human rights groups expressed alarm Thursday at Thailand's detention of more than 160 asylum seekers from hill tribe ethnic minorities in Vietnam and Cambodia, saying they face possible persecution if returned to their homelands. Thai and international rights groups said the asylum seekers were rounded up Tuesday in a northern suburb of Bangkok and charged with immigration law violations. The Thai group Human Rights Lawyers Association said some had cards from the U.N. refugee agency identifying them as having been certified as refugees. The group said the detainees, from the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Ditch identity politics: fight for one person’s rights at a time - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/aug/29/human-rights-best-defended-one-person-time</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPOoKcrpKmZXK_NR-6AssrsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 05:00:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/aug/29/human-rights-best-defended-one-person-time" target="_blank"&gt;Ditch identity politics: fight for one person’s rights at a time&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’d like to talk about heroes – and mine are people who defend human rights. They are the people who keep reminding us about the exquisite uniqueness of each individual human being and the need to protect his or her rights and dignity regardless of whatever characteristic may be attached to that person, willingly or not. Human rights are individual rights; they are not the rights of a group. This sounds obvious, yet it seems to get increasingly drowned out in the way we react to crises or events, and not least in the way politics is framed. Recalling how the international human rights movem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>A Too-Narrow Vision of Religious Freedom - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/18/opinion/sunday/trump-pence-religious-freedom-evangelicals.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPj96Pj00pqkyOF3krOXJwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzwwpoIY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 18:30:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/18/opinion/sunday/trump-pence-religious-freedom-evangelicals.html" target="_blank"&gt;A Too-Narrow Vision of Religious Freedom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration embraces a laudable desire to expand religious tolerance, but its own intolerance toward some undermines the message.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Human rights have become the kryptonite of the populist west. It wasn't always like this - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/jun/27/nhs-70th-birthday-universal-declaration-human-rights</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMRtDmbTQnNhj17aR04Lu9YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 04:59:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/jun/27/nhs-70th-birthday-universal-declaration-human-rights" target="_blank"&gt;Human rights have become the kryptonite of the populist west. It wasn't always like this&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I personally struggle a bit with anniversaries. Britain loves them, of course. A century of votes for some women (not all, a nuance that is often lost); the centenary of the end of the first world war, which should also be about Britain’s imperial solders, who were treated appallingly and then forgotten. To say I had mixed feelings when the government held a Windrush 70th anniversary celebration at 10 Downing Street last week is a bit of an understatement. Theresa May was clearly not going to let the denial of basic rights to hundreds of Windrush-generation Britons get in the way of having ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Saifuddin pledges to push for ratification of six international human rights conventions - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/02/saifuddin-pledges-to-push-for-ratification-of-six-international-human-rights-conventions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPWkZHKokBucX8Dj7UMxBiwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 10:36:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/02/saifuddin-pledges-to-push-for-ratification-of-six-international-human-rights-conventions/" target="_blank"&gt;Saifuddin pledges to push for ratification of six international human rights conventions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: Newly minted Foreign Minister Datuk Saifuddin Abdullah pledged to push for the ratification of six international human rights conventions. "As stated in our (Pakatan Harapan) manifesto, we aspire to sign all the international human rights conventions.There are nine conventions, of which we have only ratified three," he told reporters after taking office in Wisma Putra after the swearing-in ceremony at Istana Negara earlier on Monday (July 2). Besides the nation playing a more effective role in promoting human rights, Saifuddin said that it was also his personal goal to see Malays...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>