<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Raymond Koh - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZqTnpKcmR6RjRPQklDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:21:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Suhakam closes inquiry on Pastor Raymond's disappearance - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/07/suhakam-closes-inquiry-on-pastor-raymonds-disappearance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780129269109</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/07/suhakam-closes-inquiry-on-pastor-raymonds-disappearance/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam closes inquiry on Pastor Raymond's disappearance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/07/suhakam-inquiry-into-disappearance-of-pastor-koh-ends-on-friday-dec-7/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam inquiry into disappearance of Pastor Koh ends on Friday (Dec 7) - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/116740" target="_blank"&gt;LIVE: New witnesses as inquiry into missing pastor reaches the end&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Malaysian Insight&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/12/07/cop-tells-inquiry-how-he-seized-items-linked-to-missing-pastor-from-suspects-home/" target="_blank"&gt;Cop tells inquiry how he seized items linked to missing pastor from suspect's home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/08/pastor-kohs-inquiry-ends-wife-hopes-truth-will-prevail/" target="_blank"&gt;Pastor Koh's inquiry ends, wife hopes truth will prevail - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWoxNnV5bWpZQU1FWkFYYkRzMU5RdTZLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/guD8Sct4wuOUbRcShDwbbSqPW3qKHkAyi3uiOJ5MECTP1ZZ28wKHIIBOYIsUPBg2WdCDBIiiUSOzWju9WrlhY2ohO6uyYyMjFgdY60WeFQ_Lezf0g8t5P2Eegpu1jPI1_0rcTgzb0xiJRjt-y_13Ow=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Mother of missing pastor passes away - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/14/mother-of-missing-pastor-passes-away/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKVPYUewtnvz1aqJ_nSFl7oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/14/mother-of-missing-pastor-passes-away/" target="_blank"&gt;Mother of missing pastor passes away - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The mother of missing Pastor Raymond Koh has passed away at the age of 93.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Inquiry into Raymond Koh case resumes, Suhakam to call new witness - Nation - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/15/inquiry-into-raymond-koh-case-resumes-suhakam-to-call-new-witness/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECzcm7uUisXsZXSvFVy-KykqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/15/inquiry-into-raymond-koh-case-resumes-suhakam-to-call-new-witness/" target="_blank"&gt;Inquiry into Raymond Koh case resumes, Suhakam to call new witness - Nation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Human Rights Commission of Malaysia's (Suhakam) inquiry into the disappearance of pastor Raymond Koh will resume next month with ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Suhakam inquiry into Pastor Koh's disappearance comes to an end - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LT-CZoxMi7U</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGqpwDr4jsjMTEc5EbFqiWAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMJOsiAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:15:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LT-CZoxMi7U" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam inquiry into Pastor Koh's disappearance comes to an end&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry into the disappearance of Pastor Raymond Koh ended on Friday, with two more witnesses being questioned.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Koh’s wife questions IGP in open letter - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/08/31/kohs-wife-questions-igp-in-open-letter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPq8y8sC-l9FL90Ece3ZDBsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/08/31/kohs-wife-questions-igp-in-open-letter/" target="_blank"&gt;Koh’s wife questions IGP in open letter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The wife of missing Pastor Raymond Koh has expressed her disappointment in the Inspector-General of Police on the eve of the 200th day of her husband’s abduction. Susanna Liew Sow Yoke (pic), in an open letter, chastised Tan Sri Khalid Abu Bakar over the handling of the investigation into Koh’s disappearance. “We are devastated. What makes it worse is the way you and the police under your command have treated us, Raymond’s family, his friends and the Malaysian public while conducting investigations into his abduction,” she said. Liew claimed that the police had not done enoug...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pastor's wife writes open letter to IGP 200 days after abduction - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/08/30/pastors-wife-writes-open-letter-to-igp-200-days-after-abduction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKyn4K8arEy0mYJbz_ni4isqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 04:47:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/08/30/pastors-wife-writes-open-letter-to-igp-200-days-after-abduction/" target="_blank"&gt;Pastor's wife writes open letter to IGP 200 days after abduction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The wife of missing Pastor Raymond Koh (pic) has expressed her disappointment in Inspector-General of Police Tan Sri Khalid Abu Bakar on the eve of the 200th day of her husband's abduction. Susanna Liew Sow Yoke, in an open letter on Wednesday, chastised the IGP over the handling of the investigation into Koh's disappearance. "We are devastated. What makes it worse is the way you and the police under your command have treated us, Raymond's family, his friends and the Malaysian public while conducting investigations into his abduction," she said. Liew claimed that the police h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Khalid as Prasarana chief is like a fish out of water - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOGtxo1FrS8zfvN5YXluU7gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:37:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;YOURSAY | ‘I pity Khalid, who actually wanted to enrol himself in culinary classes.’ Of all people, why Khalid as Prasarana chief? Slumdog: Dear Malaysiakini contributor P Gunasegaram, based on the Malaysian Code on Corporate Governance, former inspector-general of police (IGP) Khalid Abu Bakar is totally incapable and unfit to be chairperson of Prasarana Malaysia Bhd. He will be like a fish out of water. So now Prime Minister Najib Abdul Razak has let loose another of his henchmen on another government-linked company (GLC). It does not get better. The company does not disclose its financia...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Suhakam closes inquiry into disappearance of Amri Che Mat - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/suhakam-closes-inquiry-into-disappearance-of-amri-che-mat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDo6w2oE88uYzGSsfnlLTQEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 10:11:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/31/suhakam-closes-inquiry-into-disappearance-of-amri-che-mat/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam closes inquiry into disappearance of Amri Che Mat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) has closed the inquiry into the disappearance of missing activist Amri Che Mat. It, however, can be reopened subject to the availability of a potential witness, said the panel of inquiry chairman Datuk Mah Weng Kwai. Mah said the panel came up with the unanimous decision to close the proceedings in the interest of time. "We must get the submissions in order. We need time to go through all the documents and come up with a decision," said Mah who added that the panel's term as commissioners ends in April next year. The inquiry wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Suhakam inquiry into disappearance of Pastor Raymond Koh to resume on Aug 27 - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/26/suhakam-inquiry-into-disappearance-of-pastor-raymond-koh-to-resume-on-aug-27/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMkgkubR7uyneG-_ZGA87zMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 03:20:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/26/suhakam-inquiry-into-disappearance-of-pastor-raymond-koh-to-resume-on-aug-27/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam inquiry into disappearance of Pastor Raymond Koh to resume on Aug 27&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The Suhakam inquiry into the disappearance of Pastor Raymond Koh (pic) is scheduled to resume on Monday (Aug 27) afternoon, after an almost eight-month hiatus. In January, the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) had ceased the inquiry as a suspect had been charged in court in relation to the case. Suhakam commissioner Datuk Mah Weng Kwai, who is leading the inquiry, had cited Section 12(3) of the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia Act, which states that it should "immediately cease" an inquiry if the allegation becomes the subject matter of any court proceeding. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pastor Raymond Koh's wife makes tearful plea for answers over his disappearance - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/27/pastor-raymond-koh-wife-makes-tearful-plea-for-answers-over-his-disappearance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGKg2sXrafMzvuq4ZBl6IrwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 08:35:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/27/pastor-raymond-koh-wife-makes-tearful-plea-for-answers-over-his-disappearance/" target="_blank"&gt;Pastor Raymond Koh's wife makes tearful plea for answers over his disappearance&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: "It is hard to go on like this." This was the tear-filled plea made by Susanna Liew for the new Pakatan Government to solve the mystery over her husband Pastor Raymond Koh's disappearance in February 2017. "It has been more than 500 days since his disappearance. "That is a long time to wait over the uncertainty over what happened. "There is no closure," she said while struggling to hold back tears when met after the resumption of the public inquiry into Koh's disappearance by the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) on Monday (Aug 27). Liew, 62, who was accompanied by...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Police only there to help out, ex-IGP says on religious raids - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/28/police-only-there-to-help-out-exigp-says-on-religious-raids/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHEmtVrOcR52ji_e79I05fEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 07:34:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/28/police-only-there-to-help-out-exigp-says-on-religious-raids/" target="_blank"&gt;Police only there to help out, ex-IGP says on religious raids&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Police would accompany religious authorities in their raids to provide assistance on security and logistics matters, claimed Tan Sri Khalid Abu Bakar. The former Inspector-General of Police (IGP) claimed that any raid to do with religious matters would be led by the religious authorities and not the men in blue. "They would decide if it is an offence under their act. That has always been the case," he told a Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry into the abduction of activist Amri Che Mat on Tuesday (Aug 28). He had been asked if the police had initiated the ra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Probe all enforced disappearance cases, Suhakam urges Govt - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/29/probe-all-enforced-disappearance-cases-suhakam-urges-govt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEICe2PTtyRGlP-w48Lwn-k0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 06:58:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/29/probe-all-enforced-disappearance-cases-suhakam-urges-govt/" target="_blank"&gt;Probe all enforced disappearance cases, Suhakam urges Govt&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) has urged the Government to conduct an independent investigation on all reported enforced disappearance cases and bring the perpetrators to book. "The rule of law must prevail and there is no place for a culture of impunity in Malaysia," its chairman Tan Sri Razali Ismail (pic) said during the keynote speech of the 2018 Regional Conference on Victims of Enforced Disappearances here on Wednesday (Aug 29). His speech was read out by Suhakam secretary Dr Cheah Swee Neo. In Malaysia, the disappearances of Pastor Raymond Koh, activi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Fear drove me to lodge police report, Special Branch officer tells Suhakam inquiry - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/24/fear-drove-me-to-lodge-police-report-exsb-officer-tells-suhakam/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMoIE6ohobu8HbztEGzwjxMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 12:41:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/24/fear-drove-me-to-lodge-police-report-exsb-officer-tells-suhakam/" target="_blank"&gt;Fear drove me to lodge police report, Special Branch officer tells Suhakam inquiry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A Special Branch officer from Perlis says that he was “in fear of everyone” when he finally decided to lodge a police report against the wife of a missing activist. Sgt Shamzaini Mohd Daud, during the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry into the disappearance of Amri Che Mat (pic), Pastor Raymond Koh as well as Pastor Joshua Hilmi and his wife Ruth Sitepu on Tuesday (July 24), said that he took a long time to lodge a police report because he was concerned about what people would think of him. Amri's wife Norhayati Mohd Ariffin, had lodged a police report alle...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Restaurant owner to be charged for not turning up at Suhakam inquiry - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/23/restaurant-owner-to-be-charged-not-turning-up-at-suhakam-inquiry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEExQah9Wz_FBj8NdcMfB82YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 05:18:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/23/restaurant-owner-to-be-charged-not-turning-up-at-suhakam-inquiry/" target="_blank"&gt;Restaurant owner to be charged for not turning up at Suhakam inquiry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A restaurant owner is expected to be charged by the police for his failure to show up at a Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry on the disappearance of activist Amri Che Mat. Saiful Afdzan, the owner of the Mak Lang restaurant in Kangar, Perlis, had refused to attend the inquiry, despite being issued a subpoena to appear. The inquiry heard on Monday (July 23) that the investigation papers on this matter have been returned to the Kuala Lumpur police headquarters, with instructions to charge him under Section 174 of the Penal Code for non-attendance in obedience...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>SB officer caught off guard during inquiry into missing activist - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/05/sb-officer-caught-off-guard-during-inquiry-into-missing-activist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECh_KNNNEQ_8Kn2fOVx4Kz0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 08:04:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/05/sb-officer-caught-off-guard-during-inquiry-into-missing-activist/" target="_blank"&gt;SB officer caught off guard during inquiry into missing activist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A retired special branch officer was caught off guard and contradicted himself several times when grilled during a Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry on the disappearance of activist Amri Che Mat. CP Datuk Awaludin Jadid, the former principal assistant director of Special Branch's Social Extremism Division (E2) had to be reminded several times by the inquiry panel to answer the questions posed to him. When lawyer Nizam Bashir pointed out several passages by Awaludin in a speech that he had made about extremism in 2016, Awaludin said that he had dramatised se...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Suhakam inquiry: Cop denies missing activist's wife’s allegations - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/06/suhakam-inquiry-cop-denies-missing-activists-wifes-allegations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMP1mx7Z-xvLaB7UN9PdDZwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 05:27:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/06/suhakam-inquiry-cop-denies-missing-activists-wifes-allegations/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam inquiry: Cop denies missing activist's wife’s allegations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A police officer has denied allegations by the wife of missing activist Amri Che Mat that he had told her that the police were behind her husband’s abduction. Sarjan Mohd Shamzaini Mohd Daud, who is a Special Branch officer in Perlis, admitted that he had met Norhayati Mohd Ariffin on May 12, but claimed it was only to enquire about renting a shoplot within the compound of her house. “I strongly deny her allegations,” he told the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry on the disappearance of Amri on Friday. In a police report she made on May 15 at the Shah Alam ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Retired cop denies allegations linking him to Amri Che Mat abduction - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/03/retired-cop-denies-allegations-linking-him-to-amri-che-mat-abduction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIrmw4NG5NedmqTzIyobUuEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 13:04:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/07/03/retired-cop-denies-allegations-linking-him-to-amri-che-mat-abduction/" target="_blank"&gt;Retired cop denies allegations linking him to Amri Che Mat abduction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A retired high-ranking police officer has denied claims linking him to the abduction of missing activist Amri Che Mat. CP Datuk Awaludin Jadid, the former principal assistant director of Special Branch's Social Extremism Division (E2) denied claims by Amri's wife Norhayati Mohd Ariffin that he was in charge of a police team that abducted Amri in 2016. "No, I wasn't involved," he said on Tuesday (July 3) to a question during the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry on the disappearance of Amri. In a police report she made on May 15 at the Shah Alam police stati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Group hopes new govt can revive search for missing pastors, activist - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/24/revive-search-for-pastor-koh-amri-other-two-missing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ3zYb-cl-0Dea2X2G5Mp4EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 14:29:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/24/revive-search-for-pastor-koh-amri-other-two-missing/" target="_blank"&gt;Group hopes new govt can revive search for missing pastors, activist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: NGO Citizen Action Group on Enforced Disappearance hopes that the newly-formed pakatan Harapan government will revive efforts to find missing Pastor Raymond Koh, Amri Che Mat, Pastor Joshua Hilmy and Ruth Sitepu. A crowd gathered at Dataran Merdeka at around 8pm Sunday (June 22) to hold a vigil seeking justice for the missing persons. The group's spokesman Thomas Fann said that it had been over a year since the four individuals went missing. "We hope that the new Government will succeed where the old one failed, and make sure justice is done for the missing persons and their f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Perlis Special Branch was monitoring Amri before he disappeared, Suhakam inquiry told - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/26/perlis-special-branch-was-monitoring-amri-before-he-disappeared/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF17P-mGy5yBd9ShBU77bKYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 06:26:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/26/perlis-special-branch-was-monitoring-amri-before-he-disappeared/" target="_blank"&gt;Perlis Special Branch was monitoring Amri before he disappeared, Suhakam inquiry told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A Perlis Special Branch officer has confirmed that social activist Amri Che Mat was being monitored over his alleged Syiah links prior to his disappearance. "According to the investigation of my research papers on Syiah, Amri Che Mat is also on the list to be monitored," Asst Supt Razman Ramli told an inquiry of the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) over the disappearance of Pastor Raymond Koh, Amri, Pastor Joshua Hilmi and his wife Ruth Sitepu. ASP Razman heads the Perlis Special Branch Social Department. During the inquiry Tuesday (June 26), he explained that his...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>… And justice for all - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/on-the-beat/2018/06/24/and-justice-for-all-the-closet-is-bursting-with-skeletons-and-the-carpet-is-a-mile-high-and-while-t/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKF0-wOAVCAJKVqVRVlIVVAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/columnists/on-the-beat/2018/06/24/and-justice-for-all-the-closet-is-bursting-with-skeletons-and-the-carpet-is-a-mile-high-and-while-t/" target="_blank"&gt;… And justice for all&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW government, new expectations and new hope. First to roll out was the reopening of Mongolian Altantuya Shaariibuu’s murder case. Then, the Cabinet mooted a fresh probe into Teoh Beng Hock’s sinister death. Inspector-General of Police Tan Sri Mohamad Fuzi Harun said the Altantuya case has earned re-examination based on the old police report and the one lodged in Dang Wangi by her father Shaaribuu Setev recently. Teoh’s case awaits Attorney-General Tommy Thomas’ consultation for further action. (Altantuya was murdered and her body blown up with explosives at a secondary jungle between 10pm...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Wives of missing activists plead for PM’s help to locate their husbands - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/12/wives-of-missing-activists-plead-for-pms-help-to-locate-their-husbands/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP8PbpeAJ-0NDO6PaIjyR6YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 05:20:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/06/12/wives-of-missing-activists-plead-for-pms-help-to-locate-their-husbands/" target="_blank"&gt;Wives of missing activists plead for PM’s help to locate their husbands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The wives of missing activists Pastor Raymond Koh and Amri Che Mat have pleaded with Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad to help them find their husbands who have been missing for more than a year. In an open letter to the Prime Minister, they said that any delay in the matter could be seen as a denial of their husbands’ rights to be protected under the rule of law. “Please help us find out what happened to our husbands, who took them and where they are now. "We want them back with us. We beg for justice. We plead for the truth,” said Susanna Liew and Norhayati Mohd Ariffin in a joint le...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Special Branch cop lodges report denying statement by Amri Che Mat's wife - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/31/special-branch-cop-lodges-report-denying-statement-by-amri-che-mat-wife/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHft-OMWy5cv0xAg7_ELbeoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 15:59:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/31/special-branch-cop-lodges-report-denying-statement-by-amri-che-mat-wife/" target="_blank"&gt;Special Branch cop lodges report denying statement by Amri Che Mat's wife&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The cop who claimed that missing activist Amri Che Mat was taken away by Special Branch officers from Bukit Aman has lodged a police report denying that he made such claims. Sentul police chief Assistant Commissioner R. Munusamy had showed Amri's wife Norhayati Mohd Ariffin the police report that Sgt Shamzaini Mohd Daud had made on May 30 during the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry on Thursday (May 31). The policeman attached with Special Branch in Perlis was supposed to take the stand to testify on Thursday but his session was postponed to a later date. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Wife of missing activist Amri Che Mat claims police officer told her SB did it - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/30/wife-of-missing-activist-amri-che-mat-claims-police-officer-told-her-sb-did-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELumDBEYMf7vD964nXJqgvgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 06:16:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/30/wife-of-missing-activist-amri-che-mat-claims-police-officer-told-her-sb-did-it/" target="_blank"&gt;Wife of missing activist Amri Che Mat claims police officer told her SB did it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The wife of missing activist Amri Che Mat claims that a police officer told her that Special Branch officers from Bukit Aman abducted her husband without the knowledge of Perlis police. Norhayati Mohd Ariffin said that a Sgt Shamzaini Mohd Daud came to see her to reveal information about her husband after the change in government following the May 9 polls. "He told me that he did not want to be complicit in the abduction of my husband," she told a Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry on the abduction on Wednesday (May 30). She was called in to testify again at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Missing activist's wife hope protection will be given to 'whistleblowing' policeman - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/30/missing-activists-wife-hope-protection-will-be-given-to-whistleblowing-policeman/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECMhwqfH0gjULUwifClu2ZAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 09:18:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/30/missing-activists-wife-hope-protection-will-be-given-to-whistleblowing-policeman/" target="_blank"&gt;Missing activist's wife hope protection will be given to 'whistleblowing' policeman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Norhayati Mohd Ariffin, the wife of missing activist Amri Che Mat hopes the Home Ministry will protect the police officer who gave her information about those responsible for her husband's abduction. She hoped that Sgt Shamzaini Mohd Daud would speak the truth when he eventually testifies at a Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry looking into the abduction of her husband and three other individuals. She said that she met an aide of Home Minister Tan Sri Muhyiddin Yassin on Monday (May 28) to voice her concerns. "I hope that he will be given protection so that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>In Malaysia, Calls for New Leaders to Revisit Old Abductions and Deaths - The New York Times</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/05/25/world/asia/malaysia-najib-mahathir-abductions.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELE3uAIFBUjCnANsQ61DpJMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowjuuKAzCWrzww5oEY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 08:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/05/25/world/asia/malaysia-najib-mahathir-abductions.html" target="_blank"&gt;In Malaysia, Calls for New Leaders to Revisit Old Abductions and Deaths&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new government is being urged to re-examine mysterious abductions, deaths of prisoners in custody and politically charged murders.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nytimes.com">The New York Times</source></item><item><title>Suhakam restarts inquiry into Pastor Raymond Koh - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/16/suhakam-restarts-inquiry-into-pastor-raymond-koh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKuETVJxOl4ERfhCaWr_q3wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 04:13:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/16/suhakam-restarts-inquiry-into-pastor-raymond-koh/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam restarts inquiry into Pastor Raymond Koh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) will restart the public inquiry into the disappearance of Pastor Raymond Koh. “The panel hereby decides that it will proceed and continue with the hearing in the public inquiry into the alleged disappearance of Koh, notwithstanding the letter received from the Royal Malaysian Police... to cease the public inquiry,” commissioner Datuk Mah Weng Kwai said while delivering the decision. The public inquiry into Koh's case was put on hold as a 31-year-old man claimed trial to extorting Koh's son, Jonathan Koh Szu Hao. Part-time drive...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Special Branch officers took Amri, says activist’s wife - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/17/special-branch-officers-took-amri-says-activists-wife/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBi9JPS8DBLhyS6mDMssw1MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/05/17/special-branch-officers-took-amri-says-activists-wife/" target="_blank"&gt;Special Branch officers took Amri, says activist’s wife&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Special Branch officers from Bukit Aman were the ones who abducted Perlis activist Amri Che Mat, his wife claims in a police statement. Norhayati Mohd Ariffin made the allegations in a statement to the police. Counsel Larissa Ann Louis read out the statement yesterday at the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia’s (Suhakam) public inquiry on the disappearance of Pastor Raymond Koh, Amri, Joshua Hilmi and his wife Ruth Sitepu. In the statement, she alleged that her husband was being monitored by the Special Branch police officers before he was abducted on Nov 24, 2016 in Kangar, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Questioning of Perlis mufti at Suhakam inquiry gets heated - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/04/12/questioning-of-perlis-mufti-at-suhakam-inquiry-gets-heated/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBxnp33VZz2HasbV5N0V4wQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 07:37:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/04/12/questioning-of-perlis-mufti-at-suhakam-inquiry-gets-heated/" target="_blank"&gt;Questioning of Perlis mufti at Suhakam inquiry gets heated&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The proceedings at a Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry got heated when Bar Council lawyer Siti Kasim questioned the Perlis mufti about missing activist Amri Che Mat. Siti had asked Datuk Dr Mohd Asri Zainul Abidin a series of questions, with the latter visibly annoyed with some of them. These questions included whether Dr Asri knew that he had been accused of being a Wahabi. "What is your point," he replied when testifying on Thursday (April 12) in the Suhakam inquiry into the disappearance of Amri and two others. Siti also asked Dr Asri if he agreed that I...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Details of meeting between police and JAIP over Amri's disappearance a secret, says police officer - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/04/02/details-of-meeting-between-police-and-jaip-over-amri-disappearance-a-secret-says-police-officer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB2RtYazgybPFAvBfuBW7O8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 12:33:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/04/02/details-of-meeting-between-police-and-jaip-over-amri-disappearance-a-secret-says-police-officer/" target="_blank"&gt;Details of meeting between police and JAIP over Amri's disappearance a secret, says police officer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The details of the meeting between the police and the Perlis Islamic Religious Department (JAIP) cannot be revealed as it is under the Official Secrets Act 1972 (OSA), said a police officer investigating the disappearance of activist Amri Che Mat (pic). "I can't reveal what was discussed in the meeting. It is under OSA," said investigating officer Khor Yi Shuen at the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry on Monday (April 2). Khor said he was not involved in the meeting between both parties, but was told what had transpired. Amri, who co-founded Perlis Hope, a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Restaurant operator says he witnessed abduction of activist Amri Che Mat - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/03/20/restaurant-operator-says-he-witnessed-abduction-of-activist-amri-che-mat/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJOtL6S-QFZkJuN6pPsJOCcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 07:28:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/03/20/restaurant-operator-says-he-witnessed-abduction-of-activist-amri-che-mat/" target="_blank"&gt;Restaurant operator says he witnessed abduction of activist Amri Che Mat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A restaurant operator has testified to witnessing the abduction of missing social activist Amri Che Mat in Nov 2016. Syed Amri Syed Abdul Jalil, 24, said he was riding his motorcycle along Jalan Padang Behor, Kangar, on Nov 24, 2016, when he saw several vehicles stopped on the opposite site of the dual carriageway. "I thought there was an accident. After the lights turned green, I slowed down my motorcycle to see what had happened," he told a Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry on the disappearance of Amri on Tuesday (March 20). Amri had gone out from his hom...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Suhakam inquiry on Pastor Koh’s abduction should go on, say lawyers - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/03/06/suhakam-inquiry-on-pastor-kohs-abduction-should-go-on-say-lawyers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELhIf1k0ji9ibt2bbNLjzVYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 07:11:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/03/06/suhakam-inquiry-on-pastor-kohs-abduction-should-go-on-say-lawyers/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam inquiry on Pastor Koh’s abduction should go on, say lawyers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The lawyers for the family of Pastor Raymond Koh (pic) have argued that the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry into his disappearance should proceed to its conclusion. They argued that the subject matter of the inquiry and the court case related to Koh's abduction were different. Suhakam ceased the inquiry into the abduction of Pastor Koh in January after a suspect was charged in court in relation to the case. The NGO cited Section 12(3) of the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia Act which states that it should “immediately cease” an inquiry if the allegati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Driver claims trial to kidnapping Pastor Koh - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/02/28/driver-claims-trial-to-kidnapping-pastor-koh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMFF_1xb6hP6jilr-LncufsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/02/28/driver-claims-trial-to-kidnapping-pastor-koh/" target="_blank"&gt;Driver claims trial to kidnapping Pastor Koh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: A ride-sharing driver pleaded not guilty at the magistrate’s court here to kidnapping and confining Pastor Raymond Koh in February last year. Lam Chang Nam, 32, pleaded not guilty after the charge was read before magistrate Nurshahirah Abdul Salim yesterday. Lam, together with seven other suspects still at large, were alleged to have kidnapped Koh, 64, whose real name is Keng Joo Koh, and wrongly confining the victim, at 10.45am along Jalan SS4B/10A, Kelana Jaya, here, at 10.45am on Feb 13 last year. Koh is still missing. In the same court, Lam also claimed trial to a charge ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Ride-sharing driver pleads not guilty to kidnapping Pastor Koh - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/02/27/ride-sharing-driver-pleads-not-guilty-to-kidnapping-pastor-koh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIdd9dyLbSJatn5Qs1WYgvwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 13:19:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/02/27/ride-sharing-driver-pleads-not-guilty-to-kidnapping-pastor-koh/" target="_blank"&gt;Ride-sharing driver pleads not guilty to kidnapping Pastor Koh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: A ride-sharing driver pleaded not guilty at the magistrate's court here to kidnapping Pastor Raymond Koh in February last year. Lam Chang Nam, 32, pleaded not guilty after the charge was read before Magistrate Nurshahirah Abdul Salim on Tuesday (Feb 27). Lam, together with seven other suspects still at large, were alleged to have kidnapped Pastor Koh, 64, or his real name Keng Joo Koh, and wrongly confining the victim, at Jalan SS4B/10A, Kelana Jaya, here at 10.45am on Feb 13 last year. He was charged with committing the offence under Section 365 of the Penal Code read togeth...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pastor’s family hopes he will be home for reunion dinner - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/02/13/pastors-family-hopes-he-will-be-home-for-reunion-dinner/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXsmia_g-Tg27xGGEIi9yIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/02/13/pastors-family-hopes-he-will-be-home-for-reunion-dinner/" target="_blank"&gt;Pastor’s family hopes he will be home for reunion dinner&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: It has been a year since Pastor Raymond Koh was abducted but his wife is praying for a miracle, hoping he will somehow show up for the Chinese New Year reunion meal. Susanna Liew, 62, said her family was not giving up on seeing him again. “Our hope is for him to join us for the celebrations and see his mother. She doesn’t know about his abduction,” she said. Liew said the past year had been long and difficult for the family. The couple, who were married in 1983, have three children – Jonathan, Esther and Elizabeth. Liew said Esther had lost a lot of weight since her dad’s dis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Perlis Hope claims it was asked to cancel programme, inquiry told - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/25/perlis-hope-asked-to-cancel-programme-inquiry-told/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBKfk83SMF9z_tXZU3SWaKsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 12:46:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/25/perlis-hope-asked-to-cancel-programme-inquiry-told/" target="_blank"&gt;Perlis Hope claims it was asked to cancel programme, inquiry told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The charity organisation co-founded by missing activist Amri Che Mat had been asked to cancel one of its programmes previously, a public inquiry heard on Thursday (Jan 25). Perlis Hope spokesman Faisol Abdul Rahman claimed that a government department had told the organisation to cancel a programme to give out school bags and uniforms. “They said that they got instructions from above to stop it. They told me to understand,” he said during a Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry Thursday (Jan 25) on the disappearance of Amri. Faisol, 54, added that Perlis Hope’s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘We won’t leave victims in the dark’ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/25/we-wont-leave-victims-in-the-dark-police-working-to-fix-major-flaws-in-investigation-process-vows-ig/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFs_OB1V3D5Fd3edfKlOoX0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/25/we-wont-leave-victims-in-the-dark-police-working-to-fix-major-flaws-in-investigation-process-vows-ig/" target="_blank"&gt;‘We won’t leave victims in the dark’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: One of the biggest weaknesses in the police investigation process is the failure to update victims or their next of kin on the progress of the probes, said Tan Sri Mohamad Fuzi Harun. The Inspector-General of Police highlighted this as an alarming weakness that needed to be rectified. “We at the top have stressed this to our officers over and over again. But the problem persists,” he said at a press conference after officiating the handover of a CID (criminal investigation department) investigation guidelines book at Sogo shopping centre here yesterday. Mohamad Fuzi admitted t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>NGO had nothing to with religion, says missing activist's wife - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/22/ngo-had-nothing-to-with-religion-says-missing-activists-wife/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH1-3q-7N4qXWMyVhGvxWFIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 09:43:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/22/ngo-had-nothing-to-with-religion-says-missing-activists-wife/" target="_blank"&gt;NGO had nothing to with religion, says missing activist's wife&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The wife of missing activist Amri Che Mat says that the non-governmental organisation (NGO) her husband co-founded in 2015 had nothing to do with religion and politics. Norhayati Mohd Ariffin told a Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry on Monday (Jan 22) that Perlis Hope helped everyone from the poor and single mothers to victims of fires. "We help everyone regardless of their background or religion," she told the inquiry on the disappearance of her husband. She added that the organisation donated rice and provisions to those who needed it as well as helped bu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Suhakam: Suspension of inquiry into Pastor Koh's disappearance required by law - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/17/suhakam-suspension-of-inquiry-into-pastor-koh-disappearance-required-by-law/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPsJw3nKbEQ9xfr-qxLavwkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 08:16:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/17/suhakam-suspension-of-inquiry-into-pastor-koh-disappearance-required-by-law/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam: Suspension of inquiry into Pastor Koh's disappearance required by law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) has clarified that it ceased the inquiry into the abduction of Pastor Raymond Koh as law requires it, and not because it "caved in to the police". Its chairman Tan Sri Razali Ismail said it was untrue that Suhakam ceased the inquiry because it had to obey the police or because of an injunction by the authorities. "We have to respect the law. We will proceed with the other inquiries. The panel has not caved in to the police," he said at a press conference on Wednesday. Suhakam commissioner Datuk Mah Weng Kwai, who was leading th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Sudden halt to inquiry crushes Pastor Koh’s family - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/17/sudden-halt-to-inquiry-crushes-pastor-kohs-family/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPc18yyXqndeZ_l2Ku12SSgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/17/sudden-halt-to-inquiry-crushes-pastor-kohs-family/" target="_blank"&gt;Sudden halt to inquiry crushes Pastor Koh’s family&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The family of missing Pastor Raymond Koh (pic) is crushed over the abrupt halt to the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia’s (Suhakam) public inquiry into his disappearance. Suhakam suspended the inquiry after receiving a letter from the police to put a stop to it because of a pending court case. “It is very shocking for us as a family, as we had no idea this was going to happen,” wife Susanna Liew told reporters yesterday at Suhakam’s office. She said they had come to find answers to the many questions they have over Koh’s disappearance. “We hope that there will be justice. “...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Suhakam halts inquiry into Pastor Koh's disappearance on IGP's request - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/16/suhakam-halts-inquiry-into-pastor-kohs-disappearance-on-igps-request/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHYmIkq1HnwzXGdwn_Qz-6wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 04:54:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/16/suhakam-halts-inquiry-into-pastor-kohs-disappearance-on-igps-request/" target="_blank"&gt;Suhakam halts inquiry into Pastor Koh's disappearance on IGP's request&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) has put an abrupt halt to its public inquiry into the disappearance of Pastor Raymond Koh (pic) after receiving a letter from the police to cease the inquiry. Commissioner Datuk Mah Weng Kwai revealed that Suhakam received a letter from Inspector-General of Police Tan Sri Mohamad Fuzi Harun at 3pm on Monday (Jan 15) asking it to stop as there was a court case pending. According to the letter, part-time driver Lam Chang Nam, who claimed trial to extorting Koh’s son last year, had been charged under Section 365 of the Penal Code ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Man charged with extorting Pastor Koh's son now claims trial to kidnapping charge - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/16/man-charged-with-extorting-pastor-kohs-son-now-claims-trial-to-kidnapping-charge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENsqpLi0kIJBjtvTgrZ49iEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 08:55:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/16/man-charged-with-extorting-pastor-kohs-son-now-claims-trial-to-kidnapping-charge/" target="_blank"&gt;Man charged with extorting Pastor Koh's son now claims trial to kidnapping charge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The 31-year-old man who claimed trial to extorting the son of missing Pastor Raymond Koh has now been charged with kidnapping, a development described by his lawyer as "shocking".&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Wife of missing pastor expresses disappointment with police - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/17/wife-of-pastor-koh-expresses-disappointment-with-police/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDHcMBsfchgAz8JZnrl7nrUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 15:12:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/17/wife-of-pastor-koh-expresses-disappointment-with-police/" target="_blank"&gt;Wife of missing pastor expresses disappointment with police&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The wife of missing Pastor Raymond Koh has expressed disappointment towards the police following the abrupt halt to the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia’s (Suhakam) public inquiry into his disappearance. In a statement issued on Wednesday (Jan 17), Susanna Liew said that her family was unaware that part-time driver Lam Chang Nam would be charged under Section 366 for kidnapping or abduction on Monday (Jan 15). Lam had originally claimed trial to extorting Koh’s son last year. On Wednesday, Suhakam clarified that it ceased the inquiry into the abduction of Pastor Raymond Koh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>IGP: New evidence led authorities to charge suspect with kidnapping Pastor Koh - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/16/igp-new-evidence-led-authorities-to-charge-suspect-with-kidnapping-pastor-koh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC30RPvJgPH3bXT66Vjop7UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 13:43:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/01/16/igp-new-evidence-led-authorities-to-charge-suspect-with-kidnapping-pastor-koh/" target="_blank"&gt;IGP: New evidence led authorities to charge suspect with kidnapping Pastor Koh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: New evidence led the authorities to charge suspect Lam Chang Nam in court with the kidnapping of missing Pastor Raymond Koh, said Inspector-General of Police Tan Sri Mohamad Fuzi Harun. "The police have found new leads to link Lam Chang Nam to the case. Our investigation on the kidnapping is still ongoing," he said in a statement on Tuesday night (Jan 16). He added that the suspect was charged on Monday (Jan 15) under Section 365 of the Penal Code for abduction. "He is a suspect in the kidnapping of Pastor Raymond Koh early last year along with seven more individuals still at...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Beautiful Stripes: A year of strange - Star2</title><link>https://www.star2.com/living/2018/01/09/a-year-of-strange/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEPAZV8RLwyw0q5KmJY2zl0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4ajwCjCk9LcCMPK9iAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:01:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.star2.com/living/2018/01/09/a-year-of-strange/" target="_blank"&gt;Beautiful Stripes: A year of strange&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Star2&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A couple of days before Christmas, I tried on a pair of navy blue shorts and almost had a heart attack. I had just bought them the month before but couldn’t get them past my thighs! I admit I had been guilty of over-indulging over the holiday season, but this was ridiculous! Then, I took a closer look and realised they were actually my son’s shorts – he had a similar pair and they must have gotten mixed up after laundry day. Whew! For a moment, I thought all the feasting had finally caught up with me. It feels like I’m just done with Christmas 2016 and someone had stolen 2017 from right und...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.star2.com">Star2</source></item><item><title>SAC Fadzil: Pastor Koh's abduction 'similar to police operation' - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/23/pastor-koh-abduction-similar-to-police-operation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK8njupVCXrolcsL_IRs0TcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 07:06:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/23/pastor-koh-abduction-similar-to-police-operation/" target="_blank"&gt;SAC Fadzil: Pastor Koh's abduction 'similar to police operation'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The tactics used in the abduction of Pastor Koh were similar to those used in a police operation, a senior police officer told an inquiry. "This is what I can say. Actually all police operations are organised. We even plan incoming and exit routes. "If we look at this video (the video of the abduction) then it looked like a police operation. "It is the same in terms of tactical operation. It has a similar tactical operational pattern," Selangor CID chief Senior Asst Comm Fadzil Ahmat (pix) told the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) public inquiry on the disappearan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>No common link in disappearances of pastor and activists, cop tells inquiry - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/16/no-common-link-in-disappearances-of-pastor-and-activists-cop-tells-inquiry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIJSm4UeV_bsWJtCvUi8jnEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 05:40:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/16/no-common-link-in-disappearances-of-pastor-and-activists-cop-tells-inquiry/" target="_blank"&gt;No common link in disappearances of pastor and activists, cop tells inquiry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: There is no common link in the disappearances of Pastor Raymond Koh, Perlis activist Amri Che Mat and Pastor Joshua Hilmi, a public inquiry heard Thursday. “So far in there is no (common link),” investigating officer ASP Supari Muhammad told a Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) inquiry looking into the disappearances of Koh, Amri, and Joshua and his wife Ruth Hilmi here. “I’m investigating Koh's case which is classified as an abduction. The others have been classified as missing persons cases,” said ASP Supari. He was answering a question from the panel of inquiry c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pastor Koh inquiry: Same person behind kidnaps of missing four, say cops - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/16/pastor-koh-inquiry-same-person-behind-kidnaps-of-missing-four-say-cops/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBl1oGg4hdi9O5Y8ukEgWG4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 11:31:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/16/pastor-koh-inquiry-same-person-behind-kidnaps-of-missing-four-say-cops/" target="_blank"&gt;Pastor Koh inquiry: Same person behind kidnaps of missing four, say cops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Police suspect that the same individual are behind the disappearances of Pastor Raymond Koh, Perlis activist Amri Che Mat, Pastor Joshua Hilmi and his wife Ruth Hilmi. "Yes, we suspect that there's a connection because of the modus operandi used, but there is no evidence," said Selangor CID chief Senior Asst Comm Fadzil Ahmat "But we suspect that it could be the same individual in all three cases," added Fadzil, who heads a task force investigating Koh's abduction. He also said that the police also have sketches of two men involved in Koh's abduction "We have two face sketches...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Probe on Pastor Koh's disappearance focused more on alleged proselytisation of Muslims, says investigating officer - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/14/probe-on-pastor-kohs-disappearance-focused-more-on-alleged-proselytisation-of-muslims/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFFZPYljkuBUoWpcMBvY34kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 15:42:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/14/probe-on-pastor-kohs-disappearance-focused-more-on-alleged-proselytisation-of-muslims/" target="_blank"&gt;Probe on Pastor Koh's disappearance focused more on alleged proselytisation of Muslims, says investigating officer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The investigating officer probing the abduction of Pastor Raymond Koh agreed that the case was focused more on the alleged proselytisation of Muslims. "I needed to focus (on my investigation), which is why my investigation was geared towards that. I moved away from the ransom angle when I found that was not the case," ASP Supari Muhammad told a public inquiry by the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) into the disappearance of Pastor Raymond Koh, social activist Amri Che Mat, Pastor Joshua Hilmi and his wife Ruth Sitepu. The inquiry is being held under Section 12(1) ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pastor Koh inquiry: Witness claims his detention was to intimidate others - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/14/pastor-koh-inquiry-witness-claims-his-detention-was-to-intimidate-others/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJhSO47PjKhGx0DKqyoi42cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 06:52:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/14/pastor-koh-inquiry-witness-claims-his-detention-was-to-intimidate-others/" target="_blank"&gt;Pastor Koh inquiry: Witness claims his detention was to intimidate others&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former Petaling Jaya city councillor Peter Chong claims that he was held against his will in Hatyai, Thailand in order to intimidate those attending candlelight vigils in Malaysia. “I asked them why they chose me and they said they thought I was the one who organised vigils for Pastor Raymond Koh. “I tried to convince them that I personally did not know Koh at all," Chong told a public inquiry by the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) into the disappearance of Koh and three others. He said that the two men who held him claimed to belong to a group promoting Islam. C...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Police can't trace Pastor Koh's abductors due to faulty CCTVs, inquiry told - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/13/police-unable-to-gain-footage-of-pastor-koh-abductors-due-to-faulty-cctvs-inquiry-told/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHnTU7IE6gVhIycQC60OlcEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 08:54:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/13/police-unable-to-gain-footage-of-pastor-koh-abductors-due-to-faulty-cctvs-inquiry-told/" target="_blank"&gt;Police can't trace Pastor Koh's abductors due to faulty CCTVs, inquiry told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Police were unable to obtain footage on the exit routes taken by Pastor Raymond Koh's abductors because of faulty CCTVs, a public inquiry heard. Investigating officer ASP Supari Muhammad said there were about four or five cameras at the Jalan Bahagia and Jalan Majlis junctions, with some belonging to traffic police and others to the Petaling Jaya City Council (MBPJ). "The traffic police cameras, however, is only used to record traffic offences but was not functioning at the time. The MBPJ cameras were also not functioning," he told the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Police observers object to photo in Suhakam inquiry into disappearances - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/15/police-observers-object-to-photo-in-suhakam-inquiry-into-disappearances/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKlXIDIPb_SaPF-aPc3ZRwwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 13:12:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/15/police-observers-object-to-photo-in-suhakam-inquiry-into-disappearances/" target="_blank"&gt;Police observers object to photo in Suhakam inquiry into disappearances&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The public inquiry into the disappearances of Pastor Raymond Koh, Perlis activist Amri Che Mat, Pastor Joshua Hilmi and his wife Ruth Hilmi saw police observers objecting to a photo submitted by Koh's family lawyers. On Nov 3, lawyers had submitted a photo to the panel showing two masked policemen wearing uniforms without the police insignia arresting a suspect during a police operation. They had sought the opinion of investigating officer ASP Supari Muhammad in identifying whether they were policemen in police outfits. On Wednesday however, police observers requested for the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Panel visits site of Pastor Koh's abduction - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/03/panel-visits-site-of-pastor-koh-abduction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBkO48juPHrjcv-7lx27xbAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 09:24:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/03/panel-visits-site-of-pastor-koh-abduction/" target="_blank"&gt;Panel visits site of Pastor Koh's abduction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: A panel of commissioners looking into the disappearances of four people visited the site of Pastor Raymond Koh's abduction in Petaling Jaya on Friday (Nov 3). Also present at the site at about 4.30pm were observers, the police and Pastor Koh's family. Investigating officer ASP Supari Muhammad was on hand to brief the inquiry panel about Koh's abduction. Koh was abducted from his car by a group of men along Jalan SS4B/10 in Petaling Jaya on Feb 13 at about 11am while on his way to a friend's house. At the public inquiry earlier, the panel had made an ad-hoc decision to visit th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Family and friends mark missing Pastor Koh's 63rd birthday - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/02/family-and-friends-mark-missing-pastor-koh-63rd-birthday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAge11EWu2AarN3TqZIjvx0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 08:26:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/02/family-and-friends-mark-missing-pastor-koh-63rd-birthday/" target="_blank"&gt;Family and friends mark missing Pastor Koh's 63rd birthday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The family and friends of missing Pastor Raymond Koh "celebrated" his 63rd birthday which fell on Thursday. They were seen cutting a cake during a session break at a public inquiry by the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) into the disappearance of four people. Pastor Koh's wife Susanna Liew hoped that her husband would be found soon and reunited with his family. "We are sad in a way he's not here but we are hopeful he will be released soon. We pray he will be treated well and will be in good health and strength," she said tearfully. Pastor Koh has been missing for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Investigating officer claims Pastor Koh's family not cooperative - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/02/investigating-officer-claims-pastor-kohs-family-not-cooperative/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEExfvSsqUSnowItgkdRzOkkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 12:40:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/11/02/investigating-officer-claims-pastor-kohs-family-not-cooperative/" target="_blank"&gt;Investigating officer claims Pastor Koh's family not cooperative&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The family of Pastor Raymond Koh has not been cooperative with the police, the case's investigating officer told a public inquiry. ASP Supari Muhammad, who is attached with the Petaling Jaya district police station, said this related to questions on alleged proselytisation of Muslims. He claimed he had asked the family about an episode where Koh had gone away somewhere for four days and that that they did not want to cooperate. "His children and wife just said they didn't know. His wife screamed at me and asked why I am harping on the conversion aspect. "To me, it's not fair ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Ex-IGP: Pastor Koh's abductors could have learnt moves from the movies - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/30/ex-igp-pastor-kohs-abductors-could-have-learnt-moves-from-the-movies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ42UhenOTNbQS99E4Qf7pIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 05:27:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/30/ex-igp-pastor-kohs-abductors-could-have-learnt-moves-from-the-movies/" target="_blank"&gt;Ex-IGP: Pastor Koh's abductors could have learnt moves from the movies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The group who abducted Pastor Raymond Koh could have learnt how to carry out their operation from the movies, says Tan Sri Khalid Abu Bakar. The former Inspector of General of Police was asked at an inquiry on Monday if he thought the abduction was professionally done. "Can see in the movies everyday. Can learn from the movies," he told a public inquiry by Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) into the disappearance of Pastor Koh and three others. However, he agreed with a lawyer from Pastor Koh's family that to a layperson, it could appear to be a highly- organised op...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pastor Koh’s phone signal detected three hours after abduction, inquiry told - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/30/pastor-kohs-phone-signal-detected-three-hours-after-abduction-inquiry-told/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPOuYCSimnoYbtFB9iZe91UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 03:42:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/30/pastor-kohs-phone-signal-detected-three-hours-after-abduction-inquiry-told/" target="_blank"&gt;Pastor Koh’s phone signal detected three hours after abduction, inquiry told&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Pastor Raymond Koh's (pic) mobile phone signal was last detected about three hours after he was abducted, his son Jonathan said on Monday. Jonathan said a “technical officer” from the police had told him that this signal was detected at 2pm at Taman Mayang in Petaling Jaya on Feb 13. The police however did not find anything there, he told a public inquiry by Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) into the disappearance of four people, including Pastor Koh. Jonathan said that on Feb 14, the technical officer sent him CCTV records for his father’s Honda Accord's movement ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Cops may have fumbled in missing pastor case, says ex-IGP - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/31/cops-may-have-fumbled-in-missing-pastor-case-says-exigp/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEhgqddvyf_r8RzqgEwWQB0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/31/cops-may-have-fumbled-in-missing-pastor-case-says-exigp/" target="_blank"&gt;Cops may have fumbled in missing pastor case, says ex-IGP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: There might have been “lapses” by police in their initial investigation into the abduction of Pastor Raymond Koh, said Tan Sri Khalid Abu Bakar. The former Inspector-General of Police was agreeing to points raised by lawyer Gurdial Singh who is representing Koh’s family at a public inquiry by the Human Rights Commission of Malaysia (Suhakam) into the disappearance of the pastor and three other people in separate incidents. One of the points raised by Gurdial was that it was Pastor Koh’s children instead of the police who obtained CCTV recordings of the abduction from the house...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pastor Koh told volunteers not to talk about religion, wife tells inquiry - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/20/pastor-koh-told-volunteers-not-to-talk-about-religion-wife-tells-inquiry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDgdRrYhXadYjXk3TjCxvMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/20/pastor-koh-told-volunteers-not-to-talk-about-religion-wife-tells-inquiry/" target="_blank"&gt;Pastor Koh told volunteers not to talk about religion, wife tells inquiry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The wife of Pastor Raymond Koh claimed that her husband did not allow the preaching of religion to the marginalised communities that he was helping. Suzanne Liew, 61, told an inquiry on Friday (Oct 20) that Koh had told volunteers of a non-profit organisation he founded not to talk about religion. The organisation, Harapan Komuniti, was founded by Koh in 2004 to undertake social and charity work among underprivileged communities. Among others, it runs a reading room in Petaling Jaya, a prison programme with the Prisons Department and works with people living with HIV/Aids. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pastor’s wife recounts incidents before hubby’s disappearance to Suhakam inquiry - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/21/we-were-threatened-and-harassed-pastors-wife-recounts-incidents-before-hubbys-disappearance-to-suhak/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECHg89GBGCDEPzZ5meSNttsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/21/we-were-threatened-and-harassed-pastors-wife-recounts-incidents-before-hubbys-disappearance-to-suhak/" target="_blank"&gt;Pastor’s wife recounts incidents before hubby’s disappearance to Suhakam inquiry&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Pastor Ray­mond Koh (pic) and his family were threatened and harassed following a fund-raising dinner for his non-profit organisation that was raided by the Selangor Islamic Religious Depart­ment in August 2011, a public inquiry heard. His wife Susanna Liew, 61, said that right-wing radical groups, politicians and bloggers had targeted their family, Harapan Komuniti and leaders of the Damansara Utama Methodist Church (in Petaling Jaya) where the dinner was held. Koh had also received an anonymous letter written in red ink and containing two bullets on Aug 26, 2011, she added. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘I thought it was a movie shoot’ - The Star Online</title><link>http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/20/i-thought-it-was-a-movie-shoot-law-student-says-policeman-told-him-abduction-had-police-ops-trademar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELwWOVQ2-An9ITyD3f6we5wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2017/10/20/i-thought-it-was-a-movie-shoot-law-student-says-policeman-told-him-abduction-had-police-ops-trademar/" target="_blank"&gt;‘I thought it was a movie shoot’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: When Roeshan Celestine Gomez stumbled across the abduction of Pastor Raymond Koh on Feb 13, he thought it was a movie shoot. But when he realised there were no cameras around, the 25-year-old chambering student knew something was not right. The incident happened as Gomez and his friend were on their way to a crematorium for a funeral. After the cremation, Gomez called the Kelana Jaya police station to tell them about what he had seen. A police officer told him to make a report, which Roshan did at the station. Gomez also claimed that the investigating officer told him the inc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item></channel></rss>