<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Goods and Services Tax - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZqTlRZNU9UbDZkaElDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-MY&amp;gl=MY&amp;ceid=MY:en</link><language>en-MY</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:11:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Audit report shows two companies exempted from paying GST but allowed to claim refunds - New Straits Times</title><link>https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/436812/audit-report-shows-two-companies-exempted-paying-gst-allowed-claim</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI4oM0oDqryNpCX2k6Ony8UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow9sveCjC0m9YBMJHSoQM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 08:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/436812/audit-report-shows-two-companies-exempted-paying-gst-allowed-claim" target="_blank"&gt;Audit report shows two companies exempted from paying GST but allowed to claim refunds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The National Audit Department has discovered that two companies were exempted by the Ministry of Finance from paying the Goods and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nst.com.my">New Straits Times</source></item><item><title>PAC wraps up probe on GST repayment fund - Free Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/14/pac-wraps-up-probe-on-gst-repayment-fund/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiZmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZyZWVtYWxheXNpYXRvZGF5LmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yeS9uYXRpb24vMjAxOC8xMS8xNC9wYWMtd3JhcHMtdXAtcHJvYmUtb24tZ3N0LXJlcGF5bWVudC1mdW5kL9IBAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/nation/2018/11/14/pac-wraps-up-probe-on-gst-repayment-fund/" target="_blank"&gt;PAC wraps up probe on GST repayment fund&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Free Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Public Accounts Committee (PAC) has completed its investigative proceedings on the controversial loss of the goods and services tax ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.freemalaysiatoday.com">Free Malaysia Today</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/k2x97A59BIwPkw1BIEqfCjVzulIvMfuaBDVwd4-5h4yTR5jpCJ55RVOxwXCVeXrXG9EBhU6ML8piHHQyBN5pfaK9WAjLkR81R0U04CvpN9GGIpmwJnGtQ1vx6EfmqaffyHcNxHP0UWvrFoeyIzcK_rQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>BN govt failed to pay GST refunds to 121429 firms, individuals, says Guan Eng - The Malaysian Insight</title><link>https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/116808</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780129465098</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 06:51:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com/s/116808" target="_blank"&gt;BN govt failed to pay GST refunds to 121429 firms, individuals, says Guan Eng&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Malaysian Insight&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/12/438279/bn-govt-failed-reimburse-rm1947-billion-gst-refunds" target="_blank"&gt;BN govt failed to reimburse RM19.47 billion in GST refunds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/12/07/rm19pt47b-in-gst-refund-not-paid-to-121429-individuals-companies/" target="_blank"&gt;RM19.47b in GST refund not paid to 121,429 individuals, companies - Business News&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thesundaily.my/local/rm19-47b-in-gst-refund-not-paid-to-121-429-individuals-companies-LH229195" target="_blank"&gt;Rm19.47b in GST refund not paid to 121,429 individuals, companies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Sun Daily&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWlLNXZpbWpZQU1FWWcxR0pCeTJITF9LQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.themalaysianinsight.com">The Malaysian Insight</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/A7FjvDq_bIe23F-C6-IsgppYgvClhtinVG9L513egkcaNAOx2DLzmwIyPjYZGve-ZdwgeGOxmhdv2yxcfv3fIy-cFm4igTbkNElQm0AGLmDLlVdhu_zQBnuxQUVjF06YcTEb6ymXs6nOJ_a5rcmkLBmQXeIQs5_vRnbXtCNNLMvqEg=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Guan Eng: Government will honour GST refund payments - New Straits Times</title><link>https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/431443/guan-eng-government-will-honour-gst-refund-payments</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ44DB93MMCeqr030LQbPGwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow9sveCjC0m9YBMJHSoQM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nst.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/431443/guan-eng-government-will-honour-gst-refund-payments" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng: Government will honour GST refund payments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Straits Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng has given his assurance that the government will honour outstanding Goods and Services Tax refund ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nst.com.my">New Straits Times</source></item><item><title>RM19.47b in GST refunds not paid to 121,429 individuals, companies - Malaysiakini</title><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPBbKmB_DxjNye-TpK4f9ZMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowt5HeCjDXqdUBMPOetgM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:23:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysiakini&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The former government failed to reimburse RM19.47 billion in goods and services tax (GST) refunds to 121,429 companies and individuals, says Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng. He said under Section 54 of the GST Act 2014, the monies collected must be deposited into the GST Trust Fund to enable reimbursements. “Unfortunately, the former government did not do this and the entire amount was instead deposited directly into the Consolidated Fund Account, contravening the GST Act,” said Lim in a statement, adding that the Customs Department confirmed that an audit on the GST refund claims of RM19.47 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>SST trumps GST, Dr M tells why - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/28/sst-trumps-gst-dr-m-tells-why/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP6kwiuhWv-AcSo2UX7br9wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 02:07:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/28/sst-trumps-gst-dr-m-tells-why/" target="_blank"&gt;SST trumps GST, Dr M tells why&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – Dr Mahathir Mohamad has defended the decision to revert to the sales and services tax (SST) some eight months after the goods and services tax (GST) was abolished, despite complaints that the move has not succeeded in bringing down prices. Speaking on a wide range of topics in an exclusive interview with FMT recently, the prime minister said the cost of living was connected to wages. “It is easy to bring up the cost of living. All we have to do is pay higher salaries. Immediately the cost of production goes up, the cost of services goes up,” he said, when told that prices of daily i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng chides Najib for his 'denial syndrome' over missing RM19.4bil GST refunds - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/21/guan-eng-chides-najib-for-his-denial-syndrome-over-missing-gst-refunds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGITgzLLMihB7yY8xeCurlUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 13:04:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/21/guan-eng-chides-najib-for-his-denial-syndrome-over-missing-gst-refunds/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng chides Najib for his 'denial syndrome' over missing RM19.4bil GST refunds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng and former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak engaged in a heated argument in Parliament today (Nov 21) over the missing RM19.4bil Goods and Services Tax (GST) refund. Najib claimed that the money was not missing and the figure given by Lim emerged because the new Pakatan Harapan federal government had decided to abolish the GST. "The GST refund is supposed to be between RM7bil to RM8bil. "But because the Government abolished GST, of course so many people came forward to claim refunds," claimed Najib. Lim chided Najib, saying he was suffering from "denia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>PAC completes probe on 'missing' RM19.4bil GST refunds - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/14/pac-completes-probe-on-missing-rm194bil-gst-refunds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFgxheU8UeHpW6oUmpyZe54qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 09:19:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/14/pac-completes-probe-on-missing-rm194bil-gst-refunds/" target="_blank"&gt;PAC completes probe on 'missing' RM19.4bil GST refunds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Public Accounts Committee (PAC) has wrapped up its investigations into the "missing" RM19.4bil Goods and Services Tax (GST) credit refunds. Its chairman Datuk Seri Dr Ronald Kiandee (pic) said the committee had finished its probe after calling its final witness, Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng. "We will be holding another meeting to make a final report before tabling it in Parliament," he told reporters at the Parliament lobby after chairing the meeting on Wednesday (Nov 14). Asked if there were any wrongdoings detected, Dr Kiandee said he cannot pre-empt the conclusion of t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Khairy unveils BN's shadow budget, proposes to bring back GST at 3% - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/01/khairy-unveils-shadow-budget-proposes-return-of-gst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFB2lVgUjXvJfG5rELHxl64qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 09:06:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/01/khairy-unveils-shadow-budget-proposes-return-of-gst/" target="_blank"&gt;Khairy unveils BN's shadow budget, proposes to bring back GST at 3%&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Barisan Nasional has unveiled its first "shadow budget", with a proposal to re-introduce the Goods and Services Tax (GST) at 3% being the key element. Rembau MP Khairy Jamaluddin, who holds the shadow Finance Ministry portfolio, said the alternative budget titled People's Economic Initiative, seeks to reintroduce the GST, among others because the Sales and Service Tax (SST) had failed to bring down prices of basic goods and items. "We need a more efficient and transparent taxing system and we will bring back GST but lower it to 3%," he said when unveiling it during a press con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Govt needs to find new revenue to address GST removal, says bank - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/03/govt-needs-to-find-new-revenue-to-address-gst-removal-says-bank/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEETeQMMgx5Rcx5X_NeKGYzAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 10:49:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/11/03/govt-needs-to-find-new-revenue-to-address-gst-removal-says-bank/" target="_blank"&gt;Govt needs to find new revenue to address GST removal, says bank&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – The Budget 2019 shows a lack of sustainable revenue measures being proposed to address the shortfall in revenue after the goods and services tax (GST) was replaced with the sales and service tax (SST), according to Standard Chartered (StanChart). It said expenditure rationalisation and leveraging of assets are short-term measures. The leveraging of assets includes raising RM4 billion from selling a 30% stake of the Airport Real Estate Investment Trust that the government intends to set up. In the more immediate term, the government may still have to find new revenue measures to addr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>SST and its impact on Budget 2019 - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/11/02/sst-and-its-impact-on-budget-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA-XVfxmYzneglitU4NiDWQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/11/02/sst-and-its-impact-on-budget-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;SST and its impact on Budget 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT is now almost two months since the heavily debated Sales Tax and Service Tax (SST) was reintroduced in Malaysia. The new tax regime replaces the goods and services tax (GST) after just three years of its launch, and is touted as a friendlier and more painless tax system for the rakyat. The key difference between the SST and its predecessor is that SST is a single-stage tax regime unlike the GST that is a multi-stage tax and the full tax burden is shouldered by the end consumer (rakyat). Under the new tax system, goods/services are only taxed once at the importer, manufacturer or service ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Pakatan leaders unimpressed with BN's shadow budget, say GST is a non-issue - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/01/pakatan-leaders-unimpressed-with-bns-shadow-budget/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEPPFF49qCEGMk0Y4t07r3gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 12:56:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/11/01/pakatan-leaders-unimpressed-with-bns-shadow-budget/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan leaders unimpressed with BN's shadow budget, say GST is a non-issue&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Pakatan Harapan leaders are unfazed over Barisan Nasional's "shadow budget" which boasts a proposal to reintroduce the Goods and Services Tax (GST) at 3%, saying the previous government had more than 60 years to bring beneficial policies to Malaysians. Economics Affairs Minister Datuk Seri Mohamed Azmin Ali said that the proposal to reintroduce the GST is no longer an issue, as it has been replaced by the Sales and Service Tax (SST) by the Pakatan government. "If Barisan wants to put forward its manifesto or its proposals, it's entirely up to Malaysians whether they want to ac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>PAC expects to wind up missing GST refund proceedings by December - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/23/pac-expects-to-wind-up-missing-gst-refund-proceedings-by-december/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOE4d_vF5XhbfJ0uicqUavMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 04:39:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/23/pac-expects-to-wind-up-missing-gst-refund-proceedings-by-december/" target="_blank"&gt;PAC expects to wind up missing GST refund proceedings by December&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Parliament's Public Accounts Committee (PAC) expects to wind up its proceedings with regard to the "missing" RM19.4bil Goods and Services Tax (GST) credit returns by the end of Parliament sessions in December. PAC chairman Datuk Seri Ronald Kiandee said after Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng, who is the last witness to be called on Oct 30, the committee will wind up the case and present the outcome in Parliament. "We hope we will wind up this case before the end of this Parliament meeting," Kiandee told reporters, after former Treasury secretary-general Tan Sri Mohd Irwan Ser...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>PAC: Najib may be recalled over RM19.4bil input tax credit - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/pac-najib-may-be-recalled-over-rm194bil-input-tax-credit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3VQCmwu_F6ww1zRdaBXzoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/25/pac-najib-may-be-recalled-over-rm194bil-input-tax-credit/" target="_blank"&gt;PAC: Najib may be recalled over RM19.4bil input tax credit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Public Accounts Committee chairman Datuk Seri Dr Ronald Kiandee says former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak may be recalled over the RM19.4bil input tax credit under the Goods and Services Tax (GST). He told reporters after chairing the meeting in Parliament that at this point, PAC could not determine whether he would be recalled. “But we will refer back on whether there is a necessity to do so and if need be, we will call him back,” said Kiandee. Former Treasury secretary-general Tan Sri Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah and Customs Department director-general Datuk Seri ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>4 million general Insurance policy holders affected by SST - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/10/26/insurance-policy-holders-affected-by-sst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENipTyPK9YRQtIkhM3B6Om8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 11:58:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/10/26/insurance-policy-holders-affected-by-sst/" target="_blank"&gt;4 million general Insurance policy holders affected by SST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: About four million general insurance policy holders who renewed or purchased their policies during the Goods and Services Tax (GST) tax-holiday period will be affected by the Sales and Services Tax (SST) regime, says the General Insurance Association of Malaysia (PIAM). Deputy Chairman Chua Seck Guan said affected policy members included those who purchased or renewed their motor, fire or personal accident insurance during the zero-rated GST period from June to August. “When they purchased or renewed their policies during the tax holiday, they made a lump-sum payment for 12 mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib, Irwan to appear before PAC next week over 'missing' RM19.6bil GST refunds - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/17/najib-irwan-to-appear-before-pac-next-week-over-missing-gst-refunds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEISkUCN3w7H0i8XzXfFtrg0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 02:20:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/17/najib-irwan-to-appear-before-pac-next-week-over-missing-gst-refunds/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib, Irwan to appear before PAC next week over 'missing' RM19.6bil GST refunds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak (pic) and former Treasury secretary-general Tan Sri Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah will be asked to testify before Parliament's Public Accounts Committee (PAC) next week. Its head Datuk Seri Dr Ronald Kiandee confirmed that the duo was slated to appear before the committee with regard to the "missing" RM19.4bil Goods and Services Tax (GST) credit returns. According to a PAC media statement on Oct 16, Irwan will testify on Oct 23, while Najib will do so on Oct 24. Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng will also appear before the committee o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Vehicle sales skid in September as reality bites after GST tax holiday - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/10/15/vehicle-sales-skid-in-september-as-reality-bites-after-gst-tax-holiday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN5sILqC4CWLBl_Ep4fxGjAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 09:14:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/10/15/vehicle-sales-skid-in-september-as-reality-bites-after-gst-tax-holiday/" target="_blank"&gt;Vehicle sales skid in September as reality bites after GST tax holiday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Vehicle sales fell in September after the Goods and Services Tax (GST) tax holiday ended on Aug 31 while stocks of some vehicle distributors were depleted, according to the Malaysian Automotive Association (MAA). It said on Monday sales volume in September fell 23% or 9,715 units from a year ago to 31,241 units. They comprise of 27,022 passenger vehicles and 4,219 commercial vehicles. “Sales volume in September 2018 were depleted following the overwhelming demand during the GST tax holiday period,” it added. The MMA said the total industry vehicles (TIV) from January to Septem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib slams Finance Ministry over contradictory SST statements - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/16/najib-slams-finance-ministry-over-contradictory-sst-statements/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL7NaEFpZ0ug3kVbyWKY-nkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 04:36:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/10/16/najib-slams-finance-ministry-over-contradictory-sst-statements/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib slams Finance Ministry over contradictory SST statements&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Pekan MP Datuk Seri Najib Razak (pic) has taken a jab at the Finance Ministry over its contradictory statements on the Sales and Service Tax (SST). In a Facebook post on Tuesday (Oct 16), Najib highlighted previous news reports quoting the political secretary to the Finance Minister, Tony Pua, as saying that SST would reduce the prices of goods. Najib pointed out that Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng had on Monday (Oct 15) denied this, saying that prices of goods would come down once the Goods and Services Tax (GST) was replaced with the SST. “Their communication strategy is gre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Australia scraps controversial tampon tax - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/10/03/australia/australia-tampon-tax-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDq3eRRzCyZkFPdcWgXdLUUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 04:57:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/10/03/australia/australia-tampon-tax-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Australia scraps controversial tampon tax&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia is to scrap a controversial tampon tax bringing an end to an 18-year campaign to make feminine sanitary products exempt from a nationwide Goods and Services Tax (GST). The move follows a landmark vote in the country's Senate to remove the 10% tax on tampons and pads, items previously marked "non-essential" despite being required by most women on a monthly basis. On Wednesday, lawmakers from each state and territory unanimously agreed to adopt federal proposals in a move supported by both major political parties. Though the details have yet to be finalized, the ABC reports that pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Why prices are still high - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2018/10/02/why-prices-are-still-high/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHnU8C2SluQiZHBb3RR8_TMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMMPNpgM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/opinion/letters/2018/10/02/why-prices-are-still-high/" target="_blank"&gt;Why prices are still high&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OIL exporting countries should be happy with the current level and outlook for crude petroleum prices. From a low of around US$30 per barrel just two years ago, prices have climbed steadily, reaching highs of about US$80 per barrel. Malaysia should benefit as crude oil is one of our main exports. It is much needed as the Goods and Services Tax (GST) has been replaced with the purportedly “cheaper” Sales and Service (SST) to fulfil an electoral promise. Consequentially, the state coffers are expected to be reduced by about RM21bil. Against this backdrop, the man on the street is a bit confus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng urges restaurants and coffee shops to reduce 10% service charge - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/22/guan-eng-urges-restaurants-and-coffee-shops-to-reduce-10pc-service-charge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP5sXUsKIbHoBKjoOKx0-tkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 14:56:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/22/guan-eng-urges-restaurants-and-coffee-shops-to-reduce-10pc-service-charge/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng urges restaurants and coffee shops to reduce 10% service charge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GEORGE TOWN: Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng is urging restaurants and coffee shops imposing a 10% service charge to be "reasonable" and reduce it, as it is quite high. "Service charge is collected by the restaurants and coffee shops for their employees, so they can pay them better salaries. "Previously service charge was also taxed with Goods and Services Tax (GST) but now no longer since we imposed Sales and Services Tax (SST). "We have made many changes to make it easier for restaurants and coffee shops so the impact of SST is lesser on them," he said during a press conference held after c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>India eyes relief package for struggling airlines - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d62bbeec-bcab-11e8-94b2-17176fbf93f5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGGQ4M-qzWiY3Q-e8x9tRdAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 15:58:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d62bbeec-bcab-11e8-94b2-17176fbf93f5" target="_blank"&gt;India eyes relief package for struggling airlines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ministers in New Delhi are pushing for a package of relief measures to help India’s ailing airlines, which are struggling to cope with a sharp rise in oil prices and a collapse in the rupee. The country’s domestic aviation market has been growing more quickly than any in the world for the past few years, but airline profits have dropped off in the past six months because of higher fuel prices. With Jet Airways, the country’s second-largest airline, already in significant financial difficulty, the government is pushing for measures to help control costs and make it easier to secure funding...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Najib asks Guan Eng: Will there be an SST song to follow your GST tune? - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/22/najib-asks-guan-eng-will-there-be-an-sst-song-to-follow-your-gst-tune/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJJSuz6eg5H9Mtpw77zW_XkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 06:44:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/22/najib-asks-guan-eng-will-there-be-an-sst-song-to-follow-your-gst-tune/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib asks Guan Eng: Will there be an SST song to follow your GST tune?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak has sarcastically asked Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng if he will be doing a song about the Sales and Service Tax (SST). The former prime minister said Lim had in the past blamed the Goods and Services Tax (GST) for the rising cost of living and even sang a song about it at an event attended by children. "Now he is saying that the prices of goods are not rising because of SST, but because of other factors. "Maybe there will be a song about the SST after this?" Najib said on Facebook on Saturday (Sep 22). His post was in response to reports quoting Li...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Report less than RM1.5 million sales to escape paying SST - Malaysia Today</title><link>https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/12/report-less-than-rm1-5-million-sales-to-escape-paying-sst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOsHhwHpVqZ5SYIfsGrSWokqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 09:03:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/12/report-less-than-rm1-5-million-sales-to-escape-paying-sst/" target="_blank"&gt;Report less than RM1.5 million sales to escape paying SST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – The Sales and Services Tax (SST) will not be imposed on 75 per cent of shops and restaurants after the threshold for the tax was raised to RM1.5 million yearly revenue from RM500,000 under the Goods and Services Tax (GST), Lim Guan Eng said today. The finance minister pointed out that only 4,372 restaurants were registered under SST compared to 15,574 under GST. “Isn’t the impact of SST far less than the GST since only 25 per cent of restaurants and coffee shops are affected by the SST compared to the GST?” Lim said in a statement. Among the goods that are cheaper under the SST are ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>India's tax effect: Hundreds of thousands laid off despite growth - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-tax-insight/indias-tax-effect-hundreds-of-thousands-laid-off-despite-growth-idUSKCN1LL374</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED1lokTqyjMdvjSfcEH4GcEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 23:48:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-tax-insight/indias-tax-effect-hundreds-of-thousands-laid-off-despite-growth-idUSKCN1LL374" target="_blank"&gt;India's tax effect: Hundreds of thousands laid off despite growth&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tilak Raj Bathla's tiny weaving factory is one of the few still humming on a once busy road in the northern Indian city of Panipat, known as the country's "textile city". Nearby, more than two dozen other workshops are locked from the outside, while dogs and cows roam through other abandoned factories. Scrap dealers enquire about idle powerlooms. India launched the Goods and Services Tax (GST) just over a year ago, its biggest ever tax reform, aiming to replace more than a dozen federal and state levies and unify the sprawling economy. The move improved economic efficiency but critics say t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Business operators uncertain about effects of SST - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/09/13/business-operators-uncertain-about-effects-of-sst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKOuC0OF1-JajDDoidtypAsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/09/13/business-operators-uncertain-about-effects-of-sst/" target="_blank"&gt;Business operators uncertain about effects of SST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BATU PAHAT: Local businesses have welcomed the return of Sales and Service Tax (SST) but are still uncertain how it will affect their businesses. The SST came into effect on Sept 1, following the abolition of GST. The new tax system imposes a tax of five to 10% on the sale of goods and six percent on services. Sundry shop co-owner Koo Siew Lan, 45, said although SST was implemented before, he was unsure how the market will react to it this time around. “I believe it will be able to improve the market flow but there is no guarantee as so much has changed in recent years. “For now, we can onl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Prices of five car models drop after SST, says Guan Eng - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/11/prices-of-five-car-models-drop-after-sst-says-guan-eng/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECnodd932ELf8feCvvJDSScqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 10:17:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/11/prices-of-five-car-models-drop-after-sst-says-guan-eng/" target="_blank"&gt;Prices of five car models drop after SST, says Guan Eng&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GEORGE TOWN (Bernama): Several makes of cars including imported ones recorded a price reduction of up to RM3,000 after the implementation of the Sales and Service Tax (SST), said Lim Guan Eng. The Finance Minister, when announcing the matter, said the five makes were Perodua, Honda, Toyota, BMW and Volkswagen. "I have received information that several makes of cars whose prices when compared to the Goods and Services Tax (GST) are much lower. “This is because we don't collect as much (tax) compared with the GST, the prices of goods can be flexible and it is also adopted by the government to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Factbox: Over 200 tweaks in India's biggest tax reform create confusion - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-tax-factbox/factbox-over-200-tweaks-in-indias-biggest-tax-reform-create-confusion-idUSKCN1LL37F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBiGmz9FuLygqV7gDTVfyHUqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 23:48:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-election-tax-factbox/factbox-over-200-tweaks-in-indias-biggest-tax-reform-create-confusion-idUSKCN1LL37F" target="_blank"&gt;Factbox: Over 200 tweaks in India's biggest tax reform create confusion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;India introduced a new national Goods and Services Tax (GST) in July last year, aiming to unify its $2.6 trillion economy and 1.3 billion people into a single market for the first time. After 14 months, small businesses are struggling to keep up with over 200 tweaks in the tax system. Below is a description of the tax and some of the major changes: WHAT IS IT The GST replaced more than a dozen central and state tariffs, duties and fees levied - often at different rates across India's 29 states - into a single tax. All goods and services have been put into one of five tax brackets ranging fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Lim slams Najib's remark on paying sales and services tax for 'kuih pau' - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/11/lim-slams-najibs-remark-on-paying-sales-and-services-tax-for-kuih-pau/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaFTzW2-42d1gQUWuVQRWsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 23:53:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/11/lim-slams-najibs-remark-on-paying-sales-and-services-tax-for-kuih-pau/" target="_blank"&gt;Lim slams Najib's remark on paying sales and services tax for 'kuih pau'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;GEORGE TOWN (Bernama): Malaysia's Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng on Monday (Sept 10) lambasted former Prime Minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak who disputed the implementation of the Sales and Services Tax (SST). Lim noted that when the Barisan Nasional (BN) government implemented the Goods and Services Tax (GST), Najib did not hear the grumblings from the people who had to pay tax for every product. However, after the implementation of the SST, the Pekan Member of Parliament had started to complain. "I'm astonished, when he (Najib) charged GST last time, he didn't complain. At that time (GS...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>The pau-wow continues: Why am I charged SST if I am a consumer, asks Najib - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/11/the-pauwow-continues-why-am-i-charged-sst-if-i-am-a-consumer-asks-najib/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGikMN6lKslvRpgMTIOcqRAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 07:43:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/09/11/the-pauwow-continues-why-am-i-charged-sst-if-i-am-a-consumer-asks-najib/" target="_blank"&gt;The pau-wow continues: Why am I charged SST if I am a consumer, asks Najib&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak has hit out at Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng’s remarks dismissing concerns over the Sales and Service Tax (SST) charged at a shop selling steamed buns or “pau”. In a Facebook post on Tuesday (Sept 11), Najib showed a picture of his receipt from the pau shop and questioned why he had been charged SST when he is a consumer. “Didn’t Guan Eng say a few times that the SST would only be imposed upon manufacturers and not consumers? “I’m not a manufacturer, so why I am being charged the 6% tax?” he said. Najib also questioned why the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Perodua cars are 1-3% cheaper with SST re-introduction - Carsifu</title><link>https://www.carsifu.my/news/perodua-prices-slashed-between-1-3-with-sst-reintroduction</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDd1cg0Ibk_fzvadpDZLK3oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowmN_eCjDJ09YBMIHXpgM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 05:21:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.carsifu.my/news/perodua-prices-slashed-between-1-3-with-sst-reintroduction" target="_blank"&gt;Perodua cars are 1-3% cheaper with SST re-introduction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Carsifu&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: In line with the government’s re-introduction of the Sales and Service Tax (SST) effective Sept 1, 2018 Perodua has released new prices for all its models, which have been reduced between 1% – 3% compared with Goods and Services Tax (GST)-era pricing. “Based on the new tax structure, almost all Perodua models see price reductions compared to the GST price structure,” said Perodua Sales Sdn Bhd Managing Director Datuk Dr Zahari Husin. To recap, the government zeroed the GST rate (from 6%) on 1 June 2018, opening up a ‘tax holiday’ and a spike in vehicle demand that lasted thre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.carsifu.my">Carsifu</source></item><item><title>Tony Pua speech in Parliament: prices will come down once the GST is replaced with the SST - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/01/tony-pua-speech-in-parliament-prices-will-come-down-once-the-gst-is-replaced-with-the-sst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMn52w6q5NoeyjLHhS99SIcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNr8nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 07:32:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/09/01/tony-pua-speech-in-parliament-prices-will-come-down-once-the-gst-is-replaced-with-the-sst/" target="_blank"&gt;Tony Pua speech in Parliament: prices will come down once the GST is replaced with the SST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Talk to educate public and traders on SST - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/09/03/talk-to-educate-public-and-traders-on-sst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPRO26BUAsBh5f2HcJ7N6AAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/09/03/talk-to-educate-public-and-traders-on-sst/" target="_blank"&gt;Talk to educate public and traders on SST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;SIBU: Sibu DAP will hold a talk on the Sales and Services Tax (SST) to educate the public and businessmen. Its chairman Oscar Ling said the public had been misled by the Opposition that claimed SST would cause more inflation than the Goods and Services Tax (GST). He added that under SST, the government would be collecting only RM21bil in tax compared to RM42.7bil per year from GST. “Businesses registered under SST only number 80,000 compared to 540,000 under GST. “The consumer benefits under the SST as the government will collect less tax,” he added. Ling, who is also Sibu MP, said the aim ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>SST sets in, car makers start releasing new prices - Carsifu</title><link>https://www.carsifu.my/news/sst-sets-in-car-makers-start-releasing-new-prices</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBn9cfzXNI-FhRjHTLmUsyMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowmN_eCjDJ09YBMIHXpgM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 07:42:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.carsifu.my/news/sst-sets-in-car-makers-start-releasing-new-prices" target="_blank"&gt;SST sets in, car makers start releasing new prices&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Carsifu&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Perodua, Honda Malaysia and Volkswagen are the early birds to announce their new pricing following the return of the Sales and Services Tax on Sept 1. The new pricing adds on the 10% sales tax for vehicles. The SST replaces the Goods and Services Tax (GST). The updated prices are shown in a separate list. Honda Honda’s Completely Knocked Down (CKD) models namely Jazz, BR-V, City, Civic, CR-V and Accord will be priced ranging from RM70,242 to RM169,398. Prices of its Completely Built Unit (CBU) models such as the Odyssey and Civic Type R will be priced at RM258,896 and RM330,0...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.carsifu.my">Carsifu</source></item><item><title>Lim: SST will ease people’s burden - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/31/lim-sst-will-ease-peoples-burden-govt-will-earn-less-revenue-but-people-come-first/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJJlCOj94ZCcDdAr8p1bPIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/31/lim-sst-will-ease-peoples-burden-govt-will-earn-less-revenue-but-people-come-first/" target="_blank"&gt;Lim: SST will ease people’s burden&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The reintroduction of the Sales and Service Tax (SST) to replace the Goods and Services Tax (GST) is meant to ease the people’s burden, says Lim Guan Eng. The Finance Minister said although it would mean less revenue for the government, it was more important that the people’s welfare was taken care of. “When the government made the decision to replace the GST with the SST, it is because we have the people’s well-being as a priority. “We put the people’s well-being before collecting higher revenue from taxes. In other words, ensuring that the people are less burdened is more impor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>JTI to raise cigarette prices post-SST - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/31/jti-to-raise-cigarette-prices-postsst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEoJu3EWfpzYP1irqeAWa-0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/31/jti-to-raise-cigarette-prices-postsst/" target="_blank"&gt;JTI to raise cigarette prices post-SST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: JT International Bhd (JTI), the maker of Mevius and Winston cigarette brands, says it will increase the selling prices of its products due to the higher sales tax effective Sept 1. “The introduction of sales tax at 10% for tobacco products in Malaysia translates to a price increase for all our cigarette brands, taking into account the incremental rate differential from the previous goods and services tax (GST) rates levied on cigarettes,” managing director Cormac O’Rourke said in a statement. Cigarette prices had not been revised post-June 2018 zero-rating of GST following dir...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Total of 5,445 consumer goods to be exempted from SST - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/30/total-of-5445-consumer-goods-to-be-exempted-from-sst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC4Z29-DGnIK0gA-AW3c0RMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 03:42:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/30/total-of-5445-consumer-goods-to-be-exempted-from-sst/" target="_blank"&gt;Total of 5,445 consumer goods to be exempted from SST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PUTRAJAYA: The number of consumer goods to be exempted from the sales tax is 10 times the number of goods that were exempted from the now-repealed Goods and Services Tax (GST). A total of 5,443 consumer items have been exempted from the sales tax that is set at 5% or 10%. Only 545 consumer items were exempted from GST when it was introduced in 2015. Customs Department deputy director-general Datuk Seri Subromaniam Tholasy revealed the list of items that would be exempted from the Sales and Services Tax (SST) during a briefing with the media on Thursday (Aug 30). Among the items that will no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>RM19.25b shortfall: Only Finance Minister has power to approve: LGE - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/27/rm19-25b-shortfall-only-finance-minister-has-power-to-approve-lge/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIKhqzwqA8aMSJSgVI6WlWcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 04:08:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/27/rm19-25b-shortfall-only-finance-minister-has-power-to-approve-lge/" target="_blank"&gt;RM19.25b shortfall: Only Finance Minister has power to approve: LGE&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng today said that former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Abdul Razak had the power to approve the decision not to transfer RM19.25 billion to the Goods and Services Tax (GST) Refunds Trust Account. (The Sun Daily) – He said if Najib, who was the then Finance Minister, did not give approval for the money not to be transferred to the GST Refunds Trust Account, then the former Treasury secretary-general Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah should be held responsible for all the alleged offences. “Not only for the alleged criminal breach of trust, but also for abus...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Service tax to be imposed on general insurance products - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/28/service-tax-to-be-imposed-on-general-insurance-products/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBTA0fzzIgtSog_tx6HbGoYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/28/service-tax-to-be-imposed-on-general-insurance-products/" target="_blank"&gt;Service tax to be imposed on general insurance products&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: General insurance products will be subject to service tax following the recent passing of the Service Tax Bill in Parliament, said the General Insurance Association of Malaysia (PIAM). The tax would be applicable to individuals who purchase general insurance policies except for medical policies. “Consumers who purchase or renew their general insurance policies on or after Sept 1, 2018 will be charged a service tax at 6% on their premium. “Policies bought prior that span the tax holiday period, that is from June to August and continuing after September will need to have service...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng finally admits the country is not going bankrupt after all - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/21/guan-eng-finally-admits-the-country-is-not-going-bankrupt-after-all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKyTHoEIQrtbmNmjQT2J7WwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 16:27:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/21/guan-eng-finally-admits-the-country-is-not-going-bankrupt-after-all/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng finally admits the country is not going bankrupt after all&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – The abolition of the Goods and Services Tax (GST) by the new government did not cause the country to go bankrupt but has in fact been able to survive so far, said Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng. “Although the new government has abolished the GST, so far Malaysia has not become a bankrupt. We can still hang on, it proves that we can survive without GST,” he said when winding up the debate on the 2018 Goods and Services Tax (Repeal) Bill in the Dewan Negara today.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Najib says LGE smart not to lodge report, wants RCI on IRB, GST allegations - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/24/najib-says-lge-smart-not-to-lodge-report-wants-rci-on-irb-gst-allegations/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFcQb6Ckqvn3V5CKcTvJmeAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 04:25:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/24/najib-says-lge-smart-not-to-lodge-report-wants-rci-on-irb-gst-allegations/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib says LGE smart not to lodge report, wants RCI on IRB, GST allegations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;He (Lim) did not even lodge the report himself based on his allegations that Barisan had robbed RM18bil of GST funds during a parliament session, as it grants him immunity. (The Star) – The Pakatan Harapan Government should form a Royal Commission of Inquiry (RCI) for the alleged RM35bil shortfall in refunds for income tax and Goods and Services Tax (GST), says Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak. The former premier said this was necessary to ascertain whether the previous Barisan Nasional government, Customs Department and the Inland Revenue Board (IRB) had committed criminal breach of trust (CBT) ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>What Guan Eng should do about RM19.4b GST ‘robbery’ - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/16/what-guan-eng-should-do-about-rm19-4b-gst-robbery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOyKF47JgxJSB_lux9Gf1hMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 07:33:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/16/what-guan-eng-should-do-about-rm19-4b-gst-robbery/" target="_blank"&gt;What Guan Eng should do about RM19.4b GST ‘robbery’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;P. Gunasegaram, Malaysiakini The first thing that Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng should do is to establish whether there was a robbery or not from payments of the goods and services tax or GST to the government. As I pointed out in this article, it is not a robbery if funds were merely moved from one government account into another. That’s plain common sense and cannot be disputed. It only becomes a robbery if it was embezzled from one or both of the accounts. The two relevant accounts are the trust account into which GST refunds are made and the government’s consolidated revenue account int...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>A challenging year of 2019 awaits all Malaysians - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/23/a-challenging-year-of-2019-awaits-all-malaysians/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIZfy9G95x0W74FWn0bOoXgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/23/a-challenging-year-of-2019-awaits-all-malaysians/" target="_blank"&gt;A challenging year of 2019 awaits all Malaysians&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The government will start 2019 with a whopping RM35bil shortfall because refunds for income tax and GST will have to be paid off next year. It is also going to be a challenging year with a lower tax revenue due to the reintroduction of Sales and Services Tax (SST), amid expectation of a slower economic growth. On Wednesday, the Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng dropped another bombshell, claiming that the previous Barisan Nasional government has not refunded a total of RM16.046bil of excess income tax and real property gains tax to taxpayers. The RM16.046bil is on top of the RM19...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng drops another GST bombshell: Missing amount is larger - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/13/guan-eng-drops-another-gst-bombshell-missing-amount-is-larger/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDgnijwdKmH6bCDiz4BCjEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 06:39:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/13/guan-eng-drops-another-gst-bombshell-missing-amount-is-larger/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng drops another GST bombshell: Missing amount is larger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – The previous amount that he revealed was not the actual total, owing a mistake by a ministry officer who misplaced a decimal point. Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng has not only stood by his allegations that the previous government had falsified the Goods and Services Tax (GST) credit refund, but claims that the missing amount was even larger than he had declared in Parliament last week. “The actual amount of shortfall in the fund for unpaid GST input tax is RM19.248bil, and not RM17.911bil which I had reported to the House last week,” Lim said in Parliament on Monday (Aug 13). Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Is Guan Eng lying about RM18 billion ‘robbery’? - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/14/is-guan-eng-lying-about-rm18-billion-robbery/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOfaxzaf8b8HgBriCj6l1TQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInmnwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 05:23:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/14/is-guan-eng-lying-about-rm18-billion-robbery/" target="_blank"&gt;Is Guan Eng lying about RM18 billion ‘robbery’?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;P Gunasegaram, Malaysiakini Another shocking accusation has been hurled against the previous BN government by Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng in Parliament on Aug 8, alleging the government robbed from GST refunds, not long after he accused it of having run the national debt up to over RM1 trillion instead of the officially announced RM687 billion. “I want to say here, it was not robbing GST, but robbing from GST refunds,” Lim thundered in the Dewan Rakyat when winding up debate on the Sales Tax Bill 2018 on Aug 8. “This is a serious robbery where money which was supposed to be in trust funds...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>SST may hike cost of doing business for several sectors - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/17/sst-may-hike-cost-of-doing-business-for-several-sectors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK4y1X0_COR2DuM98WtUf3EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMOu1sAM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/17/sst-may-hike-cost-of-doing-business-for-several-sectors/" target="_blank"&gt;SST may hike cost of doing business for several sectors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The re-introduced sales and services tax (SST) may likely increase the cost of doing business for several industries in Malaysia post-Sept 1, according to KPMG executive director for indirect tax practice Ng Sue Lynn. Speaking to StarBiz after The Star’s empowerment talk on “Transitioning to SST”, she pointed out that the SST will be an additional cost for businesses in several sectors that are not exempted under the indirect tax regime. “In comparison, the goods and services tax (GST) is a cost for the end consumers, rather than the businesses. This was because companies can...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib: Govt income reduced by RM15bil without GST - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/16/najib-govt-income-reduced-by-rm15bil-without-gst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELr9NaJ2yz98aLKJLswHXKYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 15:29:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/16/najib-govt-income-reduced-by-rm15bil-without-gst/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib: Govt income reduced by RM15bil without GST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Pakatan Harapan's decision to not collect Goods and Services Tax (GST) has reduced the Government's income by at least RM15bil, says Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak. In a Facebook post, the former prime minister said that there was also a shortfall in income of RM8bil between September and December 2018. "The Government will also have to pay back traders input tax of RM8bil for GST incurred on business purchases and expenses. That will total up to a loss of RM31bil this year alone," he said. On Monday (Aug 13), Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng stated that Barisan Nasional had "robbed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Lim: Hold open inquiry into ‘missing’ RM18 billion GST refunds - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/11/lim-hold-open-inquiry-into-missing-rm18-billion-gst-refunds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP2-wTSeThOYqnCA8SxLqhwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 08:20:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/11/lim-hold-open-inquiry-into-missing-rm18-billion-gst-refunds/" target="_blank"&gt;Lim: Hold open inquiry into ‘missing’ RM18 billion GST refunds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(FMT) – The finance ministry will propose to the Cabinet to hold an open inquiry into why RM18 billion in goods and services tax (GST) refunds was not transferred into a trust fund for this purpose. Minister Lim Guan Eng suggested that this inquiry be headed by independent professionals. He said he was waiting for a full report of an internal inquiry, headed by the new Treasury secretary-general Ismail Bakar, to be submitted. The ministry will also co-operate with any authority, including the Malaysian Anti-Corruption Commission, investigating this matter, he said in a statement today. Lim ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng, the tokong of idiots - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/13/guan-eng-the-tokong-of-idiots/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFxju0b9mBvX8_jZBbPrnfcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMOvrnwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 13:29:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/13/guan-eng-the-tokong-of-idiots/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng, the tokong of idiots&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;So there you have it. Lim Guan Eng made a mistake when he reported that the previous Barisan Nasional government stole RM17.911 billion of the GST refund money. (Actually he said the amount was RM18 billion). The amount that Barisan Nasional really stole was RM19.248 billion. NO HOLDS BARRED Raja Petra Kamarudin (The Star) – The previous amount that he revealed was not the actual total, owing a mistake by a ministry officer who misplaced a decimal point. Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng has not only stood by his allegations that the previous government had falsified the Goods and Services Tax ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>GST refunds put under trust accounts on monthly basis, says former Treasury Sec-Gen - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/09/gst-refunds-put-under-trust-accounts-on-monthly-basis-says-former-treasury-sec-gen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOJceobcBY9eoHjfktJSFmEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 08:10:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/09/gst-refunds-put-under-trust-accounts-on-monthly-basis-says-former-treasury-sec-gen/" target="_blank"&gt;GST refunds put under trust accounts on monthly basis, says former Treasury Sec-Gen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – Former Treasury Secretary-General of the Ministry of Finance (MoF) Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah has dismissed allegations that money due for refund under the Goods and Services Tax (GST) has gone missing. He said all monies collected are put under the government consolidated funds and amounts due for refund are put under the trust accounts on a monthly basis based on the requirements of the Customs Department. “I believe this information is available from the Accountant General’s Department and the fiscal division of the MoF,” he said. Irwan was responding to allegati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Pakatan govt promises to help all including the poor, says Finance Minister - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/13/lim-therell-be-no-discrimination-pakatan-govt-promises-to-help-all-including-the-poor-says-finance-m/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHTgonla6d4MbRv0E2fucxQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/13/lim-therell-be-no-discrimination-pakatan-govt-promises-to-help-all-including-the-poor-says-finance-m/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan govt promises to help all including the poor, says Finance Minister&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The Goods and Services Tax (GST) has impacted all Malaysians, especially the poor who never had to pay taxes before this, says Lim Guan Eng. The Finance Minister said the GST had imposed a heavy financial burden on the ordinary rakyat until they felt compelled to change the Government for the first time in 61 years. Lim was responding to former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak who claimed that the GST had made it difficult for the rich to evade tax. With the abolition of GST, the era of “black economy” would return under the Sales and Service Tax (SST), he claimed. L...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>‘RM19bil GST collected, RM18bil taken’ - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/09/rm19bil-gst-collected-rm18bil-taken/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAlkeghNPKJAFxwWBrkmUA4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 06:01:56 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/09/rm19bil-gst-collected-rm18bil-taken/" target="_blank"&gt;‘RM19bil GST collected, RM18bil taken’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The previous government has not been able to refund companies their tax credit that came about following the implementation of the Goods and Services Tax (GST) because 93% of the money was not placed in the correct account, Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng revealed. (The Star) – He said some RM18bil of the RM19.4bil input tax credit under the GST system since 2015 was “robbed” by the previous administration. “I was very shocked when informed that this happened because the previous government had failed to enter the GST collection in the trust account specifically meant for the repaying of GST ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng caught lying again - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/12/guan-eng-caught-lying-again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIaTDgr2gykyulUY0umKC8MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMOvrnwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 09:48:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/12/guan-eng-caught-lying-again/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng caught lying again&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;And this is why the Chinese are the most vocal in opposing the GST. And this is why 98% of the Chinese voted Pakatan Harapan — because they are angry about the GST. And this is why Pakatan Harapan abolished the GST — to make the Chinese happy. But the cost of living has still not gone down. So, to the Malays, it is still life as usual. NO HOLDS BARRED Raja Petra Kamarudin Tun Dr Mahathir Mohamad proudly announced that 90% of the personal income tax which the government collects are paid by the Chinese. If that is so then the spending power is in the hands of the Chinese and not in the hands...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Try 3% GST till December before junking the whole thing, urges Wee - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/10/try-3-gst-till-december-before-junking-the-whole-thing-urges-wee/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI5GCydlTJa2LSrkp4oUzEkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 03:59:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/10/try-3-gst-till-december-before-junking-the-whole-thing-urges-wee/" target="_blank"&gt;Try 3% GST till December before junking the whole thing, urges Wee&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The Government should first study the effects of a lower Goods and Services Tax (GST) rate before it is abolished, said MCA deputy president Datuk Seri Dr Wee Ka Siong. The GST was implemented by the previous government on April 1, 2015, at a rate of 6%. It is being replaced by the Sales and Services Tax (SST). The Ayer Hitam MP said in Parliament that a parliamentary select committee should be set up to study the effects of a 3% GST rate that would be collected until the end of the year. "During this period of transition, we should set the GST rate at maybe 3%, and we collec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>PAC’s BN chairman to initiate probe into ‘missing’ GST refunds - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/09/pacs-bn-chairman-to-initiate-probe-into-missing-gst-refunds/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKLHhoeMorjI-JrQCUU01ugqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 12:06:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/09/pacs-bn-chairman-to-initiate-probe-into-missing-gst-refunds/" target="_blank"&gt;PAC’s BN chairman to initiate probe into ‘missing’ GST refunds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The newly-appointed Public Accounts Committee (PAC) chairman Datuk Ronald Kiandee today said that he would initiate a probe into claims that RM18 billion from Goods and Services Tax (GST) refunds had been “missing”. “I will use my powers to bring this matter to the PAC,” said the Beluran MP, who is the first Opposition lawmaker to head the committee. Kiandee said so during a press conference in Parliament today alongside several Barisan Nasional lawmakers who called for thorough investigations on the claims made by Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng yesterday, in which he said the funds were “ro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Pakatan keeps its word, bill to repeal GST passed - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/pakatan-keeps-its-word-bill-to-repeal-gst-passed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOzVq9ABHroDTSbyA90JsuQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 13:15:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/pakatan-keeps-its-word-bill-to-repeal-gst-passed/" target="_blank"&gt;Pakatan keeps its word, bill to repeal GST passed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Pakatan Harapan’s promise to abolish the Goods and Services Tax (GST) materialised with the passing of a bill to repeal the consumption-based tax. Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng, in his wrapping up address in Parliament on Wednesday (Aug 8), had promised a thorough investigation on some RM18bil of the input tax credit under the GST which he claimed was “robbed” and “misappropriated” by the Barisan Nasional administration. “It is a very heavy responsibility. We want to know how it has happened for three years in a row. “This is not just immoral and unethical. I guarantee that we...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib: Pakatan Government may have spent the ‘missing’ RM18 billion - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/10/najib-pakatan-government-may-have-spent-the-missing-rm18-billion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKMAMuAxNWbK0juLrrU1y8kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 15:21:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/10/najib-pakatan-government-may-have-spent-the-missing-rm18-billion/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib: Pakatan Government may have spent the ‘missing’ RM18 billion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – Datuk Seri Najib Razak (pic) believes that the Pakatan Harapan Government may have spent the “missing” RM18bil to make up for fiscal shortfalls after zero-rating the Goods and Services Tax (GST) in June. The former finance minister said this could have happened when businesses filed their tax refunds to try to claim it immediately as soon as GST was zero-rated in June. “The Government lost a source of income for three months, and it may have spent funds from the consolidated revenue account. “These funds are supposed to be channelled to a GST refunds trust account for its month...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Dr Mahathir to Najib: Show us the money - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/12/dr-mahathir-to-najib-show-us-the-money/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENZrANtdeIc6tj2y5Wl0GmoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 07:07:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/12/dr-mahathir-to-najib-show-us-the-money/" target="_blank"&gt;Dr Mahathir to Najib: Show us the money&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prime minister says his predecessor should prove that the GST refunds are not missing. (FMT) – Prime minister Dr Mahathir Mohamad today challenged his predecessor to prove the latter’s claim that RM18 billion in goods and services tax (GST) refunds were not missing. “Lim Guan Eng said it is missing, Najib says it is not,” Mahathir said, referring to the finance minister and former prime minister respectively. “If the money is not missing show us where it went to,” he said after attending an art exhibition here. On Wednesday, Lim revealed that there was a shortfall of RM18 billion in a t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Increase in prices will not be much - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/08/13/increase-in-prices-will-not-be-much-only-certain-goods-will-be-taxed-under-new-law-come-sept-1-say-t/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEISB3ykYEzHYYzbtZX1VzFYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMPKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/metro/metro-news/2018/08/13/increase-in-prices-will-not-be-much-only-certain-goods-will-be-taxed-under-new-law-come-sept-1-say-t/" target="_blank"&gt;Increase in prices will not be much&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CONSUMERS can expect a hike in prices for certain goods after the implementation of the Sales and Service Tax (SST) on September 1. Sunshine Bakery Sdn Bhd managing director Tan Kim Seng said the price for baked goods was expected to increase from 5% to 10% after the implementation. “The increase will not be too high as not all raw materials are subjected to SST such as flour and sugar,” he said. “However, ingredients such as margarine will have to increase because of SST,” he said, adding that plastic bags used to package the baked goods would also go up in price. “We will make sure that t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Najib: Pakatan Government may have spent the 'missing' RM18bil - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/10/najib-pakatan-government-may-have-spent-the-missing-rm18bil/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG1HBRXRAthRTmi_NPXhF1cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 10:12:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/10/najib-pakatan-government-may-have-spent-the-missing-rm18bil/" target="_blank"&gt;Najib: Pakatan Government may have spent the 'missing' RM18bil&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Datuk Seri Najib Razak (pic) believes that the Pakatan Harapan Government may have spent the "missing" RM18bil to make up for fiscal shortfalls after zero-rating the Goods and Services Tax (GST) in June. The former finance minister said this could have happened when businesses filed their tax refunds to try to claim it immediately as soon as GST was zero-rated in June. "The Government lost a source of income for three months, and it may have spent funds from the consolidated revenue account. "These funds are supposed to be channelled to a GST refunds trust account for its mon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Saifuddin to Najib: We’ll do fine without GST - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/08/saifuddin-to-najib-well-do-fine-without-gst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG3B1Xuvokwu4cNHXFILIDYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 06:38:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/08/saifuddin-to-najib-well-do-fine-without-gst/" target="_blank"&gt;Saifuddin to Najib: We’ll do fine without GST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(The Star) – Datuk Saifuddin Nasution Ismail has refuted claims by the former prime minister that the country will lose its economic advantage following the abolition of the Goods and Services Tax (GST). The Domestic Trade and Consumer Affairs Minister said that the country had used the Sales and Service Tax prior to 2015, but still managed national development and economic growth. “So what was the economic problem that we faced at that time?” he told reporters at the Parliament lobby on Wednesday. He was responding to the remarks by Datuk Seri Najib Tun Razak that the country would lose th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Take stern action against culprit, says KJ - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/10/take-stern-action-against-culprit-says-kj/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPRdQQriv5LC88BdZHA1SRcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/10/take-stern-action-against-culprit-says-kj/" target="_blank"&gt;Take stern action against culprit, says KJ&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Pakatan Harapan government has been urged to take stern action against the culprit involved in the alleged misuse of input tax credit under the Goods and Services Tax (GST) system. Former Cabinet minister Khairy Jamaluddin said Barisan Nasional cannot accept the allegation by Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng, who accused in Parliament that the Barisan administration had stolen a total of RM18bil in GST refunds. “If indeed there was a misappropriation and the refund was not returned, then those responsible for it must be brought to book. “Barisan cannot accept being accused of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>What took you so long to notice missing GST refunds? Najib asks Guan Eng - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/11/what-took-you-so-long-to-notice-missing-gst-refunds-najib-asks-guan-eng/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKNA74euqtLaHwIeaS2WfKkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMNj5nwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 13:56:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/11/what-took-you-so-long-to-notice-missing-gst-refunds-najib-asks-guan-eng/" target="_blank"&gt;What took you so long to notice missing GST refunds? Najib asks Guan Eng&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Former prime minister Datuk Seri Najib Razak today questioned Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng on why it took him three months before realising that the GST refunds trust account was missing RM18 billion. “The question is why did it take three months before the Finance Minister realised that RM18 billion was not paid (to the GST Refund trust account) and now they say the government can’t pay the refunds because they have been ‘robbed’. “RM18 billion is not a small amount. What I see is that the Pakatan Harapan (PH) government did not expect the spike in GST refund claims the moment it ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item><item><title>Customs DG: RM19.4bil for GST refunds not approved during monthly meetings - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/10/customs-dg-rm19_4bil-for-gst-refunds-not-approved-during-monthly-meetings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIbElLjp-S6L9xQ4Te5LrMEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 10:38:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/10/customs-dg-rm19_4bil-for-gst-refunds-not-approved-during-monthly-meetings/" target="_blank"&gt;Customs DG: RM19.4bil for GST refunds not approved during monthly meetings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: The Customs Department had requested for RM19.4bil for the Goods and Services Tax (GST) refunds over a period of three years but it was not approved during the monthly trust fund meetings, said its director-general Datuk Seri T. Subromaniam. He said the required amount for the refunds for the period of April 1, 2015 until May 31, 2018 was RM82.9bil but only RM63.5bil was transferred to the trust fund throughout the period. “The Customs Department has requested for RM82.9bil from the monthly meetings but the amount was not transferred in full. “We have reported during the mont...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>GST refund money 'robbed' by BN govt, says Guan Eng when rebuffing Khairy - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/07/gst-refund-money-robbed-by-bn-govt-says-guan-eng-when-rebuffing-khairy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGV2AvJnPmeLqzHuMdWozOIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 13:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/07/gst-refund-money-robbed-by-bn-govt-says-guan-eng-when-rebuffing-khairy/" target="_blank"&gt;GST refund money 'robbed' by BN govt, says Guan Eng when rebuffing Khairy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: An emotionally-charged Lim Guan Eng (pic) revealed that refunds for the Goods and Services Tax (GST) were delayed as the money was "robbed" and spent first by the previous Barisan Nasional Government. Lim, who is the Finance Minister, revealed in Parliament today (Aug 7) that some GST input tax refunds took up to two years as there was no money in the Government trust fund (akaun amanah). "There was no money in the Government trust fund, the money instead went into the consolidated fund and was considered as revenue. "That money (refund fund) was spent by the Government. "This...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>FMM: Refund outstanding GST input tax before implementing SST - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/10/fmm-refund-outstanding-gst-input-tax-before-implementing-sst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGvBMTAwmUCVkHeHwevy6BsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 01:10:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/10/fmm-refund-outstanding-gst-input-tax-before-implementing-sst/" target="_blank"&gt;FMM: Refund outstanding GST input tax before implementing SST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: The Federation of Malaysian Manufacturers (FMM) is urging the government to return the outstanding GST input tax refunds to businesses before it imposes the Sales and Services Tax (SST), which is set to be enforced on September 1, 2018. “While we appreciate the Minister of Finance’s candid and transparent announcement that the Government owes businesses RM19.4bil in GST refunds, FMM hopes for the approved refunds to be channelled back to members as soon as possible,” it said in a statement. The federation also urged the government to ensure that all pending cases on special sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng: RM18bil input tax credit ‘robbed’ by BN administration - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/guan-eng-rm18bil-input-tax-credit-robbed-by-bn-administration/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM1rZA56Yo3ESBIaaYoNX7wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMInmqgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 13:33:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/08/guan-eng-rm18bil-input-tax-credit-robbed-by-bn-administration/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng: RM18bil input tax credit ‘robbed’ by BN administration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Some RM18bil or 93% of the RM19.4bil input tax credit under the Goods and Services Tax (GST) system since 2015 had been misappropriated by the previous administration, claimed Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng. “I was very shocked when informed that this happened because the previous government had failed to enter the GST collection in the trust account specifically meant for repaying GST claims. “Instead, the Barisan Nasional government pilfered the trust account and entered cash GST collection directly into the consolidated fund as revenues to be spent freely,” he said when tabl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Finance Minister says only 43.5pct of services subject to SST - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/08/finance-minister-says-only-43pt5pct-of-services-subject-to-sst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPxKpl5EICznZXq5_VaN-x4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMLfbhwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 08:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/business/business-news/2018/08/08/finance-minister-says-only-43pt5pct-of-services-subject-to-sst/" target="_blank"&gt;Finance Minister says only 43.5pct of services subject to SST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KUALA LUMPUR: Only 43.5 per cent of services will be subject to the Sales and Services Tax (SST) come Sept 1, compared with the 64.8 per cent of services which were subjected to the Goods and Services Tax (GST). During the second reading of the proposed Service Tax Bill 2018 in Parliament today, Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng said the model and scope of the proposed tax would be implemented based on the Service Tax Act 1975, which was repealed following the introduction of the GST in 2014. However, he noted that the existing model and scope needed to be improved in several areas to facilitat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Guan Eng: Construction services, building materials exempted from SST - The Star Online</title><link>https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/12/guan-eng-construction-services-building-material-costs-exempted-from-sst/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENyVf7xSk9BOU8fpWY-OZ4oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow-N7eCjC60NYBMNKriAM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 04:03:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thestar.com.my/news/nation/2018/08/12/guan-eng-construction-services-building-material-costs-exempted-from-sst/" target="_blank"&gt;Guan Eng: Construction services, building materials exempted from SST&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Star Online&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETALING JAYA: Construction services and building material costs will not be charged under the Sales and Service Tax (SST), said Finance Minister Lim Guan Eng. In a statement on Sunday (Aug 12), Lim said basic materials such as bricks, cement, sand and other construction materials were subjected to the Goods and Services Tax (GST) at 6%, with the same applying to construction services. “This had led to increased construction costs under the GST era, including the increase in house prices,” he added. Lim expects the pressure on house prices, industrial and commercial buildings is to be eased...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thestar.com.my">The Star Online</source></item><item><title>Success of SST hinges on enforcement, says tax expert - Malaysia Today</title><link>http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/03/success-of-sst-hinges-on-enforcement-says-tax-expert/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEDOglGQYeTtk7cgOrxaIC4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow7LveCjCF9NUBMInznwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 07:29:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.malaysia-today.net/2018/08/03/success-of-sst-hinges-on-enforcement-says-tax-expert/" target="_blank"&gt;Success of SST hinges on enforcement, says tax expert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Malaysia Today&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(MMO) – Enforcement will play a pivotal role in ensuring the success of the implementation of the Sales and Service Tax (SST) says Axcelasia Taxand chairman, Veerinderjeet Singh. “Previously the enforcement was lacking during the implementation of the previous Goods and Services Tax (GST). Many businesses took advantage of this by hiking prices wantonly,” said Veerinderjeet at a briefing after presenting at the ‘Axcelasia Taxand’s SST 2.0’ seminar at Hotel Istana here today. He said businesses added on the input tax to their cost of goods sold and this resulted in higher prices, adding that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.malaysia-today.net">Malaysia Today</source></item></channel></rss>