<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Maria Ressa - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNR0o1TW00MUVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-NZ&amp;gl=NZ&amp;ceid=NZ:en</link><language>en-NZ</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:27:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Rappler CEO vows to report on Duterte drug war amid arrest threat - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/rappler-ceo-vows-report-duterte-drug-war-arrest-threat-181204074322749.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELM6WSbx7KjsykMxSjFicUAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/rappler-ceo-vows-report-duterte-drug-war-arrest-threat-181204074322749.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rappler CEO vows to report on Duterte drug war amid arrest threat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maria Ressa vows to fight tax evasion charges and calls out Duterte administration for weaponising laws against critics.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Philippines journalist Maria Ressa vows to challenge tax fraud charges after arrest - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/03/philippines-journalist-maria-ressa-turn-herself-in-police-warrant-rappler</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMvrSCJaCos9vuBnBNFfdlMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 05:16:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/03/philippines-journalist-maria-ressa-turn-herself-in-police-warrant-rappler" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines journalist Maria Ressa vows to challenge tax fraud charges after arrest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Editor of independent news website Rappler has been released on bail over charges she says are being used to intimidate her.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Philippine government to charge veteran journalist critical of Duterte with tax evasion - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/duterte-charge-critical-journalist-maria-ressa-rappler-tax-avoidance-philippine-government-a8628491.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA3JqkVtfrp4oqcdUvb9pNUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/duterte-charge-critical-journalist-maria-ressa-rappler-tax-avoidance-philippine-government-a8628491.html" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine government to charge veteran journalist critical of Duterte with tax evasion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Philippine government said that it would charge a veteran journalist and her online news startup with tax evasion, a move the publication described as an ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Rappler chief Maria Ressa returns to Manila to fight 'ridiculous' tax charges - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/asia/maria-ressa-philippines-posts-bail-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPDs6Noko38FnMwMXzWS4JgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 08:51:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/03/asia/maria-ressa-philippines-posts-bail-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rappler chief Maria Ressa returns to Manila to fight 'ridiculous' tax charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A leading journalist and vocal critic of Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte has surrendered to a Manila court after arriving back in the country to fight tax charges that were filed in her absence. Maria Ressa, the CEO of Philippine news site Rappler presented herself to court with a bail application, that was approved, guaranteeing her freedom until her next court appearance scheduled for December 7. Ressa and her company were formally indicted on multiple counts of tax evasion last week, charges critics say are politically motivated and designed to silence independent media in the sout...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>She exposed Duterte's drug war in the Philippines. Now she faces a possible prison term - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/asia/maria-ressa-philippines-duterte-media-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDwxqo0Y5WmEsDbdEBFwbWIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMSUnAY</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 01:48:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/asia/maria-ressa-philippines-duterte-media-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;She exposed Duterte's drug war in the Philippines. Now she faces a possible prison term&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Images and stories from Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte's brutal war on drugs have shocked audiences worldwide, as bodies have stacked up in cities across the country, many of them victims of extrajudicial and vigilante killings. While the government has hardly been shy about its intention to go after both dealers and users, hard data on the number of killings has often been tough to come by. One indispensable source of information, both for the international media and readers in the Philippines has been the upstart news site Rappler, which is now facing a reckoning with the governmen...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Philippine court grants bail to news site chief in tax evasion case - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-media/philippine-court-grants-bail-to-news-site-chief-in-tax-evasion-case-idUSKBN1O20FH</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHrZ9N8HBBkvRcff-pNAQw8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 07:27:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-media/philippine-court-grants-bail-to-news-site-chief-in-tax-evasion-case-idUSKBN1O20FH" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine court grants bail to news site chief in tax evasion case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Philippine court on Monday granted bail to the top executive of a news website critical of President Rodrigo Duterte's policies after she was indicted of tax evasion charges, a case she described as "politically motivated". The Department of Justice in October indicted the executive, Maria Ressa, and online news platform Rappler (www.rappler.com), for attempting to evade taxes by not reporting gains of almost $3 million in the company's 2015 tax returns. "I will continue addressing the charges with nothing other than to show they are politically motivated, and they are manufactured," Ress...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Philippine website chief turns herself in to authorities - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4ac63e42-f6d8-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL4Gs3buSkD9kvOtRBRGL0QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:27:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4ac63e42-f6d8-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine website chief turns herself in to authorities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president of Rappler, the Philippine news website known for its unblinkingly critical coverage of Rodrigo Duterte, posted bail for alleged tax code violations after turning herself in to authorities on Monday. Maria Ressa posted bail at Pasig City Regional Trial Court in metropolitan Manila, Rappler reported, after an arrest warrant was issued against her. Her arraignment at the court was set for December 7. The tax charge is one of five levelled by authorities last week against the news website, which Mr Duterte and his administration have accused of violating a constitutional ban on f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Drop charges against news site Rappler, Human Rights Watch says - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/asia/maria-ressa-philippines-journalist-hrw-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIL7XRUZ_r68W-05tYzFAjgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:53:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/30/asia/maria-ressa-philippines-journalist-hrw-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Drop charges against news site Rappler, Human Rights Watch says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human Rights Watch has called on Philippine authorities to drop criminal charges against the news website Rappler and its editor, Maria Ressa, criticizing the legal action against them as politically motivated. The international rights watchdog accused the government of using tax laws "to muzzle prominent critics of President Rodrigo Duterte and his 'war on drugs.'" Rappler said five cases were formally filed against Ressa and Rappler Holdings in two courts. Philippine officials say some of the charges stem from Rappler and Ressa failing to declare about $3 million in 2015 on tax returns fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Maria Ressa, Rappler formally indicted by the Philippines on tax evasion charges - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/asia/maria-ressa-rappler-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPbz9s27Ht0a4-SRkLe4irEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 12:40:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/29/asia/maria-ressa-rappler-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Maria Ressa, Rappler formally indicted by the Philippines on tax evasion charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philippines news website Rappler and its chief executive have been indicted on tax evasion charges, the latest in a case that free speech and civil liberties advocates have warned is part of a wider crackdown on dissent by President Rodrigo Duterte's administration. Rappler said five cases were formally filed against Ressa and Rappler Holdings in two courts, just weeks after the Philippines Department of Justice announced it had found probable cause to indict the pair. Philippines officials say some of the charges stem from Rappler and Ressa failing to declare about $3 million in 2015 on ta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Jamal Khashoggi's memory hangs heavy over press freedom dinner - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/21/media/reliable-sources-11-20-18/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4b6u2HbHSQyj3mc8aQn7MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 16:44:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/21/media/reliable-sources-11-20-18/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jamal Khashoggi's memory hangs heavy over press freedom dinner&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A version of this article first appeared in the Reliable Sources newsletter. You can sign up for free right here. US president or Saudi PR person? The headline on the Washington Post website right now: "For Trump, the bottom line on Saudi Arabia takes precedence over human rights." Anne Gearan says President Trump's declaration "that he won't hold Saudi rulers accountable for the killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi distilled the president's foreign policy approach to its transactional and personalized essence." Senate Foreign Relations Committee Chairman Bob Corker's reaction: "I never th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Philippine government threatening Rappler - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/11/18/philippine-government-threatening-rappler-rs.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMMYL4o0gzJBwkzxMrVWvzUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 20:01:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/business/2018/11/18/philippine-government-threatening-rappler-rs.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine government threatening Rappler&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rappler founder and editor Maria Ressa responds to the Philippine government's new threat to indict her. "The end goal of all of these cases is political harassment," Ressa tells Brian Stelter. "They want to intimidate us into stopping the stories we're doing." ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rappler chief Maria Ressa says tax evasion charges won't silence news site's journalists - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/asia/maria-ressa-intv-philippines-rappler-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBk-b8ciK1gZ0XBX8PZBXuMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 17:50:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/12/asia/maria-ressa-intv-philippines-rappler-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rappler chief Maria Ressa says tax evasion charges won't silence news site's journalists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maria Ressa, the CEO of the Philippine news website Rappler, said Monday that her reporters would not be silenced in the face of tax evasion charges, telling CNN that "journalists are more important today than ever." Ressa vowed to fight the charges from the Philippines Department of Justice for tax evasion, which many see as a thinly veiled attempt by President Rodrigo Duterte to muzzle the investigative news site. "In many ways the government's attacks against Rappler have made it very clear to us exactly who we are, what our identity is, and for our young reporters who are on the ground,...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Philippine editor accuses Duterte of 'weaponising' rule of law - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/12/maria-ressa-rappler-philippines-duterte-outcry-tax-charges</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFhLzh8DkbweVr3r9eyuNJUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 04:57:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/12/maria-ressa-rappler-philippines-duterte-outcry-tax-charges" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine editor accuses Duterte of 'weaponising' rule of law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The editor of a Philippine news organisation charged with tax evasion has accused the government of President Rodrigo Duterte of using “brute force and intimidation” and “weaponising” the rule of law against its critics. Rappler, which was founded and is run by Maria Ressa, was charged with tax evasion over the weekend – the latest in an onslaught of government-initiated criminal charges and attacks on news organisations that have been critical of Duterte, putting the country’s free press at stake. “This is a completely uneven legal battle that bends the rule of law till the point it’s near...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Top Philippines news site and company chief face tax evasion charges - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/10/asia/philippine-news-site-charges/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA731TsusmHfuswIC0sqJiQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 23:39:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/10/asia/philippine-news-site-charges/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Top Philippines news site and company chief face tax evasion charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A move by the Philippines Justice Department to charge investigative news site Rappler with tax evasion is being seen as a thinly disguised attempt to stifle press freedom in the Southeast Asian country. On Friday, the Justice Department said it had "found probable cause" to indict Rappler and its CEO and executive editor, former CNN bureau chief Maria Ressa, on charges of tax evasion. "We are not at all surprised by the decision, considering how the Duterte administration has been treating Rappler for its independent and fearless reporting," Rappler said in statement. Officials said Rapple...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Journalists are more important than ever - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/11/12/news-stream-intv-ceo-rappler-tax-evasion-charges-stout-ressa.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENeji5Zwnog26JiqkOZHPakqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 14:25:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/11/12/news-stream-intv-ceo-rappler-tax-evasion-charges-stout-ressa.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Journalists are more important than ever&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rappler's CEO Maria Ressa is facing tax evasion charges at a time of pressure on the media in the Philippines, especially for outlets that are critical of the 'war on drugs'. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Philippines: threat to indict news site ‘assault on press freedom’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/11/philippine-rappler-news-outlet-critical-of-duterte-hit-with-tax-evasion-charge</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGlNZvZ4ZEBUl2974eLbKhkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 12:12:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/11/philippine-rappler-news-outlet-critical-of-duterte-hit-with-tax-evasion-charge" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines: threat to indict news site ‘assault on press freedom’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Campaigners for press freedom have expressed alarm after authorities in the Philippines said they would file charges of tax evasion against a news website that has been an outspoken critic of the country’s authoritarian president, Rodrigo Duterte. The US-based Committee to Protect Journalists said on Sunday it was “extremely concerned” about the threat to indict the major news site Rappler and its president, Maria Ressa, calling the charges “a direct assault on press freedom in the Philippines”. The country’s justice department said it found probable cause to indict Rappler Holdings Corp an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Facebook under pressure in SE Asia - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/0137a68c-3769-11e8-8b98-2f31af407cc8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAwQ1DsApvVXafau_P8XIXoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 18:11:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0137a68c-3769-11e8-8b98-2f31af407cc8" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook under pressure in SE Asia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well before the election of Donald Trump forced Facebook to acknowledge its potential as a means of influencing US politics, its executives were already receiving early warnings from south-east Asia. As reported in today’s FT Big Read from John Reed and Hannah Kuchler, the populist Rodrigo Duterte had relied heavily on Facebook in his election campaign earlier in 2016 – and after his victory, supporters began using Facebook to attack critics of his bloody war on drugs. Among those targeted was Maria Ressa (pictured on the left above), chief executive of the Philippines-based news site Rappl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Why south-east Asia’s politics are proving a problem for Facebook - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/9b84a5a4-33ff-11e8-a3ae-fd3fd4564aa6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJih9xpXY7S5lNVhBQ5oqjsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwktp6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 04:00:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/9b84a5a4-33ff-11e8-a3ae-fd3fd4564aa6" target="_blank"&gt;Why south-east Asia’s politics are proving a problem for Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Philippines-based news website Rappler, launched in 2012, was an early and enthusiastic adopter of Facebook’s “Instant Articles” service, which allowed it to speed up the loading of stories for readers. By 2015 it had added video on Facebook too, and was reporting triple-digit readership growth as millions of Filipinos began turning to the social media site as their main source of news. Then, says Maria Ressa, Rappler’s chief executive, “Facebook ran into trouble”. In May 2016, six months before Americans elected Donald Trump, Filipinos voted in their own populist president, Rodrigo Dut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>The woman taking on Duterte in a press freedom fight in the Philippines - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/mar/12/maria-ressa-rappler-rodrigo-duterte-woman-press-freedom-in-the-philippines</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKN_CsDeIYt9tt_9luUVzkkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 03:36:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/mar/12/maria-ressa-rappler-rodrigo-duterte-woman-press-freedom-in-the-philippines" target="_blank"&gt;The woman taking on Duterte in a press freedom fight in the Philippines&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The warning signs were all there. But Maria Ressa says “I never saw it coming.” The founder and driving force behind the Philippines news organisation Rappler admits to surprise when President Rodrigo Duterte effectively declared war on her journalists and heralded with it the biggest threat to freedom of the press the country has seen in decades. Rappler has only been in existence since 2012, beginning as an online news start-up with 12 reporters, established by Ressa, a former CNN Bureau chief. But over the past two months this small yet bullish group has been at the forefront of a battle...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Duterte bans Rappler reporters from presidential palace - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/02/duterte-bans-rappler-reporters-presidential-palace-180220130842018.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE8H2dFUfbYGLkT1VjqizTkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 20:49:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/02/duterte-bans-rappler-reporters-presidential-palace-180220130842018.html" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte bans Rappler reporters from presidential palace&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president of the Philippines has ordered that two journalists be banned from entering the presidential palace, an act one Filipino reporters' rights group described as "appalling and extremely unbecoming" of a president. Independent news website Rappler reported on Tuesday that Rodrigo Duterte directly ordered his presidential security team to bar the organisation's CEO and one of its reporters from covering events at the palace. The report was later confirmed by state television PTV. {articleGUID} Rappler said the president made the decision after watching a Senate hearing, in which hi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Philippine news site chief says complaint of cyber libel is 'baseless' - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-media/philippine-news-site-chief-says-complaint-of-cyber-libel-is-baseless-idUSKBN1FL4LM</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJt0XwPdCeeGAlDRapduMeMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:36:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-media/philippine-news-site-chief-says-complaint-of-cyber-libel-is-baseless-idUSKBN1FL4LM" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine news site chief says complaint of cyber libel is 'baseless'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANILA (Reuters) - The head of a Philippine online news site battling revocation of its license for violation of ownership conditions on Thursday said law enforcers should drop a complaint of cyber libel against her, describing it as "baseless". Maria Ressa, chief executive of Rappler (www.rappler.com), responding to a complaint last year by businessman Wilfredo Keng, also called the allegations "baffling" and "unfounded". Keng featured in a 2012 Rappler story, updated in 2014, that cited an intelligence report linking him to illegal activities such as human trafficking and drug smuggling. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Asia's strongmen follow Trump's lead on fake news - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/01/28/asia/asia-fake-news-media-repression-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKfAYTLvFuLJtcUURWpJylEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 07:23:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/01/28/asia/asia-fake-news-media-repression-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Asia's strongmen follow Trump's lead on fake news&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Spies." An "iceberg of misinformation," and "a media that acts as a mafia." And, of course, "fake news." These are some of the terms leaders across Southeast Asia are using to discredit journalists and media outlets -- and the rhetoric is morphing into action, with arrests of journalists and the shuttering of news sites across the region. In the Philippines, an independent news site, which has been accused of being "fake news" by the country's leader, Rodrigo Duterte, faces closure after the country's SEC pulled its license. Elsewhere, two journalists in Myanmar are facing charges filed wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Philippine news site head meets investigators over 'suspicious' complaint - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-media/philippine-news-site-head-meets-investigators-over-suspicious-complaint-idUSKBN1FB0FY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcs9PqPoIysQ1eIMf6BJZQqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 05:23:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-media/philippine-news-site-head-meets-investigators-over-suspicious-complaint-idUSKBN1FB0FY" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine news site head meets investigators over 'suspicious' complaint&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Neil Jerome Morales MANILA (Reuters) - The head of a Philippine news site ordered closed for ownership violations met state investigators on Monday to answer what she called a "suspicious" complaint about a five-year-old story, as domestic fears grow of an impending crackdown on media. Maria Ressa, chief of Rappler (www.rappler.com), maintains that the Jan. 11 Securities and Exchange Commission's revoking of Rappler's license was designed to intimidate journalists whose reporting has challenged President Rodrigo Duterte, notorious for his public tirades against opponents. Ressa was met b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Philippine Investigators Summon Boss of News Site Derided by Duterte - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/philippine-investigators-summon-boss-of-news-site-derided-by-duterte/4214159.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAq8fletZnqP4cPgu4OZVp0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 21:17:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/philippine-investigators-summon-boss-of-news-site-derided-by-duterte/4214159.html" target="_blank"&gt;Philippine Investigators Summon Boss of News Site Derided by Duterte&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Philippine law enforcement agency has summoned the head of Rappler, a news site known for challenging President Rodrigo Duterte, to answer a complaint related to cyber crime, adding to problems for an outlet central to a row over press freedom. The country's corporate regulator last week revoked the site's operating license for violating the constitution's restrictions on foreign ownership of media, while the justice minister on Wednesday ordered an investigation into Rappler's possible criminal liability. Known for its investigative reporting, Rappler has repeatedly drawn the ire of the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Rappler CEO: Stripping of license is political - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/01/16/philippines-rappler-maria-ressa-intv.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOO0pPvsa6uSTa2-mZ0T7_YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 04:59:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/01/16/philippines-rappler-maria-ressa-intv.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Rappler CEO: Stripping of license is political&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CEO and editor of new Philippines media company Rappler says the government is stripping the organization of its operating license because of its critical coverage of the country's outspoken president, Rodrigo Duterte. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Philippines revokes license of Rappler, news site critical of Duterte administration - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2018/01/15/asia/philippines-rappler-sec-license-revoked/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN5RRK0DJvwV8ZTTOohvkEgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 05:00:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2018/01/15/asia/philippines-rappler-sec-license-revoked/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines revokes license of Rappler, news site critical of Duterte administration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Philippines new media company fiercely critical of the government has had its operating license revoked, in what critics say is a move to silence the press. The country's Security and Exchange Commission (SEC) said online news site Rappler had violated the country's constitution and its registration would be revoked over foreign ownership rules. The outlet has been fiercely critical of president Rodrigo Duterte's administration since the controversial leader came to power in June 2016. Rappler's founder and CEO, Maria Ressa, told CNN the organization plans to fight the decision. "We plan ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Government targets Rappler, website critical of Duterte - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/01/philippine-government-seeks-close-rappler-website-180115084959311.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG9awL4Ki-_pqsFztix_J9IqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 06:11:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/01/philippine-government-seeks-close-rappler-website-180115084959311.html" target="_blank"&gt;Government targets Rappler, website critical of Duterte&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Philippine government has sought to shut down an independent news website, which has published critical stories about President Rodrigo Duterte, a move observers and journalists say is an attack on press freedom and democracy. The Philippine Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced on Monday that it has revoked the registration of Rappler, citing violations of foreign ownership and control of the Manila-based news organisation. The SEC, an agency under the president, is responsible for enforcing securities and investment laws in the country, as well as maintaining company regi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Philippines' Duterte had 'nothing to do' with news site's license: spokesman - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-media/philippines-duterte-had-nothing-to-do-with-news-sites-license-spokesman-idUSKBN1F50HL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGd0cg-To7HCA2BOnuxVeL0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 06:16:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-media/philippines-duterte-had-nothing-to-do-with-news-sites-license-spokesman-idUSKBN1F50HL" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines' Duterte had 'nothing to do' with news site's license: spokesman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Martin Petty and Karen Lema MANILA (Reuters) - The office of Philippine leader Rodrigo Duterte sought to distance itself on Tuesday from a regulator's decision to revoke the license of a prominent news site, rebuffing allegations the administration had initiated a crackdown on the media. Presidential spokesman Harry Roque said Duterte had not influenced the corporate regulator's decision against digital news outlet Rappler, and that Duterte had called him to ask why critics were pointing the finger at him. Rappler, whose reporting has infuriated the volatile leader, was found by the Secu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>