<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Passport - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRFZ6ZGpFU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-NZ&amp;gl=NZ&amp;ceid=NZ:en</link><language>en-NZ</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:04:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>The United Arab Emirates has been named the new 'most powerful passport' - Stuff.co.nz</title><link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/travel/news/109098530/the-united-arab-emirates-has-been-named-the-new-most-powerful-passport</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMidGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnN0dWZmLmNvLm56L3RyYXZlbC9uZXdzLzEwOTA5ODUzMC90aGUtdW5pdGVkLWFyYWItZW1pcmF0ZXMtaGFzLWJlZW4tbmFtZWQtdGhlLW5ldy1tb3N0LXBvd2VyZnVsLXBhc3Nwb3J00gEA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.stuff.co.nz/travel/news/109098530/the-united-arab-emirates-has-been-named-the-new-most-powerful-passport" target="_blank"&gt;The United Arab Emirates has been named the new 'most powerful passport'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Stuff.co.nz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's a new number one in the "world's most powerful passport" league - well, in one league at least. The United Arab Emirates has overtaken Singapore to ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.stuff.co.nz">Stuff.co.nz</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/NnSaPA6ZmIcbeDcP6aY6mNCrcMTkyyfpOvDQm5kR56beTIh0BJDnAuggCr0Kvn_KhzWdM8sSJSjY_aQNBBo8IaQaSuBlrZ_5hhTzEX2iInY9exRNXAk3B3xEEeUHhzOCg_TVImCV5E-AfRsY4z3l7NpdFCXu56QAdKD-pe-WOqNX8lE5_E9RWB1yU0-jmvpCccThTH6kq46_unRcvzrLqQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Passport check: The United Arab Emirates has eclipsed Singapore and Germany to become the most powerful - New Zealand Herald</title><link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/travel/news/article.cfm?c_id=7&amp;objectid=12170816</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiS2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm56aGVyYWxkLmNvLm56L3RyYXZlbC9uZXdzL2FydGljbGUuY2ZtP2NfaWQ9NyZvYmplY3RpZD0xMjE3MDgxNtIBAA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.nzherald.co.nz/travel/news/article.cfm?c_id=7&amp;objectid=12170816" target="_blank"&gt;Passport check: The United Arab Emirates has eclipsed Singapore and Germany to become the most powerful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Zealand Herald&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a surprise shake up, the United Arab Emirates now has the world's most powerful passport with access to the greatest number of countries visa-free.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.nzherald.co.nz">New Zealand Herald</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/EHxo3DzxO5n0u5PuXfKJWR1A4Ybd2vysKZdzamynTvt7CyD4KA_ca5-8gWgJEJr8Q-M9I52hQgnZVItizLxhqjxV9pg00aYZ2dezvk4iyhfwpZA_pn2BWEmM5caPqdqoN_Jhv8XvF5Q2SkomJs4=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Passport missing following woman's disappearance - The Nation's Local News - newsie.co.nz</title><link>https://www.newsie.co.nz/news/130484-passport-missing-following-womans-disappearance.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiWWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3Lm5ld3NpZS5jby5uei9uZXdzLzEzMDQ4NC1wYXNzcG9ydC1taXNzaW5nLWZvbGxvd2luZy13b21hbnMtZGlzYXBwZWFyYW5jZS5odG1s0gEA</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:21:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.newsie.co.nz/news/130484-passport-missing-following-womans-disappearance.html" target="_blank"&gt;Passport missing following woman's disappearance - The Nation's Local News&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;newsie.co.nz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The investigation into the disappearance of English tourist Grace Millane has revealed several of her belongings are missing, including her passport. Detective ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWl3MHBxbmpZQU1FVVpsRThCM2dTcWtLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.newsie.co.nz">newsie.co.nz</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/-b3LrFsHBs3A0do6oNx6A7MTBe5Q99qtARizXmE5GagXUDS-YqjpM6GaQCWb1jhBfY0fQ2uGaTkPzilpHqIQn8HPWba0RDayag9ElFKC9jTGaE5lc291AVbgL9qiKwWfNM1u=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>EU nationals highlight multiple bugs in Home Office Brexit app - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/dec/08/another-blow-brexit-app-eu-nationals-string-bugs-home-office</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJNTD3tr_ViAaeF-HibFiosqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDHmu8F</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 10:26:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/dec/08/another-blow-brexit-app-eu-nationals-string-bugs-home-office" target="_blank"&gt;EU nationals highlight multiple bugs in Home Office Brexit app&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Home Office efforts to launch a phone app for EU nationals registering to stay in Britain have been dealt a blow after complaints that the passport recognition function does not work on all phones. Universities participating in a trial of the app have resorted to buying a supply of phones that do work as has one law firm advising applicants. Earlier this year the government admitted that the app, which is supposed to enable applicants to complete a necessary ID verification check, did not work on iPhones. But months after the former home secretary Amber Rudd claimed that applying for “settl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>This is the most powerful passport in the world (it’s not American) - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-the-most-powerful-passport-in-the-world-its-not-american-2018-12-05</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBiO8Cc2WA3DZSKNH2IGI84qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-the-most-powerful-passport-in-the-world-its-not-american-2018-12-05" target="_blank"&gt;This is the most powerful passport in the world (it’s not American)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Quentin Fottrell The U.S. made it to No. 14 on a ranking that measured the ease of access for gaining a second citizenship Which passport is the most powerful of them all? It’s not the U.S. Getty Images The most powerful passport in the world is not American. The United Arab Emirates was No. 1 on the list on a ranking that went to 167, according to a compilation by the “Global Passport Ranking,” created by Arton Capital a Montreal–based organization that helps high-net-worth clients gain second citizenship and/or residency. This was followed by Singapore, Germany, Denmark and Sweden, Fin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Ending ‘golden visas’ for oligarchs is a start – but not a solution - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/07/golden-visa-oligarch-super-rich-british-citizenship-global</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC_cr9gixNTYtEOcDLq6AzIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 15:46:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/dec/07/golden-visa-oligarch-super-rich-british-citizenship-global" target="_blank"&gt;Ending ‘golden visas’ for oligarchs is a start – but not a solution&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government has finally stopped a programme that sells British visas for a £2m investment in UK bonds, but anyone who thinks this will free London of the influence of kleptocrats is mistaken. The UK’s “golden visa” programme began back in 1994, when the Conservative government sought to woo wealthy Hong Kong residents, and was boosted by Labour in 2008. The programme has brought billions into the bond market over the past 24 years, primarily from Chinese and Russian applicants. Since 2015, applicants have had to pass banks’ due diligence tests, but no one in government has ever bothered ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Chuck Schumer: Marriott should replace all passports if their numbers have been stolen - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/chuck-schumer-marriott-should-replace-all-passports-of-everyone-impacted-by-hack-2018-12-05</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJDZVhcL0qJX15ks8eA_KvAqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwuJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/chuck-schumer-marriott-should-replace-all-passports-of-everyone-impacted-by-hack-2018-12-05" target="_blank"&gt;Chuck Schumer: Marriott should replace all passports if their numbers have been stolen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Kari Paul The hotel chain said it would reimburse guests who require a new passport, but only if it determines that fraud has taken place Senator Charles Schumer, a Democrat from New York, has some harsh words for Marriott International after the hotel chain admitted 500 million customer accounts had been hacked. Getty Images The fallout from Marriott’s massive data breach could cost the company millions. On Monday, Marriott (MAR) told MarketWatch that it would foot the bill for customers directly impacted by the hack to replace their passports. The hotel chain said it would reimburse ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Exclusive: After massive hack, Marriott pledges to pay for new passports if fraud has taken place - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/after-massive-hack-marriott-pledges-to-pay-for-new-passports-if-fraud-has-taken-place-2018-12-03</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHrGlCA8_xnR9IAD2fvlOqoqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/after-massive-hack-marriott-pledges-to-pay-for-new-passports-if-fraud-has-taken-place-2018-12-03" target="_blank"&gt;Exclusive: After massive hack, Marriott pledges to pay for new passports if fraud has taken place&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Kari Paul The promise could be expensive. It costs approximately $110 to get a new passport A sign marks the location of a Marriott hotel on November 30, 2018 in Chicago, Illinois. Getty Images Marriott International (MAR) customers are being given free identity theft monitoring software to keep an eye on accounts after a massive hack exposed the data of more than 500 million people. But on Monday evening, Marriott said it would go even further to help customers impacted by the massive hack. “As it relates to passports and potential fraud, we are setting up a process to work with our gu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>UAE now has the most powerful passport in the world - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/uae-passport-most-powerful-passport-index-global-ranking-uk-blue-germany-japan-a8664076.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAMX50VvhVJ8jGelUu0g48MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 19:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/uae-passport-most-powerful-passport-index-global-ranking-uk-blue-germany-japan-a8664076.html" target="_blank"&gt;UAE now has the most powerful passport in the world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Arab Emirates (UAE) has overtaken Singapore and Germany as the country with the world’s most powerful passport. According to Passport Index, UAE passport holders are now able to gain entry to 167 countries without obtaining a prior visa - 113 countries visa-free, and another 54 using visas on arrival. The oil rich state jumped from third place last month into first after four more countries were added to its list of visa-free destinations on 1 December, Gulf News reported. Read more - British academic jailed by UAE for 'spying' lands back in UK - De La Rue profits slump after los...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>US airport opens first fully biometric terminal - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/atlanta-airport-first-us-biometric-terminal-facial-recognition/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELBczzW5uaHImZCWQXaj1woqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 10:57:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/atlanta-airport-first-us-biometric-terminal-facial-recognition/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;US airport opens first fully biometric terminal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;What if you could simply look at a screen for two seconds and check in for your flight? Imagine glancing at a screen for another two seconds to drop off your bags at a luggage station? How easy would it be to merely look at another screen to breeze through ID checks at TSA security checkpoints or the departure gate? All this, without having to use your passport. Well, now you can. Atlanta's Hartsfield Jackson International Airport and Delta Air Lines have opened the nation's first curb-to-gate biometric terminal, which promises to improve aviation security while moving travelers faster thro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Marriott breach: State Department says don’t panic over stolen passport numbers - Fast Company</title><link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90274320/marriott-breach-state-department-says-dont-panic-over-stolen-passport-numbers</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF4kyDBFF1mOH88yLzWFgQ4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowlacCMKBPMOGbAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 11:24:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90274320/marriott-breach-state-department-says-dont-panic-over-stolen-passport-numbers" target="_blank"&gt;Marriott breach: State Department says don’t panic over stolen passport numbers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fast Company&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As many as 500 million guests may have had their personal information disclosed by a data breach in Marriott’s Starwood guest reservation database. While some guests “only” had their names and addresses accessed, around 327 million guests had some combination of the following information compromised: name, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, email address, Starwood Preferred Guest account information, date of birth, gender, arrival and departure information, reservation date, and passport number. That last one might give you pause. Passport numbers are especially sensiti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.fastcompany.com">Fast Company</source></item><item><title>Grandfather banned from US holiday after accidentally ticking 'terrorist' box on visa form - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/john-stevenson-us-visa-ban-terrorist-esta-form-mistake-a8660441.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHj5pyoiKehJ2AVjHhQb6t0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 10:09:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/john-stevenson-us-visa-ban-terrorist-esta-form-mistake-a8660441.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grandfather banned from US holiday after accidentally ticking 'terrorist' box on visa form&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Scottish couple's festive holiday plans are in disarray after a 70-year-old grandfather accidentally declared himself a terrorist on a crucial visa form. John Stevenson and his wife, Marion, had planned to fly to New York City on 3 December. The couple spent around £2,000 on flights and accommodation for the trip. But Mr Stevenson mistakenly answered a question on the Esta visa form, which asked if he was a terrorist, by declaring that he was one. The couple now fear that the 70-year-old will never be allowed into the US again. - Read more US visa applicants might have to hand over their ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>How China uses 'exit bans' on relatives to force suspected fugitives to return - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/china-uses-exit-bans-relatives-force-suspected-fugitives-return/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEFZeAjApYbiKRXSWw1yvE4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/11/28/china-uses-exit-bans-relatives-force-suspected-fugitives-return/" target="_blank"&gt;How China uses 'exit bans' on relatives to force suspected fugitives to return&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;China is preventing the family members of suspected fugitives, including foreign nationals, from leaving the country in order to force alleged criminals to return and face charges. Among those are Americans Sandra Han and her two adult children, Victor and Cynthia Liu. Ms Han’s husband, Liu Changming, a former executive at a state-owned bank, stands accused of being at the centre of one of China’s largest bank frauds, totalling £1 billion. Ms Han is being held in a secret jail, and her children have not been allowed to leave China since arriving this summer to visit a sick relative, accordi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>De La Rue profits slump after losing contract to make blue UK passports after Brexit - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/brexit-blue-passport-de-la-rue-profits-contract-gemalto-economy-a8653476.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFIHUWJJg4eXKKiVixu8UOwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRxP0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 08:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/brexit-blue-passport-de-la-rue-profits-contract-gemalto-economy-a8653476.html" target="_blank"&gt;De La Rue profits slump after losing contract to make blue UK passports after Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Banknote printer and passport maker De La Rue has reported a slump in profit in the first half of the year, after losing a key contract to manufacture UK passports. Despite revenue rising 5 per cent to £257.6m, operating profit plunged by 36 per cent from £26.6m to £17m. The company took a hit earlier this year when the government decided to award the contract for post-Brexit British passports to Franco-Dutch group Gemalto. De La Rue’s 10-year contract, worth £400m, will come to an end in July 2019. Read more - De La Rue sensibly quits battle over blue passports - UK firm 'will not appeal' ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Why do we cancel passports for terror suspects — and not just let them leave? - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-21/why-do-we-cancel-passports-for-terror-suspects-and-not-arrest/10517112</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDtJH-EWN9sfaPDKcRydIUqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD6kIkG</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:28:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-21/why-do-we-cancel-passports-for-terror-suspects-and-not-arrest/10517112" target="_blank"&gt;Why do we cancel passports for terror suspects — and not just let them leave?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has been revealed the trio charged with plotting a terrorist attack in Melbourne all had their passports previously cancelled. Two weeks ago we found out Bourke Street killer Hassan Khalif Shire Ali's passport was cancelled in 2015. It's prompted some to ask why, if we deem someone such a threat, do we cancel their passport? Why not just arrest them, or let them leave to fight and maybe die in a conflict overseas? External Link: Why do we cancel passports? External Link: Why do we cancel passports? Why do we cancel passports? The first and most simple reason is Australia has a legal obli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Freed Pakistani Christian needs German passport to leave: lawyer - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-blasphemy-lawyer/freed-pakistani-christian-needs-german-passport-to-leave-lawyer-idUSKCN1NP19I</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENpS63VmD1lDUE0sNePLdn8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 18:37:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pakistan-blasphemy-lawyer/freed-pakistani-christian-needs-german-passport-to-leave-lawyer-idUSKCN1NP19I" target="_blank"&gt;Freed Pakistani Christian needs German passport to leave: lawyer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lawyer for Asia Bibi, a Pakistani Christian acquitted of capital blasphemy charges, appealed on Tuesday to Germany to give her whole family citizenship to start a new life in Europe. Saiful Mulook told a news conference in Frankfurt that Bibi was now free but she and her family needed a passport to leave the country. Bibi, 53, was convicted of blasphemy in 2010 over allegations she made derogatory remarks about Islam after neighbors objected to her drinking water from their glass because she was not Muslim. The Supreme Court acquitted her last month. "The whole world is asking why she's...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Brexit: EU to decide whether Britons will need visas in event of no-deal - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/brexit-news-no-deal-visa-travel-eu-holiday-passport-strasbourg-a8631011.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFU_VCoccThjR5Y4tTgIZ7EqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 09:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/brexit-news-no-deal-visa-travel-eu-holiday-passport-strasbourg-a8631011.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit: EU to decide whether Britons will need visas in event of no-deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;European officials are meeting in Strasbourg to decide if British travellers will need a visa to visit the EU in the event of a no-deal Brexit. These are the key questions. What’s happening? The College of Commissioners – the political leadership of the European Commission, effectively the EU’s cabinet – will decide how the European Union will treat the UK after Brexit, if no agreement is reached on a transition period. What are the options? The default position for a third country is that it joins the “visa required” list, along with people from China, Russia, India, Thailand, and all of A...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Scouted: Passport Covers For Kids Will Help You Win at Parenting - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/passport-covers-for-kids-will-help-you-win-at-parenting</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSeS9cXBxX7iF_EigSGRjYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/passport-covers-for-kids-will-help-you-win-at-parenting" target="_blank"&gt;Scouted: Passport Covers For Kids Will Help You Win at Parenting&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first thing I bought when I learned I was pregnant was not a crib, nor a pack of swaddles, nor any other product related to the day-to-day logistics of infant care. Rather, it was a $13.99 passport cover—a cute, pastel little thing scrawled with “Off to See the World!” At that point, I didn’t know how to change a diaper, but I did know that I wanted to raise a traveler. According to the State Department, some 60 percent of U.S. citizens don’t own a passport. Couple that with the Trump Administration’s travel ban, visa restrictions, and curtailing of refugees, plus reports that passports...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>'I've been warned about overstaying my US visa – even though I left the country months ago' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/advice/overstaying-us-visa-warning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN4Lo1jzzCYvFVzHY6qZxeIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 10:07:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/advice/overstaying-us-visa-warning/" target="_blank"&gt;'I've been warned about overstaying my US visa – even though I left the country months ago'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peter Hill writes In June my wife and I spent two weeks touring the United States and Canada. We flew from the UK into Seattle and departed for Canada three days later on the fast ferry to Victoria on Vancouver Island. At the end of our trip we flew back to the UK from Calgary. At the end of August we both had an email from US Customs and Border Protection stating that we must leave the US within 10 days to comply with our ESTA visa requirements. It would seem that we were never signed out of the US by the port authorities at Seattle. Three weeks ago I contacted the Department of Homeland S...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Henley Index: Japanese passport now world's most powerful - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/most-powerful-passport-henley-index-2018/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL8AnglNSUyjHOsKYD8zBuMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMMXoyQU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 18:01:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/most-powerful-passport-henley-index-2018/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Henley Index: Japanese passport now world's most powerful&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;World's most powerful passports: Global citizenship and residence advisory firm Henley &amp; Partners has released its quarterly report on the world's most desirable passports. Citizens of Hungary (such as this chap), Slovenia and Malaysia can enjoy seamless travel to 180 destinations. AFP/AFP/AFP/Getty Images 9. Iceland: The wild and wonderful landscape of Iceland has proved a magnet for foreign visitors in recent years, but Icelanders themselves can easily head in the other direction with visa-free or visa-on-arrival access to 181 destinations. Joe Raedle/Getty Images 8. Czech Republic and Ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Americans to Get Access to Shorter UK Airport Passport Line - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/americans-to-get-access-to-shorter-uk-airport-passport-line/4635194.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDB_qSTjz4IhEAZwGsqlxe8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 15:16:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/americans-to-get-access-to-shorter-uk-airport-passport-line/4635194.html" target="_blank"&gt;Americans to Get Access to Shorter UK Airport Passport Line&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The head of Europe's largest airport is urging the British government to quickly implement plans allowing more overseas passengers, including Americans, to use the shorter e-passport gates. Under the plan outlined by Treasury chief Philip Hammond in his budget Monday, air passengers from the United States, Canada, Australia, New Zealand and Japan will be allowed to use the gates starting this summer. Heathrow CEO John Holland-Kaye said Tuesday the government should think about making it happen sooner, perhaps before March, when Britain is set to leave the European Union. He says doing so wo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>AI lie detectors to be tested by the EU at border points - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/01/ai-lie-detectors-tested-eu-border-points/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJ87yHN_Ez3VRPoCig4A3IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCuqhU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 11:19:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/11/01/ai-lie-detectors-tested-eu-border-points/" target="_blank"&gt;AI lie detectors to be tested by the EU at border points&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lie detectors equipped with artificial intelligence are set to be tested at border points in Europe as part of an EU-funded project to combat crime and terrorism. Travellers will be asked to upload pictures of their passport, visa and proof of funds, and will then use a webcam to answer questions such as "what is in your suitcase" from a computer-animated border guard. The €4.5m project, called iBorderCtrl, will be tested at the borders of Hungary, Latvia and Greece for six months. The aim of the project is to speed up traffic at the EU's external borders. The UK, Spain, Poland, Germany an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Traveling to the UK is about to get easier (for some) - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/fast-tracked-passport-control-uk-heathrow/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHyeF0ihV_nJEaQUDgDGyyMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 13:18:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/fast-tracked-passport-control-uk-heathrow/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Traveling to the UK is about to get easier (for some)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;World's most powerful passports: Global citizenship and residence advisory firm Henley &amp; Partners has released its quarterly report on the world's most desirable passports. Citizens of Hungary (such as this chap), Slovenia and Malaysia can enjoy seamless travel to 180 destinations. AFP/AFP/AFP/Getty Images 9. Iceland: The wild and wonderful landscape of Iceland has proved a magnet for foreign visitors in recent years, but Icelanders themselves can easily head in the other direction with visa-free or visa-on-arrival access to 181 destinations. Joe Raedle/Getty Images 8. Czech Republic and Ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>British applications for Irish passports almost double as Brexit looms - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/10/31/uk/irish-passport-applications-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELWwc8gBfQAWgBGHpBPe-RMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 13:32:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/10/31/uk/irish-passport-applications-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;British applications for Irish passports almost double as Brexit looms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of British residents applying for Irish passports has almost doubled since the Brexit referendum, new figures show. Negotiations over the UK's scheduled March 2019 departure from the European Union (EU) are complex and ongoing, but its citizens are likely to lose their current rights to move freely through the bloc's 27 other member countries. As a result many people are seeking to acquire a second citizenship within the bloc. A large proportion have been looking to the Republic of Ireland and that number is continuing to rise, according to Neale Richmond, chairman of the Brexit ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Employers to have transition period before EU right-to-work checks - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/nov/01/home-office-caroline-nokes-eu-checks-immigration-brexit-employers-right-to-work</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG7eng5yYmyUl58fY6zZxksqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDHmu8F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 11:48:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/nov/01/home-office-caroline-nokes-eu-checks-immigration-brexit-employers-right-to-work" target="_blank"&gt;Employers to have transition period before EU right-to-work checks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Employers will have a transition period before being forced to make immigration checks on EU citizens in the event of a no-deal Brexit, the government has said, contradicting comments from the immigration minister, Caroline Nokes. The home secretary, Sajid Javid, told ITV’s Peston there would be a “sensible transition period” for EU citizens should an agreement not be reached. “We’ve just got to be practical,” he said. Downing Street confirmed Javid was right to say a transition period would be a likely solution to help employers adapt to new immigration enforcement, contradicting Nokes’s r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Confusion about who can get an Irish passport shows how poorly informed we are about Brexit - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/irish-passport-british-citizen-applications-surge-information-brexit-no-deal-andrew-bridgen-a8610986.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMdijcCskaPwte4T5wpXx-8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 16:56:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/voices/irish-passport-british-citizen-applications-surge-information-brexit-no-deal-andrew-bridgen-a8610986.html" target="_blank"&gt;Confusion about who can get an Irish passport shows how poorly informed we are about Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rush to claim Irish heritage and ensure your rights to freedom of movement among the 27 EU states that will remain after 29 March next year shows no sign of slowing down, with Irish passport applications surging again in the first half of this year. Since the Brexit vote, people have been scrabbling around trying to find an Irish grandparent to ensure their ability to live and work in the rest of the EU. Of course, relatives from other European nations will do too, but it’s thought that at least 10 per cent of the British population, not including Northern Ireland, qualifies for Irish p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Australians to be fast-tracked through UK immigration from 2019 - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-30/australians-to-be-fast-tracked-through-uk-immigration/10445312</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHqnSJ9-QZh6Ev467vtEjBUqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 19:57:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-30/australians-to-be-fast-tracked-through-uk-immigration/10445312" target="_blank"&gt;Australians to be fast-tracked through UK immigration from 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australians will be able to be fast-tracked through immigration upon arriving in the UK from next year, the British Government says. External Link: Aus High Commission tweet: "Our High Commissioner George Brandis warmly welcomes the #Budget2018 announcement by @hmtreasury @PhilipHammondUK that Aussie passport holders will soon be able to use UK ePassport gates - we've been working towards this for some time so it is great to see it announced. ✈️" Chancellor to the Exchequer Philip Hammond made the surprise announcement when delivering the UK's budget at the House of Commons, saying those wi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Americans to get access to shorter UK airport passport line - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/0f1eaa83db974cd8b9821c73c35a8ab8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGaYs5fNDKV_lP8OhSAjOfUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 14:48:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/0f1eaa83db974cd8b9821c73c35a8ab8" target="_blank"&gt;Americans to get access to shorter UK airport passport line&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;LONDON (AP) — The head of Europe's largest airport is urging the British government to quickly implement plans allowing more overseas passengers, including Americans, to use the shorter e-passport gates. Under the plan outlined by Treasury chief Philip Hammond in his budget Monday, air passengers from the United States, Canada, Australia, New Zealand and Japan will be allowed to use the gates starting this summer. Heathrow CEO John Holland-Kaye said Tuesday the government should think about making it happen sooner, perhaps before March, when Britain is set to leave the European Union. He sa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Opening of UK ePassport Gates Is Great News For US Travelers - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/zakdoffman/2018/10/30/opening-of-uk-epassport-gates-is-great-news-for-us-travelers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELryG73-a13TTX7SQnOwCfYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/zakdoffman/2018/10/30/opening-of-uk-epassport-gates-is-great-news-for-us-travelers/" target="_blank"&gt;Opening of UK ePassport Gates Is Great News For US Travelers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday’s news that United Kingdom ePassport gates will open to travelers from outside Europe for the first time will be welcomed by regular visitors to the country, including nearly four million from the United States. Overseas visitors to the UK have endured a year of painful immigration queues, and this was a clear signal as to the intended international openness of a post-Brexit Britain: easier trade, easier travel. London Gatwick Airport ePassport Gates. (Photo by Oli Scarff/Getty Images) However, the announcement made by UK Chancellor Philip Hammond in his ‘give-away’ budget, might ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Barred from flying from a British airport – over a visa he didn’t need - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/money/2018/oct/22/airlines-bar-passengers-visa-rules-no-recourse</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAcZ6hbH6ldg6kUYj7ucMR4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDMwRU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 10:24:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/money/2018/oct/22/airlines-bar-passengers-visa-rules-no-recourse" target="_blank"&gt;Barred from flying from a British airport – over a visa he didn’t need&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Varun Warrier spent months planning a hiking holiday in the former Soviet republic of Georgia to celebrate a friend’s birthday. The Indian academic, who holds a British residence permit, never got further than the Wizz Air check-in desk at Luton airport. Staff told him he could not travel without a visa and refused to check him in even when he produced an email from the Georgian embassy confirming that British residence permit holders are exempt from visas for short stays. Warrier had to return home to Cambridge while his travel companions took off without him. “Wizz Air staff did not accep...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>British relatives of Nazi-era refugees seek German passports before Brexit - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/19/british-relatives-of-nazi-victims-seek-german-passports-before-brexit</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF8ZsmZ4ISJJA-TZBgSAOQgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 13:23:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/19/british-relatives-of-nazi-victims-seek-german-passports-before-brexit" target="_blank"&gt;British relatives of Nazi-era refugees seek German passports before Brexit&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;British descendants of refugees who fled Nazi Germany, including many Jewish families, are racing to secure German nationality so they can remain EU citizens after Brexit, according to official data. The number of Britons applying for German passports using a special legal provision, article 116-2, that aims to make amends for Nazi-era persecutions has soared by more than 1,500% since the UK voted to leave the bloc in June 2016. Germany received 43 such passport requests in 2015 and 684 in 2016, nearly all of them submitted after the Brexit referendum. Last year the number jumped again to 1...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>What are 'golden passport' schemes and how do they enable tax dodging? - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/analysis-and-features/golden-passports-explained-visas-oecd-tax-dodging-investors-a8587051.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELrstiJx2Yi_SmhzecUmypsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 16:20:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/analysis-and-features/golden-passports-explained-visas-oecd-tax-dodging-investors-a8587051.html" target="_blank"&gt;What are 'golden passport' schemes and how do they enable tax dodging?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The OECD, a multilateral club of mostly rich countries, has created a blacklist of countries that offer “golden passports” or special investor visas to overseas investors which it says undermine the fight against tax dodging. But what are these golden passports? Who offers them? How to they interfere with the battle against tax dodging? And what action will be needed to crack down on this practice? What are golden passports? They are schemes which essentially allow rich foreign investors to buy citizenship, or long term residency rights, in a country. For instance Cyprus offers citizenship ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>The passport king who markets citizenship for cash - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/16/the-passport-king-who-markets-citizenship-for-cash</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDTgCzmylbniyHO3eXWjHjgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 15:00:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/16/the-passport-king-who-markets-citizenship-for-cash" target="_blank"&gt;The passport king who markets citizenship for cash&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was supposed to be a lunch, but the Swiss businessman was not eating. As his companions tucked into their pasta, Christian Kälin sipped mineral water. Related: Henley &amp; Partners statement The party had gathered at a restaurant overlooking the golf course in Frigate Bay, on the Caribbean island of St Kitts. Kälin, wiry and softly spoken, was in town to keep an eye on the general election in the former British colony. The date had been set for 25 January 2010. With him was Alexander Nix, the now-notorious founder of Cambridge Analytica. Back then, the bespectacled old Etonian was running t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Cheech and Chong star tries to travel to Canada for cannabis legalisation day 'but can't find passport' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/tommy-chong-canada-cannabis-legal-cheech-legalisation-drugs-passport-marijuana-a8587691.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHz04rD3Tp80IUE90QjRChcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 08:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/tommy-chong-canada-cannabis-legal-cheech-legalisation-drugs-passport-marijuana-a8587691.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cheech and Chong star tries to travel to Canada for cannabis legalisation day 'but can't find passport'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canada’s most famous stoner, comedian and actor Tommy Chong, is unsure if he can make it back home for the day cannabis is legalised because he has lost his passport. The 80-year-old, who starred in the famous reefer comedy Up In Smoke in 1972 and now lives in California, was supposed to appear at an event in British Columbia on Wednesday but discovered while packing that he has mislaid his travel documents. “We’re trying. Right now, I’m stuck here. I lost my passport, so we’re going through the dance of a celebrity trying to get a passport fast,” he told the Toronto Star. - Read more Stop ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>'Golden passports' firm was consulted by government over investor visas - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/17/golden-passports-firm-was-consulted-by-government-over-investor-visas</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKF1O5NcoLRhsBSL2z5yonYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:59:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/17/golden-passports-firm-was-consulted-by-government-over-investor-visas" target="_blank"&gt;'Golden passports' firm was consulted by government over investor visas&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Henley &amp; Partners, the firm at the centre of the Caribbean passports controversy, was among a group of private-sector specialists consulted by the UK government ahead of changes to immigration rules that led to a surge in wealthy Russians and other non-Europeans securing the right to live in Britain. Theresa May’s Home Office redesigned its visa programme with a view to attracting rich foreign investors, after the coalition had entered government, as ministers pursued investment from global elites. The changes came as the then home secretary was introducing controversial hostile environment...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The World's Most Powerful Passports [Infographic] - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/niallmccarthy/2018/10/11/the-worlds-most-powerful-passports-infographic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH3NKgVjwND5419M3BYUnNUqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/niallmccarthy/2018/10/11/the-worlds-most-powerful-passports-infographic/" target="_blank"&gt;The World's Most Powerful Passports [Infographic]&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some passports afford their bearers more freedom than others and if you’re a U.S. holder, you’ll be able to enjoy an impressive level of visa-free travel. According to the latest edition of the Henley Passport Index, the U.S. passport is one of the world’s most powerful, granting its holders visa-free access or visa-on-arrival access to 186 countries. That’s a level of freedom shared with Austria, Luxembourg, the Netherlands, Norway, Portugal and the United Kingdom. After its citizens gained visa-free access to Myanmar earlier this month, Japan has been named the country with the most power...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Which country has the most powerful passport in the world? - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-11/which-country-has-the-most-powerful-passport-in-the-world/10363766</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENnnmVCwayEdrlOv0nM7uPQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDoiokG</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 06:12:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-11/which-country-has-the-most-powerful-passport-in-the-world/10363766" target="_blank"&gt;Which country has the most powerful passport in the world?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Erin Handley Japan now has the most powerful passport in the world in terms of travel freedom, according to the 2018 Henley Passport Index. Japanese citizens can enter without a visa or get a visa on arrival to 190 countries, overtaking Singapore, which enjoys visa-free access to 189 countries. Germany, France and South Korea tied in third, with a group of European nations — Denmark, Finland, Italy, Sweden and Spain — in hot pursuit. The United Kingdom and the United States slid down into the fifth spot with other European countries, followed by Belgium, Switzerland, Ireland and Canada i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Super-rich passport schemes open door to criminals, activists say - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/10/super-rich-passport-schemes-open-door-to-criminals-activists-say</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHArHSAWRLW7N8dWU1GWPXkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 08:00:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/10/super-rich-passport-schemes-open-door-to-criminals-activists-say" target="_blank"&gt;Super-rich passport schemes open door to criminals, activists say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;European governments have been accused of opening the door to criminals through lax sales of passports and visas to the super-rich. The European Union had gained nearly 100,000 new residents and 6,000 new citizens in the last decade through poorly managed residency and passport sale schemes that were “shrouded in secrecy”, a report by Transparency International and Global Witness says. The campaign groups studied four EU member states that sell passports and 12 that offer residency rights to foreign investors. Spain, Hungary, Latvia, Portugal and the UK have granted the most “golden visas” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Japan now offers world's most powerful passport - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/gallery/henley-passport-index-2018-photos/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMVf4nmxO93tqVoWbxKuS_YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 11:42:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/travel/gallery/henley-passport-index-2018-photos/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Japan now offers world's most powerful passport&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;World's most powerful passports: Global citizenship and residence advisory firm Henley &amp; Partners has released its quarterly report on the world's most desirable passports. Citizens of Hungary (such as this chap), Slovenia and Malaysia can enjoy seamless travel to 180 destinations. AFP/AFP/AFP/Getty Images 9. Iceland: The wild and wonderful landscape of Iceland has proved a magnet for foreign visitors in recent years, but Icelanders themselves can easily head in the other direction with visa-free or visa-on-arrival access to 181 destinations. Joe Raedle/Getty Images 8. Czech Republic and Ne...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Japanese passport is now the strongest in the world - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/japan-visa-henley-passport-index-singapore-uk-us-best-worst-a8575666.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFI6xwpzVUMP53Vt-GGOp1UqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 14:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/japan-visa-henley-passport-index-singapore-uk-us-best-worst-a8575666.html" target="_blank"&gt;The Japanese passport is now the strongest in the world&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese passport is now the strongest in the world, overtaking Singapore, according to research released today. According to the 2018 Henley Passport Index released today, Japanese citizens can travel without a visa or gain a visa on arrival in 190 destinations – the most globally. The Japanese passport overtook the Singapore passport, which allows travel to 189 destinations without a prior visa, after gaining visa-free access to Myanmar earlier this year. - Read more With only 200 days until Brexit, here's what we do and don't know Third place is shared with Germany, South Korea and F...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>UK slides again as world's most powerful passports revealed - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/powerful-passports-2018/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEItDEcEmMiXyJ8WX22WqKw8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/powerful-passports-2018/" target="_blank"&gt;UK slides again as world's most powerful passports revealed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan has knocked Singapore off top spot on the list of the world’s most powerful passport, according to new research, while the UK has slipped again to 11th. The ranking by Henley &amp; Partners, a citizenship and planning firm, takes into account how many countries can be visited without applying for a visa. Japanese citizens can travel to a record 190 out of a possible 218, having recently gained visa-free access to Myanmar, while Singaporeans can visit 189 and Britons 186. Japan and Singapore had previously been neck and neck - both on 189 - following a visa-exemption from Uzbekistan, with ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Fish and chips but no passport: Windrush victim returns to UK - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/11/windrush-ken-morgan-stuck-jamaica-passport-confiscated-returns-uk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC3KfB4Bj3CHDl_uiVotlBYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 10:18:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/11/windrush-ken-morgan-stuck-jamaica-passport-confiscated-returns-uk" target="_blank"&gt;Fish and chips but no passport: Windrush victim returns to UK&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ken Morgan, a Windrush victim who spent the past 25 years in Jamaica after his British passport was taken from him, had been looking forward to tucking into some fish and chips the day he finally returned to the UK. But he was taken back by what his local shop served him. “It shocked me, I didn’t know it had morphed into this fine food. Fish and chips is fish and chips – street food. It’s morphed into a gourmet dish. What the hell?” He was also stunned to learn it now cost £8. But much of his hometown was how he remembered it. The Walthamstow markets still served an abundance of fruit and v...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>EU to act on visa-for-sale schemes after warnings of money laundering risks - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eu-passports/eu-to-act-on-visa-for-sale-schemes-after-warnings-of-money-laundering-risks-idUSKCN1MK0S0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELZsoFViWyAjSszvQOWfoTAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 11:32:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eu-passports/eu-to-act-on-visa-for-sale-schemes-after-warnings-of-money-laundering-risks-idUSKCN1MK0S0" target="_blank"&gt;EU to act on visa-for-sale schemes after warnings of money laundering risks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Commission said on Wednesday it will provide guidance to EU states on how to manage national schemes to sell passports and residency permits to wealthy foreign citizens, as campaigners and lawmakers warned of money laundering risks. Government schemes to trade citizenship or residence rights for large investment are currently applied in 13 EU countries: Austria, Cyprus, Luxembourg, Malta, Greece, Latvia, Portugal, Spain, Ireland, Britain, Bulgaria, the Netherlands and France. Hungary has terminated its program. "If you have a lot of money that you acquired through dubious means...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Artist Tom Sachs is selling Swiss 'passports' for €20 - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/tom-sachs-swiss-passport/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELunpdTyRWAPZ6CylxFkjJgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 08:42:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/style/article/tom-sachs-swiss-passport/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Artist Tom Sachs is selling Swiss 'passports' for €20&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In March 2019, the United Kingdom is set to leave the European Union, and while politicians are still arguing terms for the divorce and many people disagree about the full implications of a post Brexit world for all sides, one common question among many has been: Will I be able to move as freely as before? All passports are not equal; the rights yours offers, such as the ability to stay or even work in other countries without the hassle of first obtaining a visa, depend on the global standing of the issuing government and as such some passports are more coveted than others, and whether the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Most Powerful Passports, the Least Expensive Michelin-Starred Restaurants and More - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/passport/2018/10/12/the-most-powerful-passports-the-least-expensive-michelin-starred-restaurants-and-more/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED5XjBtocQFB1PUW8UJ29EcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMLGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/passport/2018/10/12/the-most-powerful-passports-the-least-expensive-michelin-starred-restaurants-and-more/" target="_blank"&gt;The Most Powerful Passports, the Least Expensive Michelin-Starred Restaurants and More&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;5 Hotel Spas with a Twist Not all spas are created equal. While most feature a soothing ambiance, areas to swim and sauna, and rooms for massages, facials and scrubs, there are many that stand out because of the unique experiences they provide. These five hotel spas offer luxurious twists that will keep you coming back for more. Spa Treatment in a Treehouse: Marigot Bay Resort, St. Lucia You don’t have to be a kid to dream about escaping to a treehouse. At St. Lucia’s Marigot Bay Resort, above, you can get a treatment in their beautiful treehouse, which is surrounded by the island’s lush fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Brexit and travel: Leaving the EU is turning into a disaster movie for holidaymakers - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/brexit-no-deal-travel-europe-flights-healthcare-a8578431.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGdhsiM8Kf5DjgDM02QN8IAqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 07:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/brexit-no-deal-travel-europe-flights-healthcare-a8578431.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit and travel: Leaving the EU is turning into a disaster movie for holidaymakers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A no-deal Brexit would be ‘a disaster’ for Spain, the country’s UK tourism chief has warned” – so began a news story from this week’s Abta Travel Convention in Seville. Javier Piñanes, director of the Spanish tourist office in London, may have been more candid that his advisers wished. Yet by naming the issues that desperately need to be resolved by 29 March 2019, he has done the travel industry – and holidaymakers – a favour. On an average day, more than 50,000 British visitors touch down in Spain, far more than any other nationality. Several million of us have already booked places on th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Missouri Judge Strikes Down Portion Of State's Voter ID Law - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/missouri-voter-id-law-photo-id_us_5bbd261ae4b028e1fe42b140</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELDfAgAG7gf6Rx6yMDADidAqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:53:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/missouri-voter-id-law-photo-id_us_5bbd261ae4b028e1fe42b140" target="_blank"&gt;Missouri Judge Strikes Down Portion Of State's Voter ID Law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Missouri judge upheld most of the state’s voter ID law on Tuesday, but struck down one provision that required voters to sign a sworn affidavit if they wanted to vote but did not have one of the favored forms of photo identification. Under the state law, which went into effect in 2017, people must show a Missouri driver’s or nondriver’s license, a passport or a military identification card ― all of which have photos ― before they can cast their ballot. If they don’t have any of those, they can show a number of other prescribed forms of identification that may not have photos. Under the pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>EU states warned over billions banked through ‘golden visa’ schemes - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/3084f63a-cc5e-11e8-b276-b9069bde0956</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEppsvkGtQiR-gMvq1vFexAqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 09:24:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/3084f63a-cc5e-11e8-b276-b9069bde0956" target="_blank"&gt;EU states warned over billions banked through ‘golden visa’ schemes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;EU states have banked tens of billions of euros in investment from “golden visa” schemes that open the door to criminals even as the bloc takes a hard public line on corruption, two leading anti-graft campaign groups have warned. At least 6,000 passports and almost 100,000 residence permits have been granted in the past decade under programmes that are sometimes laxly supervised, according to research published on Wednesday jointly by Global Witness and Transparency International. The paper stokes concerns that the widespread money-for-status schemes offer kleptocrat cronies and criminal ga...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>FCA unveils no-deal Brexit plan for EU finance firms - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/d35903f2-cc99-11e8-9fe5-24ad351828ab</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF5BHGvSQxE4OkcCZZfEGXUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw4tp6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 19:02:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d35903f2-cc99-11e8-9fe5-24ad351828ab" target="_blank"&gt;FCA unveils no-deal Brexit plan for EU finance firms&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK financial regulator on Wednesday stepped up its preparations for a no-deal Brexit by outlining detailed plans for the oversight of EU financial services firms with operations in Britain. The Financial Conduct Authority published a blueprint for how it would issue temporary authorisations for EU firms doing business in the UK. The regulator also revealed that 1,300 EU firms that have activities in Britain would be willing to sign up to its proposal that they have time-limited permits lasting three years. This figure represents fewer than 20 per cent of the 8,000 EU entities that hold ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>It’s Absurd to Claim That Non-Binary People Are a ‘Security Risk’ - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/its-absurd-to-claim-that-non-binary-people-are-a-security-risk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP5_XDzdY77IVLVxkWmJ1AcqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMIv-lwI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 08:56:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/its-absurd-to-claim-that-non-binary-people-are-a-security-risk" target="_blank"&gt;It’s Absurd to Claim That Non-Binary People Are a ‘Security Risk’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast Like clockwork, the same myth emerges every time there’s progress for non-binary people who want more gender options on their identity documents: Allowing an “X” option in addition to “M” and “F,” the critics say, could pose a security risk. This time, it’s a lawmaker in Minnesota who questioned the state’s recent introduction of a new “X” option for driver’s licenses. As the Minneapolis Star Tribune reported in their article on the change—which took effect this Monday—Republican state senator Scott Newman responded in a statement: “Will this change ham...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Nauru 19: at least three members denied passports despite court throwing out case - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/04/nauru-19-at-least-three-members-denied-passports-despite-court-throwing-out-case</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO9mjUU6FSjIOOcgEh48He0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/04/nauru-19-at-least-three-members-denied-passports-despite-court-throwing-out-case" target="_blank"&gt;Nauru 19: at least three members denied passports despite court throwing out case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Nauruan government has refused passports to at least three members of the so-called Nauru 19, who were charged over attending a political rally in 2015, despite the court throwing out a criminal case against them. The three people, including a former Nauruan government minister, were all told their applications were rejected on the grounds of “potential for harmful conduct” legislation. The trio wrote to the minister on Wednesday, asking him to explain the decision and detail the concerns he held about them. “We believe the minister needs to give us clarification on what his concerns ar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Quiz: Which passport stamps can you identify? - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/quizzes/Which-passport-stamps-can-you-identify/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDKkW_QyfyDFxXvhAi-90gMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 08:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/quizzes/Which-passport-stamps-can-you-identify/" target="_blank"&gt;Quiz: Which passport stamps can you identify?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will Brexit mean that we get more passport stamps? Possibly. In fact, some might say that it's the best by-product of leaving the EU. Inspired by this prospect, we've devised the following quiz. Which passport stamps will you recognise? Find out below. • Why is renewing a child's passport so difficult? • The world’s coolest passport • The world's most powerful passports&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tim Dowling: ‘I know better than to risk flippancy at passport control’ - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/oct/06/tim-dowling-i-know-better-than-to-risk-flippancy-at-passport-control</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFQiEN8BySwfvsWdyxX1cH8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCcwRU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 05:00:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/oct/06/tim-dowling-i-know-better-than-to-risk-flippancy-at-passport-control" target="_blank"&gt;Tim Dowling: ‘I know better than to risk flippancy at passport control’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heathrow airport, some months ago: my wife, my middle son and I arrive back from holiday. At passport control they both go through the electronic gates, while I follow signs for non-EU arrivals. It’s only after I turn the corner that I see the queue is enormous, winding back on itself a dozen times. Fifteen minutes after joining the queue, I have yet to reach the first turn. After 20 minutes I ring my wife. “You should go home,” I say. “I’ll be at least another hour.” “Really?” she says. “I feel a bit shifty leaving you.” “There’s no point in you waiting,” I say. I can hear her turning away...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Ukraine, Hungary expel consuls as passport row deepens - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-hungary/ukraine-hungary-expel-consuls-as-passport-row-deepens-idUSKCN1ME0V0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENL9t7enurooeiyOFn3WbSkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 12:09:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-hungary/ukraine-hungary-expel-consuls-as-passport-row-deepens-idUSKCN1ME0V0" target="_blank"&gt;Ukraine, Hungary expel consuls as passport row deepens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ukraine and Hungary announced tit-for-tat expulsions of each other's diplomats on Thursday, the latest in a series of spats between the neighbors that threatens to set back Kiev's aspirations for European Union and NATO membership. Ukraine said it had given a Hungarian consul 72 hours to leave the country after accusing his consulate of illegally issuing passports to members of an ethnic Hungarian minority in Ukraine. Ukraine's constitution bars Ukrainians from holding citizenship of other countries. Kiev accused the consul, who is based in the western town of Berehove near the Hungarian bo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Syrian asylum seeker living in Malaysia airport since March arrested and threatened with deportation - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/hassan-kontar-syria-malaysia-airport-terminal-arrest-deportation-a8565046.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE9kICoJxYfBuxqCCOqJwFMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCRx_0F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/hassan-kontar-syria-malaysia-airport-terminal-arrest-deportation-a8565046.html" target="_blank"&gt;Syrian asylum seeker living in Malaysia airport since March arrested and threatened with deportation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Syrian asylum seeker stuck in transit in Kuala Lumpur airport since March has been arrested by the Malaysian authorities who said he will be deported to his home country. Hassan al-Kontar, 36, attracted world attention when he started posting videos of his life stranded at KLIA2, the Malaysian airport’s budget terminal, on Twitter and Facebook. Born in Sweida, southwest Syria, the insurance marketing manager fears returning back to war-torn Syria as he will be forced to do his military service. He was working in the UAE when the Syrian civil war broke out in 2011 but could not renew his p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Russian passport leak after Salisbury may reveal spy methods - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/23/russian-passport-leak-after-salisbury-may-reveal-spy-methods</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOTjhDf_Khv8J-oilvKg-KwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 11:53:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/23/russian-passport-leak-after-salisbury-may-reveal-spy-methods" target="_blank"&gt;Russian passport leak after Salisbury may reveal spy methods&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A leak of Russian government data about the suspects in the Salisbury poisoning may provide a rare insight into how Russia’s military intelligence agency provides cover identities for its agents abroad. Investigative journalists have unearthed what appears to be a series of passports with similar numbers belonging to suspected Russian intelligence officers, including the Salisbury suspects Ruslan Boshirov and Alexander Petrov. The passport holders include a former Russian military attache who was expelled from Poland for espionage in 2014 and is alleged to be tied to an attempted coup in Mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Immigration delays making people ‘suicidal’ as Home Office holds passports for years - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/home-office-uk-immigration-delays-visa-applications-suicidal-passports-a8543246.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGnFAWNo_fxOiYfLqQd8FSEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 19:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/home-office-uk-immigration-delays-visa-applications-suicidal-passports-a8543246.html" target="_blank"&gt;Immigration delays making people ‘suicidal’ as Home Office holds passports for years&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man who has lived in the UK for more than a decade says he has been made to feel “suicidal” after waiting for more than two years for the Home Office to process his settlement application. Mushtaque Shah and his wife Sehar, both Pakistani nationals who have lived in the UK for 12 years and have a British-born daughter, applied for indefinite leave to remain in May 2016. They are still waiting for a decision from the Home Office 28 months later. The family, who live in Newcastle, have been unable to visit terminally ill relatives before they died as the Home Office is holding onto their pa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>‘I’m stuck here’: The desperate search for a passport in Venezuela - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/venezuela-passport-leave-economy-maduro-colombia-border-immigration-a8548806.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH0bSgYlxyvltP0NZDL-Ex0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 13:39:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/venezuela-passport-leave-economy-maduro-colombia-border-immigration-a8548806.html" target="_blank"&gt;‘I’m stuck here’: The desperate search for a passport in Venezuela&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a year struggling to make ends meet under Venezuela's crushing hyperinflation, Jennyfer, and her boyfriend decided to flee the country. Everything was ready, except a small but important detail: Jennyfer’s passport. It is now five months since Jennyfer Avero applied for her travel document. But, until today, the 23-year-old craftswoman from Caracas hasn’t heard a word about the state of her request. Last month, her boyfriend Javier left to Ecuador and became part of one of the biggest exoduses in Latin American history. And in the mean while, Jennyfer continues to wait, hoping she wil...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Judge: US can't deny passport over refusing to pick gender - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/09d479d845ca4f1d930497daea518f54</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJimzOgJSOKh6Wyu9gORa3AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 01:34:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/09d479d845ca4f1d930497daea518f54" target="_blank"&gt;Judge: US can't deny passport over refusing to pick gender&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DENVER (AP) — U.S. officials cannot deny a passport application from an intersex Colorado resident based solely on a refusal to select male or female for gender, a federal judge said Wednesday. The U.S. State Department's varied explanations for rejecting the application weren't reasonable, U.S. District Judge R. Brooke Jackson said in his ruling, forcing him to set aside the decision as "arbitrary and capricious." The ruling is limited, but advocates said they hope it leads to expanded gender choices on federal identification. Dana Zzyym, who was born with ambiguous physical sexual charact...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Bombshell Washington Post Story On Trump Passport Crackdown Withheld, Distorted Key Facts - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/washington-post-trump-passport-crackdown_us_5b9ec246e4b046313fbc2bd1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBT7ZLPTdLQ23rYUvGq8XUgqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 15:28:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/washington-post-trump-passport-crackdown_us_5b9ec246e4b046313fbc2bd1" target="_blank"&gt;Bombshell Washington Post Story On Trump Passport Crackdown Withheld, Distorted Key Facts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUSTIN, Texas ― On Aug. 29, The Washington Post published a bombshell report alleging that the Trump administration had orchestrated a campaign to systematically deny passports to Latinos born along the border. “The Trump administration is accusing hundreds, and possibly thousands, of Latinos along the border of using fraudulent birth certificates since they were babies, and it is undertaking a widespread crackdown,” the paper wrote. But the Post withheld key data, mischaracterized information and lobbed an allegation of fraud at a deceased doctor without speaking to his family members, who...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>For me and millions others, Brexit will turn home turf into a foreign land - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/20/brexit-millions-eu-citizens-foreigners</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEETYH_3dioBz8BSf_9qZKeQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 16:18:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/20/brexit-millions-eu-citizens-foreigners" target="_blank"&gt;For me and millions others, Brexit will turn home turf into a foreign land&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can try and surprise European citizens currently living in the UK, but there is very little chance you will succeed. There are about 3.7 million of us. We are from all over the EU, of various ages, professions and history, and our only shared characteristic is that we have settled in Britain at some point, because we wanted to and could, and then we suddenly became one unit of people – “EU citizens” – in the British public eye, on 24 June 2016. We have lived the past two and a half years in limbo. We heard one home secretary after another promising that we would be fine after Brexit, wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UK passports could lose up to nine months' validity after rule change - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/sep/14/uk-passports-could-lose-up-to-nine-months-validity-after-rule-change</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDt28lxGiTkj9ixbmjdb6RcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 05:00:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/sep/14/uk-passports-could-lose-up-to-nine-months-validity-after-rule-change" target="_blank"&gt;UK passports could lose up to nine months' validity after rule change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Travellers who renew their passports face losing up to nine months’ validity due to a little-publicised change to rules brought in by the Home Office. Up until last week, when British citizens renewed their passports, time remaining on the existing document was added to the new one – up to a maximum of nine months. But passport applicants have been told this no longer applies and any remaining months will be lost if an attempt is made to renew the document early. The change was uncovered by the consumer affairs website Money Saving Expert after members of the public got in touch. The Home O...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Italy stance clear on passports - Conte - Agenzia ANSA</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/09/18/italy-stance-clear-on-passports-conte_cf121595-0725-4efe-838d-be516bcc188a.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDNUDFKYvP830-YH0-GPrzwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 10:49:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/politics/2018/09/18/italy-stance-clear-on-passports-conte_cf121595-0725-4efe-838d-be516bcc188a.html" target="_blank"&gt;Italy stance clear on passports - Conte&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia ANSA&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Rome, September 18 - Premier Giuseppe Conte said Tuesday that he reiterated Italy's opposition to Vienna's plan to give a double passport to Alto Adige's German and Ladin speakers during a meeting with Austrian Chancellor Sebastian Kurz. "I had the opportunity to express to Kurz that Italy has a clear position on the passports and dual nationality," Conte told a joint press conference with Kurz after the leaders met in Rome. On Monday that Italian foreign ministry said Foreign Minister Enzo Moavero Milanesi would not go to Vienna for one of the regular bilateral meetings proposed b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia ANSA</source></item><item><title>Britons 'duped' by new passport renewal policy - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/new-passport-renewal-policy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJoqWBLv5SgcG9da_JrLCB0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 09:01:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/news/new-passport-renewal-policy/" target="_blank"&gt;Britons 'duped' by new passport renewal policy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Government has been accused of short-changing millions of British travellers with an unannounced change to its passport renewal policy. Until this month a Briton renewing their passport would have had any time left over on their old document, up to a maximum of nine months, added to their new one. Someone whose passport expires on March 1, 2019, for example, would have been able to renew today and still be handed a fresh document valid until March 1, 2029. Now, however, a new passport issued to them today will only be valid until September 13, 2028. The change may encourage travellers t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Imran Khan to grant surprise Pakistan citizenship to 1.5 million Afghan refugees - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/pakistan-afghan-refugees-imran-khan-citizenship-grant-prime-minister-a8543131.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJUdOSJbUWTGdd7fv356Nr8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/pakistan-afghan-refugees-imran-khan-citizenship-grant-prime-minister-a8543131.html" target="_blank"&gt;Imran Khan to grant surprise Pakistan citizenship to 1.5 million Afghan refugees&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imran Khan has pledged to grant citizenship to an estimated 1.5 million Afghan refugees, many of whom have lived in Pakistan for decades. The Pakistani prime minister made the surprise announcement during his first visit to Karachi since his election last month. He indicated passports would be given not only to children who were born and brought up in the country but also their parents. Speaking at a fundraiser for dam construction, Mr Khan said the lack of documentation and education had prevented the refugees from getting jobs or accessing the social security system. Read more - More Afgh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Brexit: The tangle of red tape awaiting UK travellers to Europe - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/brexit-travel-europe-holidays-uk-tourists-leave-eu-passports-a8536451.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDPgnIJurAgTIILjfS_gCo8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/brexit-travel-europe-holidays-uk-tourists-leave-eu-passports-a8536451.html" target="_blank"&gt;Brexit: The tangle of red tape awaiting UK travellers to Europe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;British travellers to Europe face a monumental tangle of red tape in the event of a no-deal Brexit. The government has published details of contingency planning for travel if the UK crashes out of the European Union without an agreement. Yet many of the complications may prevail even if a deal is reached; it is unclear what exactly the government is hoping to achieve in terms of post-Brexit travel arrangements. - Read more With only 200 days until Brexit, here's what we do and don't know British passports with EU branding will continue to be valid as UK travel documents after Brexit. But fr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Criminals faking Malaysian identities to obtain Australia visas, exploiting cosy international relationship - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-16/criminals-faking-malaysian-identities-to-obtain-australia-visa/10237506</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMvK1Dnn6VlEht7nUtSNTooqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 19:04:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-16/criminals-faking-malaysian-identities-to-obtain-australia-visa/10237506" target="_blank"&gt;Criminals faking Malaysian identities to obtain Australia visas, exploiting cosy international relationship&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Criminal syndicates are using counterfeiting networks in Malaysia to smuggle people into Australia, exploiting a relaxed visa agreement between the countries. About 10,500 people from Malaysia are in Australia unlawfully — significantly more than any other country. Malaysian passport holders enjoy an easier passage to Australia than people from almost anywhere else — a process that Department of Home Affairs officials have described as "the lightest touch." But an ABC investigation has uncovered that people smugglers have helped nationals of other countries assume fake Malaysian identities ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Frank Foley: Statue for man who saved thousands of German Jews - CNN</title><link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/18/uk/frank-foley-spy-holocaust-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFMu8iSbJ69GKEjQc3GX3PwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:17:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2018/09/18/uk/frank-foley-spy-holocaust-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Frank Foley: Statue for man who saved thousands of German Jews&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former British spy who saved thousands of Jews from death in Nazi Germany will be honored with a statue in his memory on Tuesday. Frank Foley, a former officer with the Secret Intelligence Service, or MI6, who served in both World Wars, saved more than 10,000 people from the Nazis during his time working in Berlin. Prince William, the Duke of Cambridge, will unveil the statue in Stourbridge, the West Midlands English town where Foley died in 1958. Working under cover as a passport control officer, Foley provided visas to Jews who were being persecuted by the Nazis. His work led MI6 to dec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://edition.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Documents reveal Salisbury poisoning suspects' Russian defence ministry ties - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/sep/15/documents-show-novichok-salisbury-suspects-alexander-petrov-ruslan-boshirov-links-defence</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPVGynuLLo3ViWjg5fjTgeAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 13:10:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/sep/15/documents-show-novichok-salisbury-suspects-alexander-petrov-ruslan-boshirov-links-defence" target="_blank"&gt;Documents reveal Salisbury poisoning suspects' Russian defence ministry ties&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Documents uncovered by investigative journalists have provided the first public evidence that the suspects in the Salisbury novichok attack have formal ties to the Russian ministry of defence. British authorities have charged Alexander Petrov and Ruslan Boshirov with conspiracy to murder Sergei and Yulia Skripal and Detective Sergeant Nick Bailey. The former Russian spy and his daughter were found collapsed on 4 March; the police officer fell ill after trying to help them. Prosecutors say Petrov and Boshirov work for Russian military intelligence, which President Vladimir Putin has denied. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Trump State Department Just Made an Ominous Passport Change for Transgender Americans - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-state-department-just-made-an-ominous-passport-change-for-transgender-americans</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBfVKNo0zc6_HV6PUBW26i0qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 11:54:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-state-department-just-made-an-ominous-passport-change-for-transgender-americans" target="_blank"&gt;Trump State Department Just Made an Ominous Passport Change for Transgender Americans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joe Raedle/Getty All the while that the Trump administration has been attacking transgender rights, rescinding school-restroom guidance and trying to kick people out of the military, LGBT advocates have been nervously watching a certain State Department website. That page—now only accessible via an internet archive—showed transgender Americans how to update the gender markers on their U.S. passports. In 2010, under Secretary Hillary Clinton, the State Department began allowing transgender people to change an “M” to an “F” or vice versa without undergoing sex-reassignment surgery, provided t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item></channel></rss>