<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Tokelau - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRGRtT1hFU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-NZ&amp;gl=NZ&amp;ceid=NZ:en</link><language>en-NZ</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:40:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Winston Peters gives early Christmas present to Tokelau - an $860000 boat - TVNZ</title><link>https://www.tvnz.co.nz/one-news/new-zealand/winston-peters-gives-early-christmas-present-tokelau-860-000-boat</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMibWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnR2bnouY28ubnovb25lLW5ld3MvbmV3LXplYWxhbmQvd2luc3Rvbi1wZXRlcnMtZ2l2ZXMtZWFybHktY2hyaXN0bWFzLXByZXNlbnQtdG9rZWxhdS04NjAtMDAwLWJvYXTSAQA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:24:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.tvnz.co.nz/one-news/new-zealand/winston-peters-gives-early-christmas-present-tokelau-860-000-boat" target="_blank"&gt;Winston Peters gives early Christmas present to Tokelau - an $860000 boat&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TVNZ&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deputy PM Winston Peters gifted Tokelau an $860,000 boat today to be used as an emergency response vessel and a ferry between the New Zealand territory's ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.tvnz.co.nz">TVNZ</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/HR0hzsv3Idus-eFRo2g-zSwiLgFYLRn3Qrs01mcrXJ3HohGRQG4Uut5ZgA0EtXZxYLNGGzJxCRYRBX269nK28TcEt7so3tkD1O5Ap0OQ-nJ7rPvTjvEsfDRjnrLFT3Onr3vVHnhMR5Yqmk4lqTXpUqj_vKqZVAtkbPDhOTjYjdf8=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>10 amazing facts about the Pitcairn Islands - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/galleries/bizarre-facts-about-the-pitcairn-islands/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO123GNL5TjDsa6RHZygLlYqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCy8LkF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 13:01:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/galleries/bizarre-facts-about-the-pitcairn-islands/" target="_blank"&gt;10 amazing facts about the Pitcairn Islands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;03 Jul 2017 10 things you probably didn't know about the Pitcairn Islands Previous slideNext slide1 of 11View AllSkip Ad It’s 250 years since the Pitcairn Islands – a remote archipelago in the Pacific Ocean – were discovered by European sailors. Despite being one of the loneliest places on the planet, this British Overseas Territory has a fascinating history and regularly hits the headlines (though not always for the right reasons). Here are 10 things you may not know about this beguiling destination... What's left of the British Empire (and how to visit it) GETTY Back to image&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Detained on Nauru: 'This is the most painful part of my story – when you realise no one cares' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/australia-books-blog/2017/mar/24/detained-on-nauru-this-is-the-most-painful-part-of-my-story-when-you-realise-no-one-cares</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOt5AoGP1AEgoPqQ8pmLCksqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 00:08:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/australia-books-blog/2017/mar/24/detained-on-nauru-this-is-the-most-painful-part-of-my-story-when-you-realise-no-one-cares" target="_blank"&gt;Detained on Nauru: 'This is the most painful part of my story – when you realise no one cares'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benjamin was taken to Nauru in 2013 with his family. He told the first part of this story on Christmas Day 2014. He is still on Nauru. ‘You just have to cope with it’ We were in Offshore Processing Centre compound number 3 – the family compound in the Nauru detention facility – for a year and three weeks. In that time lots of things happened between us and Wilsons, the security guards running the camp, especially with my father because everyone trusted him. So if problems happened, people would tell my father and my father would try to help. But after a couple of months the Wilsons tried to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>France's Secret North American Outpost - The Daily Beast</title><link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2016/10/30/france-s-most-dramatic-little-secret-the-amazing-history-of-st-pierre-miquelon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELOtqXmLUbeSfPCe_6inOB4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 04:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2016/10/30/france-s-most-dramatic-little-secret-the-amazing-history-of-st-pierre-miquelon.html" target="_blank"&gt;France's Secret North American Outpost&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This summer I drove to Europe—but I didn’t put my car on a transatlantic ferry. I walked through Canadian immigration and emerged on the other side in France. One of the world’s oddest geopolitical quirks, St. Pierre &amp; Miquelon, is a small archipelago floating just a short boat ride off the coast of Canada’s Newfoundland. It’s a destination that’s so unexpected, you practically rub your eyes with disbelief at the signs for the France-Canada border crossing overhead. And there’s no mistaking that you’re in France once you arrive: North American decals are swapped for EU license plates, bague...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Navy member of 36 years, Steven Noakes, died on border patrol operation - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-06-28/navy-member-who-died-identified-as-steven-noakes/8661312</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF7jqnJQSQmYHCFz7bL456UqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 10:17:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-06-28/navy-member-who-died-identified-as-steven-noakes/8661312" target="_blank"&gt;Navy member of 36 years, Steven Noakes, died on border patrol operation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Department of Defence has identified the Royal Australian Navy member who died while deployed on a border patrol operation as Lieutenant Commander Steven Noakes. A statement released by Defence on behalf of his family described Lieutenant Commander Noakes as "a much loved husband, father, brother, uncle, son and proud Navy member". "He devoted 36 years of his life to serving his country and for that we couldn't be more proud of him," the statement said. "When not home with his family, he was most happiest when at sea with his crew. "We wish to extend our thanks to his shipmates and coll...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Just 10 People Will See Next Year's Total Solar Eclipse From A Remote Island In The Pacific - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2018/11/16/just-10-people-will-see-next-years-total-solar-eclipse-from-a-remote-island-in-the-pacific/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGbne7amJa-zQSokFOkKWkwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2018/11/16/just-10-people-will-see-next-years-total-solar-eclipse-from-a-remote-island-in-the-pacific/" target="_blank"&gt;Just 10 People Will See Next Year's Total Solar Eclipse From A Remote Island In The Pacific&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oeno Island in the South Pacific is the only place where July 2, 2019′s Path of Totality strikes land until its hits Chile. Experiencing a total solar eclipse is one thing. So how about seeing one from a tiny tropical atoll in the South Pacific? In July 2019 a dramatic total solar eclipse will plunge parts of the southern hemisphere into darkness for a few minutes, just as happened on August 21, 2017 in 14 U.S. states. In 2019, most eclipse-chasers are headed for Chile or Argentina, thinking them the only places that the Path of Totality will cross. From there, a spectacular pre-sunset tota...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Chagos Islanders in UK pin hopes on private member's bill - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/25/chagos-islanders-in-uk-pin-hopes-on-private-members-bill</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJ89VHyUaQGPTyxC7lpnLoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:14:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/25/chagos-islanders-in-uk-pin-hopes-on-private-members-bill" target="_blank"&gt;Chagos Islanders in UK pin hopes on private member's bill&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A private member’s bill providing a legal route to UK citizenship for anyone descended from islanders evicted from British Indian Ocean Territory (BIOT) in the 1960s and 70s is due to have its second reading on Friday. Drafted by Henry Smith, the Conservative MP for Crawley, the proposed legislation will return to the Commons on Friday. Smith has held talks with the home secretary, Sajid Javid, in the hope of securing government support for those with links to BIOT, also known as the Chagos Islands. Smith believes his bill could eventually form part of broader legislation to resolve nationa...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The emotional toll of counselling asylum seekers on Christmas Island 'just to tick a box' - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-14/inside-the-trauma-therapy-sessions-of-christmas-island-detainees/10366218</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENd2xGkYgNr4cyEUXRM-N10qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-14/inside-the-trauma-therapy-sessions-of-christmas-island-detainees/10366218" target="_blank"&gt;The emotional toll of counselling asylum seekers on Christmas Island 'just to tick a box'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Teresa Tan For three years from 2011, social worker Poh Lin Lee worked as a trauma counsellor for the Christmas Island Torture and Trauma Service. She offered therapy and support to detained asylum seekers referred from the nearby detention centre, which closed this month. At her lowest, most conflicted moments she wondered who she was providing the care for. "It might be enough for someone to get through the next week or the next day, but for whose benefit is that?" she says. "Altruistically I like to think it's for the person, but very often it felt very much like it was just for the s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Trevor the 'world's loneliest duck' puts tiny Niue on the map - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-21/trevor-the-worlds-loneliest-duck-puts-tiny-niue-on-the-map/10287508</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKLo67-zyHsGAsV2H32lInIqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 21:00:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-21/trevor-the-worlds-loneliest-duck-puts-tiny-niue-on-the-map/10287508" target="_blank"&gt;Trevor the 'world's loneliest duck' puts tiny Niue on the map&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Catherine Graue When the results came up you may have quickly found yourself dreaming about a tropical island getaway, to a place with glittering turquoise waters and palm trees swaying in the wind. A cynic would say the mysterious story of how a mallard duck made its way to a coral atoll in the Pacific ocean, without wetlands or ponds, is in fact a stroke of marketing brilliance. "I think Trevor is an excellent ambassador for Niue and the reason I say that, is that he has raised the profile of people globally who may or may not have been aware of Niue's existence beforehand," Felicity B...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Mauritius disputes UK acquisition of Chagos Islands in International Criminal Court - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/03/mauritius-disputes-uk-acquisition-chagos-islands-international/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjXcYGdmNeOApv7ki9bVWcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 17:47:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/03/mauritius-disputes-uk-acquisition-chagos-islands-international/" target="_blank"&gt;Mauritius disputes UK acquisition of Chagos Islands in International Criminal Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain has apologised for the "shameful" way it evicted islanders from the Chagos archipelago in the Indian Ocean, but insisted Mauritius was wrong to bring a dispute over sovereignty of the strategic atoll group to the United Nations' top court. The apology came on the first day of a hearing on the future of the islands, the site of a key UK and US military base, at the International Court of Justice in the Hague. Mauritius has asked the ICJ for a legal opinion on sovereignty over the archipelago on the grounds they were “unlawfully” separated and incorporated it into British Indian Ocea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>UN Court Hears Case Over Strategic Indian Ocean Islands - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-court-hears-case-over-strategic-indian-ocean-islands/4556205.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGj3noV9py_DtBiiHhCEkB8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 22:12:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-court-hears-case-over-strategic-indian-ocean-islands/4556205.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Court Hears Case Over Strategic Indian Ocean Islands&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials from the Indian Ocean island nation of Mauritius told United Nations judges Monday that former colonial power Britain strong-armed its leaders half a century ago into giving up territory as a condition of independence, a claim that could have an impact on a strategically important U.S. military base. Judges at the International Court of Justice began hearing arguments for an advisory opinion the U.N. General Assembly requested on the legality of British sovereignty over the Chagos Islands. The largest island, Diego Garcia, has housed the U.S. base since the 1970s. "The process of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Mauritius takes UK to court over Chagos Islands sovereignty - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/03/mauritius-takes-uk-to-court-over-chagos-islands-sovereignty</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEERjqbOdqwcxj3kRGfHSYu8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 08:37:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/03/mauritius-takes-uk-to-court-over-chagos-islands-sovereignty" target="_blank"&gt;Mauritius takes UK to court over Chagos Islands sovereignty&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK’s possession of a remote archipelago in the Indian Ocean that includes the strategic US airbase of Diego Garcia is being challenged at the international court of justice. Despite British attempts at the United Nations to prevent Mauritius’s claim to the Chagos Islands reaching The Hague, judges will spend four days from Monday hearing representatives from 22 countries arguing over colonial history and the rights of exiled islanders to return. The overwhelming majority of states intervening in the dispute oppose Britain’s assertion that it has sovereignty over what it calls British In...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Christmas Island: Australia's unlikely new frontier of coffee production - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-08-16/christmas-island-becomes-unlikely-frontier-of-coffee-production/10118648</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC29_6yjs-ZQ2vors-ckqIIqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDD9QQ</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 20:33:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/rural/2018-08-16/christmas-island-becomes-unlikely-frontier-of-coffee-production/10118648" target="_blank"&gt;Christmas Island: Australia's unlikely new frontier of coffee production&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a tropical island paradise known internationally for its unique red crab migration, but Christmas Island locals hope the territory might, in future, also be known for its single origin coffee. For the first time 150 arabica coffee plants, grown on old phosphate mining land, have produced a crop large enough to harvest and roast beans for a local brew. The coffee trial is part of the Mining to Plant Enterprises (MINTOPE) project, which is funded by the Commonwealth Government, local mining company Christmas Island Phosphates and Murdoch University. In recent years, MINTOPE has trialled...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Christmas Island facing economic collapse as mine expansion rejected to save famous red crabs - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-31/proposal-to-expand-christmas-island-phosphate-mine-knocked-back/9820382</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBZrpxiAcK0vNyMppAZu2J8qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDM2g4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 04:48:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-05-31/proposal-to-expand-christmas-island-phosphate-mine-knocked-back/9820382" target="_blank"&gt;Christmas Island facing economic collapse as mine expansion rejected to save famous red crabs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The community of Christmas Island could face an economic collapse after a proposal to expand the island's phosphate mine was knocked back over fears of the impact to the island's wildlife, including its world-famous red crabs. Phosphate Resources Limited has been mining on the Indian Ocean Territory for more than 100 years, but claims it needs to clear more crown land to access new deposits in order for the operations to remain viable. Under the expansion, the company wanted to clear an additional 6.83 hectares of land to undertake exploration drilling to determine the extent of more phosph...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Tokelau's first newspaper aims to inform locals about climate change - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-04-21/tokelau-newspaper-aims-to-inform-locals-about-climate-change/9680392</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK1Td83-N5vxuwl3pr1o3joqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtiw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 23:27:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-04-21/tokelau-newspaper-aims-to-inform-locals-about-climate-change/9680392" target="_blank"&gt;Tokelau's first newspaper aims to inform locals about climate change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chiefs and local leaders from the tiny Pacific territory of Tokelau are heralding the launch of the island nation's first ever local newspaper that claims to meet international standards. Key points: - Tokelau consists of three small atolls, and is a dependent territory of New Zealand - It has a population of around 1,500 people - The newspaper hopes to keep people informed about climate change The Te Uluga Talafau monthly newspaper would provide up-to-date information on council decisions, village matters, as well as inspirational stories from Tokelauans living overseas. Tokelau lies just ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Norfolk Island - a tiny island of 1,700 people - celebrates first medal in 24 years with lawn bowls bronze - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/2018/04/08/norfolk-island-tiny-island-1700-people-celebrates-first/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDGPz3fZrxAsoCpxhRLAtKsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 11:34:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/sport/2018/04/08/norfolk-island-tiny-island-1700-people-celebrates-first/" target="_blank"&gt;Norfolk Island - a tiny island of 1,700 people - celebrates first medal in 24 years with lawn bowls bronze&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Norfolk Island pine trees that are ubiquitous along the east coast of Australia have been described by some detractors as the country’s biggest feral pest. One particularly irate Australian columnist even suggested the “giant weed” dominating skylines was “raising a wooden middle digit to us all”. But to a trio of Norfolk Island countrymen who will receive a hero’s welcome when they return home to their tiny stretch of land in the Pacific Ocean around 900 miles east of mainland Australia next week, the sight of the trees has been a source of both comfort and motivation. “It’s nice to lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The ICJ may help Chagossians to finally return home - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/180216221326071.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEksiLvAvz8ZwrkH0kLSIaUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 15:53:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/180216221326071.html" target="_blank"&gt;The ICJ may help Chagossians to finally return home&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Did the UK act illegally in splitting off the Chagos Islands from Mauritius prior to its independence in 1968? Mauritius successfully petitioned the UN to ask the International Court of Justice (ICJ) to consider this question, against the UK's wishes, but the outcome might not be what either country is hoping for. Following a vote in the UN last June, the ICJ is due to consider the "legal consequences" of the separation of the Chagos Islands from Mauritius in 1965, three years before Mauritius gained independence. The deadline for written submissions has been extended to March 1, 2018. It's...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>These Are The 7 Most Secret and Mysterious Places You Should Visit in 2018 - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/these-are-the-7-most-secret-and-mysterious-places-you-should-visit-in-2018</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO484rXMv_2hHUi4sgxM5aoqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMNCZmAI</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 02:27:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/these-are-the-7-most-secret-and-mysterious-places-you-should-visit-in-2018" target="_blank"&gt;These Are The 7 Most Secret and Mysterious Places You Should Visit in 2018&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;We could debate the merits of visiting South Korea during its hosting year of the Winter Olympics, or we could drill down to find the very last hillside village in Italy unexploited by the marauding snap of the smartphone, but why not spin the globe in a completely different direction and fill our 2018 travel bucket lists with some of the world’s truest wonders that are, for the time being, obscure dots on the map. Credit: Michael Dunning/Getty Pitcairn, Pacific Ocean Often considered the most remotely inhabited destination in the world, Pitcairn—with its mere 45 inhabitants—floats on an en...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>The unusual location where people drink the most wine, according to new study - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/where-drink-most-wine-location-study-norfolk-island-australia-a8112461.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDwbu9XxoS64rognR_Q6vtMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDdyhU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 14:27:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/where-drink-most-wine-location-study-norfolk-island-australia-a8112461.html" target="_blank"&gt;The unusual location where people drink the most wine, according to new study&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the season of festive fun gets well underway, you might well think that the location where people drink the most wine is not unusual at all and is in fact your living room. However, according to a new study it is actually a far more exotic location, one that you might not have even heard of: Norfolk Island, Australia. After collating data from the Wine Institute, the World Bank and Numbeo, moving company Move Hub have ranked every country in terms of wine spend per capita. - Read more You are probably storing your wine the wrong way Norfolk Island, which is just 8km long and 5km wide, is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Millions of crabs take over Google Street View - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2017/12/13/christmas-island-google-crab-migration-orig-vstan.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFf8zK0U6dMoKpePU0sBBeoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 18:54:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2017/12/13/christmas-island-google-crab-migration-orig-vstan.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Millions of crabs take over Google Street View&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google Street View recorded millions of red crabs during their annual migration across Christmas Island in Australia. ©2017 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item></channel></rss>