<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Robert Mueller - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREprYW0xb0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-NZ&amp;gl=NZ&amp;ceid=NZ:en</link><language>en-NZ</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:56:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Robert Mueller says Paul Manafort told 'discernible lies' in Trump-Russia probe - Stuff.co.nz</title><link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/world/americas/109198785/robert-mueller-says-paul-manafort-told-discernible-lies-in-trumprussia-probe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780126510889</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:47:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.stuff.co.nz/world/americas/109198785/robert-mueller-says-paul-manafort-told-discernible-lies-in-trumprussia-probe" target="_blank"&gt;Robert Mueller says Paul Manafort told 'discernible lies' in Trump-Russia probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Stuff.co.nz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;objectid=12173587" target="_blank"&gt;Robert Mueller says Paul Manafort told 'discernible lies'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New Zealand Herald&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hf_KNIMlO1I" target="_blank"&gt;Burnett: Mueller drops a major bomb on Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/07/opinion/trump-collusion-cohen-manafort.html" target="_blank"&gt;Is This the Beginning of the End for Trump?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;New York Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.stuff.co.nz/world/americas/109200589/trumps-lawyer-met-russian-offering-political-synergy" target="_blank"&gt;Trump's lawyer met Russian offering 'political synergy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Stuff.co.nz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqfggKInhDQklTVkRvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NrY0tFUWlwdnNTbGpZQU1FZHBtU0x4S2xCZjdFakpRY205elpXTjFkRzl5Y3lCbWFXeGxJSE5sYm5SbGJtTnBibWNnYldWdGJ5Qm1iM0lnVFdsamFHRmxiQ0JEYjJobGJpZ0FQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://www.stuff.co.nz">Stuff.co.nz</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/OG6PukQr2JQbi_NgugKNODSaF-V7sp596K4u1syppSiTUHLpTWTFD-1_a2uw_sjY5418CvgJCAp-g4rB28uDTqHQ539ax7Cj2aNd-WKEmgStIjuXCrusKfh2p5W66ngcmU9MycL35eYrLYIOHnzXAbJRnnpKwMymC3GGDVMFpfvI8QvrADLjSIg4s2G0SOQveczRB1X_zCR9nE1DRWcPJA=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>US: Trump lawyer met Russian who offered 'political synergy' - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/c42e3f73b2104b539264249f08935e2e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECkQ-5IW_6I-iImN7BdZTDsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:31:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/c42e3f73b2104b539264249f08935e2e" target="_blank"&gt;US: Trump lawyer met Russian who offered 'political synergy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's former lawyer, Michael Cohen, was in touch as far back as 2015 with a Russian who offered "political synergy" with the Trump election campaign and proposed a meeting between the candidate and Russian President Vladimir Putin, the federal special counsel said. Court filings from prosecutors in New York and special counsel Robert Mueller's office Friday laid out previously undisclosed contacts between Trump associates and Russian intermediaries and suggested the Kremlin aimed early on to influence Trump and his campaign by playing to both his politic...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Here Are The Most Interesting Parts Of The Latest Mueller Filings - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/these-are-new-key-pieces-of-information-in-the-russia-investigation_us_5c0b03a3e4b035a7bf5b3a27</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKwb6a4IK1e9uaED24GGoI8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 03:59:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/these-are-new-key-pieces-of-information-in-the-russia-investigation_us_5c0b03a3e4b035a7bf5b3a27" target="_blank"&gt;Here Are The Most Interesting Parts Of The Latest Mueller Filings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three documents filed in court Friday revealed new details in special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation of Russian interference in the 2016 presidential election. The documents pertained to the government’s cooperation agreement with Michael Cohen, President Donald Trump’s former personal lawyer, as well as Mueller’s assessment of why former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort breached his plea deal with investigators. The special counsel said in a memo to a federal judge that Manafort lied to investigators in the special counsel’s office about his contacts with administration offici...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>U.S. prosecutors name Trump in hush payments, detail Russian contacts - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/BigStory12/idUSKBN1O60P2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDg-LBDQbQuAYaeT7kAZMJ8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 03:04:18 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/BigStory12/idUSKBN1O60P2" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. prosecutors name Trump in hush payments, detail Russian contacts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. prosecutors said on Friday President Donald Trump directed his personal lawyer to make illegal hush payments to two women ahead of the 2016 election, and also detailed a previously unknown attempt by a Russian to help the Trump campaign. In court filings, federal prosecutors in New York and those working for Special Counsel Robert Mueller made the case for why Trump's former personal lawyer, Michael Cohen, and his former campaign chairman, Paul Manafort, deserved prison time. The documents turned up the heat on Trump by confirming prosecutors' belief of his involvement in a campaign fi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Mueller Implicates Trump Administration Officials With New Filings Against Manafort and Cohen - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mueller-implicates-trump-administration-officials-with-new-filings-against-manafort-and-cohen</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENCr7uvVgQoWktFwjQn9nwQqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 05:51:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/mueller-implicates-trump-administration-officials-with-new-filings-against-manafort-and-cohen" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller Implicates Trump Administration Officials With New Filings Against Manafort and Cohen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alex Wong/Getty A number of interesting facts emerge from the documents filed by special counsel Robert Mueller on Friday in the cases against Michael Cohen and Paul Manafort, but the submissions have one thing in common: both implicate unnamed members of the Trump administration. In a sentencing memo filed in the case against Cohen, President Donald Trump’s former lawyer, Mueller notes topics about which Cohen has provided information. Mueller states that Cohen provided “relevant and useful information concerning contacts with persons connected to the White House during the 2017-2018 time ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Toobin outlines Mueller's Cohen documents - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/toobin-cohen-documents-mueller-filing-tsr-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGlZf3rajIh6WkHl8bNU5DcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:12:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/toobin-cohen-documents-mueller-filing-tsr-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Toobin outlines Mueller's Cohen documents&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors from special counsel Robert Mueller's office outlined Michael Cohen's cooperation with the Russia investigation in sentencing recommendation documents. CNN's Jeffrey Toobin breaks down the documents. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Mob mentality: how Mueller is working to turn Trump's troops - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/08/robert-mueller-donald-trump-loyalty-organized-crime</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGm2loTy98MT90SbtatWRSwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 06:00:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/08/robert-mueller-donald-trump-loyalty-organized-crime" target="_blank"&gt;Mob mentality: how Mueller is working to turn Trump's troops&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the curtain lifts on the final act of the Robert Mueller investigation – which is not necessarily to say the final act of the Donald Trump presidency – there has been a a scramble for seats as second-tier figures in the drama choose sides. Related: Cohen spoke to Russian offering Putin meeting for Trump, Mueller reveals Some of the players have agreed to work with the special counsel as he investigates possible collusion between Russia and Donald Trump’s presidential campaign. Others are standing by Trump. Former campaign chairman Paul Manafort vowed never to work with Mueller, then ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Mueller opened the floodgates on Cohen and Manafort - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/robert-mueller-donald-trump-week-in-review/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO8gdVFbcthR0xvBCVcOZuwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 02:07:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/robert-mueller-donald-trump-week-in-review/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller opened the floodgates on Cohen and Manafort&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In what has been a slow drip of information on Robert Mueller's Russia investigation, the spigot opened up today with insight on four key players: 1) Michael Cohen: Southern District of New York investigators today asked the court to impose a "substantial term of imprisonment" for Cohen's various finance-related crimes -- and that Cohen "was motivated ... by personal greed, and repeatedly used his power and influence for deceptive ends." Why it matters: While prosecutors don't mince words about Cohen -- and stop short of calling him a cooperative witness -- they do say he has been helpful i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Woman Behind The Sketch: Courtroom Artist Dana Verkouteren - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-woman-behind-the-sketch-courtroom-artist-dana-verkouteren</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAKVBfdUaUyiX7Gm4Fep8_8qFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:48:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-woman-behind-the-sketch-courtroom-artist-dana-verkouteren" target="_blank"&gt;The Woman Behind The Sketch: Courtroom Artist Dana Verkouteren&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dana Verkouteren/AP An expensive suit. A silky tie. A fresh shave and perfectly coiffed hair. That used to be Paul Manafort, the former campaign manager of President Donald Trump who is now one of two former Trump associates expected to be the subjects of new disclosures from the office of Special Counsel Robert Mueller coming Friday. Manafort, 69, was previously convicted in a Virginia federal court this September of eight criminal counts, mainly regarding his work for a Ukrainian political party that is pro-Russia. Though he was expected to face a second trial shortly thereafter, he reach...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Manafort told 'multiple lies' after agreeing to cooperate, Mueller says - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/paul-manafort-mueller-special-counsel-filing</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFuizkqDIhQRkeUJWClfAi4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:29:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/paul-manafort-mueller-special-counsel-filing" target="_blank"&gt;Manafort told 'multiple lies' after agreeing to cooperate, Mueller says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump’s former campaign chairman Paul Manafort lied to the FBI and to the special counsel’s office on five different matters after entering an agreement to cooperate with prosecutors, Robert Mueller alleged in a court filing on Friday. Related: Cohen spoke to Russian offering Putin meeting for Trump, Mueller reveals Manafort tried to hide the fact that he had contact with “an administration official” inside the White House as late as May 2018, according to Mueller’s filing, which was partially redacted and did not specify what Manafort had discussed with the White House. Manafort was...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Trump to Nominate William Barr as Attorney General - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-to-nominate-william-barr-as-attorney-general/4691027.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENaN3IK4YEpXeIjUAgmtqioqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:08:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/trump-to-nominate-william-barr-as-attorney-general/4691027.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump to Nominate William Barr as Attorney General&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former U.S. attorney general known for supporting sweeping presidential powers is President Donald Trump's choice to again run the U.S. Department of Justice. Trump said Friday that William Barr, who was attorney general during the administration of the late former President George H.W. Bush, is his selection, describing him as "a terrific man, a terrific person, a brilliant man." The president told reporters at the White House that Barr, a 68-year-old conservative Republican and corporate lawyer, "was my first choice from day one. Respected by Republicans and respected by Democrats." Lat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Mueller: ex-Trump campaign chairman Manafort lied to investigators about funds, contacts - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/mueller-ex-trump-campaign-chairman-manafort-lied-to-investigators-about-funds-contacts-idUSKBN1O62K5</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIb_L8er1WdImlwNdAJqNSoqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:55:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/mueller-ex-trump-campaign-chairman-manafort-lied-to-investigators-about-funds-contacts-idUSKBN1O62K5" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller: ex-Trump campaign chairman Manafort lied to investigators about funds, contacts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort lied to federal investigators about a payment and contacts with Trump administration officials, the U.S. special counsel investigating whether Trump's 2016 campaign colluded with Russia said in a court filing on Friday. Special Counsel Robert Mueller's office submitted the filing to a U.S. District Court judge in Washington who had asked for more details on Mueller's allegations last month that Manafort had breached a plea agreement by lying. "In his interviews with the Special Counsel's Office and the FBI, Manafort told m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Mueller Is Telling Us: He's Got Trump on Collusion - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mueller-is-telling-us-hes-got-trump-on-collusion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGDFD8NQ9KRz5RtySHN0DG0qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPrwlwI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 03:38:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/mueller-is-telling-us-hes-got-trump-on-collusion" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller Is Telling Us: He's Got Trump on Collusion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Lyne Lucien/The Daily Beast For nearly two years, since the U.S. intelligence community released its report on the Russian campaign to assist Donald Trump in the 2016 election, the American people have been seeking an answer as to whether the Trump campaign colluded with its Russian counterpart. In the endless speculation about the direction of the investigation, a common view was that maybe the investigation would never implicate President Trump or find any collusion. But a flurry of recent activity this past week all points in the same direction: Special Counsel Robe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Read Robert Mueller's Assessment Of Paul Manafort's False Statements - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/paul-manafort-robert-mueller-court-filing-lies_us_5c0ab740e4b0ab8cf69312f6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELk87Oev7PlrpvH9zyiGvzAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:14:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/paul-manafort-robert-mueller-court-filing-lies_us_5c0ab740e4b0ab8cf69312f6" target="_blank"&gt;Read Robert Mueller's Assessment Of Paul Manafort's False Statements&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller met a deadline on Friday to release a court filing explaining why he accused former Donald Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort of breaching his plea deal with investigators. Mueller said last week that Manafort had broken the agreement by “lying” about “a variety of subject matters.” The special counsel said Manafort’s actions nullified any promises federal prosecutors made to him as part of the plea deal he agreed to in September as part of the investigation into Russian meddling in the 2016 presidential election. In Friday’s filing, Mueller detailed Manafo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Read Michael Cohen Sentencing Recommendations From Robert Mueller - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/michael-cohen-sentence-recommendations-mueller_us_5c0ab54ee4b035a7bf5aed6a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDojbsyp5zBcMHB9_gW3YNgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:07:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/michael-cohen-sentence-recommendations-mueller_us_5c0ab54ee4b035a7bf5aed6a" target="_blank"&gt;Read Michael Cohen Sentencing Recommendations From Robert Mueller&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller on Friday did not recommend a specific sentence for President Donald Trump’s former personal attorney Michael Cohen, citing his continued cooperation. “The sentence imposed should reflect the fact that lying to federal investigators has real consequences, especially where the defendant lied to investigators about critical facts, in an investigation of national importance,” prosecutors wrote in their court filing Friday. “However, the defendant has made substantial and significant efforts to remediate his misconduct, accept responsibility for his actions, and a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Significant filings in Russian investigation - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IBwXdu4X3CE</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENvbRYc0O8dl11PqUHOj_o0qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6OVAw</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 03:24:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IBwXdu4X3CE" target="_blank"&gt;Significant filings in Russian investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(7 Dec 2018) Special counsel Robert Mueller made court filings in cases against President Donald Trump's former personal lawyer Michael Cohen and former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort on Friday. (Dec. 7) Subscribe for more Breaking News: http://smarturl.it/AssociatedPress Website: https://apnews.com Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP Facebook: https://facebook.com/APNews Google+: https://plus.google.com/115892241801867723374 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/ ​ You can license this story through AP Archive: http://www.aparchive.com/metadata/youtube/37e84dd41f43d50a73e0f09bbe7b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Michael Cohen made illegal hush payments at direction of Trump, prosecutors say - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/07/michael-cohen-should-serve-substantial-prison-sentence-prosecutors/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENK_BK7k4c0cxaILJjkiSzwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 04:34:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/07/michael-cohen-should-serve-substantial-prison-sentence-prosecutors/" target="_blank"&gt;Michael Cohen made illegal hush payments at direction of Trump, prosecutors say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump directed his personal lawyer to make illegal hush payments to two women ahead of the 2016 election, US prosecutors said on Friday. In court filings that revealed details of how Michael Cohen has helped the Russia investigation, prosecutors also detailed a previously unknown attempt by a Russian to help the Trump campaign. Prosecutors in New York asked a judge to sentence Cohen to a "substantial term of imprisonment" for paying an adult film star hush money on Mr Trump's behalf, and for evading taxes. Cohen pleaded guilty to the charges in August. He has been cooperating with Mr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>What has Robert Mueller told us about Cohen, Flynn and Manafort? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/robert-mueller-trump-russia-investigation-cohen-flynn-manafort</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELBLAOyvnh7t6hfuy-3nj68qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 06:00:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/robert-mueller-trump-russia-investigation-cohen-flynn-manafort" target="_blank"&gt;What has Robert Mueller told us about Cohen, Flynn and Manafort?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;There has been intense activity over the past two weeks in Robert Mueller’s investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 US election and possible collusion by members of Donald Trump’s campaign team. Developments in the criminal prosecutions of three of Trump’s most important former advisers have enraged the president and shed new light on what Mueller has learned in the 19 months since his appointment as special counsel. Here, the Guardian reviews the key updates in the cases of Michael Cohen, Michael Flynn and Paul Manafort – and explores what the new disclosures could mean for Tru...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Here’s the status of the former Trump advisers charged by Mueller - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-the-status-of-the-former-trump-advisers-charged-by-mueller-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBH7EhOu69HPYySC2qeXr_IqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-the-status-of-the-former-trump-advisers-charged-by-mueller-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;Here’s the status of the former Trump advisers charged by Mueller&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CAPITOL REPORT By Elisabeth Buchwald Special counsel Robert Mueller is expected to recommend more charges Special Counsel Robert Mueller departs after briefing members of the U.S. Senate on his investigation into potential collusion between Russia and the Trump campaign on Capitol Hill in Washington, U.S., June 21, 2017. Reuters Like a complicated House of Cards episode, there have been so many twists and turns it may be difficult to keep track of special counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation into Russian meddling in the 2016 U.S. election. There may even be more plot twists as more charge...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Mueller: Manafort Lied About Another DOJ Probe - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mueller-manafort-lied-about-another-doj-probe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKwEsopQi2-hrsGp-900yD0qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:00:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/mueller-manafort-lied-about-another-doj-probe" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller: Manafort Lied About Another DOJ Probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mandel Ngan/Getty In court documents filed Friday evening, special counsel Robert Mueller claimed Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort lied about another Justice Department investigation. In a redacted portion of the memo, Mueller said Manafort “provided information” about a redacted subject that was “pertinent to an investigation in another district” before he pleaded guilty and signed his plea agreement. After signing the agreement, Manafort then told a “different and exculpatory version of the events,” according to the special counsel’s office. “He then subsequently changed that version...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Mueller accuses Manafort of ‘multiple discernible lies’ &amp; plea violation - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445914-mueller-manafort-memo-lying/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAQmo1aUTF8Pt3cbfafhhdkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 04:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445914-mueller-manafort-memo-lying/" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller accuses Manafort of ‘multiple discernible lies’ &amp; plea violation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller has accused former Trump campaign chair Paul Manafort of making false statements in the “Russiagate” investigation, including about a man Mueller insinuated might be a Russian spy. In a heavily redacted court filing on Friday, Mueller’s prosecutors argue that Manafort breached his plea agreement by making false statements, which were “not instances of mere memory lapses.” One of the issues Manafort allegedly lied about were his contacts with Konstantin Kilimnik, a Russian-Ukrainian citizen living in Kiev. In June, Mueller named Kilimnik as a co-conspirator in ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Fox News host Sean Hannity’s advice about cooperating with the FBI: Don’t - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fox-news-host-sean-hannitys-advice-about-cooperating-with-the-fbi-dont-2018-12-06</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBlxhExRBfn17EDUhkYqDpsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUw2JS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fox-news-host-sean-hannitys-advice-about-cooperating-with-the-fbi-dont-2018-12-06" target="_blank"&gt;Fox News host Sean Hannity’s advice about cooperating with the FBI: Don’t&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;KEY WORDS By Shawn Langlois Fox News host Sean Hannity visiting the White House briefing room. Getty Fox News host and breathless Trump supporter Sean Hannity clearly has a real problem with how Robert Mueller is running his investigation into Russian collusion, and he’s got a message for those thinking about cooperating: ‘If you’re like me, and you were – grew up to revere an FBI agent, and the FBI comes to your house, and maybe some crime took place in the neighborhood, and maybe you have a little bit of information, but you don’t quite fully recall everything, but you’re pretty sure you ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Feds Recommend Substantial Sentence For Michael Cohen - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mueller-cohen-sentencing-trump-manafort_us_5c0acb0be4b0a606a9a88114</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELRlu-enoyzrBPGu6gETBwEqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:53:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/mueller-cohen-sentencing-trump-manafort_us_5c0acb0be4b0a606a9a88114" target="_blank"&gt;Feds Recommend Substantial Sentence For Michael Cohen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal prosecutors filed court documents on Friday that revealed new details about the government’s cooperation with Michael Cohen, President Donald Trump’s former personal lawyer, ahead of his sentencing next week. The U.S. Attorney’s Office for the Southern District of New York submitted a sentencing memo for Cohen recommending a sentence of 42 months. Cohen, 52, has been cooperating for months with Robert Mueller’s investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 U.S. election, and Cohen’s attorneys revealed in their own sentencing memo last week that their client sat for seven inter...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Thursday US briefing: Wisconsin GOP votes to weaken incoming Democrats - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/06/thursday-us-briefing-wisconsin-gop-votes-weaken-incoming-democrats</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELUBZa4OCdxE9FoT2j_mWfsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:59:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/06/thursday-us-briefing-wisconsin-gop-votes-weaken-incoming-democrats" target="_blank"&gt;Thursday US briefing: Wisconsin GOP votes to weaken incoming Democrats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good morning, I’m Tim Walker with today’s essential stories. Top story: sweeping bill strips new governor’s powers Republican state lawmakers in Wisconsin have been accused of subverting democracy after passing a bill designed to weaken the incoming Democratic governor, Tony Evers, who dislodged Scott Walker at last month’s midterms. The bill was passed on Wednesday in a lame duck session, despite widespread outrage, and sent to Walker’s desk, where he has indicated he will sign it before leaving office in January. The outgoing governor was later booed at a Christmas tree lighting ceremony ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Mueller: Manafort Lied About Contacts With Trump Officials - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mueller-manafort-lied-about-contacts-with-trump-officials</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBh9pkA7ykBnvZXMV4nzzMgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:19:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/mueller-manafort-lied-about-contacts-with-trump-officials" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller: Manafort Lied About Contacts With Trump Officials&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alex Wong/Getty Former Trump campaign chief Paul Manafort lied to prosecutors about his contacts with senior Trump administration officials and his interactions with a suspected former Russian intelligence officer, according to court papers filed Friday by Special Counsel Robert Mueller. The memo claims Manafort lied to prosecutors about his contacts with an unnamed person in an attempt to get them to “speak with an Administration official on Manafort's behalf” in May 2018. Manafort, according to electronic documents found by prosecutors, has had “additional contacts” with Trump administrat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Prosecutors request 'substantial term of imprisonment' for ex-Trump lawyer Cohen - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445907-michael-cohen-jail-term/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDkMbuJIsVo6T2bqjk-N1zYqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445907-michael-cohen-jail-term/" target="_blank"&gt;Prosecutors request 'substantial term of imprisonment' for ex-Trump lawyer Cohen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump lawyer turned federal informant Michael Cohen may be going to jail for a long time. New York prosecutors and “Russiagate” special counsel Robert Mueller both released their separate sentencing recommendations on Friday. New York prosecutors have requested that Michael Cohen receive a “substantial term of imprisonment” for tax evasion and paying hush money to a porn star on Trump’s behalf. Cohen, who pled guilty to the charges in August, has been cooperating with special counsel Robert Mueller’s “Russiagate” probe for several months. In a separate sentencing memo, Mueller sought no add...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Former Trump campaign adviser targeted by Mueller for his appearances on RT - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/445933-malloch-investigated-rt-appearance/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHDYkQg3R5Mzro2_3shdymEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 09:25:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/445933-malloch-investigated-rt-appearance/" target="_blank"&gt;Former Trump campaign adviser targeted by Mueller for his appearances on RT&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;London-based academic Ted Malloch has come under scrutiny by Russiagate investigators for his appearances on RT, the Guardian reports. Malloch denies the claim. Ted Malloch, who was briefly touted as the next US ambassador to the EU, has been a guest on several episodes of RT’s ‘Going Underground’ with Afshin Rattansi talking Brexit, the allegations of collusion between Russia and the Trump campaign and the ensuing mainstream media fuss, the US trade war with China, and other topics. These appearances have now become a subject of the investigation by special counsel Robert Mueller, whose lo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Robert Mueller Details Paul Manafort's Lies In Trump-Russia Probe - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/robert-mueller-paul-manafort-lies-trump-russia_us_5c0986a6e4b04046345a4f3b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECCC4gDDo2sov2923qGM6zcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:12:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/robert-mueller-paul-manafort-lies-trump-russia_us_5c0986a6e4b04046345a4f3b" target="_blank"&gt;Robert Mueller Details Paul Manafort's Lies In Trump-Russia Probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― Former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort lied to investigators with the special counsel’s office about his contacts with administration officials, Robert Mueller’s team told a federal judge in a court memo filed Friday ahead of his sentencing. Manafort, a longtime Washington operative who chaired the Trump campaign for several months during the 2016 election cycle, was accused by Mueller’s team last month of breaking a plea deal reached in September by lying to investigators. Mueller’s team didn’t specify the lies at the time, writing only that Manafort had committed additi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>N.Y. federal prosecutors seek prison for former Trump lawyer Cohen - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-cohen/ny-federal-prosecutors-seek-prison-for-former-trump-lawyer-cohen-idUSKBN1O62FN</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECoBP3bg-CC2AFi3mEwesYwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:06:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-cohen/ny-federal-prosecutors-seek-prison-for-former-trump-lawyer-cohen-idUSKBN1O62FN" target="_blank"&gt;N.Y. federal prosecutors seek prison for former Trump lawyer Cohen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal prosecutors in Manhattan on Friday asked a judge to sentence Michael Cohen, U.S. President Donald Trump's former personal lawyer, to a "substantial term of imprisonment" for paying an adult film star hush money on Trump's behalf and evading taxes. Cohen, who has been cooperating with U.S. Special Counsel Robert Mueller's probe into possible collusion between Russia and Trump's 2016 election campaign, pleaded guilty to the charges in August. Cohen pleaded guilty last week to a separate charge by Mueller's office that he lied to Congress about discussions over the construction of a pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Mueller interviewed WH Chief of Staff John Kelly - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/12/07/lead-dana-bash-mueller-talked-to-john-kelly-live-jake-tapper.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF7ua6uIiQbPu5AQmRIVJCEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:33:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/12/07/lead-dana-bash-mueller-talked-to-john-kelly-live-jake-tapper.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller interviewed WH Chief of Staff John Kelly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;White House Chief of Staff John Kelly was interviewed by Robert Mueller about obstruction as part of the Russia investigation. CNN's Dana Bash reports. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>The Latest: White House says court filings show nothing new - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/3448dc500cee4f999f8fecfec43a61f2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF91894V_scSPI5KEOI8iHIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:31:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/3448dc500cee4f999f8fecfec43a61f2" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: White House says court filings show nothing new&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the special counsel's Russia investigation (all times local): 7:20 p.m. The White House says new court filings about President Donald Trump's former lawyer and campaign chairman offer nothing new or damaging about Trump. White House spokeswoman Sarah Huckabee Sanders says government filings about former Trump attorney and personal "fixer" Michael Cohen "tell us nothing of value that wasn't already known." That's despite the fact that the federal special counsel said in one of the documents that Cohen was in touch as far back as 2015 with a Russian who offered...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>John Kelly interviewed by Mueller's team and expected to quit – report - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/john-kelly-mueller-investigation-interview-expected-resign-report</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELL_iqMScDp8DLztz_hoo9YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:15:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/john-kelly-mueller-investigation-interview-expected-resign-report" target="_blank"&gt;John Kelly interviewed by Mueller's team and expected to quit – report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Kelly, the White House chief of staff, has been interviewed by special counsel Robert Mueller’s team and is expected to quit in the coming days, CNN reported on Friday. Related: Donald Trump nominates William Barr as next attorney general Kelly “responded to a narrow set of questions” in recent months related to potential obstruction of justice, the TV network said, citing three sources. This was after White House lawyers initially objected to Mueller’s request to do the interview earlier in the summer. Most of Mueller’s other interviewees were part of the Trump election campaign or pr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Prosecutors Expose Trump Hush Money Payments, Russian Contacts - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/prosecutors-expose-trump-hush-money-payments-russian-contacts/4692122.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENE_BapgmepIqtJmUWTCqb0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 08:20:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/prosecutors-expose-trump-hush-money-payments-russian-contacts/4692122.html" target="_blank"&gt;Prosecutors Expose Trump Hush Money Payments, Russian Contacts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Court filings Friday from prosecutors in New York and special counsel Robert Mueller laid out why Michael Cohen, U.S. President Donald Trump’s former personal lawyer, and Paul Manafort, Trump’s former campaign manager, deserve prison time. The filings say Cohen made illegal hush money payments to two women — Stormy Daniels, an adult film actress, and former Playboy model Karen McDougal — ahead of the 2016 election to keep them quiet about their sexual encounters with Trump. Federal prosecutors said Cohen made the payments in “coordination with and the direction of” Trump. The filings also d...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Cohen spoke with Russian to set up Trump-Putin meeting, Mueller reveals - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/michael-cohen-trump-former-fixer-prison-time</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1hj7JOCluUrarUs6HRFiAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:00:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/michael-cohen-trump-former-fixer-prison-time" target="_blank"&gt;Cohen spoke with Russian to set up Trump-Putin meeting, Mueller reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Donald Trump’s closest advisers spoke during the 2016 election campaign with a Russian offering help from Moscow and a meeting with the Russian president, Vladimir Putin, the special counsel Robert Mueller revealed on Friday. Related: Manafort lied on five separate matters after agreeing to cooperate, Mueller says Federal prosecutors also alleged that Trump directed the adviser, Michael Cohen, to make illegal payoffs to two women who claimed to have had sexual relationships with Trump, implicating the president in the violation of campaign finance laws. They recommended that Cohen re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>'Dumb as a rock' former secretary of state says Trump 'doesn't like to read' - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/trump-opens-fire-on-dumb-as-a-rock-rex-tillerson/10596638</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENGuNQA3u1BNJh3DmzVkPr8qFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:20:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-08/trump-opens-fire-on-dumb-as-a-rock-rex-tillerson/10596638" target="_blank"&gt;'Dumb as a rock' former secretary of state says Trump 'doesn't like to read'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has blasted former secretary of state Rex Tillerson in a sharply critical tweet, a day after the nation's former top diplomat publicly recounted that the President had tried to do things in a way that violated the law. In an interview with CBS News, Mr Tillerson described Mr Trump as "pretty undisciplined, doesn't like to read, doesn't read briefing reports … doesn't like to get into the details of a lot of things". Asked how his relationship with Mr Trump had gone off the rails, Mr Tillerson said it might have reflected what he saw as his obligation to tell the President that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>John Kelly Questioned by Mueller in Obstruction Probe: CNN - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/john-kelly-questioned-by-mueller-in-obstruction-probe-cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIA0tcX96TDu-RgSbhKuzN4qFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:16:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/john-kelly-questioned-by-mueller-in-obstruction-probe-cnn" target="_blank"&gt;John Kelly Questioned by Mueller in Obstruction Probe: CNN&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joshua Roberts/Reuters, White House Chief of Staff John Kelly has been interviewed by Robert Mueller’s Russia investigation team, CNN reports. Kelly responded to questions from special counsel investigators after White House lawyers initially objected to Mueller’s request to do the interview earlier this summer, according to CNN. Kelly is expected to leave his position in the coming days, as he is reported to no longer be on speaking terms with President Donald Trump. , The questions for Kelly centered on an incident that occurred following the publication of a New York Times reportthat sai...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Takeaways from the new Cohen and Manafort filings - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/cohen-manafort-mueller-takeaways/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMu7kj-3hC02Kyspruy6VFAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 06:16:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/cohen-manafort-mueller-takeaways/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Takeaways from the new Cohen and Manafort filings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone's lying to Robert Mueller -- and he knows it. The court filings released Friday by Robert Mueller and federal prosecutors detail the alleged lies Donald Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen and former campaign chairman Paul Manafort told both publicly and to the special counsel's investigators. And for the first time, prosecutors publicly endorsed Cohen's earlier statements in court that he acted at the direction of Trump when he committed two crimes in 2016: making payments to the two women alleging affairs with Trump in order to keep them silent. The court documents provide new in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Cohen was in touch with Russian seeking 'political synergy' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/federal-prosecutors-seek-prison-trump-lawyer-cohen-181207214905016.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEONPDl2BwbtFOdgbQk1HIT0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:27:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/federal-prosecutors-seek-prison-trump-lawyer-cohen-181207214905016.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cohen was in touch with Russian seeking 'political synergy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump's former lawyer, Michael Cohen, was in touch as far back as 2015 with a Russian who offered "political synergy" with the Trump election campaign, the federal special counsel said Friday in a court filing. Filings by prosecutors from both New York and the Trump-Russia special counsel's office laid out for the first time details of the cooperation of Cohen, a vital witness who once said he'd "take a bullet" for the president but who in recent months has become a prime antagonist and pledged to come clean with the government. In hours of meetings with prosecutors, Cohen ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Mueller: Manafort lied to investigators about funds, contacts - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/mueller-manafort-lied-investigators-funds-contacts-181207234556279.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBCxxsgkwd4sxQH1kjKlnQEqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:38:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/mueller-manafort-lied-investigators-funds-contacts-181207234556279.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller: Manafort lied to investigators about funds, contacts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman, Paul Manafort, lied to federal investigators about a payment and contacts with Trump administration officials, the US special counsel investigating whether Trump's 2016 campaign colluded with Russia said in a court filing on Friday. Special Counsel Robert Mueller's office submitted the filing to a US District Court judge in Washington, DC who had asked for more details on Mueller's allegations last month that Manafort had breached a plea agreement by lying. "In his interviews with the Special Counsel's Office and the FBI, Manafort told m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Justice Department office gave advice on acting AG's role in Russia probe: report - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-whitaker-idUSKBN1O62C0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI0Z6ItzmPnDLrBY6Nu48gsqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:57:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-whitaker-idUSKBN1O62C0" target="_blank"&gt;Justice Department office gave advice on acting AG's role in Russia probe: report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A U.S. Justice Department ethics office has received requests for advice and issued guidance about Acting U.S. Attorney General Matthew Whitaker's role in the special counsel investigation into Russian meddling in the 2016 election, the Washington Post reported on Friday. Citing information about department records obtained through a Freedom of Information Act request, the Post said it was unclear who had asked the Justice Department’s Professional Responsibility Advisory Office for guidance, and what advice the office had offered. "But the records’ existence shows, for the first time, that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Rahm Emanuel: Trump's making a big mistake - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/rahm-emanuel-axe-files-special-counsel-sot-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECnUs1FFUDr09Nu2yuQ-TNcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:35:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/rahm-emanuel-axe-files-special-counsel-sot-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Rahm Emanuel: Trump's making a big mistake&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel tells CNN's David Axelrod that President Donald Trump's decision to immerse himself into special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation rather than separate himself from it is a mistake. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Mueller is putting the puzzle pieces together on Trump - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/opinions/mueller-is-putting-the-puzzle-pieces-together-on-trump-honig/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB05OpDqKvmUTMRGHHXA7tkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 02:06:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/opinions/mueller-is-putting-the-puzzle-pieces-together-on-trump-honig/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller is putting the puzzle pieces together on Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elie Honig, a former federal and state prosecutor, is a CNN legal analyst and a Rutgers University scholar. The views expressed in this commentary are his own. View more opinion articles on CNN. President Trump and his allies have long rallied around the defiant battle cry that special counsel Robert Mueller is conducting a "witch hunt" that has uncovered "no collusion" with Russia. But public filings by Mueller and the Southern District of New York over the past two weeks have changed the game. We still do not know everything Mueller knows, but the contours of a broad scheme by the adminis...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Putin’s Mouthpiece Is Center Stage in the Mueller Investigation - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/putins-mouthpiece-is-center-stage-in-the-mueller-investigation</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOqnGTyUIgHCbTUwoKluqTwqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLzdlwI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 10:26:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/putins-mouthpiece-is-center-stage-in-the-mueller-investigation" target="_blank"&gt;Putin’s Mouthpiece Is Center Stage in the Mueller Investigation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast Why own a $620,000 Richard Mille watch if you can't show it off? If such was the reasoning of Dmitry Peskov, Vladimir Putin's press secretary, it failed him. After he was photographed wearing the luxury timepiece at his extravagant August 2015 wedding, anti-corruption crusader Aleksei Navalny posted the photo on his website, which has thousands of Russian viewers daily, and pointed out that the price of the watch was four times Peskov's annual government salary. Navalny followed up with an exposé that purportedly showed Peskov honeymooni...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Comey testifies at House hearing he calls 'desperate' attack on investigators - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/comey-testifies-at-house-hearing-he-calls-desperate-attack-on-investigators</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJHhjrpgQQREHYR2dhhESfgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 02:25:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/dec/07/comey-testifies-at-house-hearing-he-calls-desperate-attack-on-investigators" target="_blank"&gt;Comey testifies at House hearing he calls 'desperate' attack on investigators&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;James Comey, the former FBI director called to testify before members of the House of Representatives on Friday, called the hearing a “desperate attempt to find anything that can be used to attack the institutions of justice investigating this president”. Comey, who was subpoenaed, spoke to the GOP-led House judiciary and oversight and government reform committees for nearly seven hours behind closed doors, later telling reporters that they were “talking again about Hillary Clinton’s emails, for heaven’s sakes”. “I’m not sure we need to do this at all. But I’m trying to respect the institut...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Mueller: Manafort lied about major issues - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/manafort-mueller-court-filing-pam-brown-tsr-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPekQQnhblOag0NNYqKZhFUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 02:14:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/manafort-mueller-court-filing-pam-brown-tsr-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller: Manafort lied about major issues&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller's team believes President Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort lied during his cooperation sessions with the FBI and Special Counsel's Office following his guilty plea deal, according to court filings. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Comey faces off with GOP over Clinton emails, alleged bias - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/734284dd1aa746c19bf209770ae1ce54</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECLXK0gOuO8NJj29_LUpJwUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 02:39:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/734284dd1aa746c19bf209770ae1ce54" target="_blank"&gt;Comey faces off with GOP over Clinton emails, alleged bias&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former FBI Director James Comey spoke to House investigators behind closed doors for almost seven hours Friday, begrudgingly answering questions about the Justice Department's decisions during the 2016 presidential election. Comey, who appeared under subpoena, announced after the meeting that he would return for more questioning Dec. 17. Appearing annoyed, he said "we're talking about Hillary Clinton's emails, for heaven's sake, so I'm not sure we needed to do this at all." A transcript of the interview, expected to be released shortly, "will bore you," Comey said. Two GOP...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Prosecutors: Michael Cohen acted at Trump's direction when he broke the law - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/michael-cohen-robert-mueller-donald-trump/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBR9m4OG4oZWOsYQZqr57EcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 03:25:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/michael-cohen-robert-mueller-donald-trump/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Prosecutors: Michael Cohen acted at Trump's direction when he broke the law&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal prosecutors said for the first time Friday that Michael Cohen acted at the direction of Donald Trump when the former fixer committed two election-related crimes during the 2016 presidential campaign, as special counsel Robert Mueller outlined a previously undisclosed set of overtures and contacts between the Trump campaign and Russian nationals. Those revelations came in a set of court filings in which federal prosecutors in New York said Cohen should receive a "substantial" prison sentence of roughly four years for tax fraud and campaign-finance crimes, and as Mueller's office accu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Friday was a very, very bad day for Donald Trump - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/mueller-manafort-cohen-comey-trump/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFIrk_2zpOsuOUvz0WVLqEAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 03:50:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/mueller-manafort-cohen-comey-trump/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Friday was a very, very bad day for Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Friday, President Donald Trump (and the rest of us) got the most fulsome look into the inner workings of special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation yet. And what Trump saw has to terrify him. What was on display -- in sentencing documents for former Trump lawyer Michael Cohen and a memo detailing how one-time Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort broke the terms of his plea agreement -- was the depth and breadth of what Mueller and his team are investigating, what they already know and just how close they are to the President himself. Consider what we learned from the filings from Mu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Giuliani’s Report Will Hit All Of Trump’s Favorite Fox News Conspiracy Theory Villains - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/rudy-giuliani-mueller-report_us_5c0ab85ce4b035a7bf5aefdc</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFwclRgs9NzDLdYKi8Y0DJMqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:24:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/rudy-giuliani-mueller-report_us_5c0ab85ce4b035a7bf5aefdc" target="_blank"&gt;Giuliani’s Report Will Hit All Of Trump’s Favorite Fox News Conspiracy Theory Villains&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON ― Donald Trump’s legal team has prepared a response to Robert Mueller’s probe that features the president’s favorite conspiracy-theory villains, from Peter Strzok and his lover to those who financed a dossier that Trump falsely claims sparked the investigation against him. Strzok, Lisa Page, Bruce and Nellie Ohr, Christopher Steele and Hillary Clinton’s campaign lawyers will all be covered in the report, which Trump boasted was “already 87 pages” in a tweet Friday morning. When asked Friday whether the report would attack the various players involved in the investigation, Trump a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>Trump Attacks Mueller Team ‘Conflicts of Interest’ as Manafort, Cohen Filings Loom - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-attacks-mueller-team-conflicts-of-interest-as-manafort-cohen-filings-loom</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMCSdu_aRdVKTAcIQMXkzYoqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:57:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-attacks-mueller-team-conflicts-of-interest-as-manafort-cohen-filings-loom" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Attacks Mueller Team ‘Conflicts of Interest’ as Manafort, Cohen Filings Loom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pool, Donald Trump launched an early morning Twitter attack on Robert Mueller’s investigative team Friday, hours before the special counsel’s team is set to deliver important court filings in cases against the president’s former campaign chairman and his longtime legal “fixer.” In a five-post dawn rant against his legal foes, Trump dubbed fired FBI director “Leakin’ Lyin’ James Comey” and said his friendship with Mueller was “just one of many Mueller Conflicts of Interest.” He went on to list them—attacking Jeannie Rhee, the prosecutor in the Jerome Corsi investigation, as being “in charge ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>READ: Special counsel Robert Mueller's filing on Paul Manafort - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/mueller-manafort-filing/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOv-ZD32NQWcrtiBQEsmo18qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:23:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/mueller-manafort-filing/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;READ: Special counsel Robert Mueller's filing on Paul Manafort&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump falsely claims court memos clear him as prosecutors reveal how his associates repeatedly lied over Russia - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-mueller-court-documents-clear-tweet-cohen-manafort-lies-russia-a8673461.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEkO_AkSbR_jkupNFmoAV9kqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-mueller-court-documents-clear-tweet-cohen-manafort-lies-russia-a8673461.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump falsely claims court memos clear him as prosecutors reveal how his associates repeatedly lied over Russia&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump has falsely claimed that prosecutors have cleared him in legal documents that accuse two of his former associates of repeatedly lying about Russia. On a day that started with the president launching an angry Twitter rant about special prosecutor Robert Mueller – a suggestion he knew bad news was coming – it ended with prosecutors asking for “substantial” jail time for his former lawyer Michael Cohen, and saying his one time campaign manager had lied not just about interactions with Russians, but over his continued contact with the White House, six months after turning himself i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Quickly catch up on the day's news - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/app-news-section/quickly-catch-up-december-7-trnd/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHqH6ezcYG2pdxzyYpmyPxAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:31:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/app-news-section/quickly-catch-up-december-7-trnd/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Quickly catch up on the day's news&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's what you might have missed Friday on CNN: -- There's a lot happening with special counsel Robert Mueller today. In separate filings, prosecutors from special counsel Robert Mueller's office and the Southern District of New York outlined their cases for former Trump attorney Michael Cohen's future. We're now learning that the President's former associate Paul Manafort lied about five major issues after his plea, according to Mueller's filing. Former FBI Director James Comey testified before members of Congress behind closed doors. Mueller's team also interviewed John Kelly in the obst...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump nominates William Barr to be his next attorney general - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/william-barr-attorney-general-nomination/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJObChhEiVdimktfI1VSKYgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:44:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/william-barr-attorney-general-nomination/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump nominates William Barr to be his next attorney general&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump has decided to nominate former Attorney General William Barr to be the next permanent head of the Justice Department, the President told reporters Friday. "I want to confirm that Bill Barr, one of the most respected jurists in the country, highly respected lawyer, former attorney general under the Bush administration, a terrific man, a terrific person, a brilliant man," Trump said as he departed the White House. "I did not know him until recently when I went through the process of looking at people and he was my first choice from day one, respected by Republicans and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Feds Recommend Several Years in Prison for Michael Cohen - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/feds-recommend-several-years-in-prison-for-michael-cohen</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBQY_6ZYVx0m096-lFyK7_kqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:56:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/feds-recommend-several-years-in-prison-for-michael-cohen" target="_blank"&gt;Feds Recommend Several Years in Prison for Michael Cohen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hector Retamal/AFP/Getty Federal prosecutors in New York recommended a “substantial” prison term of several years for Michael Cohen, Donald Trump’s former fixer. But special counsel Robert Mueller’s office asked for no extra jail time in a separate case, citing his cooperation with investigators, including information Cohen provided about an offer of “political synergy” from Russia for the Trump campaign. In a memo filed late Friday afternoon, Mueller said Cohen had gone to “significant lengths” to assist his probe into Russian interference in the 2016 election and possible collusion by the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Cohen Refused to Fully Cooperate With Federal Prosectors in New York: Memo - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cohen-refused-to-fully-cooperate-with-federal-prosectors-in-new-york-memo</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEVjX0Me0GbxZKVkpvaB-7cqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:41:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/cohen-refused-to-fully-cooperate-with-federal-prosectors-in-new-york-memo" target="_blank"&gt;Cohen Refused to Fully Cooperate With Federal Prosectors in New York: Memo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Kelly/Reuters Federal prosecutors in New York submitted a sentencing memo Friday for Michael Cohen, revealing the former Trump lawyer refused to fully cooperate with their probe. “Had Cohen actually cooperated, it could have been fruitful: He did provide what could have been useful information about matters relating to ongoing investigations being carried out by this Office. But as Cohen partially acknowledges, it was his decision not to pursue full cooperation,” the memo read. Prosecutors also said Cohen only met with them “about the participation of others” in financial crimes he h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Mueller: Paul Manafort lied about contacts with Trump administration this year - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/paul-manafort-robert-mueller-donald-trump/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAVKkIUW5OFYxOrKIpSCSREqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:53:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/07/politics/paul-manafort-robert-mueller-donald-trump/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller: Paul Manafort lied about contacts with Trump administration this year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller said Friday that former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort lied about five major issues after agreeing to cooperate with prosecutors, including his "contact with administration officials." In a heavily redacted document, Mueller also said Manafort lied about his interactions with Konstantin Kilimnik. Mueller has said Kilimnik has ties to the Russian military intelligence unit accused of hacking the Democrats, and they've previously outlined how the two men may have worked together to tamper with witnesses following Manafort's arrest last year. The accusatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US Attorney recommends 'substantial term of imprisonment' for Michael Cohen - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/12/07/lead-shimon-prokupecz-mueller-reveals-new-details-in-cohen-filing-live-jake-tapper.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ24D9zkTNoMary6w_P8sFcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:38:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2018/12/07/lead-shimon-prokupecz-mueller-reveals-new-details-in-cohen-filing-live-jake-tapper.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;US Attorney recommends 'substantial term of imprisonment' for Michael Cohen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN's Shimon Prokupecz reports. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>AP Top Stories December 7 A - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2q4KqYcQn6Y</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENj-ZrVr6JXRQZTcpLi0xIwqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwn6OVAw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:40:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2q4KqYcQn6Y" target="_blank"&gt;AP Top Stories December 7 A&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(7 Dec 2018) Here's the latest for Friday December 7th: Mueller memos on Cohen and Manafort due today; NC Democrat house candidate withdrawl concession amid vote investigation; State Dept. spokeswoman Nauert said to be top pick for UN Ambassador; Winter storms in Southern California. Subscribe for more Breaking News: http://smarturl.it/AssociatedPress Website: https://apnews.com Twitter: https://twitter.com/AP Facebook: https://facebook.com/APNews Google+: https://plus.google.com/115892241801867723374 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/APNews/ ​&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Burnett: Mueller drops a major bomb on Trump - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/08/trump-mueller-filings-michael-cohen-erin-burnett-sot-ebof-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAb3hlNz_W-w5gPO_fV5iRYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 02:31:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/08/trump-mueller-filings-michael-cohen-erin-burnett-sot-ebof-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Burnett: Mueller drops a major bomb on Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN's Erin Burnett examines revelations detailed in separate filings by special counsel Robert Mueller and the Southern District of New York, on Donald Trump's former personal attorney Michael Cohen. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>U.S. Supreme Court appears wary of expanding 'double jeopardy' - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-doublejeopardy-idUSKBN1O521Y</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECUz5W2d-gi-pirNX-GGaCIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMMT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:39:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-doublejeopardy-idUSKBN1O521Y" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. Supreme Court appears wary of expanding 'double jeopardy'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. Supreme Court justices on Thursday expressed skepticism about putting limits on criminal charges being brought against people for the same offenses by both federal and state prosecutors in a case involving an Alabama man charged with illegally possessing a gun. Depending on how the court rules, the case could have implications for Special Counsel Robert Mueller's investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 U.S. election and any coordination between Moscow and Republican Donald Trump's campaign. A ruling against the government could limit the ability of states to bring charges a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Paul Manafort: Mueller alleges five key lies by ex-Trump campaign manager in latest court filing - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-mueller-russi-manafort-cohen-sentencing-lies-tweet-latest-court-a8673451.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL1KEmtqkzTWJUjFJvKi0_MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/trump-mueller-russi-manafort-cohen-sentencing-lies-tweet-latest-court-a8673451.html" target="_blank"&gt;Paul Manafort: Mueller alleges five key lies by ex-Trump campaign manager in latest court filing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert Mueller has accused Donald Trump's former campaign manager Paul Manafort of lying over five key issues - including his contacts with Trump administration officials - after entering a deal to cooperate with the Russia investigation. “In his interviews with the Special Counsel's Office and the FBI, Manafort told multiple discernible lies — these were not instances of mere memory lapses,” Mr Mueller's office said in the filing citing "independent documentary and testimonial evidence" and electronic records. Manafort has denied lying. Manafort tried to hide the fact that he had contact w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Trump Today: President blasts Mueller in tweetstorm and taps Barr, Nauert for posts - MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-today-president-blasts-mueller-in-tweetstorm-and-taps-barr-nauert-for-posts-2018-12-07</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELnDppqG9xsSEnUn8xY6C1UqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowjujJATDXzBUwiJS0AQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:13:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-today-president-blasts-mueller-in-tweetstorm-and-taps-barr-nauert-for-posts-2018-12-07" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Today: President blasts Mueller in tweetstorm and taps Barr, Nauert for posts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MarketWatch&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TRUMP TODAY By Robert Schroeder China trade talks ‘going very well,’ Trump tweets after volatile week for markets President Donald Trump speaks to the media before boarding Marine One to depart from the White House on Friday. Getty Images President Donald Trump on Friday freshly attacked the Russia investigation as Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s office was expected to release details about former Trump associates, and said he’s nominating William Barr as attorney general and Heather Nauert as U.S. ambassador to the United Nations. TRUMP SUGGESTS ROSENSTEIN CONFLICTED In a barrage of tweet...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.marketwatch.com">MarketWatch</source></item><item><title>Mueller to drop Cohen, Manafort memos - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/michael-cohen-paul-manfort-mueller-probe-brown-dnt-lead-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAnHK7JntNe5iRgR_Iqd5y0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:22:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/07/michael-cohen-paul-manfort-mueller-probe-brown-dnt-lead-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Mueller to drop Cohen, Manafort memos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller's team could reveal tantalizing new details in its investigation into possible Russian collusion thanks to a pair of court filing deadlines involving President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort and former lawyer Michael Cohen. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Trump: Cohen Sentencing Memo ‘Totally Clears’ Me - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-cohen-sentencing-memo-totally-clears-me</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENqOLOrOlq8BfMXO9Jp0DdoqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 23:31:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-cohen-sentencing-memo-totally-clears-me" target="_blank"&gt;Trump: Cohen Sentencing Memo ‘Totally Clears’ Me&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark Wilson/Getty President Trump insisted on Friday evening that a sentencing memo filed by federal prosecutors in New York for his former personal attorney Michael Cohen “totally clears” him of wrongdoing. “Totally clears the President. Thank you!” Trump wrote shortly after the memo was filed. But the filing directly implicates Trump in Cohen’s hush-money payments to Karen McDougal and Stormy Daniels, who alleged they’d had affairs with the president. “In particular, and as Cohen himself has now admitted, with respect to both payments, he acted in coordination with and at the direction of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>Trump Justice pick likely to be queried on Mueller comments - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/089bf90df8c04950a7fb14215fca87dd</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEkgmPaJ_FGqb0IJ9a7J0_wqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 21:20:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/089bf90df8c04950a7fb14215fca87dd" target="_blank"&gt;Trump Justice pick likely to be queried on Mueller comments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump on Friday picked former Attorney General William Barr to once again serve as America's top law enforcement official. But while his experience and mainstream background may boost his prospects for confirmation, Democrats are raising alarms about his comments on the Russia investigation and Hillary Clinton. Barr has expressed concerns about political donations made by prosecutors on special counsel Robert Mueller's team and has supported calls for an investigation into a uranium deal approved while Clinton was secretary of state, a pet issue of Trump s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>SCOTUS case could impact presidential pardons - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/06/supreme-court-double-jeopardy-mueller-flynn-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG3mz2VpsYvC4DCWPxNO8PsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:34:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/politics/2018/12/06/supreme-court-double-jeopardy-mueller-flynn-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;SCOTUS case could impact presidential pardons&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN's Ariane de Vogue explains the connection between a Supreme Court case related to the Fifth Amendment's double jeopardy clause and the Mueller investigation. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A WarnerMedia Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court takes up closely watched double jeopardy case - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/c9c65cff3e4f4420aa4fe86d7554ea6d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM5czPAV7gdaWcAaHwztCnkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 18:21:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/c9c65cff3e4f4420aa4fe86d7554ea6d" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court takes up closely watched double jeopardy case&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Constitution says you can't be tried twice for the same offense. And yet Terance Gamble is sitting in prison today because he was prosecuted separately by Alabama and the federal government for having a gun after an earlier robbery conviction. The Supreme Court is considering Gamble's case on Thursday, and the outcome could have a spillover effect on the investigation into Russian meddling in the 2016 election. At issue is whether to overturn a court-created exception to the Constitution's double-jeopardy bar that allows state and federal prosecutions for the same crim...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>President 'Individual-1' Trump Hasn't A Clue, But Twitter Wits Aim to School Him - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/twitter-trump-individual-1_us_5c0b4142e4b035a7bf5b4c71</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA5UEC9lFXAx3AJomvmHPEIqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMOGXAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 06:14:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/twitter-trump-individual-1_us_5c0b4142e4b035a7bf5b4c71" target="_blank"&gt;President 'Individual-1' Trump Hasn't A Clue, But Twitter Wits Aim to School Him&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump apparently doesn’t have an inkling that he is “Individual-1” implicated in suspected crimes linked to Russia and payoffs to women in court documents filed Friday by special counsel Robert Mueller. If he did, Trump wouldn’t have crowed that he has been “totally” cleared by the investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 presidential election that favored him. And so a furiously popular hashtag has been launched by agog tweeters: #Individual1. Rep. Ted Lieu (D-Calif.) tried to break the bad news to Trump on Twitter — gently. Dear @realDonaldTrump: I think you mi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>George Papadopoulos Walks Free After Spending 12 Days in Prison - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/george-papadopoulos-walks-free-after-spending-12-days-in-prison?source=cheats&amp;via=rss</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPtt3f08CojPe8oZj21mAagqFggEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMLXUiQY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:41:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/george-papadopoulos-walks-free-after-spending-12-days-in-prison?source=cheats&amp;via=rss" target="_blank"&gt;George Papadopoulos Walks Free After Spending 12 Days in Prison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Caballero-Reynolds/AFP/Getty, Former Trump campaign adviser George Papadopoulos left federal prison Friday after he was sentenced to only 12 days for lying to federal investigators about his conversations with Russia-linked individuals during the 2016 presidential campaign. CNN reports that Papadopoulos left a federal prison in Wisconsin at about 10 a.m. ET. He will now be supervised for 12 months, and must serve 200 hours of community service and pay $9,500. In the August 17 sentencing memo, Mueller wrote that Papadopoulos “knew the questions he was asked by the FBI were important, ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item></channel></rss>