<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Grammar school - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREUwYldwakVnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-NZ&amp;gl=NZ&amp;ceid=NZ:en</link><language>en-NZ</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:31:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Eton and Westminster among eight schools dominating Oxbridge - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/07/eton-and-westminster-among-eight-schools-dominating-oxbridge</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOtp-wtRJErjsdg8YhW9tu0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 00:01:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/07/eton-and-westminster-among-eight-schools-dominating-oxbridge" target="_blank"&gt;Eton and Westminster among eight schools dominating Oxbridge&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eight top schools in the UK get as many pupils into the universities of Oxford and Cambridge as three-quarters of all schools and colleges together, according to new research. Over a three-year period the eight leading schools – which are mainly in the independent sector – sent 1,310 of their students to Oxbridge, while 2,900 schools, each with two or fewer acceptances, sent 1,220 pupils in total. The research showed that high-flying pupils from state schools were far less likely to apply to Oxbridge than their peers in the private sector, and were less likely to be successful when they did...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>‘An education arms race’: inside the ultra-competitive world of private tutoring - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/05/an-education-arms-race-inside-the-ultra-competitive-world-of-private-tutoring</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEW7H6RbT8UXw9me8ryK76oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 06:00:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/05/an-education-arms-race-inside-the-ultra-competitive-world-of-private-tutoring" target="_blank"&gt;‘An education arms race’: inside the ultra-competitive world of private tutoring&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As dusk falls in the Girlington district of Bradford, a trickle of cars begin to arrive in front of a small parade of shops. Parents who have just collected their children at the end of the school day are dropping them off at the Explore Learning tuition centre for extra maths and English coaching. The children sit at a cluster of computer terminals, where they log in to begin their evening studies. The atmosphere is relaxed and lighthearted. The children stay for an hour to work through their lessons, helped where necessary by a member of staff, with 15 minutes’ playtime at the end. Locate...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Campaigners criticise £50m fund for grammar schools expansion - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/03/campaigners-criticise-50m-fund-for-grammar-schools-expansion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG1pZtZNbrWSyH-r4SzUxikqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 15:15:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2018/dec/03/campaigners-criticise-50m-fund-for-grammar-schools-expansion" target="_blank"&gt;Campaigners criticise £50m fund for grammar schools expansion&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Headteachers and campaigners for children with special educational needs and disabilities (SEND) have reacted with fury to a government announcement that 16 grammar schools are to split a £50m bonus to create new school places. Related: Councils face £536m shortfall in Send budgets, says LGA Making the announcement on Monday, the education secretary, Damian Hinds, said the 16 schools chosen to receive the additional funding out of 39 applications had been given permission to expand after setting out clear actions to prioritise access for disadvantaged children. “I have always been clear tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Government gives 16 grammar schools in England a share of £50m funding pot to expand - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/grammar-schools-england-funding-government-academic-selection-department-for-education-a8664691.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMT_kj7Ifh6rFaPgKw38nC8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/grammar-schools-england-funding-government-academic-selection-department-for-education-a8664691.html" target="_blank"&gt;Government gives 16 grammar schools in England a share of £50m funding pot to expand&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The identities of the grammar schools which will share £50m funding to create just 4,000 additional places for pupils, have been unveiled by the government. Campaigners have criticised the allocation of the taxpayers' money which comes during a funding crisis in state schools. Almost half of the grammar schools chosen to receive the funding are located in the Home Counties and only one school that will benefit from the Selective School Expansion Fund is in the north of England. - Read more One in five grammar schools prepare bids to expand under £50m fund Three in four of the selective scho...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Free education is disappearing before our eyes - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/28/free-education-schools-money-parents-children</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHdoRj3r1jCGk2Zck8Apw-sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 06:00:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/nov/28/free-education-schools-money-parents-children" target="_blank"&gt;Free education is disappearing before our eyes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second world war references are hard to avoid in the context of Brexit, so here’s one that actually has something constructive to offer. When Britain was facing the horror of Stalingrad, the second battle of El Alamein and the challenge of the Normandy landings, it was also undertaking wholesale reform of the education system. The mass evacuation of children from British cities to rural areas laid bare the abysmal lack of education many had received. The government response was the 1944 Education Act, which established what we now call state-maintained comprehensive schools and free, compul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Bursaries mean private schools 'more diverse' than grammars - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/11/20/bursaries-mean-private-schools-diverse-grammars/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDNgadd0SrkbnqDMF8pAR7YqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:20:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2018/11/20/bursaries-mean-private-schools-diverse-grammars/" target="_blank"&gt;Bursaries mean private schools 'more diverse' than grammars&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Private schools are now more socially diverse than grammars, a leading headmistress has claimed. Sally-Anne Huang, head of the £18,000-a-year James Allen’s Girls’ School (JAGS) in south London, said that pupils at fee-paying schools mix with peers from a range of backgrounds since there are so many pupils receiving bursaries. She said that 16 per cent of her girls are on bursaries, and the average bursary makes up 85 per cent of the cost of fees. But far from this putting parents off sending their daughters there, it is in fact sought after, she said. “My experience is that parents will com...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Teach First head criticises 'depressing' grammars and says free schools don't work outside London - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/head-teach-first-grammar-schools-most-depressing-brett-wigdortz-free-london-dubai-a7637031.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFiqt8f57LnATEuWQ10iyM0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 15:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/head-teach-first-grammar-schools-most-depressing-brett-wigdortz-free-london-dubai-a7637031.html" target="_blank"&gt;Teach First head criticises 'depressing' grammars and says free schools don't work outside London&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Government plans to open more free schools are too London-centric and risk neglecting children from the poorest regions of the country, the CEO and founder of Teach First has said. Speaking to an audience at the Global Education and Skills Forum in Dubai, Brett Wigdortz took a swipe at grammar schools, claiming that schools he had visited in Kent, which has a largely selective education system, were “some of the most depressing things” he’d ever seen. Former Ofsted chief Sir Michael Wilshaw, who was also on the panel, argued new schools should have autonomy – unlike traditional state compre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pupils from ten private and grammar schools dominate applications for top graduate schemes - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/05/06/pupils-ten-private-grammar-schools-dominate-applications-top/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDOO5cTxw98kvPu2z_rNxzcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 16:06:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/05/06/pupils-ten-private-grammar-schools-dominate-applications-top/" target="_blank"&gt;Pupils from ten private and grammar schools dominate applications for top graduate schemes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pupils from ten private and grammar schools are 100 times more likely to apply for the most prestigious graduate schemes than their peers who were educated at the bottom ten per cent of schools, regardless of which universities they went on to, new analysis has revealed. Jobs at the most sought after law firms, management consultancies, banks and FTSE 100 companies - which offer starting salaries to graduates of around £45,000 - are dominated by applications from an elite set of schools. According to research carried out by Rare, a recruitment company which specialises in encouraging divers...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Theresa May’s grammar school places plan shelved until after 2020 - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/theresa-may-grammar-school-places-plan-delayed-funding-shortfall-2020-a7639906.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIOTA_qLmKl-AXvNowlmRI8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 15:50:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/theresa-may-grammar-school-places-plan-delayed-funding-shortfall-2020-a7639906.html" target="_blank"&gt;Theresa May’s grammar school places plan shelved until after 2020&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May’s flagship education pledge to create 70,000 new grammar school places will not happen until after the 2020 general election, the Education Secretary has confirmed. Justine Greening was told in the Commons this afternoon that it was “answer time” after The Independent last week revealed a huge funding shortfall in the promise – announced personally by the Prime Minister ahead of the Budget. - Read more May faces fresh Budget storm over unfunded new grammar school places The Education Secretary on Monday pledged “further investment in the next Parliament” to make up the massive s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Where to buy to be near the UK's best state schools - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/property/buy/buy-near-uks-best-state-schools/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEZkvSEA4nziznxAXSPU7G0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDIr80F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/property/buy/buy-near-uks-best-state-schools/" target="_blank"&gt;Where to buy to be near the UK's best state schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is the start of another school year, and young parents in London and the Home Counties will be scanning the property websites for those parts of the country where the price of a family home is not beyond the dreams of avarice. Many have made the move already. The number of people fleeing London in 2016 alone reached 300,000, according to Savills – 80 per cent higher than five years ago. These émigrés, most aged between 29 and 39, come in search of many things – open countryside, gastropubs and a solid community, to name a few. But the education of their children is of uppermost importanc...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>New grammars would harm British schools, says Ofsted chief - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2016/oct/30/grammars-harm-british-schools-says-ofsted-chief-michael-wilshaw</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEIfviVG5ryTsMLFOuJSkE4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 12:03:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2016/oct/30/grammars-harm-british-schools-says-ofsted-chief-michael-wilshaw" target="_blank"&gt;New grammars would harm British schools, says Ofsted chief&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;British schools deserve to score only 6.5 out of 10 compared with education systems in other countries and would be further set back if new grammar schools were allowed, the chief inspector of schools has said. Sir Michael Wilshaw, head of Ofsted, said the UK education system was getting better since it had been in “special measures, in intensive care, in the 70s, 80s and much of the 90s”, but an expansion of grammar schools planned by Theresa May would stall progress. Wilshaw has spoken out several times against new grammars since the policy was announced by the prime minister. May wants s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Grammar school 'U-turns on excluding pupils who failed to get B grades' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/exam-st-olaves-policy-a-levels-a7925386.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIrU4k9vLW5gMw69xThh3ZMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 12:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/exam-st-olaves-policy-a-levels-a7925386.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grammar school 'U-turns on excluding pupils who failed to get B grades'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A-level students who had their places withdrawn at a grammar school after failing to achieve certain grades will now be allowed to return, it has been reported. Legal action was being pursued against the governing body of St Olave's grammar school in Orpington in south east London after two students were told they could not continue their A-level studies into Year 13. The pupils, who cannot be named for legal reasons, failed to achieve Bs in any of their subjects taken in the first year of sixth form, lawyers said. Days ago they were told they could return to the school but only to study a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Schools around England ejecting 'underperforming' sixth-formers - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/aug/30/mps-attack-ejection-of-underperforming-sixth-formers</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEpnsM9gz81gIgKjqn98mT0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 12:08:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/aug/30/mps-attack-ejection-of-underperforming-sixth-formers" target="_blank"&gt;Schools around England ejecting 'underperforming' sixth-formers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dozens of parents and pupils have contacted the Guardian complaining that schools in different areas of the country are ejecting sixth form students half way through their two-year A-level course after failing to achieve sufficiently high grades. Some of the schools identified are in areas where there are a high number of grammar schools, including Kent, Buckinghamshire and Lincolnshire, though non-selective schools elsewhere are also implicated. The testimony from parents and students suggests the practice is widespread, and is having a detrimental effect on students. One student who lost ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>May’s Easter message did little to bring together this Disunited Kingdom - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/letters/may-s-easter-message-did-little-to-bring-together-this-disunited-kingdom-a7687361.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ0oErpEZO7jsQHse_dXQ7MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 13:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/letters/may-s-easter-message-did-little-to-bring-together-this-disunited-kingdom-a7687361.html" target="_blank"&gt;May’s Easter message did little to bring together this Disunited Kingdom&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;May will know that in the Archbishop of Canterbury's Easter message he spoke of the importance of facts rather than opinion. Did she, I wonder, pause to reflect on the misinformation surrounding last year's referendum before issuing her clumsy attempt to link Christianity to Brexit. In it she said, "There is a sense that people are coming together and uniting behind the opportunities that lie ahead." I would be very interested to know of the evidence for this opinion. In my experience, those who voted Remain, whether Christian or not, are as appalled at the direction of travel of this Disun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Grammar schools lose top spots after league table shakeup - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/jan/19/grammar-schools-lose-top-spots-after-league-table-shakeup</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK8DnJNUqMNOEz86c5FsyCEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 09:30:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/jan/19/grammar-schools-lose-top-spots-after-league-table-shakeup" target="_blank"&gt;Grammar schools lose top spots after league table shakeup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government’s new performance measure has upended the traditional pecking order of England’s secondary schools, knocking grammar schools out of the top spots and boosting schools that dramatically improved results among their pupils. The Department for Education’s latest performance tables, published on Thursday — including 2016’s GCSE exams and ranked by its new Progress 8 measure — reveals that the best schools in England are those which make the greatest advances in their pupils’ grades. GCSE league table At the top of the national Progress 8 league table sit two faith schools in Blac...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Depression, opportunity and that life abroad – podcasts of the week - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/jun/02/depression-opportunity-and-that-life-abroad-podcasts-of-the-week-hear-here</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBkrhFRbvAGJR0UXw-Rt1rAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 06:00:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2017/jun/02/depression-opportunity-and-that-life-abroad-podcasts-of-the-week-hear-here" target="_blank"&gt;Depression, opportunity and that life abroad – podcasts of the week&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hear here is here. Hooray! Now, first things first. An incredible number of people have subscribed to this column. What a joy that there are so many of you who love the medium as much I do. If you’ve emailed in with your recommendations, I promise I’ll listen to them – I’ve made an excel spreadsheet and everything – but there have just been so many, it’s incredible. Please keep them coming in, I want to listen to all the podcasts I can fit into my ears. If you haven’t subscribed yet, come and join us. It’s great fun. So, on to the recommendations. A couple of weeks ago it was my birthday, a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Case for opening new grammar schools is yet to be proved, MPs say - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/feb/13/case-opening-new-grammar-schools-yet-proven-mps-say</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPd7dEd5Cno9WvdDssbBTt4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 13:32:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/feb/13/case-opening-new-grammar-schools-yet-proven-mps-say" target="_blank"&gt;Case for opening new grammar schools is yet to be proved, MPs say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government has “lost the argument” on grammars, it has been claimed, after an influential cross-party committee of MPs published a highly sceptical report saying ministers have yet to prove the case for opening a new wave of selective schools. After hearing wide-ranging evidence from academics and policy experts, the chair of the Commons education committee, Neil Carmichael, said the focus on opening new grammar schools was an unnecessary distraction. The Tory MP warned that if the government wanted to push ahead with its plans, it would have to demonstrate how opening new grammars woul...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Top 10 grammar schools for GCSE results - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2016/09/08/top-10-grammar-schools-for-gcse-results2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTUCS7HkY4Wce0wb0nVznQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 13:15:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2016/09/08/top-10-grammar-schools-for-gcse-results2/" target="_blank"&gt;Top 10 grammar schools for GCSE results&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;08 Sep 2016 Top 10 grammar schools for GCSE results Previous slideNext slide1 of 11View AllSkip Ad As Theresa May, the Prime Minister, defends plans to lift the ban on new grammar schools, we take you through the top 10 selective schools based on 2016 GCSE results submitted to the Telegraph. GCSE results 2016: state school results Back to image&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Conservative manifesto launch: Failing schools to be banned from expanding - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/05/18/conservative-manifesto-launch-failing-schools-banned-expanding/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEELik22NVAH2__GoQv5ExgAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 12:41:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/05/18/conservative-manifesto-launch-failing-schools-banned-expanding/" target="_blank"&gt;Conservative manifesto launch: Failing schools to be banned from expanding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Failing schools will be banned from expanding, under the Conservatives' education proposals. The Tory manifesto states that ministers will bar councils from creating new places at schools that have been rated "inadequate" or "requires improvement" by Ofsted, the regulator. It also pledges to create online maps which will allow parents to compare the quality of teaching, results and the curriculum in order to "support their decisions" over which schools they choose for their children. The announcements are among a raft of pledges covering schools and universities contained in the Conservativ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Parents pay £52,000 more to live in areas with outstanding schools, new survey reveals - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/04/04/parents-pay-52000-live-areas-outstanding-schools-new-survey/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBYmd-Rmqf5DCZj92He8l8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/04/04/parents-pay-52000-live-areas-outstanding-schools-new-survey/" target="_blank"&gt;Parents pay £52,000 more to live in areas with outstanding schools, new survey reveals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parents are paying more than £50,000 in order to move to catchment areas with outstanding schools, raising fears that the country’s top state schools are becoming selective according to family wealth. A survey of more than one million homes across England has revealed that parents are paying vast property premiums to move home, with the average house in outstanding school catchment area costing £52,000 more on average than those near schools which require improvement. In London, where competition for good or outstanding school places is the fiercest nationally, the price squeeze is even mor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Tory manifesto: What policies will change after Theresa May's humiliating election result? - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/tory-manifesto-changes-fox-hunting-dementia-tax-grammar-schools-policies-theresa-may-election-result-a7786691.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPiwJex-8WDLXW4cYE_pfsYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 17:12:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/tory-manifesto-changes-fox-hunting-dementia-tax-grammar-schools-policies-theresa-may-election-result-a7786691.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tory manifesto: What policies will change after Theresa May's humiliating election result?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the looming Queen’s Speech, Theresa May will outline her minority government’s plans for new laws. It should have been an opportunity for the Prime Minister to implement the main contents of the Conservative’s general election manifesto. But with her authority in tatters following last weeks calamitous election result, Ms May will be forced to substantially water down some of the policies in the Conservative manifesto, or drop them entirely. Read more - Theresa May admits 'I got us into this mess' in meeting with Tory MPs - Theresa May's chance to rescue a softer Brexit from election wre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>I went to a grammar school – that doesn’t mean I have to support them - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/may/17/grammar-school-identity-social-place-education</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ7EwRNlvtww86fwNDSD30oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 09:04:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/may/17/grammar-school-identity-social-place-education" target="_blank"&gt;I went to a grammar school – that doesn’t mean I have to support them&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;I went to a grammar school – two actually. According to one way of discussing this fascinating subject, I am disqualified from arguing that a selective system is unfair and socially damaging. I am, it seems, so much in debt to my grammar schools that this outweighs any rational argument I might make that there can be a fairer system. I must be, in a sense, so marked by the experience that the only honest comment I’m allowed to make is: “The grammar school was good for me, so the system is a good one.” Related: Grammar schools: back to the bad old days of inequality But for me to say this, I...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Greening targets 'ordinary families' in grammar schools drive - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/apr/13/greening-targets-ordinary-families-in-grammar-schools-drive</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENUcQJX0lUiSSwIBZFJt7w0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 23:01:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/apr/13/greening-targets-ordinary-families-in-grammar-schools-drive" target="_blank"&gt;Greening targets 'ordinary families' in grammar schools drive&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May’s new wave of grammar schools must give priority to “ordinary working class families” as much as to children from poorer families eligible for free school meals, the education secretary will say. Justine Greening, in a speech briefed in advance, will say she wants selective education to benefit children from households with incomes of up to £33,000, moving the focus of education policy away from targeting the most disadvantaged households. Her plan for the school system, spelled out in a consultation document, was immediately criticised by Labour but amounts to the first attempt...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Education bill scrapped after series of reversals - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2016/oct/27/government-drops-education-bill-after-series-of-reversals</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHRlpi_R8ocs8jD3Av-CxXoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 16:24:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2016/oct/27/government-drops-education-bill-after-series-of-reversals" target="_blank"&gt;Education bill scrapped after series of reversals&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government has said it is dropping the education bill unveiled in this year’s Queen’s speech, abandoning several proposals that had proved to be unpopular. However, it said it would press ahead with plans for more grammar schools. The bill was introduced in March by Nicky Morgan, then education secretary, but its most controversial clauses were quickly removed, including forcing all state schools in England to become academies by 2020 and ending statutory places for parents on boards of governors. Justine Greening, Morgan’s successor as education secretary, signalled the ditching of the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Who is Justine Greening and what has she done as Education Secretary? - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/who-is-justine-greening-education-secretary-tory-conservative-election-2017-cabinet-theresa-may-a7786296.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHTuyAw-DnD4dAJ--6-AAe0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/who-is-justine-greening-education-secretary-tory-conservative-election-2017-cabinet-theresa-may-a7786296.html" target="_blank"&gt;Who is Justine Greening and what has she done as Education Secretary?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justine Greening has been re-appointed as Secretary of State for Education and Minister for Women and Equalities, following another cabinet reshuffle. Despite winning back her Putney constituency seat with a much reduced majority vote of 1,554 down from 10,180, education industry leaders appear to be singing Ms Greening's praises as a sensible choice for education. In the run up to the general election, some had speculated that Ms Greening – herself known to be unenthusiastic about grammar schools – might be replaced by someone whose views were more in line with the Prime Minister’s. - Read...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Grammar schools are a 'distraction', says new chief inspector of schools - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/01/09/grammar-schools-distraction-says-new-chief-inspector-schools/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFCsuMr5vdpgojQQBxqeXlMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 20:52:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/01/09/grammar-schools-distraction-says-new-chief-inspector-schools/" target="_blank"&gt;Grammar schools are a 'distraction', says new chief inspector of schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grammar schools are a “distraction” and a “complication” the new chief inspector of schools in England has said, in her first public criticism of Government policy since taking up the role. Amanda Spielman’s comments have put her at odds with Prime Minister Theresa May who plans to overturn the ban on grammar schools imposed by Labour some 20 years ago. Conservative MPs have rounded on the new Ofsted chief, calling her comments “unhelpful” and “unproductive”. It certainly is a complicationAmanda Spielman, Ofsted chief inspector Senior politicians have told the Telegraph that as a civil serv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Eleven-plus exam 'a dice loaded against disadvantaged pupils', says new report - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/eleven-plus-exam-grammar-schools-11-plus-dice-loaded-disadvantaged-pupils-fre-school-meals-private-a7719306.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECyLgPKRFyCZuLnGzEJJSNMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 10:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/eleven-plus-exam-grammar-schools-11-plus-dice-loaded-disadvantaged-pupils-fre-school-meals-private-a7719306.html" target="_blank"&gt;Eleven-plus exam 'a dice loaded against disadvantaged pupils', says new report&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The dice is loaded against children from poorer backgrounds when it comes to grammar schools, according to a new report. A study of data from Kent found that about a quarter of all students went to a grammar school in 2016, but children eligible for free school meals (FSM) were less likely to sit or pass the 11-plus. The report acknowledged that the situation will vary across the country, but said Kent could be a useful case study as it is an area where selectivity “is most heavily embedded” and comprises both rural and urban communities of varying social class. Kent County Council has said...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Grammar schools are now giving priority to disadvantaged pupils, new study shows - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/03/31/grammar-schools-now-giving-priority-disadvantaged-pupils-new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHJYtz-q2kL18cpb-QNxoNkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 18:07:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/03/31/grammar-schools-now-giving-priority-disadvantaged-pupils-new/" target="_blank"&gt;Grammar schools are now giving priority to disadvantaged pupils, new study shows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grammar schools across the country are now using positive discrimination in a bid to increase their intake of children from disadvantaged backgrounds, new research has revealed. More than a third of grammars have now changed their admissions criteria for the next academic year, including lowering the 11 Plus entrance test marks, in a move seen to be paving the way for hundreds of new--more open--selective schools. The analysis, carried out by TES, reveals that more than 50 grammars will now give disadvantaged pupils priority over their wealthier peers, following proposals by the Government ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Rolling a loaded dice': the verdict on the 11-plus in Kent - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/may/05/rolling-a-loaded-dice-the-verdict-on-the-11-plus-in-kent</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKk-XqKDIxZXJ12wkUf0wZoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 23:01:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/may/05/rolling-a-loaded-dice-the-verdict-on-the-11-plus-in-kent" target="_blank"&gt;'Rolling a loaded dice': the verdict on the 11-plus in Kent&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New research into the way the 11-plus operates in Kent, one of the few remaining authorities in England that is fully selective, likens the process of trying to get into one of the county’s grammar schools to “rolling a loaded dice”. The research, by the Education Datalab thinktank, says success in the examination is to some extent arbitrary, but the dice is loaded because parts of the selection process act together to make disadvantaged children less likely to pass. The research is described as the most detailed examination of how the 11-plus operates in a single part of the country and is...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The return of the 11-plus is Theresa May’s first real Trump moment - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/mar/09/11-plus-theresa-may-trump-moment-grammar-schools</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEuLFWNo-bLOe_QoCtCAHPYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 07:01:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/mar/09/11-plus-theresa-may-trump-moment-grammar-schools" target="_blank"&gt;The return of the 11-plus is Theresa May’s first real Trump moment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May’s desire to return England to grammar schools is her first real spasm of Trumpism. It is incoherent. It makes no sense educationally, financially or politically. It is also based on a lie, that selection is about parental choice. May seems unaware that parents do not choose grammar schools, grammar schools choose children. The policy was alluded to in the budget by the chancellor, Philip Hammond, though he only mentioned more money for free schools. Budgets have a poor record in education reform. Last year, George Osborne declared every school in England was to become an academy...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>The 11-plus can 'never be tutor-proof', major grammar school exam board admits - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/05/05/11-plus-can-never-tutor-proof-major-grammar-school-exam-board/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECRfWZfuhLP8fSlPz5qWAJsqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 19:33:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/05/05/11-plus-can-never-tutor-proof-major-grammar-school-exam-board/" target="_blank"&gt;The 11-plus can 'never be tutor-proof', major grammar school exam board admits&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 11-plus can “never be tutor-proof”, a major grammar school exam board has admitted, as one of the last remaining selective counties announced it was abandoning its five-year experiment with tests designed to be immune from coaching. All 13 of Buckinghamshire County Council’s grammar schools are to re-instate GL Assessment as their 11-plus provider, despite axing it five years ago amid concern that its questions were predictable and therefore favoured wealthy parents who could pay for extra tuition. From September 2019, exams written by GL Assessment will replace the current 11-plus pape...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Schools should introduce 'grammar stream' for bright students, Ucas chief executive says - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/01/26/schools-should-introduce-grammar-stream-bright-students-ucas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA9M660ybvI6VqDxPuvQPswqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 10:26:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/01/26/schools-should-introduce-grammar-stream-bright-students-ucas/" target="_blank"&gt;Schools should introduce 'grammar stream' for bright students, Ucas chief executive says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All schools should introduce a “grammar stream” because bright students need the “right education for them right now”, the head of the university admissions service has said. Mary Curnock Cook, the outgoing chief executive of Ucas, has thrown her weight behind selective schooling, arguing that “customer logic” dictates that parents will always want to best possible education for their children. It comes as pressure mounts on Prime Minister Theresa May to announce the Government’s response to a consultation it launched following its Green Paper on grammar schools published last September. Wr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Comps aren’t helping social mobility. So why not bring back selection? - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/mar/01/comprehensives-arent-helping-so-why-not-bring-back-selection</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK2x2F6F-BPn2YuFWTINSWMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 12:22:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/mar/01/comprehensives-arent-helping-so-why-not-bring-back-selection" target="_blank"&gt;Comps aren’t helping social mobility. So why not bring back selection?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As pupils across England and Wales learn where they will be going to secondary school, two separate studies have shown that the wealth divide in education is more entrenched than ever, with children from poorer households far less likely to attend the best-performing schools. Teach First, the charity that places high-flying graduates in schools in deprived areas, found children from poorer families are half as likely to attend an outstanding school as their richer contemporaries, while the Sutton Trust, the education thinktank that focuses on social mobility, found poorer children are much ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>May's Election Catastrophe Leaves School Selection Dead In The Water - Forbes Now</title><link>http://www.forbes.com/sites/nickmorrison/2017/06/12/mays-election-catastrophe-leaves-school-selection-dead-in-the-water/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELX9F17oDQNOomkurQO0wkkqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMKGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 13:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/nickmorrison/2017/06/12/mays-election-catastrophe-leaves-school-selection-dead-in-the-water/" target="_blank"&gt;May's Election Catastrophe Leaves School Selection Dead In The Water&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prime Minister Theresa May leaves Downing Street to go to Buckingham Palace where she will seek the Queen’s permission to form a U.K. government. (Photo by Dan Kitwood/Getty Images) Theresa May’s catastrophic election campaign looks certain to have left her flagship school selection policy dead in the water. In what must rank as the biggest self-inflicted wound of any prime minister since Anthony Eden invaded Suez 60 years ago, the election that was meant to give May an overwhelming mandate has resulted in her losing her majority in the House of Commons. As a result, she will be reliant on ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Let’s build on passions unleashed in the election to blast apart the market in schools - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/jun/12/election-market-schools-fiona-millar</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENklPooKjqboo5XE2SPM_14qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 06:29:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/jun/12/election-market-schools-fiona-millar" target="_blank"&gt;Let’s build on passions unleashed in the election to blast apart the market in schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;So none of us thought we would be here: a parliament with no overall control, a revived two-party electoral system in which both main players win a higher share of the vote than in recent history but neither gets a majority. No one knows where we will end up in six months. For the education world this is probably a mixed blessing. The first assumption must be that the Conservative grammar school plan can’t possibly go ahead. The Tories don’t have a mandate and its now exiled architect, Theresa May’s former adviser Nick Timothy, has shown catastrophically bad political judgment on everything...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>There are bigger problems in education than could ever be fixed by a new generation of grammar schools - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/editorials/grammar-schools-justine-greening-education-secretary-teachers-leaving-attacked-compensation-bme-a7682906.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIhWbK8P1gubxJ0Tn3xWiUsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/editorials/grammar-schools-justine-greening-education-secretary-teachers-leaving-attacked-compensation-bme-a7682906.html" target="_blank"&gt;There are bigger problems in education than could ever be fixed by a new generation of grammar schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Education Secretary Justine Greening’s decision to focus her attention on a deliberate expansion of selective schooling through an extension of the grammar system has proved, with a certain inevitability, to be controversial. Her critics warn that, rather than encourage social mobility, selection by academic ability always achieves the opposite. Those who seek to benefit from the policy, they say, are those who already have the best of life chances, by virtue of the socioeconomic status and the cultural and academic interests of their parents. It doesn’t matter how well-intentioned the poli...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Parents pay 45pc premium to live close to top-performing English state schools - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/property/uk/parents-pay-45pc-premium-live-close-top-performing-english-state/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECrbdIbHClOGBaKQaWEcgSoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDIr80F</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/property/uk/parents-pay-45pc-premium-live-close-top-performing-english-state/" target="_blank"&gt;Parents pay 45pc premium to live close to top-performing English state schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parents in England are forced to pay a hefty premium if they want to live near one of the top state schools in the country, with homes near the best secondary institutions commanding an average house price of £415,844, adding 45pc to the English average. Homes in the postal district of Beaconsfield High School in Buckinghamshire, the highest-ranked secondary state in England, cost an average of £1,034,547. That's £643,181, or 158pc, more than the average house price in the county. The data by Lloyds Bank reveals that over the past five years, the average property price in areas with a top-p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>St Olave's chair of governors resigns after exclusion controversy - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/sep/12/st-olaves-chair-of-governors-resigns</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEEXm2zjFEhqCxO55ly6TTgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 18:23:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/sep/12/st-olaves-chair-of-governors-resigns" target="_blank"&gt;St Olave's chair of governors resigns after exclusion controversy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chair of governors at the grammar school revealed to be systematically pushing pupils out halfway through sixth form if their grades were not good enough has resigned. The Rev Peter Galloway, who chaired the governors at St Olave’s in Orpington, in the London borough of Bromley, stepped down last week, it has been revealed. His resignation came after the Guardian’s revelations that the school was unlawfully excluding pupils. Related: Schools abandon exclusion of sixth-formers after parents complain A spokeswoman for the Diocese of Rochester, which has been issuing statements on behalf o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>‘Why would a Tory object?’: crusader for grammar schools is having his moment - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2016/nov/08/tory-grammar-schools-graham-brady-selection</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB2T_4ofFSIw2f3PhRjOy1QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 07:30:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2016/nov/08/tory-grammar-schools-graham-brady-selection" target="_blank"&gt;‘Why would a Tory object?’: crusader for grammar schools is having his moment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Graham Brady’s time has come. For most of his life, the Tory MP for Altrincham and Sale West has campaigned for grammar schools. Though he is also supports leaving the EU, it was the issue of educational selection that propelled him into politics and defines him politically. As a teenager from a non-political family, he delivered leaflets during Trafford local elections in defence of Altrincham grammar school for boys, where he was deputy head boy. In his maiden Commons speech in 1997, Brady said: “I believe passionately in the role of grammar schools as the greatest of social levellers.” I...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Cross-party alliance takes on Theresa May over grammar schools - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/mar/18/cross-party-alliance-grammar-schools-theresa-may</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPnFBu4afu446ECBUyO5ICcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/mar/18/cross-party-alliance-grammar-schools-theresa-may" target="_blank"&gt;Cross-party alliance takes on Theresa May over grammar schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May’s personal crusade to expand the number of grammar schools is in serious jeopardy today as senior Tory, Labour and Liberal Democrat MPs unite in an unprecedented cross-party campaign to kill off the prime minister’s flagship education reform. In a highly unusual move, the Tory former education secretary Nicky Morgan joins forces with her previous Labour shadow Lucy Powell and the Liberal Democrat former deputy prime minister Nick Clegg to condemn the plans as damaging to social mobility, ideologically driven and divisive. Related: We must help poorer pupils, but not through sele...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Grammar school entrance exams undermined by study showing how children learn - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/grammar-schools-tests-entrance-exams-iq-education-learning-a7397876.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELBu9j7WjKk7r5h4CtaRn40qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 16:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/grammar-schools-tests-entrance-exams-iq-education-learning-a7397876.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grammar school entrance exams undermined by study showing how children learn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new psychological study has cast doubt both on the saying “you can’t teach an old dog new tricks” and claims that entrance exams for selective schools can accurately determine a child’s “true potential”. The researchers tested more than 550 school pupils aged 11 to 18 and more than 100 adults on various skills such as “non-verbal reasoning”, a process involved in maths. And they found that children aged 11 to 13 – older than the age when children typically take entrance exams – were able to improve their performance by 10 percentage points in just three weeks. Read more - This is why the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>As a product of Scotland's comprehensive system, I applaud Theresa May's green light for selective education - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/21/as-a-product-of-scotlands-comprehensive-system-i-applaud-theresa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHlkuipWAUbiKVJtt3liJdAqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:46:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/21/as-a-product-of-scotlands-comprehensive-system-i-applaud-theresa/" target="_blank"&gt;As a product of Scotland's comprehensive system, I applaud Theresa May's green light for selective education&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Theresa May completes her first hundred days as Prime Minister, commentators have been assessing her domestic political programme, particularly her most radical policy - ending the ban on academic selection that has characterised British education since 1998. Growing up in a household which fell in the bottom quintile of UK incomes and attending a school where only four per cent of pupils had prospects of achieving a good university place, the opportunities opened up by a grammar school could have been life-changing for me. I had heard the stories about successful people I looked up to f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Ministers should invest in existing grammar schools rather than create new ones, head teachers say - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/03/07/ministers-should-invest-existing-grammar-schools-rather-creating/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJUp10OVyvhPDMFTTRtARfEqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 19:31:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/03/07/ministers-should-invest-existing-grammar-schools-rather-creating/" target="_blank"&gt;Ministers should invest in existing grammar schools rather than create new ones, head teachers say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ministers should invest in existing grammar schools rather than create new ones, head teachers have said. Grammar school leaders have hit out at the Prime Minister for setting aside millions in the Budget to build a new generation of selective schools, as they warn that existing institutions are on the “cusp of viability”. Head teachers said they are already having axe subjects such as Latin and Music, and double their class sizes in order to cope under budget constraints. Dr Robin Bevan, headmaster of Southend High School For Boys, said: “The problem for me is that there are just over 150 ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>A-level pupils excluded for failing to get top grades allowed to return after grammar school U-turn - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/02/a-level-pupils-excluded-failing-get-top-grades-allow-return/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOMqWBi-D14b8ssO7UvPaJ0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 07:42:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/09/02/a-level-pupils-excluded-failing-get-top-grades-allow-return/" target="_blank"&gt;A-level pupils excluded for failing to get top grades allowed to return after grammar school U-turn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A-level students who had their places withdrawn at a grammar school after failing to achieve certain grades will now be allowed to return, it has been reported. Legal action was being pursued against the governing body of St Olave's grammar school in Orpington in south east London after two students were told they could not continue their A-level studies into Year 13. The pupils, who cannot be named for legal reasons, failed to achieve Bs in any of their subjects taken in the first year of sixth form, lawyers said. Days ago they were told they could return to the school but only to study a ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Opponent of new grammar schools to lead headteachers' union - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/feb/10/opponent-of-new-grammar-schools-to-lead-headteachers-union-ascl-geoff-barton</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL6BlJ1DIl0tXE69YOxrdaIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 12:44:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/feb/10/opponent-of-new-grammar-schools-to-lead-headteachers-union-ascl-geoff-barton" target="_blank"&gt;Opponent of new grammar schools to lead headteachers' union&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An outsider who vowed to take the fight to the government over grammar schools and funding cuts has been elected general secretary of the biggest secondary school headteachers’ union in an upset victory. Geoff Barton, the long-serving headteacher of a secondary school in Suffolk, was on Friday named the winner in the Association of School and College Leaders’ first contested election for general secretary in a landslide win. Barton had strong support among his fellow heads as well as a strong social media presence. His win upset the plans of the union’s executive, which had handpicked a con...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Queen's Speech: Theresa May's grammar school expansion plans scrapped - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/queens-speech-latest-theresa-may-grammar-school-expansion-plans-dropped-legislative-agenda-a7800951.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGIhOuzj36mjlntRrRzkX7YqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/queens-speech-latest-theresa-may-grammar-school-expansion-plans-dropped-legislative-agenda-a7800951.html" target="_blank"&gt;Queen's Speech: Theresa May's grammar school expansion plans scrapped&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Controversial plans to expand grammar schools in England have official been scrapped, after Theresa May’s flagship policy was omitted from the Queen’s Speech. The Queen said the government would “look at all options” for new schools moving forward, but no action has been stated to remove the current ban on selective school expansion. A national funding formula for schools was reaffirmed, along with a "major reform of technical education", as promised in the Tory election manifesto. - Read more May’s lack of power exposed by lack of health or education bills Plans to scrap universal free sch...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Outgoing Ofsted boss says he would only give Britain's school system a 'six and a half out of 10' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/30/outgoing-ofsted-boss-says-he-would-only-give-britains-school-sys/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBzLAXd0Iz4DnTbN2Lk3VIcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 14:39:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/30/outgoing-ofsted-boss-says-he-would-only-give-britains-school-sys/" target="_blank"&gt;Outgoing Ofsted boss says he would only give Britain's school system a 'six and a half out of 10'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain's schools system remains "mediocre" despite the Government's education reforms, the outgoing chief inspector of schools has said as he accused the unions of blocking progress. Sir Michael Wilshaw said that despite the academies system Britain's schools are still "some way behind" South Korea and other outstanding education systems. He suggested that the unions have obstructed progress and said Michael Gove will be remembered as one of the "greatest" education secretaries in history for his reforms. Michael Gove, the former Education SecretaryCredit: Peter Nicholls/Peter Nicholls He ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Do whatever it takes to make elections fair - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/03/19/do-whatever-takes-make-elections-fair/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEINHIAk5a22eLXD-te7RaFsqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/03/19/do-whatever-takes-make-elections-fair/" target="_blank"&gt;Do whatever it takes to make elections fair&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;During David Cameron’s benighted Tory leadership he was notorious for disregarding the voluntary party and appointing cronies and second-raters to run Central Office. The chickens are now coming home to roost. A failure to include the cost of national campaigns in local ones led to the Electoral Commission fining the Tories £70,000 for breaking regulations in 2015. The deputy treasurer, Simon Day, has been referred to the police – though why not Andrew Feldman, his Cameron-crony boss in charge of compliance? A Conservative 'battle bus' of the kind which is at the heart of the campaign spend...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Olive Braman obituary - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/stage/2017/jan/19/olive-braman-obituary</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFqjchykf0pr07CjI6TIbA4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCOvRU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 13:04:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/stage/2017/jan/19/olive-braman-obituary" target="_blank"&gt;Olive Braman obituary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;My mother, Olive Braman, who has died aged 82, was always strong-willed and impatient. Even on her deathbed, she sent people away, saying “boring” – only half joking. After my father, Geoffrey Braman, proposed in 1968, she told him that he ought to marry her quickly before she changed her mind (she was actually engaged to somebody else at the time). Marry they did and were, mostly, very happy together for the 37 years until his death in 2005. Olive was born in Altrincham, Cheshire, the daughter of Victor Iorns, a factory worker, and his wife, Clara (nee Brazendale). The oldest of three, she...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Head to the school gate – and see how politics is failing our children - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/may/13/tory-grammar-schools-labour-investment-politics-failing-our-children</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA4JJ_yRjnZqSGktfLc7CkMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 06:00:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/may/13/tory-grammar-schools-labour-investment-politics-failing-our-children" target="_blank"&gt;Head to the school gate – and see how politics is failing our children&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can run. But laden down with PE kits, pushchairs and hideous art projects made from empty loo rolls, you can’t hide. That’s why election candidates are so fond of lurking outside primary schools at home time, for here is where they find those voters least able to escape: parents of small children. But for Labour MPs this May, school gate canvassing isn’t just a formality. Related: ‘Tutor-proof’ 11-plus professor admits grammar school test doesn’t work Looming budget cuts are forcing many headteachers into the kind of difficult decisions – staff redundancies, begging for parental donatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Praise Philip, the Prince of Misrule - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/may/06/philip-prince-of-misrule-said-what-we-darent</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE0C1dDwU2gYwQ4ZRaUtKQkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 23:24:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/may/06/philip-prince-of-misrule-said-what-we-darent" target="_blank"&gt;Praise Philip, the Prince of Misrule&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a great dinner party game: Instant Duke of Edinburgh. First, everyone writes a little scene where two characters meet in a London street and argue. One is uneducated, only using words, including swearwords, of Anglo-Saxon origin; the other parades their formal, educated, Latinate English. Now swap the speeches around and read them out – in social reverse. The educated person speaks mockney, while the uneducated one is cut-glass RP. Every time – try it – you end up with a joyous scene in which a petty control-freak is confronted by… the Duke of Edinburgh. Prince Philip sails effortles...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Theresa May's grammar school plans were an 'unnecessary distraction' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/theresa-mays-grammar-school-plans-were-an-unnecessary-distraction-a7578246.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGKUhWz9orW66HHvAtxM0VgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 16:06:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/theresa-mays-grammar-school-plans-were-an-unnecessary-distraction-a7578246.html" target="_blank"&gt;Theresa May's grammar school plans were an 'unnecessary distraction'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May’s plans for new grammar schools have been an ‘unnecessary distraction’ from the need to equip young people to meet the demands of the workplace, according to the chair of parliament’s Education Committee, Neil Carmichael MP. Mr Carmichael’s committee has just published a report on the case for new grammar schools, a policy that was rushed out by Theresa May’s government in her first days in an official was photographed carrying plans for them out of Number 10 Downing Street. Mr Carmichael said: “The Government has yet to prove the case for opening a new wave of grammar schools. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>On this we can all agree. Selection is bad for our schools - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/mar/19/help-poorer-pupils-selection-social-mobility-education-brexit-grammar-schools</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELxUFEz1piRQvIq9s-eDpKUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/mar/19/help-poorer-pupils-selection-social-mobility-education-brexit-grammar-schools" target="_blank"&gt;On this we can all agree. Selection is bad for our schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Politics is often defined by what people disagree on. However, some issues are above party politics and it’s time that tackling social mobility became one of them. As politicians from three different parties, we sparred across the despatch box but now we’re coming together to build a cross-party consensus, focused on looking at the evidence of what works, to tackle inequality in education and boost social mobility. Successive governments have made progress in boosting attainment and tackling poor performance across the schools system, but with the attainment gap between disadvantaged childr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>England football team underperforming as it has too many privately-educated players, Labour MP suggests - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/england-performance-privately-educated-players-stella-creasy-labour-mp-comments-a7433561.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAk7o3zHjKxwRy0KzUGvpW8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 12:11:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/england-performance-privately-educated-players-stella-creasy-labour-mp-comments-a7433561.html" target="_blank"&gt;England football team underperforming as it has too many privately-educated players, Labour MP suggests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;England’s football team may be underperforming because it has too many privately-educated players, according to Labour MP Stella Creasy. The MP for Walthamstow said the team’s shortfallings could be because talented players in the state school system were being missed. Her comments came during a House of Commons debate on social mobility in which Conservative MP John Redwood said grammar school selection offered “life changing” opportunities for young talented players and musicians. Read more - Ex-England footballer reveals he was abused by coach for four years - Two fans who slept in Old T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Theresa May embroiled in fresh Budget controversy over unfunded grammar school places - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/theresa-may-grammar-schools-education-budget-unfunded-places-treasury-philip-hammond-labour-a7630276.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOaHTIp39kW8Gh_sEvPAtKQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 22:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/theresa-may-grammar-schools-education-budget-unfunded-places-treasury-philip-hammond-labour-a7630276.html" target="_blank"&gt;Theresa May embroiled in fresh Budget controversy over unfunded grammar school places&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May faces a fresh Budget storm after it emerged that £320m announced to create thousands of places at her flagship grammar schools will only cover a fraction of the cost of setting them up. Treasury officials admitted to The Independent that money set out in the Budget will not be enough to pay for the 70,000 free school places promised by the Prime Minister. Ms May was so proud of the pledge to create the places at 140 new schools, that she chose to announce it personally the day before Chancellor Philip Hammond’s Budget statement. - Read more Theresa May's grammar school plans wer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Corbyn accuses May of breaking Tory pledge on education funding - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/mar/22/jeremy-corbyn-theresa-may-tory-pledge-education-funding-cuts</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEORVPAKj4PcGSX2QkrllxUkqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 13:11:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/mar/22/jeremy-corbyn-theresa-may-tory-pledge-education-funding-cuts" target="_blank"&gt;Corbyn accuses May of breaking Tory pledge on education funding&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May has been accused by Jeremy Corbyn of breaching a Conservative manifesto pledge not to cut education funding, prompting her to launch a personal attack on the Labour frontbench for sending their children to private and grammar schools. The prime minister made the personal criticisms after Corbyn said her plans to shake up school funding would be “betraying a generation” by leaving about 9,000 schools facing steep cuts. Related: Everything you need to know about the English schools funding row He also read out a letter from Eileen, a primary school teacher, who said parents were h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Government school policies need to be based on evidence - not just a hunch - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/school-policies-government-theresa-may-education-grammar-schools-election-manifesto-a7755856.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHvLIkk7oRQn05HvXR7ELkcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/education/education-news/school-policies-government-theresa-may-education-grammar-schools-election-manifesto-a7755856.html" target="_blank"&gt;Government school policies need to be based on evidence - not just a hunch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week, the Education Policy Institute publishes a detailed assessment of what the three largest parties say about education in England. School funding, and the budget pressures being faced by schools, was an issue already being felt in schools and Westminster alike. So it is not surprising to see significant commitments from all the major parties. All are committed to reforming the funding system so that similar pupils receive the same funding wherever they are in the country. They also promise that no school should lose out in cash terms from this change – which ought to help secure po...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Children need to be educated for the Fourth Industrial Revolution, but grammar schools are leaving them behind - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/theresa-may-grammar-schools-future-of-work-failing-children-a7630971.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKKiamdV-DfU5EYCoR044foqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 11:55:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/theresa-may-grammar-schools-future-of-work-failing-children-a7630971.html" target="_blank"&gt;Children need to be educated for the Fourth Industrial Revolution, but grammar schools are leaving them behind&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the last few days the Prime Minister, Theresa May, claimed she was creating an extra 70,000 grammar school places while the Chancellor announced an extra £500 million for technical education. The Prime Minister claims the grammar school policy is about helping the brightest amongst the poor, the Chancellor that his skills policy is about tackling poor productivity. The grammar school policy is already falling apart. Instead of funding for 70,000 places it has emerged that funding for only 13,000 places by 2020 has been allocated by the Treasury. But even if both measures were delivered i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Grammar schools: Flagship Tory education plan 'likely to be derailed by election failure' - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/conservative-plans-new-grammar-schools-on-hold-graham-brady-theresa-may-a7784646.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPISB1l16DIU49yoQsO8RK8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/conservative-plans-new-grammar-schools-on-hold-graham-brady-theresa-may-a7784646.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grammar schools: Flagship Tory education plan 'likely to be derailed by election failure'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May’s plan to open new grammar schools across the UK is unlikely to be implemented after she failed to secure a parliamentary majority, a senior Conservative backbencher has suggested. Graham Brady, who chairs the influential 1922 Committee of Tory backbenchers and is a prominent campaigner for more grammar schools, said his party could be forced to settle for introducing a “rather modest pilot” in place of its manifesto pledge to “lift the ban on the establishment of selective schools”. It follows a general election result that saw Ms May fall eight seats short of a House of Common...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Create new grammars to help poor, white pupils, report commissioned by Labour council suggests - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/31/create-new-grammars-to-help-poor-white-pupils-report-commissione/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMk6JgAA3A12H5vjGm0HM7gqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 14:34:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/31/create-new-grammars-to-help-poor-white-pupils-report-commissione/" target="_blank"&gt;Create new grammars to help poor, white pupils, report commissioned by Labour council suggests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New grammar schools will improve the prospect of white working-class boys in Britain’s worst-performing area, a report commissioned by a Labour council has suggested. A major study, commissioned by Knowsley Council, Merseyside, said the introduction of selective schools in the area should be adopted to transform the performance among an ethnic group that has the lowest level of educational attainment. Knowsley, on the outskirts of Liverpool, is the second-poorest borough in England, and over 95 per cent of the resident population is white British. With roughly 150,000 residents, it is also ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Education Secretary could face High Court challenge over grammar school expansion plans - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/04/14/education-secretary-could-face-high-court-challenge-grammar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPkiohQ3W4bI_rNaZNsBkNgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 17:19:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/04/14/education-secretary-could-face-high-court-challenge-grammar/" target="_blank"&gt;Education Secretary could face High Court challenge over grammar school expansion plans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Education Secretary could face a High Court challenge over her grammar school expansion plans, it has emerged, as the the country’s biggest education union claimed they are illegal. Kevin Courtney, general secretary of the Nation Union of Teachers (NUT), said that a handful of schools have set up “grammar streams”, whereby a cohort of students at non-selective schools are chosen on the basis of an entrance exam and then educated separately from their peers. Speaking at the union’s annual conference in Cardiff, Mr Courtney said this was contrary to the 1998 School Standards and Framework...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Government under fire for 'cash for cabs' school transport plan - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/mar/18/government-under-fire-for-cash-for-cabs-school-transport-plan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJqr4CviYVZeIs-V2qDtlyMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 06:00:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/mar/18/government-under-fire-for-cash-for-cabs-school-transport-plan" target="_blank"&gt;Government under fire for 'cash for cabs' school transport plan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New grammar school pupils could be ferried up to 15 miles by taxi to their schools, at a cost of up to £5,000 per pupil every year, despite cuts to last year’s general school transport budget for disabled and disadvantaged pupils. The government has said it would invest £5m a year to fund transport for the poorest pupils to reach grammar schools so costs were not a barrier to a selective education for pupils who received free school meals or whose parents claimed maximum working tax credits. About 1,000-1,500 pupils are estimated to require the funding, meaning that the cost per pupil could...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>There was nothing wrong with Tesco's 'Good Friday' advert - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/letters/tesco-easter-good-friday-grammar-schools-immigration-afghanistan-nhs-a7685531.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED8ULKOvqc8F6dR2rMPoB8UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTDMyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 17:24:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/letters/tesco-easter-good-friday-grammar-schools-immigration-afghanistan-nhs-a7685531.html" target="_blank"&gt;There was nothing wrong with Tesco's 'Good Friday' advert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a church member and a believing Christian, I wasn't in the least offended by Tesco's Good Friday beer advert. If some people wish to consume more alcohol than usual on Good Friday (or any other day), that's fine by me, as long as I don't have to encounter them. It is not up to religious groups to coerce non-members into aligning with their own beliefs, and we should be wary of the danger that advertisers will be reluctant to adopt any slogan for fear of offending some group or sect or cult somewhere on the planet. Sam Boote Nottingham Grammar schools are divisive and unfair I disagree wh...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>To justify expanding grammar schools, the government is inventing evidence - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/apr/13/grammar-schools-ordinary-working-families-evidence</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOU9w4GucWwAdJkkqWJvTuMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 15:29:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2017/apr/13/grammar-schools-ordinary-working-families-evidence" target="_blank"&gt;To justify expanding grammar schools, the government is inventing evidence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone listening to the pronouncements of government ministers lately will have heard three words: “ordinary working families”. These are the people Theresa May would have you believe her government is all about. I can see why she made it a slogan. It certainly sounds a lot better than “tax cuts for the rich, cutbacks for the rest”, or any other description of the Tories’ actual policies in government. Of course, it left open the question of what exactly the prime minister means by “ordinary working families”. It seemed that ministers were struggling to make policy around an undefined sound...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>New wave of free schools planned despite secondary staff cuts - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/apr/12/new-free-schools-despite-secondary-staff-cuts</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFQZ_wcYimXPfZxgfqIOkuUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 23:01:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/education/2017/apr/12/new-free-schools-despite-secondary-staff-cuts" target="_blank"&gt;New wave of free schools planned despite secondary staff cuts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government is pressing ahead with spending on its free-school-building programme in England, despite a reported funding crisis causing nearly two-thirds of secondary schools to cut staff. Justine Greening, the education secretary, is to announce a further 111 new free schools have been given the green light to open by the Department for Education, while 20 local authorities have been granted permission to open special educational needs schools using the free school framework. The rapid expansion, which the DfE says will create more than 69,000 places across primary, secondary and specia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Children from families earning less than £33,000 should have priority for grammars, Justine Greening says - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/13/justine-greening-refuses-rule-grammar-school-quotas-poorer-children/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJ88SPpRC20zxCqvOsomhUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 14:49:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/04/13/justine-greening-refuses-rule-grammar-school-quotas-poorer-children/" target="_blank"&gt;Children from families earning less than £33,000 should have priority for grammars, Justine Greening says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children from families who earn less than £33,000 should be given priority in grammar schools, as the Government seeks to define “ordinary working families” for the first time. The Education Secretary said on Thursday that a new wave of selective schools will target children from families on modest incomes who tend to live outside inner cities, including in suburbs and coastal areas. The group will include children who come from families earning below the median income level but who do not qualify for free school meals. Data from the Department for Education shows around one in three childr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Grammar schools could ask parents for up to £40 a month to make up funding shortfalls - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/01/25/grammar-schools-could-ask-parents-40-month-make-funding-shortfalls/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELSzbQFCZzcqbbboCULSASIqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 09:19:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/01/25/grammar-schools-could-ask-parents-40-month-make-funding-shortfalls/" target="_blank"&gt;Grammar schools could ask parents for up to £40 a month to make up funding shortfalls&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grammar schools are considering asking parents for cash to make up budget shortfalls set to be caused by changes in funding, head teachers have warned. Families could be asked for £30 to £40 a month to ensure teaching standards do not fall, the Grammar School Heads Association (GSHA) has said. Conservative MPs have called for the Government to review the "unacceptable" reforms, which could leave some schools choosing between cutting facilities or switching off heating to keep costs down. Tim Gartside, head of Altrincham Grammar School for Boys and a member of the GSHA, said he was consideri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Theresa May unveils plans for new generation of grammar schools - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/03/07/theresa-may-unveils-plans-new-generation-grammar-schools/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELc7AG-1UEF2Xtjk1GIznW8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/03/07/theresa-may-unveils-plans-new-generation-grammar-schools/" target="_blank"&gt;Theresa May unveils plans for new generation of grammar schools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theresa May today unveils plans for a new generation of grammar schools as she announces that £320 million has been set aside in the Budget to help end the “brutal and unacceptable” truth of selection by income. Writing in The Daily Telegraph, the Prime Minister says she has made it her “personal mission” to build “a school system that works for everyone” and will within weeks begin the process of reversing the current ban on new grammars. The Prime Minister, who has made grammars a key part of her education policy, will fund up to 140 new free schools, many of which are expected to become ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Grammar schools to offer lower pass marks to poorer pupils - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/grammar-schools-eleven-plus-lower-pass-rate-poorer-pupils-social-mobility-justine-greening-a7624691.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBjkLiTu0FQiE2hG08W6_RMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 16:19:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/grammar-schools-eleven-plus-lower-pass-rate-poorer-pupils-social-mobility-justine-greening-a7624691.html" target="_blank"&gt;Grammar schools to offer lower pass marks to poorer pupils&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grammar schools could be forced to lower the eleven-plus pass mark for children from lower-income families in order to end the stranglehold middle-class pupils have on places, Government sources have said. The proposed reforms, to be announced next month, came as Prime Minister Theresa May was poised to allow the creation of new grammar schools for the first time since 1998. Government insiders told The Times that rules governing social mobility requirements for new selective schools could be rolled out to the existing 163 grammar schools. - Read more Toby Young: Government 'could do away w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Church of England rejects new grammar schools as it states it will build schools for the 'many, not just the few' - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/04/07/church-england-rejects-new-grammar-schools-states-will-build/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK_pSlYnMGHJF0PMWDTlh0EqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCA8LkF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 18:05:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/education/2017/04/07/church-england-rejects-new-grammar-schools-states-will-build/" target="_blank"&gt;Church of England rejects new grammar schools as it states it will build schools for the 'many, not just the few'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Church of England has rejected the Government’s plans to create hundreds of new grammar schools as it claims it will build schools for “the many, not just the few”. The Church, the largest single provider of schools in England, has ruled out the creation of any new grammars on the grounds that they cater only to a select group of “high achievers”. Responsible for more than 4,700 schools across the country, the announcement follows a decision taken at the General Synod last year, which concluded that the Church should move away from selection towards schools that serve the “whole communi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item></channel></rss>