<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Nehe Milner-Skudder - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJQgKIh9DQkFTRVFvTEwyMHZNREV5Tld3d2RuZ1NBbVZ1S0FBUAE?hl=en-NZ&amp;gl=NZ&amp;ceid=NZ:en</link><language>en-NZ</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:27:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Duncan Garner: Get a grip, Nehe Milner-Skudder, or get yourself a new gripe - Stuff.co.nz</title><link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/waikato-times/opinion/109007154/Duncan-Garner-Get-a-grip-Nehe-Milner-Skudder-or-get-yourself-a-new-gripe</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMigAFodHRwczovL3d3dy5zdHVmZi5jby5uei93YWlrYXRvLXRpbWVzL29waW5pb24vMTA5MDA3MTU0L0R1bmNhbi1HYXJuZXItR2V0LWEtZ3JpcC1OZWhlLU1pbG5lci1Ta3VkZGVyLW9yLWdldC15b3Vyc2VsZi1hLW5ldy1ncmlwZdIBAA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.stuff.co.nz/waikato-times/opinion/109007154/Duncan-Garner-Get-a-grip-Nehe-Milner-Skudder-or-get-yourself-a-new-gripe" target="_blank"&gt;Duncan Garner: Get a grip, Nehe Milner-Skudder, or get yourself a new gripe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Stuff.co.nz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPINION: I apologise in advance for using up 700 words on the breathless over-reaction of a former All Black but Nehe Milner-Skudder can't sidestep this one.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.stuff.co.nz">Stuff.co.nz</source><media:content url="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/proxy/2Mpikz1p1H7rQkfKas3fNpN9IYK4ADFgXge8RAhDmC1FF_lfvz98aaKixO8uSf-eH6lVV3ve7ZQutMKJ6Hqp15Io_Qly5xz7I0xQv5fsiV2YbPOzV15sJL13_FtiSQbWWaKPyCXaNxDw8LVOuKz9sRXQuDZWkTz_lQ9O5Djlsp3RcC1u5R96Xsw434Ej2sD3w_Xxkwo1bFCRnpAlqMEVbQ=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>All Blacks star Nehe Milner-Skudder weighs into Nelson Māori Santa saga - 'Santa is a white tradition and we can celebrate it in our own way' - TVNZ</title><link>https://www.tvnz.co.nz/one-news/new-zealand/all-blacks-star-nehe-milner-skudder-weighs-into-nelson-m-ori-santa-saga-white-tradition-and-we-can-celebrate-in-our-own-way</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMipwFodHRwczovL3d3dy50dm56LmNvLm56L29uZS1uZXdzL25ldy16ZWFsYW5kL2FsbC1ibGFja3Mtc3Rhci1uZWhlLW1pbG5lci1za3VkZGVyLXdlaWdocy1pbnRvLW5lbHNvbi1tLW9yaS1zYW50YS1zYWdhLXdoaXRlLXRyYWRpdGlvbi1hbmQtd2UtY2FuLWNlbGVicmF0ZS1pbi1vdXItb3duLXdhedIBAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:07:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.tvnz.co.nz/one-news/new-zealand/all-blacks-star-nehe-milner-skudder-weighs-into-nelson-m-ori-santa-saga-white-tradition-and-we-can-celebrate-in-our-own-way" target="_blank"&gt;All Blacks star Nehe Milner-Skudder weighs into Nelson Māori Santa saga - 'Santa is a white tradition and we can celebrate it in our own way'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TVNZ&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Blacks star Nehe Milner-Skudder has defended the choice to have a Māori man in a korowai arrive in Santa's sleigh during the Nelson Santa Parade earlier ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWpBd0ptbWpZQU1FY1dFMlZkUGRWeFNLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><source url="https://www.tvnz.co.nz">TVNZ</source><media:content url="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/Je8rvx5Y2n2M1IyZIwaW7K50MSU77rSTJJ1oVCTYp2Rbh9b6kLmBEbGJasi_TE8qgz4P9E4-8CjcWYfN1e-jPeFH3LUI9N_ZnLZ60tx1lL2O__KtJ7b5CwC103zhilQSq2p7ST46Ltg2bGo-dH6-u_tNWKkOr5ta1wYIZaBeAmtOqS75Tfo7uylhZmlnB5-9rIzDLef1szaj3a3dJ-VVUDs0fOX3FhFcs7RwBppAQp_Bnfaz4Q=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Could be January before we know how bad Nehe Milner-Skudder's shoulder injury is - Stuff.co.nz</title><link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/sport/rugby/super-rugby/108961219/could-be-january-before-we-know-how-bad-nehe-milnerskudders-shoulder-injury-is</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiiAFodHRwczovL3d3dy5zdHVmZi5jby5uei9zcG9ydC9ydWdieS9zdXBlci1ydWdieS8xMDg5NjEyMTkvY291bGQtYmUtamFudWFyeS1iZWZvcmUtd2Uta25vdy1ob3ctYmFkLW5laGUtbWlsbmVyc2t1ZGRlcnMtc2hvdWxkZXItaW5qdXJ5LWlz0gEA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.stuff.co.nz/sport/rugby/super-rugby/108961219/could-be-january-before-we-know-how-bad-nehe-milnerskudders-shoulder-injury-is" target="_blank"&gt;Could be January before we know how bad Nehe Milner-Skudder's shoulder injury is&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Stuff.co.nz&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The All Blacks and Hurricanes have yet to talk in detail about the state of Nehe Milner-Skudder's shoulder.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.stuff.co.nz">Stuff.co.nz</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/I3RNrltqlR-C4lqytDWiYKwkE62ljrUUSwMENTa2hxEvtQ1idANBq5Ca9BCvwbweeNCzR364J6faPIA4DrOpLq0-oKS_NHl_qpFAVJXX22DBQdyedUe2Tb0qveJLQvXWs7mKNKSQLZbO6TCCrREuZmDvygx7cCOactQuHFha4SrhNcPUjCrfCaCOGbeHF1STJYQdi3CoMmK9BuEEB__agw=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Sir Ian McGeechan's five players to watch in 2017 - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2016/12/31/sir-ian-mcgeechans-five-players-watch-2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHfL4_TXbVoGvAlwmNkcv90qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 16:07:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2016/12/31/sir-ian-mcgeechans-five-players-watch-2017/" target="_blank"&gt;Sir Ian McGeechan's five players to watch in 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;My five players to watch for 2017 include four Home Unions players and one from New Zealand. It is impossible to ignore the Lions and my picks reflect that – none of these players would be considered front runners to line up against the All Blacks at Eden Park in June in the First Test, but all are players who I believe have a special set of skills that will cause the All Blacks real problems, which is what must happen if the Lions are to prevail. Nehe Milner-Skudder Wing / full-back: Manawatu, Hurricanes and New Zealand Milner-Skudder has been injured for most of the last year but I’ve bee...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>New Zealand 39 Argentina 22: Vaea Fifita rescues All Blacks with solo try - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/09/09/new-zealand-39-argentina-22-vaea-fifita-rescues-blacks-solo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEISyFby6DwRoZZS03G6O8EQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 10:08:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/09/09/new-zealand-39-argentina-22-vaea-fifita-rescues-blacks-solo/" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand 39 Argentina 22: Vaea Fifita rescues All Blacks with solo try&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand needed a second-half surge, inspired by Vaea Fifita’s stunning solo try, to shake off Argentina and record a bonus-point win in New Plymouth. With just half an hour remaining, the All Blacks trailed their resolute opponents 22-15 and had been reduced to 14 men thanks to Beauden Barrett’s yellow card. However, Fifita burst down the left wing for a crucial response and late tries from Damian McKenzie and Barrett, on his return from the sin bin, secured a rather flattering result. Steve Hansen’s side are clearly looking to hone their attacking game with one eye on Rugby World Cup 2...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Bound by blood', the Maori All Blacks are ready to give Lions a stiff examination - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/06/15/bound-blood-maori-blacks-ready-give-lions-stiff-examination/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH5qzIOpzxQNX-DvfPBBdY4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 10:33:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/06/15/bound-blood-maori-blacks-ready-give-lions-stiff-examination/" target="_blank"&gt;'Bound by blood', the Maori All Blacks are ready to give Lions a stiff examination&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The British and Irish Lions will face ‘the strongest Maori side I have ever had,’ according to head coach, Colin Cooper, a team featuring nine All Blacks in the 23-man match-day squad, and ‘bound by blood,’ as they look to replicate the achievement of the 2005 side that beat the Lions. The Maori will present a fierce, highly skilled challenge, spurred on by the deeds of their tribal ancestors as well as the impetus provided by their desire to attack from all parts of the field. They field some of the most exciting runners in New Zealand rugby, from wings, Nehe Milner-Skudder and Rieko Ioane...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Marcus Smith of Quins can be England’s X-factor rookie, says Eddie Jones - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2017/sep/22/eddie-jones-marcus-smith-england-world-cup-x-factor-rookie</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKHf6S9nfegF2bS80RJw-i4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 21:00:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2017/sep/22/eddie-jones-marcus-smith-england-world-cup-x-factor-rookie" target="_blank"&gt;Marcus Smith of Quins can be England’s X-factor rookie, says Eddie Jones&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eddie Jones has said the teenage fly-half Marcus Smith can be England’s “X-factor rookie” for the 2019 World Cup but warned the Harlequins No10 he will spend most of next week’s training camp “polishing boots”. The 18-year-old has made only two Premiership starts for Harlequins, including a man-of-the-match performance against Wasps last weekend, but he was on Friday named in Jones’ 33-man squad for the three-day training camp in Oxford. In total Smith has played 196 minutes of Premiership rugby but he shone in the win over Wasps, kicking 14 points including two crucial late penalties. Jone...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>New Zealand 57 South Africa 0: All Blacks hit Springboks with record thrashing - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/09/16/new-zealand-57-south-africa-0-blacks-hit-springboks-record-thrashing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC8lOC6I8P_u16HmZ8mROe8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 10:26:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/09/16/new-zealand-57-south-africa-0-blacks-hit-springboks-record-thrashing/" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand 57 South Africa 0: All Blacks hit Springboks with record thrashing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 96-year history of this fixture has produced hard-fought, heavyweight contests that have been close and compelling. This was not one of them. New Zealand crossed the whitewash eight times on the way to a half century in North Harbour, cutting a swathe through South Africa and achieving a record margin of victory over the Springboks. A last-minute try from replacement hooker Codie Taylor, and a pinpoint conversion from Beauden Barrett, meant the All Blacks registered 57 for the second consecutive time against Allister Coetzee’s side. Last year in Durban, South Africa managed 15 points in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Julian Savea’s All Blacks omission puts superstar wing at curious crossroads - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/08/07/julian-saveas-blacks-omission-puts-superstar-wing-curious-crossroads/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKtGjf3m7VUSzCOkmvjciYYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 14:21:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/08/07/julian-saveas-blacks-omission-puts-superstar-wing-curious-crossroads/" target="_blank"&gt;Julian Savea’s All Blacks omission puts superstar wing at curious crossroads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Julian Savea turned 27 today. Presumably he received a few pleasing presents, but an ominously dark lump of coal also arrived. His omission from a 33-man New Zealand squad for The Rugby Championship, which begins on August 19 with a Bledisloe Cup encounter in Sydney, means the hulking Hurricane is at a crossroads. Steve Hansen did mention Savea senior in the subsequent press conference, praising him as a “very, very good All Black” and offering a route to redemption. “Julian’s done some great things,” Hansen said. “I feel for him a wee bit at this stage. “I’m sure he won’t have finished his...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>South Africa suffer worst defeat in their Test history at hands of rampant All Blacks - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/rugby/rugby-union/new-zealand-south-africa-result-score-report-tries-highlights-nehe-milner-skudder-a7950161.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELXMwgtrYeKK0ebB8iZ1fNcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/rugby/rugby-union/new-zealand-south-africa-result-score-report-tries-highlights-nehe-milner-skudder-a7950161.html" target="_blank"&gt;South Africa suffer worst defeat in their Test history at hands of rampant All Blacks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winger Nehe Milner-Skudder scored two of the All Blacks' eight tries as they destroyed South Africa 57-0 at North Harbour Stadium on Saturday to condemn the Springboks to their worst defeat in test history. The All Blacks were ruthless in their execution of their opportunities to post 50 points for the second successive time against the Springboks. Last year's 57-15 win in Durban had been the previous largest winning margin between the two sides. The win in front of more than 30,000 fans also surpassed the 53-3 victory England posted against the Springboks at Twickenham in 2002. Rieko Ioane...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>New Zealand v Lions: All Blacks announce formidable test squad - including the three Barrett brothers - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/06/08/new-zealand-v-lions-blacks-announce-test-squad-include-concussed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFga7CwXzamNdf3m2izi6G8qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 03:36:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/06/08/new-zealand-v-lions-blacks-announce-test-squad-include-concussed/" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand v Lions: All Blacks announce formidable test squad - including the three Barrett brothers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;In naming a full-strength 33-man All Black squad on Thursday for the series against the Lions, Steve Hansen effectively warned Warren Gatland that he hasn’t seen anything yet when it comes to the quality of New Zealand rugby. Gatland suggested on Wednesday night following the 22-16 defeat to the Auckland Blues that there was little or no difference between Super and international rugby. Hansen dismissed that notion out of court. “There is not any comparison (between the levels),” said Hansen who stated that this was the ‘toughest’ process he has ever had to go through such was the depth of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>George North is an athlete-designer's dream so why is he reticent and lacking dynamism for the Lions? - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/06/26/george-north-athlete-designers-dream-reticent-lacking-dynamism/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKUMeSvL-WmMAKwwMXePPgcqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 11:11:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2017/06/26/george-north-athlete-designers-dream-reticent-lacking-dynamism/" target="_blank"&gt;George North is an athlete-designer's dream so why is he reticent and lacking dynamism for the Lions?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A question, posed by a rugby magazine here: “How good would George North be if he had been born in New Zealand?” More pertinently: how good would George North be without the multiple concussions that may have contributed to the dip in form that caused him to lose his Lions Test place? The second question is carefully worded. Jumping to amateur medical conclusions about North’s history of head injuries is risky, and potentially irresponsible. But we do know that out here North has been a phantom of the rampaging wing who earned comparisons with Jonah Lomu on the 2013 Lions trip to Australia....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Melbourne Rebels abject as Hurricanes run out 71-6 winners - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-03-04/hurricanes-v-rebels-super-rugby/8325166</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIItXzSdmql8EUnTk9lqIqAqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDtjw4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 08:33:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-03-04/hurricanes-v-rebels-super-rugby/8325166" target="_blank"&gt;Melbourne Rebels abject as Hurricanes run out 71-6 winners&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Melbourne Rebels' nightmare start to the Super Rugby season has continued with a humiliating 71-6 loss to defending champions the Hurricanes in Wellington. The Rebels were unable to get across the try line while the home side seemingly scored at will, touching down 11 times. Following a heavy 56-18 loss to the Blues at home last Thursday night, Melbourne has now conceded 127 points in the opening two rounds in their worst possible start. Rebels captain Nic Stirzaker said there was little to like about his team's showing. "It was a pretty bad performance in all facets of the game - set p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>British and Irish Lions vs Maori All Blacks live: Latest score, what time does is start, what TV channel is it on? - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/rugby/rugby-union/lionstour/british-and-irish-lions-vs-maori-all-blacks-live-stream-latest-score-what-time-does-it-start-tv-a7794481.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEQogP4yC55eB25ld8yLrFIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 02:45:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/sport/rugby/rugby-union/lionstour/british-and-irish-lions-vs-maori-all-blacks-live-stream-latest-score-what-time-does-it-start-tv-a7794481.html" target="_blank"&gt;British and Irish Lions vs Maori All Blacks live: Latest score, what time does is start, what TV channel is it on?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The British and Irish Lions face the Maori All Blacks in their fifth warm-up match on their tour of New Zealand in what will be their penultimate game before the Test series with the All Blacks. Follow the latest here. - Maori All Blacks vs British and Irish Lions kicks off at 19:35 local time [08:35 BST] - Warren Gatland recalls a number of Test candidates to face the Maori - No Owen Farrell with fly-half ruled out through injury - Johnny Sexton starts at 10, Peter O’Mahony captains the Lions with Sam Warburton on bench - Maori All Blacks captained by Liam Messam - Nehe Milner-Skudder star...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>New Zealand name strong team to face England as Sonny Bill Williams partners Jack Goodhue at centre - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2018/11/08/new-zealand-name-strong-team-face-england-sonny-bill-williams/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMHxlgCZncjiKFWCxTKX4S0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTC-oxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:17:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2018/11/08/new-zealand-name-strong-team-face-england-sonny-bill-williams/" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand name strong team to face England as Sonny Bill Williams partners Jack Goodhue at centre&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An injury to Joe Moody has forced All Blacks coach Steve Hansen to tweak his strongest possible side for Saturday's November Test against England at Twickenham. Moody suffered a torn eyelid during training earlier this week and has been ruled out for up to six weeks, with Karl Tu'inukuafe replacing him as loosehead prop at Twickenham. "Joe Moody has found a way to get himself injured in unusual fashion this year," Hansen said. "Anyone else it would probably have missed his eye. "(The) plastic surgeon has recommended six weeks and as our doctor described it, your eyelid is your window washer...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>England look to profit from Brad Shields’ inside info against All Blacks - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/06/england-brad-shields-new-zealand</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI0aZWD_yiUjwZy_azJ8Dt0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 22:00:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/06/england-brad-shields-new-zealand" target="_blank"&gt;England look to profit from Brad Shields’ inside info against All Blacks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brad Shields knows the messages will start arriving soon. Having left New Zealand provincial rugby last summer to chase his dream of playing for England, the 27-year-old knows the All Blacks rather better than he does his new teammates and facing the haka at Twickenham will be almost like gazing into a mirror. If anything, it is his former Hurricanes teammates such as Beauden Barrett and Ardie Savea who will feel even more disconcerted. Shields was their Super Rugby captain until recently; now, according to Ben Youngs, he is divulging their trade secrets. Related: Tackle laws make red cards...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Brad Shields warned to expect stick from Beauden Barrett and co during New Zealand tie - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2018/11/06/brad-shields-warned-expect-stick-beauden-barrett-co-new-zealand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELNI46jRY79yQN40JAdVM2kqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2018/11/06/brad-shields-warned-expect-stick-beauden-barrett-co-new-zealand/" target="_blank"&gt;Brad Shields warned to expect stick from Beauden Barrett and co during New Zealand tie&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The word from the All Blacks camp is that Brad Shields should expect some ribbing during Saturday’s Quilter international at Twickenham, as the New Zealander will face the All Blacks less than six months after making his England debut. Due to the hasty nature of the back row’s departure from Wellington, the reality is that he will know some of the All Blacks and particularly his former team-mates from Super Rugby side the Hurricanes a lot more intimately than his England colleagues. Shields goes a long way back with talented New Zealand fly-half Beauden Barrett, as they lifted the 2011 Unde...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Kieran Read suggests retirement plans before All Blacks beat Japan 69-31 - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/03/youthful-all-blacks-headline-try-fest-in-tokyo-against-japan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEObSWDSrLaaJ-KuGACHvRYoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 08:00:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/nov/03/youthful-all-blacks-headline-try-fest-in-tokyo-against-japan" target="_blank"&gt;Kieran Read suggests retirement plans before All Blacks beat Japan 69-31&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Blacks captain Kieran Read has said he is likely to quit international rugby after next year’s World Cup in Japan and take a contract overseas. Read, who turned 33 last week, will line up for his third World Cup next year after helping the All Blacks raise the Webb Ellis trophy in 2011 and 2015. Related: Sportwatch: All Blacks v Japan, A-League, WNBL and more – live! “So for me I think it probably won’t be in New Zealand,” Read told New Zealand media of his post-Japan plans. “We have always thought as a family that we would like to go overseas and use that experience for the kids. That ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Sam Cane injury: All Blacks say flanker is expected to make full recovery after surgery on broken neck - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/rugby/rugby-union/international/sam-cane-broken-neck-injury-surgery-full-recovery-injury-all-blacks-full-recovery-a8576836.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ-Lq4fLvUA2kv56XybDoZ8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 07:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/rugby/rugby-union/international/sam-cane-broken-neck-injury-surgery-full-recovery-injury-all-blacks-full-recovery-a8576836.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sam Cane injury: All Blacks say flanker is expected to make full recovery after surgery on broken neck&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flanker Sam Cane is up and walking around after having surgery to repair a broken bone in his neck and is expected to make a full recovery, the All Blacks said on Wednesday. The 26-year-old suffered the injury during New Zealand's 32-30 victory over South Africa in Pretoria on Saturday. All Blacks doctor Tony Page said on Sunday Cane would probably be out of action for at least three months, while coach Steve Hansen said they would not rush his return to the field. "Sam Cane is up and about after his successful operation in South Africa," the All Blacks said on their Twitter account, also p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Money in European rugby is too good to resist, says Wasps’ Lima Sopoaga - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/sep/11/money-too-good-new-zealanders-wasps-lima-sopoaga</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELvqdnABcitSCY_sfURBk5sqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 20:59:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2018/sep/11/money-too-good-new-zealanders-wasps-lima-sopoaga" target="_blank"&gt;Money in European rugby is too good to resist, says Wasps’ Lima Sopoaga&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Wasps fly-half Lima Sopoaga believes the player drain from New Zealand to Europe will increase because the lure of the All Blacks jersey no longer outweighs the financial incentives on offer in the northern hemisphere. Sopoaga has 16 New Zealand caps – two of which are starts – and signed a lucrative two-year deal with Wasps in January. He arrived over the summer, ruling him out of the international picture in light of the All Blacks’ strict policy of picking only players based at home. Related: Brad Shields hands England injury blow as Wasps fall to Exeter It was once the case that All...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Pressure is on as Chris Boyd begins Northampton rescue mission as director of rugby - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2018/08/27/pressure-chris-boyd-begins-northampton-rescue-mission-director/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPjunI0a9AaFBHp-PJodhL4qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2018/08/27/pressure-chris-boyd-begins-northampton-rescue-mission-director/" target="_blank"&gt;Pressure is on as Chris Boyd begins Northampton rescue mission as director of rugby&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chris Boyd, Northampton Saints’ new director of rugby, believes that he is taking up the reins in what is “as tightly contested a competition as there is in the world,” as he prepares for an opening-day Gallagher Premiership trip to Gloucester. Given that the New Zealander is the man who helped nurture one of the finest talents in world rugby in the shape of All Black fly-half Beauden Barrett, during his time at Wellington and the Hurricanes, his judgment on rugby matters has merit. Boyd is a down-to-earth Kiwi, a trained pharmacist who lived in London during the Eighties, one who worked hi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>New Zealand 40 Australia 12: Four tries for Beauden Barrett in another Bledisloe Cup thrashing - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2018/08/25/new-zealand-vs-australia-bledisloe-cup-live-score-updates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE_5Apq_0kUgU7vXCHFvxMwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 09:43:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2018/08/25/new-zealand-vs-australia-bledisloe-cup-live-score-updates/" target="_blank"&gt;New Zealand 40 Australia 12: Four tries for Beauden Barrett in another Bledisloe Cup thrashing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;10:43AMPresentation Owen Franks receives his 100th cap with his family watching on. Classily, Michael Hooper congratulates the All Blacks for their victory and Franks for reaching the milestone. He reinforces his confidence in the Wallabies squad too. They need wins, though. Credit: Sky Sports Kieran Read then pays tribute to his squad. He insists that it doesn't come easy to New Zealand. At times today, that didn't look entirely accurate. Credit: Sky Sports And with that, the Bledisloe Cup is held aloft. Credit: Sky Sports 10:33AMThe difference ABs really do what should be the bare minimum...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Australia 13 New Zealand 38: All Blacks dismantle Australia with clinical second half - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2018/08/18/australia-vs-new-zealand-bledisloe-cup-live-score-updates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENJME2F00FvZhD1A4K8DXHkqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTDpy7cF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 14:13:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/rugby-union/2018/08/18/australia-vs-new-zealand-bledisloe-cup-live-score-updates/" target="_blank"&gt;Australia 13 New Zealand 38: All Blacks dismantle Australia with clinical second half&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand delivered a clinic of counter-attacking in Sydney, scoring five second-half tries to blow away their hosts in this season’s Rugby Championship opening encounter. Australia defended stoutly in the first period but invited pressure with a glut of turnovers, including seven lost lineouts, and eventually paid the price. A 25-point margin of victory did not flatter the All Blacks, such was their ruthlessness in broken-field situations. Back-rower David Pocock, outstanding in defeat, outlined where the Wallabies will begin their re-building operation ahead of next weekend’s return fix...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Steve Hansen says ill-disciplined All Blacks need a ‘wee uppercut’ to sort out their poor behaviour - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/rugby/rugby-union/international/new-zealand-rugby-all-blacks-steve-hansen-ill-discipline-wee-uppercut-joe-moody-owen-franks-a8361026.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKbFap-lIYPuLZQxPt4FSpMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTC8yxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 07:38:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/sport/rugby/rugby-union/international/new-zealand-rugby-all-blacks-steve-hansen-ill-discipline-wee-uppercut-joe-moody-owen-franks-a8361026.html" target="_blank"&gt;Steve Hansen says ill-disciplined All Blacks need a ‘wee uppercut’ to sort out their poor behaviour&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Blacks coach Steve Hansen has concerns about his squad’s discipline ahead of the June tests against France Rugby, saying suspended props Joe Moody and Owen Franks needed to give themselves a “wee uppercut” while on the sidelines. Moody was banned for two matches for elbowing Kurtley Beale in the head in a Super Rugby tie against the New South Wales Waratahs, while his Crusaders team mate Franks was handed a similar sanction for striking against the Auckland Blues. Both Canterbury props were named in Hansen’s squad on Sunday and will be available for the first test against France at Eden...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Autumn Tests prove sharpest cutting edge will lift Six Nations crown - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/blog/2017/nov/27/autumn-tests-internationals-six-nations-new-zealand-scotland-england-ireland-wales-rugby</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPvNgvVQ2a89McnOV01Q-2QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 08:30:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/sport/blog/2017/nov/27/autumn-tests-internationals-six-nations-new-zealand-scotland-england-ireland-wales-rugby" target="_blank"&gt;Autumn Tests prove sharpest cutting edge will lift Six Nations crown&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;those who assume this has been just another routine autumn of Test rugby have not been paying sufficient attention. France failing to beat Japan at home, Scotland sticking 53 points on Australia, Ireland hammering South Africa 38-3, Romania defeating Samoa … not only have there been some eye-catching results but it has proved a difficult November for defence coaches. Scotland’s three home fixtures against Samoa, New Zealand and Australia produced 28 tries, 16 of them for the home side. The All Blacks, in scoring five tries to two in a frantic game in Cardiff, burst through the 500-point bar...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item></channel></rss>