<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>AlphaZero - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqKAgKIiJDQkFTRXdvTkwyY3ZNVEZtTXpGNU1ERXhZeElDWlc0b0FBUAE?hl=en-TZ&amp;gl=TZ&amp;ceid=TZ:en</link><language>en-TZ</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 13:35:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>IBM's DeepMind creates a game learning system - Fudzilla</title><link>https://fudzilla.com/news/ai/47750-ibm-s-deepmind-creates-a-game-learning-system</link><guid isPermaLink="false">52780128760154</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:08:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://fudzilla.com/news/ai/47750-ibm-s-deepmind-creates-a-game-learning-system" target="_blank"&gt;IBM's DeepMind creates a game learning system&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fudzilla&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://mashable.com/article/alphazero-ai-neuralnet-chess-player/" target="_blank"&gt;DeepMind's AlphaZero is an AI neural-net-infused chess master&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Mashable&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.geek.com/tech/deepminds-ai-can-now-beat-humans-at-more-board-games-1764751/" target="_blank"&gt;DeepMind's AI Can Now Beat Humans at More Board Games&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Geek&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.techspot.com/news/77764-deepmind-alphazero-ai-beats-world-top-board-game.html" target="_blank"&gt;DeepMind's AlphaZero AI beats the world's top board game-playing AI models&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TechSpot&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/samshead/2018/12/07/google-deepminds-go-ai-has-mastered-chess-and-shogi/" target="_blank"&gt;Google DeepMind's Go AI Has Mastered Chess And Shogi&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqOQgKIjNDQklTSURvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoTUtFUWphNHMybWpZQU1FUkltWXZOR2M4eHJLQUFQAQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View full coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><source url="https://fudzilla.com">Fudzilla</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/n-jHnUGB79Qd7kHKY4Mi-IbMwg34C_rhfEICrJ74rElW1-gTp4zr7gKATOri2dY5sw5NnJt8MnHfnJmBM_lcu-c3YycZmkcWPGc5u2XYNvywO3k2_uG2qRSHy0RqNs9A95kOlpiNkTE=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>DeepMind in AI breakthrough with smarter version of AlphaGo - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ac50f12a-f962-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENjNbdHMmxFwogkbLz_UlO0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 19:30:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ac50f12a-f962-11e8-af46-2022a0b02a6c" target="_blank"&gt;DeepMind in AI breakthrough with smarter version of AlphaGo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DeepMind, the London-based artificial intelligence company, has announced two research successes — the strongest game-playing AI so far and the world’s most powerful predictor of the shape of protein molecules — as it returns to its scientific roots after agreeing to transfer its health division to parent company Google. In the journal Science, DeepMind presents AlphaZero, a development of its celebrated AlphaGo machine. With no prior knowledge or data input beyond the rules of the game, AlphaZero taught itself to play not only Go but also chess and shogi (Japanese chess) at a level that...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>The next big move for chess - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/53dc86f8-e8cd-11e8-885c-e64da4c0f981</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENKcWQ0hGjk8dLtzr5ZahyMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 13:53:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/53dc86f8-e8cd-11e8-885c-e64da4c0f981" target="_blank"&gt;The next big move for chess&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the World Chess Championship opened in London last week, a tantalising question hung in the air: might this nerdiest of pastimes finally be becoming cool? Two dashing grandmasters are facing off over the next month in the most anticipated clash for a generation. On one side sits Norway’s Magnus Carlsen, the “Mozart of Chess” and, at only 27, already arguably the best player in history. Staring back is yoga-loving US grandmaster Fabiano Caruana, an adventurous, attacking player just one year Carlsen’s junior. Over 12 games he aims to become the first American champion since Bobby Fischer....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>12 Amazing Deep Learning Breakthroughs of 2017 - Forbes Now</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mariyayao/2018/02/05/12-amazing-deep-learning-breakthroughs-of-2017/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB_DT8xjQyQhhjqbOGnJKckqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMJGBAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/mariyayao/2018/02/05/12-amazing-deep-learning-breakthroughs-of-2017/" target="_blank"&gt;12 Amazing Deep Learning Breakthroughs of 2017&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes Now&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shutterstock The quest to give machines a mind of their own occupied the brightest AI specialists in 2017. Machine learning (and especially the newly hip branch, deep learning) practically delivered all of the most stunning achievements in artificial intelligence so far — from systems that beat us at our own games to art-producing neural networks that rival human creativity. At the onset and in hindsight, experts have heralded 2017 as “The Year of AI”. Here are a dozen deep learning breakthroughs from the past year that validate the claim: 1. DeepMind’s AlphaZero Clobbered The Top AI Champ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes Now</source></item><item><title>Techmate: How AI rewrote the rules of chess - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/ea707a24-f6b7-11e7-8715-e94187b3017e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJXN2J9bSf0QCkH9Vb9V7coqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 10:31:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ea707a24-f6b7-11e7-8715-e94187b3017e" target="_blank"&gt;Techmate: How AI rewrote the rules of chess&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;It sounds like a classic case of the unstoppable force coming up against the immovable object. Two world-beating computers, each programmed in a completely different way, take each other on at chess. A titanic tussle seems guaranteed. But what happens if one of the machines has also learned ju-jitsu? Chess strategy has evolved considerably from the days of its first official champion, Wilhelm Steinitz, in 1886, to its latest, the Norwegian grandmaster Magnus Carlsen. But throughout there has been a constant: the number and value of a players’ pieces — known as “material” — have been key. Th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>From the future of bitcoin to Facebook, 2018 in technology - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/dec/31/2018-in-technology-bitcoin-facebook-videogames-augmented-reality</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMedBUdN8X01IcKCXrWn07MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 07:00:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/dec/31/2018-in-technology-bitcoin-facebook-videogames-augmented-reality" target="_blank"&gt;From the future of bitcoin to Facebook, 2018 in technology&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Echo and Home will start to talk back Both of the major smart home platforms have a long-running problem with “discoverability”: it’s very hard to let users know what their devices can do, particularly if they’re always improving thanks to rapid software updates. Amazon and Google are constantly experimenting with ways to get around this, but so far they have been timid. Amazon sends a weekly email, while Google includes some tips in its app. Expect to see them be bolder, particularly as powerful rivals such as Apple appear on the scene with worse AI but better sound. So don’t be surprised ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Big Mind by Geoff Mulgan — the power of collective intelligence - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/a255e6f0-e4bc-11e7-a685-5634466a6915</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMn8rlGswXQbfDubdiAEN5AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtt6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 15:11:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/a255e6f0-e4bc-11e7-a685-5634466a6915" target="_blank"&gt;Big Mind by Geoff Mulgan — the power of collective intelligence&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago AlphaZero, a programme created by Google’s DeepMind artificial intelligence division, trounced the world’s strongest chess computer, having taught itself to play the game in barely a few hours. This stupefying feat brought the usual dystopian anxieties about looming robot domination. But there is a more upbeat lesson to be taken from the rise of chess-playing machines, namely that even the best tend to lose in hybrid “freestyle” tournaments that pit them against grandmasters and computers working in concert. Freestyle chess is just one example of what Geoff Mulgan calls “col...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item></channel></rss>