<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>International Criminal Court - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNRE4yT0dzU0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-NG&amp;gl=NG&amp;ceid=NG:en</link><language>en-NG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:10:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>The Independent Tribunal Into Forced Organ Harvesting In China Begins Its Work In London - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewelinaochab/2018/12/08/the-independent-tribunal-into-forced-organ-harvesting-in-china-begins-its-work-in-london/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPZmUVGVHoc4fii22DmFXJAqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 11:59:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ewelinaochab/2018/12/08/the-independent-tribunal-into-forced-organ-harvesting-in-china-begins-its-work-in-london/" target="_blank"&gt;The Independent Tribunal Into Forced Organ Harvesting In China Begins Its Work In London&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;On October 16, 2018, at the Third Briefing on Organ Harvesting in China in the U.K. Parliament, the International Coalition to End Transplant Abuse in China announced that an independent people’s tribunal to inquire into organ harvesting from prisoners of conscience in China has been established. On December 8, 2018, the tribunal, under the name of the Independent Tribunal Into Forced Organ Harvesting from Prisoners Of Conscience in China (the China Tribunal) opened its doors for the first time and will run for three days to explore the issue of organ harvesting in China. During the hearing...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Int'l court prosecutor reports progress in Palestinian probe - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/f420f3af67c9455e97cdf74317e2c8d8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELo_DnEpXe-i8Vtlnt6yh5gqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:11:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/f420f3af67c9455e97cdf74317e2c8d8" target="_blank"&gt;Int'l court prosecutor reports progress in Palestinian probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — International Criminal Court prosecutors intend to complete "as early as possible" a long-running preliminary investigation into allegations of crimes in the Palestinian territories, according to a report issued Wednesday. The annual report by ICC prosecutors on progress in nine so-called preliminary examinations underway at the court, said that the Palestinian territories probe "has advanced and significantly progressed" analysis of whether legal conditions for opening a case have been met. Those legal conditions include whether alleged crimes were serious eno...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>A long-awaited turning point in Duterte's bloody drug war - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/long-awaited-turning-point-duterte-bloody-drug-war-181204084154287.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDgHBzQUVL1Y-9NfskWKz-wqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 08:42:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/long-awaited-turning-point-duterte-bloody-drug-war-181204084154287.html" target="_blank"&gt;A long-awaited turning point in Duterte's bloody drug war&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Never has homicide or murder been a function of law enforcement," declared Filipino Judge Rodolfo Azucena Jr in a landmark ruling, which may change the fate of Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte's bloody drug war. On November 29, the Regional Trial Court in Caloocan City found three police officers guilty of murdering Kian Delos Santos, a 17-year-old teenager, in August last year. The cold-blooded murder, caught on CCTV footage, provoked nationwide outrage, which immediately forced the Filipino president to issue, for the first time, a public apology. He even went so far as meeting and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>CAR war crimes suspect Yekatom protests transfer to Hague - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-central-african-republic-idUSKCN1NS14T</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIZytuoZC2I5Yf-8mPeFXKYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 18:40:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-warcrimes-central-african-republic-idUSKCN1NS14T" target="_blank"&gt;CAR war crimes suspect Yekatom protests transfer to Hague&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lawyer for war crimes suspect Alfred Yekatom said at his initial International Criminal Court appearance on Friday his client was tortured after his arrest in Central African Republic before being forcibly transferred to the Hague tribunal. Yekatom, wanted by the ICC for alleged deportation and torture of Muslims in the Central African Republic, was arrested by local officials there on Oct. 29 and handed to ICC custody on Nov. 17. Lawyer Xavier Jean Keita protested the circumstances of the arrest and transfer, but Presiding Judge Antoine Kesia‐Mbe Mindua said the initial appearance was on...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>'Rambo' CAR militia leader charged with war crimes and crimes against humanity - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/africa/yekatom-car-icc-war-crimes-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBQrpXKCwguOD1VPuUdxHnkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 16:18:20 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/23/africa/yekatom-car-icc-war-crimes-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;'Rambo' CAR militia leader charged with war crimes and crimes against humanity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Central African Republic (CAR) militia leader widely known as "Rambo" has been charged with a number of war crimes and crimes against humanity, including murder, torture and the use of child soldiers, at the International Criminal Court in The Hague. Alfred Yekatom is the former commander of a group of 3,000 members of the anti-balaka movement, a group consisting mainly of Christians that opposed a largely Muslim rebel alliance known as Seleka, the ICC said. His crimes allegedly took place "in various locations within the Central African Republic, including the capital Bangui and Lobaye p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>CAR war crimes suspect Yekatom appears at ICC, alleges torture - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/car-war-crimes-suspect-yekatom-appears-icc-alleges-torture-181123111318110.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDoX1R99VHJmgn7SlWYHEZIqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 13:51:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/car-war-crimes-suspect-yekatom-appears-icc-alleges-torture-181123111318110.html" target="_blank"&gt;CAR war crimes suspect Yekatom appears at ICC, alleges torture&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lawyer for war crimes suspect Alfred Yekatom, a former militia leader accused of alleged atrocities against Muslims in the Central African Republic (CAR), has said his client had been tortured and was later forcibly transferred to The Hague. Yekatom, a member of parliament previously nicknamed as "Rambo", was arrested by local officials in the CAR on October 29 and handed to International Criminal Court (ICC) custody on November 17. At his first appearance before ICC judges since his transfer to the Netherlands, Yekatom on Friday confirmed his name, age and that he had read the charges in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Central African Republic Militia Leader Appears at ICC - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/central-african-republic-militia-leader-appears-at-icc/4671258.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECKqViDEjDAlR5BjYavl-REqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:35:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/central-african-republic-militia-leader-appears-at-icc/4671258.html" target="_blank"&gt;Central African Republic Militia Leader Appears at ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Central African Republic militia leader and lawmaker who goes by the nickname Rambo told the International Criminal Court on Friday he was beaten and tortured after his arrest late last month in parliament. Prosecutors at the global court allege that 43-year-old Alfred Yekatom is responsible for crimes including murder, torture and using child soldiers during his country's bitter conflict. He allegedly commanded some 3,000 fighters in a predominantly Christian militia that killed Muslims in attacks between December 2013 and August 2014 in and around the capital, Bangui. At his first appea...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Central African war crimes suspect 'Rambo' handed to global court - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-war-crimes-central-african-republic/central-african-war-crimes-suspect-rambo-handed-to-global-court-idUSKCN1NM0M4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMObrTlKZtczRvMAD86mQ0YqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 18:20:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-war-crimes-central-african-republic/central-african-war-crimes-suspect-rambo-handed-to-global-court-idUSKCN1NM0M4" target="_blank"&gt;Central African war crimes suspect 'Rambo' handed to global court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A war crimes suspect wanted for alleged murder, deportation and torture of Muslims in the Central African Republic has been handed over to the International Criminal Court in the Hague, the tribunal said. CAR officials transferred Alfred Yekatom on Saturday to officials from the global court, which is investigating six years of violence that has destabilised a region at the heart of the continent. Yekatom, a sitting MP once nicknamed "Rambo", had been under arrest in Central African Republic since Oct. 29, when during a parliamentary session he first pointed a gun at a fellow lawmaker and t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Central African Republic MP nicknamed 'Rambo' arrested over alleged war crimes against Muslims - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/war-crimes-alfred-yekatom-rambo-central-african-republic-muslims-hague-a8639816.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHBr814KYHfqC4mShzYN0mgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 16:43:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/africa/war-crimes-alfred-yekatom-rambo-central-african-republic-muslims-hague-a8639816.html" target="_blank"&gt;Central African Republic MP nicknamed 'Rambo' arrested over alleged war crimes against Muslims&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A war crimes suspect wanted for alleged murder, deportation and torture of Muslims in the Central African Republic has been handed over to the International Criminal Court in The Hague, the tribunal said. CAR officials transferred Alfred Yekatom on Saturday to officials from the global court, which is looking into more than six years of violence that has destabilised a fragile region at the heart of the continent. Mr Yekatom, a sitting MP once nicknamed "Rambo", was flown out of the country and arrived in the court's detention centre in The Hague in the early hours of Sunday, officials ther...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Africa's 'Rambo' handed to international court over alleged war crimes - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-18/alfred-yekatom-handed-to-international-criminal-court/10508286</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFU7CBFBzbMCxSqyvvagF90qFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 20:40:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-18/alfred-yekatom-handed-to-international-criminal-court/10508286" target="_blank"&gt;Africa's 'Rambo' handed to international court over alleged war crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A war crimes suspect wanted for alleged atrocities against Muslims in the Central African Republic (CAR) has been detained and handed over to a tribunal in the Netherlands. Key points: - Mr Yekatom is accused of murder, torture and recruiting child soldiers - CAR is marred by violence between Muslim Seleka rebels and Christian Anti-Balaka militias - UN condemns "vicious cycle of repeated attacks against civilians" Christian militias under Alfred Yekatom, a sitting member of parliament once nicknamed "Rambo", were found by a United Nations commission of inquiry to have carried out war crimes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>CAR suspect wanted for war crimes against Muslims handed to ICC - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/car-suspect-wanted-war-crimes-muslims-handed-icc-181117180402662.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEeX2ND_L26ugFK8STB860oqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 19:10:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/car-suspect-wanted-war-crimes-muslims-handed-icc-181117180402662.html" target="_blank"&gt;CAR suspect wanted for war crimes against Muslims handed to ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alfred Yekatom, a war crimes suspect wanted for alleged atrocities against Muslims in the Central African Republic (CAR), has been extradited to The Hague to stand trial at the International Criminal Court (ICC). The announcement by the tribunal on Saturday came days after issuing a warrant against Yekatom - a sitting member of parliament once nicknamed "Rambo" - for his alleged criminal responsibility for war crimes and crimes against humanity The ICC launched an investigation in September 2014 into crimes committed in the resource-rich but poor country since 2012. A former army officer, Y...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>C. African Republic militia leader turned over to tribunal - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/abe734ab2e3f430da0109d1a46b88d2f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJPSWffoJ5lHxyGirexAIgkqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 20:09:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/abe734ab2e3f430da0109d1a46b88d2f" target="_blank"&gt;C. African Republic militia leader turned over to tribunal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — A commander in a Central African Republic militia has been arrested and turned over to the International Criminal Court to face charges that include murder and torture, the court announced Saturday. The court, established to prosecute atrocities such as war crimes, said Central African Republic authorities surrendered Alfred Yekatom on Saturday. Court spokesman Fadi El Abdallah would not say if Yekatom already had been sent to the court's headquarters in The Hague. The Central African Republic has been plagued by interreligious and intercommunal fighting since ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>New CAR Court Seen as Milestone in Fight Against Impunity - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/new-car-court-seen-as-milestone-in-fight-against-impunity/4632482.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDmckp1rfu5kIrlzgfS33MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 15:38:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/new-car-court-seen-as-milestone-in-fight-against-impunity/4632482.html" target="_blank"&gt;New CAR Court Seen as Milestone in Fight Against Impunity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N. Human Rights Office welcomes the establishment of the Special Criminal Court in the Central African Republic, calling it a milestone in the fight against impunity. Over the past six years, war between the mainly Muslim Seleka rebels and Christian anti-Balaka has killed thousands. It has displaced about one quarter of Central African Republic's population of 4.6 million both internally and as refugees. Violence and gross human rights violations are rampant throughout the country. The U.N. human rights office sees the establishment of the Special Criminal Court as a huge step toward ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>ICC prosecutor issues warning on Bedouin village demolition - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/24d3d2513b5241f0a7f704f1748ecedf</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK-Yzf8dpVchn3owHUo3LxUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 12:07:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/24d3d2513b5241f0a7f704f1748ecedf" target="_blank"&gt;ICC prosecutor issues warning on Bedouin village demolition&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The International Criminal Court's chief prosecutor issued a warning Wednesday that if Israel goes ahead and destroys a Palestinian Bedouin village on the West Bank that could constitute a war crime. Israel's Supreme Court recently rejected a final appeal against plans to demolish the village, Khan al-Ahmar. ICC Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said in a written statement that "evacuation by force now appears imminent." She added: "It bears recalling, as a general matter, that extensive destruction of property without military necessity and population transfers in an ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Israel's plan to demolish West Bank village 'could constitute war crime', says ICC - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/israel-west-bank-village-demolish-war-crime-bedouin-icc-idf-a8588466.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKeZcVdP3gNVylC2U1aIv9QqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 15:14:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/israel-west-bank-village-demolish-war-crime-bedouin-icc-idf-a8588466.html" target="_blank"&gt;Israel's plan to demolish West Bank village 'could constitute war crime', says ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court has warned that Israel’s planned demolition of a Palestinian Bedouin village in the West Bank could constitute a war crime as Theresa May said the action would be a “major blow” to the two-state solution peace plan. Fatou Bensouda, the ICC’s chief prosecutor, said Wednesday she was continuing to “keep a close eye” on developments as the destruction of Khan al-Ahmar seemed imminent. A few hours later, during prime ministers questions, Ms May once again urged the Israeli authorities to scrap the idea. Israel's Supreme Court recently rejected a final appeal aga...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>ICC Prosecutors Urge Judges to Continue Ivory Coast Trial - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-prosecutors-urge-judges-to-continue-ivory-coast-trial/4594465.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFGivrekW4kRzz-69eniqzUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 14:16:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-prosecutors-urge-judges-to-continue-ivory-coast-trial/4594465.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC Prosecutors Urge Judges to Continue Ivory Coast Trial&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;International Criminal Court prosecutors urged judges Monday to continue the trial of former Ivory Coast President Laurent Gbagbo and a government ex-minister on trial for their alleged involvement in deadly violence that erupted after the country's disputed 2010 presidential election. Lawyers for Gbagbo and former youth minister Charles Ble Goude filed motions earlier this year arguing that prosecutors presented insufficient evidence for the trial to continue and calling for the immediate acquittal of both men. The calls came at the end of the prosecution case. But the court's deputy prose...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>International Criminal Court urged to investigate Venezuela for alleged crimes against humanity - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/27/americas/venezuela-icc/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENIW00Jv7gVICMA3MOuGWGwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 01:12:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/27/americas/venezuela-icc/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;International Criminal Court urged to investigate Venezuela for alleged crimes against humanity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five South American countries and Canada want Venezuela placed under investigation as a humanitarian crisis continues to roil the country. The leaders of Argentina, Chile, Colombia, Paraguay, Peru and Canada on Wednesday signed a joint statement addressed to the president of the International Criminal Court asking for a probe into possible crimes against humanity in Venezuela. The alleged crimes, dating to 2014, include extrajudicial murder, torture and the arbitrary detention of political opponents and anti-government protesters. The request, made at UN headquarters in New York as the UN G...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Philippines’ Rodrigo Duterte admits to extrajudicial killings - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2f622134-c307-11e8-95b1-d36dfef1b89a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3G8h2CoQyv5oHmGDyi4lsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 11:08:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2f622134-c307-11e8-95b1-d36dfef1b89a" target="_blank"&gt;Philippines’ Rodrigo Duterte admits to extrajudicial killings&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Philippine president Rodrigo Duterte’s office on Friday said he was just “being playful” after he admitted a day earlier to carrying out extrajudicial killings, in remarks that created an international furore. Mr Duterte made the apparent admission on Thursday while speaking about corruption, after saying did not steal so much as a peso from government. “My only sin is extrajudicial killings,” he was quoted as saying in remarks to civil servants at the Malacañang presidential palace in Manila. Since Mr Duterte took office in mid-2016, nearly 5,000 people have been killed by police or others...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Duterte confesses: 'My only sin is the extrajudicial killings' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/28/duterte-confesses-my-only-sin-is-the-extrajudicial-killings</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOEUAoV3Vdjsyum518Spdk0qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 06:09:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/28/duterte-confesses-my-only-sin-is-the-extrajudicial-killings" target="_blank"&gt;Duterte confesses: 'My only sin is the extrajudicial killings'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Rodrigo Duterte has admitted for the first time to authorising extrajudicial killings as part of his war on drugs in the Philippines. Duterte made the admission during a speech at the presidential palace on Thursday, where he directly challenged anyone who criticised how he ran the country. “I told the military, what is my fault? Did I steal even one peso?” said Duterte. “My only sin is the extrajudicial killings.” Duterte has previously addressed the existence of extra-judicial killings but has always denied they were state-sponsored. This direct acknowledgment of his role in the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>UN court asked to probe Venezuela; leader defiant in speech - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/a37c3cdd90714f3eb9650ae789121fe7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJbXQiadXd6fs6TZeARg0B8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 09:49:10 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/a37c3cdd90714f3eb9650ae789121fe7" target="_blank"&gt;UN court asked to probe Venezuela; leader defiant in speech&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Six nations made the unprecedented move Wednesday of asking the U.N.'s International Criminal Court to investigate Venezuela for possible crimes against humanity, even as President Nicolas Maduro made an unexpected trip to the world body's headquarters to deliver a nearly hourlong speech declaring his nation "will never give in." Maduro's speech at the General Assembly gathering of world leaders came hours after Argentina, Chile, Colombia, Peru, Paraguay and Canada formally asked the ICC to investigate Venezuela on a range of possible charges, from murder to torture an...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>'My only sin is the extrajudicial killings' admits Philippines' Duterte - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/28/sin-extrajudicial-killings-admits-philippines-duterte/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJnzMMrdDdf5bE-wlTDjAYYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 09:43:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/28/sin-extrajudicial-killings-admits-philippines-duterte/" target="_blank"&gt;'My only sin is the extrajudicial killings' admits Philippines' Duterte&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rodrigo Duterte, the Philippine president, has admitted for the first time that extrajudicial killings have taken place during his government’s bloody crackdown on drugs, fuelling existing demands from rights groups for an international probe. Mr Duterte, who is known for his provocative, expletive-ridden statements, made his surprise confession on Thursday while speaking to government officials at the presidential palace when he said he had challenged the military to remove him if they were not satisfied with his leadership. “I told the military, what is my fault? Did I steal even one peso...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Activists urge ICC action after Philippine president's 'playful' admission - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-duterte/activists-urge-icc-action-after-philippine-presidents-playful-admission-idUSKCN1M81CI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDTv1XXTrwJdPXWtdX5oGz0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 10:54:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-philippines-duterte/activists-urge-icc-action-after-philippine-presidents-playful-admission-idUSKCN1M81CI" target="_blank"&gt;Activists urge ICC action after Philippine president's 'playful' admission&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activists and opponents of Philippine leader Rodrigo Duterte called for legal action against him on Friday after he appeared to admit responsibility for extrajudicial killings, in remarks his spokesman said were "playful" and misinterpreted. The mercurial president is the subject of two complaints before the International Criminal Court (ICC) that accuse him of crimes against humanity over thousands of deaths during his bloody anti-narcotics campaign. Duterte, known for rambling, at times perplexing speeches, apparently conceded that summary executions had taken place during his war on drug...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Palestine takes US to International Court of Justice over Jerusalem embassy move - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/439901-palestine-lawsuit-court-embassy-us/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK83FDzl2NLx07PjdGgrprgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 02:56:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/439901-palestine-lawsuit-court-embassy-us/" target="_blank"&gt;Palestine takes US to International Court of Justice over Jerusalem embassy move&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Palestinian authority has asked the International Court of Justice to compel the US to shut down its embassy in Jerusalem, because it violates the Vienna convention, which says an embassy must be located in a host country. The Palestinian government submitted its application to launch proceedings against the US on Friday. The 14-page complaint, released by the UN's principal judicial body, alleges that the US, as a party of the 1961 Vienna Convention on Diplomatic Relations, has flouted its obligation by setting up an embassy outside the territory of the host state, Israel. It points ou...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>ICC opens probe into crimes against Rohingya - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/icc-opens-investigation-crimes-rohingya-180919082206813.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELfa1G42F5feC_QIqk1x0SQqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:37:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/icc-opens-investigation-crimes-rohingya-180919082206813.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC opens probe into crimes against Rohingya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court (ICC) has launched a preliminary investigation into Myanmar's crackdown on the Muslim-majority Rohingya that forced hundreds of thousands to flee across the border to Bangladesh. The examination will look at a range of allegations against Myanmar's security forces that could include the killing of Rohingya civilians, sexual violence, forced disappearance, destruction and looting, ICC prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said in a written statement on Tuesday. "A preliminary examination is not an investigation but a process of examining the information available in orde...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>ICC Opens Preliminary Probe Into Rohingya Expulsions - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-opens-preliminary-probe-into-rohingya-expulsions/4577026.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKuYSV4kUkLxdnlo0Gso_fgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwq5wi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 19:24:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-opens-preliminary-probe-into-rohingya-expulsions/4577026.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC Opens Preliminary Probe Into Rohingya Expulsions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court’s chief prosecutor announced Tuesday that she is launching a preliminary investigation into deportations of hundreds of thousands of Rohingya Muslims from Myanmar into Bangladesh. Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said in a written statement and video message that she has begun a probe formally known as a preliminary examination to establish if there is enough evidence to merit a full-blown investigation. Bensouda said she will look at reports of “a number of alleged coercive acts having resulted in the forced displacement of the Rohingya people, including deprivati...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Jeremy Hunt: Burmese generals must face justice over Rohingya - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/20/jeremy-hunt-burmese-generals-must-face-justice-over-rohingya</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECBPy5_75oKEpTZBY94ze6UqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 15:36:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/20/jeremy-hunt-burmese-generals-must-face-justice-over-rohingya" target="_blank"&gt;Jeremy Hunt: Burmese generals must face justice over Rohingya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Burmese generals responsible for atrocities agains Rohingya Muslims must be punished for their crimes, Jeremy Hunt has said after a meeting with Myanmar’s de facto leader, Aung San Suu Kyi. The United Nations should look at all options, including a referral to the international criminal court, the British foreign secretary added. Related: Myanmar Rohingya crisis: ICC begins inquiry into atrocities Hunt was speaking after travelling to Rakhine state, from where hundreds of thousands of Rohingya were driven in clearance operations. The 700,000-plus refugees forced to flee to camps on the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Myanmar Rohingya crisis: ICC begins inquiry into atrocities - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/19/myanmar-rohingya-crisis-icc-begins-investigation-into-atrocities</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGrSl9-HnEoh3OKCLhc_B1sqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 05:13:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/19/myanmar-rohingya-crisis-icc-begins-investigation-into-atrocities" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar Rohingya crisis: ICC begins inquiry into atrocities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chief prosecutor of the international criminal court (ICC) has announced she is launching a preliminary investigation into the deportations of hundreds of thousands of Rohingya Muslims from Myanmar into Bangladesh. Fatou Bensouda said in a written statement and video message on Tuesday that she had begun an inquiry – formally known as a preliminary examination – to establish whether there was enough evidence to merit a full investigation. Bensouda said she would look at reports of “a number of alleged coercive acts having resulted in the forced displacement of the Rohingya people, inclu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>ICC Sentences Congo Politician Bemba for Witness Tampering - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-sentences-ex-congo-vp-to-1-year-for-witness-tampering/4574946.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPbcVtGplRvdXn5oBjIk6F0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 16:07:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-sentences-ex-congo-vp-to-1-year-for-witness-tampering/4574946.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC Sentences Congo Politician Bemba for Witness Tampering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court has sentenced Congolese politician Jean-Pierre Bemba to one year in prison for bribing witnesses, but says he will not be jailed due to time already served. Bemba, a key rival to Congolese President Joseph Kabila, was provisionally freed by the international court in The Hague last month and returned home hoping to make a political comeback. He was greeted by tens of thousands of supporters and announced his candidacy to challenge Kabila in elections. But the Congolese Constitutional Court ruled Bemba was ineligible to run in December presidential polls beca...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>ICC sentences DRC's Jean-Pierre Bemba over witness tampering - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/icc-sentences-drc-jean-pierre-bemba-witness-tampering-180917131831205.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKLMQpNaL0zvbemshFzhOMkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 21:54:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/icc-sentences-drc-jean-pierre-bemba-witness-tampering-180917131831205.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC sentences DRC's Jean-Pierre Bemba over witness tampering&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court (ICC) has sentenced Jean-Pierre Bemba, a former vice president and rebel leader in the Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC), for bribing witnesses during his war crimes trial. In a ruling on Monday, The Hague-based court handed Bemba a 12 month sentence and a 300,000 euros ($350,000) fine for tampering with witnesses in an earlier hearing over possible war crimes and crimes against humanity committed by fighters he sent to suppress a coup in neighbouring Central African Republic between October 2002 and 2003. ICC Judge Bertram Schmitt said the ruling would pro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>The ICC: A common cause between John Bolton and Africa? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/icc-common-john-bolton-africa-180915095755954.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDTq9Vz99flJ7tHVVm7OzeYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwob0I</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 08:08:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/opinion/icc-common-john-bolton-africa-180915095755954.html" target="_blank"&gt;The ICC: A common cause between John Bolton and Africa?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nothing in US National Security Adviser John Bolton's furious attack on the International Criminal Court (ICC) earlier this week can be of much surprise to anyone. Not that he prides himself on being a self-declared foe of the Court - he already demonstrated that when he served in the administration of George W Bush and engineered dozens of bilateral agreements preventing other countries from delivering US personnel to the ICC. Nor that in his first seminal address as US national security adviser, he played fast and loose with the facts - claiming falsely that the Court's next step would be...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>International court says it is undeterred after Bolton threatens U.S. sanctions - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-icc/international-court-says-it-is-undeterred-after-bolton-threatens-u-s-sanctions-idUSKCN1LR0OP?il=0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDzL7tN68wKj7G1qKPH-uFYqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:14:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-icc/international-court-says-it-is-undeterred-after-bolton-threatens-u-s-sanctions-idUSKCN1LR0OP?il=0" target="_blank"&gt;International court says it is undeterred after Bolton threatens U.S. sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court said on Tuesday it would "continue to do its work undeterred" a day after U.S. National Security Adviser John Bolton threatened sanctions if the tribunal investigated U.S. activities in Afghanistan. The Hague-based court said it was an independent and impartial institution with the backing of 123 countries. "The ICC, as a court of law, will continue to do its work undeterred, in accordance with those principles and the overarching idea of the rule of law," it said in a statement. ICC prosecutor Fatou Bensouda said last year there was a “reasonable basis to b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>After Trump threats, France stands by International Criminal Court - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-icc-france/after-trump-threats-france-stands-by-international-criminal-court-idUSKCN1LR1QW</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFtUo-3v1jjgybySGuHiy50qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 14:48:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-icc-france/after-trump-threats-france-stands-by-international-criminal-court-idUSKCN1LR1QW" target="_blank"&gt;After Trump threats, France stands by International Criminal Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France on Tuesday said the International Criminal Court should be able to do its work without hindrance, a day after the United States threatened sanctions if the tribunal investigated U.S. activities in Afghanistan. "France, with its European partners, supports the International Criminal Court, both in its budgetary contribution and in its cooperation with it," Foreign ministry spokeswoman Agnes von der Muhll said in a statement. "The court must be able to act and exercise its prerogatives without hindrance, independently and impartially, within the legal framework defined by the Rome Stat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Can the International Criminal Court justice experiment survive John Bolton? - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-11/will-the-icc-survive-john-bolton/10234372</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMAHf2GDpP1JAkWUmw2O7YwqFwgEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDD7kIkG</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 11:08:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-11/will-the-icc-survive-john-bolton/10234372" target="_blank"&gt;Can the International Criminal Court justice experiment survive John Bolton?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court says it will "continue to do its work undeterred" after a swingeing attack on it by US national security adviser John Bolton. Key points: - John Bolton has threatened ICC over possible investigation of US personnel in Afghanistan - Court adviser Professor McCormack says court might not survive a determined US attack - McCormack says best argument for the ICC is 45 years of "dictators and despots" post-WWII But Bolton's threats against the court have a top Australian advisor to the ICC reluctantly questioning whether the bold experiment in justice for war cri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>EU backs ICC after US questions court's legitimacy - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/abf1c69e00c440be918829bf4c3d2522</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP9Y5-5Af0DdfuB5ZVdUxYcqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 09:22:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/abf1c69e00c440be918829bf4c3d2522" target="_blank"&gt;EU backs ICC after US questions court's legitimacy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — The European Union's top diplomat says the bloc remains a staunch supporter of the International Criminal Court despite U.S. condemnation of the tribunal. EU foreign policy chief Federica Mogherini said Thursday that "we will continue to fully and strongly support the ICC and its work." The Hague-based court was created in 2002 to prosecute war crimes, crimes against humanity and genocide in areas where perpetrators might not otherwise face justice. Mogherini said the ICC "has strengthened universal justice beyond power politics and beyond geopolitical interests," and added ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Imprisonment, torture and rape: Why Myanmar must be referred to the ICC - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/18/opinions/myanmar-rohingya-action-opinion-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGkHURO02YZWUBi6QW7BjF4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:26:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/18/opinions/myanmar-rohingya-action-opinion-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Imprisonment, torture and rape: Why Myanmar must be referred to the ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shirin Ebadi is the winner of the 2003 Nobel Peace Prize. Tawakkol Karman won the Nobel Peace Prize in 2011. The opinions in this commentary are those of the authors. Today, the investigation led by the UN Independent International Fact-Finding Mission on Myanmar presented its findings to the Human Rights Council. The mission's exhaustive report defines human rights violations and abuses committed in Kachin, Rakhine and Shan states as "shocking for their horrifying nature and ubiquity" and calls for the investigation and prosecution of senior military officials for genocide, war crimes, and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>US Relationship With International Court Crashes Under Trump - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-relationship-with-international-court-crashes-under-trump/4565853.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOL5-wlUb_aWf-HMSTjmv48qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQwupwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 22:15:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-relationship-with-international-court-crashes-under-trump/4565853.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Relationship With International Court Crashes Under Trump&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;America's long-running reluctant relationship with the International Criminal Court came to a crashing halt on Monday as decades of U.S. suspicions about the tribunal and its global jurisdiction spilled into open hostility, amid threats of sanctions if it investigates U.S. troops in Afghanistan. National security adviser John Bolton denounced the legitimacy of The Hague-based court, which was created in 2002 to prosecute war crimes and crimes of humanity and genocide in areas where perpetrators might not otherwise face justice. It has 123 state parties that recognize its jurisdiction. Bolto...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>ICC 'Undeterred' by US Sanctions Threats - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-says-undeterred-by-united-states-sanctions-threats/4566751.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK9O27QSe841LjDy5cO-Fs8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 14:19:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/icc-says-undeterred-by-united-states-sanctions-threats/4566751.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC 'Undeterred' by US Sanctions Threats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court says it will continue to conduct its business as usual one day after the United States threatened to impose sanctions on ICC officials if the court investigated U.S. activities in Afghanistan A statement Tuesday from The Hague based court said, "The ICC, as a court of law, will continue to do its work undeterred, in accordance with those principles and the overarching idea of the rule of law." U.S. National Security Advisor John Bolton said Monday the U.S. would refuse to cooperate "in any way" with the tribunal if it carries out a prospective investigation ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Full text of John Bolton's speech to the Federalist Society - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/full-text-john-bolton-speech-federalist-society-180910172828633.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEClRaLIrsYX-MSv_NoctA78qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:44:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/full-text-john-bolton-speech-federalist-society-180910172828633.html" target="_blank"&gt;Full text of John Bolton's speech to the Federalist Society&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below is John Bolton's speech on Monday to the Federalist Society in Washington, DC: I am here to make a major announcement on US policy toward the International Criminal Court, or ICC. After years of effort by self-styled "global governance" advocates, the ICC, a supranational tribunal that could supersede national sovereignties and directly prosecute individuals for alleged war crimes, was agreed to in 1998. For ICC proponents, this supranational, independent institution has always been critical to their efforts to overcome the perceived failures of nation-states, even those with strong c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Trump administration takes aim at International Criminal Court, PLO - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-icc/trump-administration-to-take-tough-stance-against-international-criminal-court-idUSKCN1LQ076</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN1dcLMwC90mB10zDW_-J2YqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 21:14:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-icc/trump-administration-to-take-tough-stance-against-international-criminal-court-idUSKCN1LQ076" target="_blank"&gt;Trump administration takes aim at International Criminal Court, PLO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration on Monday threatened tough action against the International Criminal Court should it try to prosecute Americans for alleged war crimes in Afghanistan and said the PLO's office in Washington would be closed for seeking to punish Israel through the court. "The United States will use any means necessary to protect our citizens and those of our allies from unjust prosecution by this illegitimate court," national security adviser John Bolton told the Federalist Society, a conservative group, in his first major address since joining President Donald Trump's White House in...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>International court says it's 'undeterred' by US threats - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/ffc1589de40b4b56805dd4483f26a43c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPXx93HEBxY_YL-ewiOE2FkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:49:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/ffc1589de40b4b56805dd4483f26a43c" target="_blank"&gt;International court says it's 'undeterred' by US threats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ISLAMABAD (AP) — Afghan rights workers warned Tuesday that a blistering U.S. attack on the International Criminal Court investigating war crimes allegations will strengthen a climate of impunity in Afghanistan, prolong the war and embolden those committing acts of violence. In a speech Monday, U.S. National Security Adviser John Bolton said Washington would not cooperate with The Hague-based court and threatened it with sanctions, saying it put U.S. sovereignty and national security at risk. The CIA and U.S. forces have been accused of committing war crimes in Afghanistan. "It's very unfort...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>International Criminal Court unfazed by US threats of sanctions over Afghan war crimes probe - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/438175-icc-afghanistan-trump-bolton/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECo3fbf6cxP9XsVmpN9raU8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 13:30:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/438175-icc-afghanistan-trump-bolton/" target="_blank"&gt;International Criminal Court unfazed by US threats of sanctions over Afghan war crimes probe&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court (ICC) has said it will “continue to do its work undeterred,” after US National Security Advisor John Bolton threatened sanctions if the tribunal investigates alleged US war crimes in Afghanistan. The Hague-based court investigates genocide, crimes against humanity, and war crimes and is backed by 123 countries - but not by China and the US. “The ICC, as a court of law, will continue to do its work undeterred, in accordance with those principles and the overarching idea of the rule of law,” it said in a statement on Tuesday. The tribunal’s remarks came in res...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>John Bolton to threaten sanctions in virulent attack on ICC - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/sep/10/john-bolton-castigate-icc-washington-speech</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBN9qbG4CTHe_Vh7GAkgI78qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 08:51:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/sep/10/john-bolton-castigate-icc-washington-speech" target="_blank"&gt;John Bolton to threaten sanctions in virulent attack on ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Bolton, the hawkish US national security adviser, will threaten the international criminal court (ICC) with sanctions when he makes an excoriating attack on the institution in a speech in Washington. According to drafts of his speech, Bolton will push for sanctions over an ICC investigation into alleged American war crimes in Afghanistan. He is also expected to announce on Monday the closure of the Palestine Liberation Organization (PLO) office in Washington because of its calls for an ICC inquiry into Israel. Sign up to receive the top US stories every morning “The United States will ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Bolton Threatens International Criminal Court With Sanctions if They Continue Probe of Alleged U.S. War Crimes - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bolton-threatens-international-criminal-court-with-sanctions-if-they-continue-probe-of-alleged-us-war-crimes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAkersPrVAbc8wyw5iekomgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAow7s8BMNBIMPGMAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 16:50:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/bolton-threatens-international-criminal-court-with-sanctions-if-they-continue-probe-of-alleged-us-war-crimes" target="_blank"&gt;Bolton Threatens International Criminal Court With Sanctions if They Continue Probe of Alleged U.S. War Crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Daily Beast&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Denis Balibouse/Reuters In his first major speech since joining the White House, National Security Advisor John Bolton on Monday threatened sanctions against judges in the International Criminal Court if they continue attempting to probe alleged American war crimes in Afghanistan. Over the past decade, the prosecutor of the International Criminal Court has conducted a preliminary examination of allegations of war crimes and crimes against humanity in Afghanistan. But in November 2017, the the prosecutor moved a step further and requested authorization to investigate the alleged crimes carri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.thedailybeast.com">The Daily Beast</source></item><item><title>John Bolton's ICC attack is just a brick in Trump's Fortress America policy - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/12/john-bolton-icc-attack-trump-fortress-america-policy</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK8-0ReLGnBDGB2ouTZmNPcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 13:00:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/sep/12/john-bolton-icc-attack-trump-fortress-america-policy" target="_blank"&gt;John Bolton's ICC attack is just a brick in Trump's Fortress America policy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US national security adviser John Bolton’s speech attacking the International Criminal Court (ICC) was another brick in the wall of the Fortress America foreign policy that the Trump administration is trying to build. Related: Why John Bolton is much more like Trump than some think | Cas Mudde Politicians and pundits scratched their heads as Bolton gave his first major speech in his current job not on the challenge of a rising China, aggression by Russia, terrorism or the humanitarian catastrophe in Syria, but instead on an international legal body to which the US is not even a party. The s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>US: No Cooperation with ICC Probe of Alleged Afghan War Crimes - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-afghan-investigation/4564590.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDAKnphnbU8sS4EEFoBEClwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 05:48:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-afghan-investigation/4564590.html" target="_blank"&gt;US: No Cooperation with ICC Probe of Alleged Afghan War Crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States said Monday it would refuse to cooperate "in any way" with the International Criminal Court in The Hague if it carries out a prospective investigation into allegations of war crimes by U.S. military and intelligence personnel in Afghanistan. National Security Adviser John Bolton told the conservative Federalist Society in Washington that the court should not have jurisdiction over Americans or people from other nations that never ratified the treaty that created the court in 2002. At the same time, Bolton announced that the U.S. State Department is shutting down a Palestin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Trump attack on ICC is the unacceptable face of US exceptionalism - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/sep/10/trump-attack-on-icc-is-the-unacceptable-face-of-us-exceptionalism</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEGZX9WBoRaHgo3RiXqfbFwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 15:10:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/sep/10/trump-attack-on-icc-is-the-unacceptable-face-of-us-exceptionalism" target="_blank"&gt;Trump attack on ICC is the unacceptable face of US exceptionalism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The title of John Bolton’s speech in Washington – “Protecting American constitutionalism and sovereignty from international threats” – sounded innocuous enough, if a little pompous. But its text represents the Trump administration’s most devastating and unrestrained attack to date on the global rules-based order and its legal flagship, the international criminal court. Put bluntly, it is an all-out bid by Donald Trump to end the ICC, the world’s foremost criminal tribunal, and with it, the very concept of international justice. Bolton is the man wielding the knife. And there is a strong pos...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Washington’s ICC hypocrisy 'without limits,’ US doesn’t care about human rights – analysts to RT - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/438204-us-icc-hypocrisy-afghanistan/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPBiy-EPuIZZkbXezzsgz00qFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/438204-us-icc-hypocrisy-afghanistan/" target="_blank"&gt;Washington’s ICC hypocrisy 'without limits,’ US doesn’t care about human rights – analysts to RT&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Washington’s threats against the International Criminal Court (ICC) are evidence of American hypocrisy, as the US is “continually calling for the heads of others” and doesn’t actually care about human rights, analysts told RT. As US National Security Advisor John Bolton said the ICC is “dead to us” in response to a probe into US war crimes in Afghanistan, international criminal lawyer Christopher Black told RT that American hypocrisy is clearly “without limits.” He believes the US is “continually calling for the heads of others, and their entire war against Syria is based on the pretext of ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Trump administration orders closure of Palestinian office - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/a2190443fba54a548a04a0ebbca9c2e8</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIrCYZ6VuhIJNq_lRIwBfD8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 18:09:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/a2190443fba54a548a04a0ebbca9c2e8" target="_blank"&gt;Trump administration orders closure of Palestinian office&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration ordered the closure of the Palestinian diplomatic mission in Washington on Monday and threatened sanctions against the International Criminal Court if it pursues investigations against the U.S., Israel, or other allies. The moves are likely to harden Palestinian resistance to the U.S. role as a peace broker. The administration cited the refusal of Palestinian leaders to enter into peace talks with Israel as the reason for closing the Palestinian Liberation Organization office, although the U.S. has yet to present its plan to resolve the Israel-Pale...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>‘Unjust court’: Bolton vows to use ‘any means’ to protect US ally Israel from ICC - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/438099-icc-bolton-protect-us-allies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM4hBVLqHBuDq0t6EGpUHuwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 16:52:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/438099-icc-bolton-protect-us-allies/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Unjust court’: Bolton vows to use ‘any means’ to protect US ally Israel from ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US has announced its decision not to cooperate with the International Criminal Court, vowing to protect itself and its “friend and ally” Israel from the judicial body. It also threatened sanctions against the “unjust” court. Announcing the move, US National Security Advisor John Bolton on Monday warned the ICC against continuing its investigation into alleged war crimes committed by Americans in Afghanistan. If the international court continues to pursue the probe, Washington will ban ICC judges from entering the country, prosecute them and sanction their funds, the official said in a s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>John Bolton threatens ICC with sanctions: 'We will not cooperate' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/threatens-icc-judges-sanctions-180910113100340.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHdeTit_yc8uOkGkCx2BEoYqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 11:06:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/threatens-icc-judges-sanctions-180910113100340.html" target="_blank"&gt;John Bolton threatens ICC with sanctions: 'We will not cooperate'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States launched a blistering verbal attack on the International Criminal Court (ICC) and threatened sanctions against its judges if they proceed with a probe into alleged war crimes by Americans in Afghanistan. John Bolton, President Donald Trump's national security adviser, made the announcement in a speech to the Federalist Society, a conservative group, in Washington, DC, on Monday. "Today, on the eve of September 11th, I want to deliver a clear and unambiguous message on behalf of the president. The United States will use any means necessary to protect our citizens and those ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>‘ICC is dead to us’: US to use ‘any means’ to shield citizens &amp; allies from war-crime probes - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/usa/438023-icc-dead-war-crimes-bolton/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKgtrLQnndrkifNNpG9QRYMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 04:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/usa/438023-icc-dead-war-crimes-bolton/" target="_blank"&gt;‘ICC is dead to us’: US to use ‘any means’ to shield citizens &amp; allies from war-crime probes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US will fight back using any means necessary if the International Criminal Court ever dares to probe an American or Israeli, and will punish those who cooperates with war-crime investigations, John Bolton is set to announce. “The United States will use any means necessary to protect our citizens and those of our allies from unjust prosecution by this illegitimate court,” Donald Trump’s national security adviser, John Bolton, is expected to say, according to a draft speech seen by Reuters. “We will not cooperate with the ICC. We will provide no assistance to the ICC. We will not join the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>Bolton: International Criminal Court dead to us - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/09/10/bolton-us-protect-citizens-international-criminal-court-sot-vpx.cnn</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBuKtdrePR4VWBuG3hR5yVoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMI29pgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 20:05:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/world/2018/09/10/bolton-us-protect-citizens-international-criminal-court-sot-vpx.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;Bolton: International Criminal Court dead to us&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Security Adviser John Bolton announced that the US will use "any means necessary" to protect its citizens and allies from unjust prosecution by the International Criminal Court, during his speech to the Federalist Society. ©2018 Cable News Network, Inc. A Time Warner Company. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Bolton slams International Criminal Court - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/09/10/bolton-slams-international-criminal-cour?videoId=463031391</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOOPeE3APEwk-BQOv1SaCzcqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMI3s7wU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:34:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/video/2018/09/10/bolton-slams-international-criminal-cour?videoId=463031391" target="_blank"&gt;Bolton slams International Criminal Court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Trump's national security adviser John Bolton adopted an aggressive posture against the International Criminal Court on Monday, threatening sanctions against ICC judges if they proceed with an investigation into alleged war crimes committed by Americans in Afghanistan. Rough Cut (no reporter narration).&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Myanmar says International Criminal Court has no jurisdiction in Rohingya crisis - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-icc/myanmar-says-international-criminal-court-has-no-jurisdiction-in-rohingya-crisis-idUSKCN1LN22X</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECPo9dc8DK5B-S8sd8P5VS4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 18:51:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-icc/myanmar-says-international-criminal-court-has-no-jurisdiction-in-rohingya-crisis-idUSKCN1LN22X" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar says International Criminal Court has no jurisdiction in Rohingya crisis&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Myanmar's government said on Friday it "resolutely rejects" a ruling from the International Criminal Court (ICC) that said the body has jurisdiction over alleged deportations of Rohingya Muslims to Bangladesh as a possible crime against humanity. A statement from the office of Myanmar's President Win Myint dismissed Thursday's ICC ruling as "the result of faulty procedure and is of dubious legal merit". "Furthermore, allegations consisting of charged narratives of harrowing personal tragedies which have nothing to do with the legal arguments in question were permitted, thereby putting emoti...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trump official John Bolton declares International Criminal Court 'dangerous' and is 'dead to' America - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/icc-us-john-bolton-international-criminal-court-national-security-advisor-donald-trump-a8531701.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJgSrHB7STjln37_oPCesg4qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/icc-us-john-bolton-international-criminal-court-national-security-advisor-donald-trump-a8531701.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trump official John Bolton declares International Criminal Court 'dangerous' and is 'dead to' America&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Security Advisor to Donald Trump, John Bolton, has said the International Criminal Court (ICC) is "dead to us" in his latest speech. He labelled the court as "illegitimate" and "for all intents and purposes, the ICC is already dead to us." Mr Bolton was speaking at a meeting of the Federalist Society, a conservative group based in Washington DC, said the ICC “ineffective, unaccountable, and indeed outright dangerous". The court, established in 2002 in The Hague, Netherlands, has the power to prosecute individuals for war crimes, genocide, and crimes against humanity. The US never r...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>International Criminal Court rules it can investigate alleged crimes against the Rohingya in Burma - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/07/international-criminal-court-rules-can-investigate-alleged-crimes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDbRBm3c13qNLG3asI0P3pIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/07/international-criminal-court-rules-can-investigate-alleged-crimes/" target="_blank"&gt;International Criminal Court rules it can investigate alleged crimes against the Rohingya in Burma&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court in the Hague has ruled that it can investigate Burma for the alleged deportation of the Rohingya Muslim minority to Bangladesh as a possible crime against humanity. The unprecedented ruling paves the way for Fatou Bensouda, the ICC’s chief prosecutor, to further examine whether there is sufficient evidence to file charges in the case, exposing the country’s leadership to future sanction. The decision comes a week after an independent probe by United Nations investigators called for the investigation and prosecution of Burma’s top military generals, including...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>The Latest: Palestinians say they'll stick to principles - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/cb39528e1f23453f8c5561f2fab750d7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ-wchQlAb5EjmOREg0aFacqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 06:40:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/cb39528e1f23453f8c5561f2fab750d7" target="_blank"&gt;The Latest: Palestinians say they'll stick to principles&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the Trump administration and the Palestinians (all times local): 4:20 p.m. The Palestinian Authority says it will not abandon its principles following the U.S. decision to close the Palestinian Liberation Organization's office in Washington. The spokesman for Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas, Nabil Abu Rdeneh, says the Palestinian Authority will maintain its "commitment to the resolutions of international legitimacy," according to a written statement released Monday. Rdeneh says key issues, including the status of Palestinian refugees, "are more important ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>‘Collective punishment against us’: US shuts down Palestine Liberation Organization’s office in DC - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/438054-us-mission-closed-palestine/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGAKvxHtjGH-fvnBkSa0ySIqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww7oMo</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 11:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/438054-us-mission-closed-palestine/" target="_blank"&gt;‘Collective punishment against us’: US shuts down Palestine Liberation Organization’s office in DC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US State Department has announced it is shutting down the Palestine Liberation Organization (PLO) office in Washington, DC, a move which a top PLO official says is aimed at “collectively punishing the Palestinian people.” The department said that the decision to close the office is consistent with US concerns about Palestinian attempts to launch a probe into Israeli actions at the International Criminal Court (ICC). It comes after the Palestinian Foreign Ministry asked the ICC in May to open an investigation into alleged Israeli violations against Palestinians, calling Tel Aviv's action...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>International Criminal Court says it has jurisdiction over alleged crimes against Rohingya - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-icc/international-criminal-court-says-it-has-jurisdiction-over-alleged-deportations-of-rohingya-idUSKCN1LM23H</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDKwPq8WG2fJLzDJja7dHoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 16:48:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-icc/international-criminal-court-says-it-has-jurisdiction-over-alleged-deportations-of-rohingya-idUSKCN1LM23H" target="_blank"&gt;International Criminal Court says it has jurisdiction over alleged crimes against Rohingya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court (ICC) ruled on Thursday that it has jurisdiction over alleged deportations of Rohingya people from Myanmar to Bangladesh as a possible crime against humanity. The decision at the Hague-based court paves the way for prosecutor Fatou Bensouda to further examine whether there is sufficient evidence to file charges in the case, although she has not done so yet. Bensouda's representatives were not immediately available for comment. Although Myanmar is not a member of the Hague-based court, Bangladesh is, and the cross-border nature of deportation was sufficient f...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Britain, France and US 'plan tougher response to Syrian regime's use of chemical weapons' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/10/trump-administration-threatens-sanctions-against-international/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL4U1AbbLzI9KAazoGUl7dgqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 20:34:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/10/trump-administration-threatens-sanctions-against-international/" target="_blank"&gt;Britain, France and US 'plan tougher response to Syrian regime's use of chemical weapons'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump’s National Security Adviser said on Monday the United States, Britain and France had agreed that any further use of chemical weapons by Syria would prompt a “much stronger response” compared to previous air strikes. In recent days American officials have said they believe government forces are preparing to deploy chemical weapons ahead of an assault on the rebel-held enclave of Idlib. "We've tried to convey the message in recent days that if there's a third use of chemical weapons, the response will be much stronger,” said John Bolton, in his first speech since joinin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Myanmar rejects ICC ruling to probe Rohingya deportations - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/myanmar-rejects-icc-ruling-probe-rohingya-deportations-180907164410907.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENiKEJl2UsFInpdJqAaEJIgqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 18:18:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/myanmar-rejects-icc-ruling-probe-rohingya-deportations-180907164410907.html" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar rejects ICC ruling to probe Rohingya deportations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Myanmar has "resolutely" rejected a ruling from the International Criminal Court (ICC) which said that the body had jurisdiction over alleged deportations of Rohingya Muslims to Bangladesh as a possible crime against humanity. Through an unprecedented ruling on Thursday, the ICC had empowered itself to probe alleged crimes against the Rohingya, even though Myanmar is not a member of it. In response, the office of Myanmar's President Win Myint on Friday dismissed the ICC ruling, calling it "the result of faulty procedure and of dubious legal merit" and saying the country was "under no obliga...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>'Cruel and vicious': Palestinian officials condemn Trump's closure of DC office - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/10/palestinian-officials-washington-diplomatic-mission</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPSGWVFKfA9ut5R6ymUJe6oqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 16:57:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/10/palestinian-officials-washington-diplomatic-mission" target="_blank"&gt;'Cruel and vicious': Palestinian officials condemn Trump's closure of DC office&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Palestinian leaders have condemned a decision by Donald Trump to shutter their diplomatic mission to Washington as part of a “cruel and spiteful” campaign they say represents collective punishment against Palestinians. The move follows a year of US action that includes cutting hundreds of millions of dollars in humanitarian aid to Palestinians and recognising Jerusalem, a city that is territorially contested, as Israel’s capital. Related: John Bolton to threaten sanctions in virulent attack on ICC Senior Palestinian politician Hanan Ashrawi said the US government was “extremely cruel and sp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>ICC says it can prosecute Myanmar for alleged Rohingya crimes - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/06/icc-says-it-can-prosecute-myanmar-for-alleged-rohingya-crimes</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMBT1XgCZ4vj_XNdM2WdDIQqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 17:27:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/06/icc-says-it-can-prosecute-myanmar-for-alleged-rohingya-crimes" target="_blank"&gt;ICC says it can prosecute Myanmar for alleged Rohingya crimes&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The international criminal court has ruled it can prosecute Myanmar for alleged crimes against humanity against the Rohingya people, an unprecedented decision that could expose the country’s politicians and military leaders to charges. Related: Myanmar's military accused of genocide in damning UN report A pre-trial chamber at the court in The Hague said on Thursday that even though Myanmar was not a signatory to the court, its leaders could still be investigated for the crime of deportation, the forcible transfer of a population. ICC prosecutors had mounted a novel argument that even though...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>ICC rules it can investigate crimes against Rohingya - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/international-criminal-court-rohingya-deportation-myanmar-a8527626.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJPwYUuPLSDJcDe5CT1hmrEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 16:25:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/international-criminal-court-rohingya-deportation-myanmar-a8527626.html" target="_blank"&gt;ICC rules it can investigate crimes against Rohingya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The International Criminal Court (ICC) ruled on Thursday that it has jurisdiction over alleged deportations of Rohingya people from Myanmar to Bangladesh as a possible crime against humanity. The decision at the Hague-based court paves the way for prosecutor Fatou Bensouda to further examine whether there is sufficient evidence to file charges in the case, although she has not done so yet. Ms Bensouda’s representatives were not immediately available for comment. - Read more Myanmar rejects UN investigators’ report on Rohingya genocide Although Myanmar is not a member of the Hague-based cour...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>U.N.'s Bachelet presses for new body on crimes against Myanmar Rohingya - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-un/uns-bachelet-presses-for-new-body-on-crimes-against-myanmar-rohingya-idUSKCN1LQ0OB</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFqC0uu-WNG1kLM6UPl39soqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 08:24:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-rohingya-un/uns-bachelet-presses-for-new-body-on-crimes-against-myanmar-rohingya-idUSKCN1LQ0OB" target="_blank"&gt;U.N.'s Bachelet presses for new body on crimes against Myanmar Rohingya&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;United Nations human rights chief Michelle Bachelet called on Monday for a new quasi-judicial body to collect evidence with a view to future prosecution of crimes against Muslim Rohingya in Myanmar including murder and torture. An independent U.N. team of investigators said in a report last month that there was evidence indicating "genocidal intent" by the military against Rohingya and that crimes against humanity and war crimes appear to have been committed. The investigators named six generals, including the commander-in-chief, whom they said should face justice. A year ago, government tr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Judges rule ICC has jurisdiction over Rohingya deportations - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/e7c8f825dc014accb0bcdcc45bc3eb4d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDxuXABFx5UqaFpvKVJbTC8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 18:50:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/e7c8f825dc014accb0bcdcc45bc3eb4d" target="_blank"&gt;Judges rule ICC has jurisdiction over Rohingya deportations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — Judges at the International Criminal Court ruled Thursday that the court has jurisdiction to investigate widespread allegations that Myanmar forces have driven hundreds of thousands of Rohingya Muslims from their homes. The decision opens up the possibility of crimes against Rohingya people being prosecuted at the Hague-based court, even though Myanmar is not a member of the court. The court said in a statement that Prosecutor Fatou Bensouda must take the jurisdiction ruling into account "as she continues with her preliminary examination concerning the crimes a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Banned Bemba Denounces DRC Vote as 'Parody' - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/banned-bemba-denounces-drc-vote-as-parody/4557174.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMHERc4ApwNwMYmWX2CkYi0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 15:38:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/banned-bemba-denounces-drc-vote-as-parody/4557174.html" target="_blank"&gt;Banned Bemba Denounces DRC Vote as 'Parody'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Democratic Republic of Congo warlord Jean-Pierre Bemba on Tuesday denounced a long-delayed December presidential election as a "parody" after he was banned from contesting and accused President Joseph Kabila of trying to hand pick a successor by eliminating serious rivals. Bemba was one of six presidential hopefuls who was excluded by the election commission from the December 23 vote. He appealed the decision but the Constitutional Court late Monday upheld the ban due to his conviction by the International Criminal Court (ICC) for bribing witnesses at his war crimes trial. "The fact ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>I'm a revolutionary, not a criminal, Congo's 'Terminator' tells ICC - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/30/bosco-ntaganda-congolese-warlord-icc-the-hague-trial</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDD-ZmlX9PoAz2JUOpzgMQMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 15:30:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/30/bosco-ntaganda-congolese-warlord-icc-the-hague-trial" target="_blank"&gt;I'm a revolutionary, not a criminal, Congo's 'Terminator' tells ICC&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A notorious Congolese warlord known as the “Terminator” for his alleged brutality has protested his innocence at the close of his trial at the international criminal court, telling judges: “I am a revolutionary, not a criminal.” Bosco Ntaganda is charged with 13 counts of war crimes and six of crimes against humanity, all allegedly committed in 2002 and 2003 in Ituri in the east of the Democratic Republic of the Congo. He told the court he was “at peace with myself … I hope that you now realise that the ‘Terminator’ described by the prosecutor is not me.” Lawyers have presented their closin...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>DRC rebel tells ICC he's a revolutionary, not the 'terminator' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/08/drc-rebel-tells-icc-revolutionary-terminator-180830152014803.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEEDKhYWOgiRJEDjpVLdaNkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 18:51:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/08/drc-rebel-tells-icc-revolutionary-terminator-180830152014803.html" target="_blank"&gt;DRC rebel tells ICC he's a revolutionary, not the 'terminator'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former rebel leader known as "The Terminator" has denied involvement in atrocities in the Democratic Republic of Congo(DRC) at the conclusion of his three-year trial at the International Criminal Court (ICC). "The Terminator described by the prosecutor is not me," Bosco Ntaganda, who faces charges ranging from murder and rape to conscripting child soldiers and sexual slavery, told judges in his closing statement on Thursday. "I am a revolutionary, but I am not a criminal," he said, speaking in his native Kinyarwanda tongue. "I am at peace with myself. These allegations are nothing more th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item></channel></rss>