<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Sahel - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIQgKIhtDQkFTRGdvSUwyMHZNR3cxWDJ3U0FtVnVLQUFQAQ?hl=en-NG&amp;gl=NG&amp;ceid=NG:en</link><language>en-NG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:01:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>UN says 33m people are food insecure in Sahel - Daily Trust</title><link>https://www.dailytrust.com.ng/un-says-33m-people-are-food-insecure-in-sahel.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiUGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5dHJ1c3QuY29tLm5nL3VuLXNheXMtMzNtLXBlb3BsZS1hcmUtZm9vZC1pbnNlY3VyZS1pbi1zYWhlbC5odG1s0gEA</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.dailytrust.com.ng/un-says-33m-people-are-food-insecure-in-sahel.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN says 33m people are food insecure in Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Daily Trust&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;No fewer than 33 million people in the Sahel are food insecure, the UN Economic and Social Council (ECOSOC) and the UN Peacebuilding Commission have ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.dailytrust.com.ng">Daily Trust</source><media:content url="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/proxy/dRktlaj1Kl5jUern8twWnLOmovTs6s2fJUMQ_gh6V7xHzkUu1z4DMgUHQTsQJx2xfowYfSbAhqlEcYokuHjUlabWUIc1224Rn10ciyq6L8aQli-_dPjPjQZINHM__rgjADyzG0LSbWrK1R3pqOLm6IaSH7XO7ND-76l93pWV3m1Uwl5D5ZI=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>🇫🇷EU, France announce almost $3bn aid for African Sahel l Al Jazeera English - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-czNrRjH_f4</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOK6aMl6ebi5grCJvsnJIXwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwkOgB</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:31:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-czNrRjH_f4" target="_blank"&gt;🇫🇷EU, France announce almost $3bn aid for African Sahel l Al Jazeera English&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Union and France have pledged almost $3bn for the Sahel region in West and Central Africa. The heads of state of the G5 Sahel (G5S) nations are meeting in the Mauritanian capital, Nouakchott, to raise funds. The five nations represent a huge area in the southern Sahara desert that has been blighted by years of conflict and lack of infrastructure. Al Jazeera's Nicolas Haque reports from Nouakchott. - Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe - Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish - Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera - Check our websi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>EU, France announce $1.5bn aid for African Sahel - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/eu-france-announce-15bn-aid-african-sahel-181206120109665.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENDKNOesBd_1njjdQYHHrz0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 14:39:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/12/eu-france-announce-15bn-aid-african-sahel-181206120109665.html" target="_blank"&gt;EU, France announce $1.5bn aid for African Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Union and France have announced 1.3bn euros ($1.5bn) of development funding aimed at combatting armed groups in African Sahel countries, which are struggling with armed groups and lawlessness. The EU has pledged 800m euros to the effort, Neven Mimica, the bloc's international cooperation and development commissioner, told a conference in Mauritania on Thursday. France for its part "will invest 500m euros to benefit the priorities" of the G5 Sahel, added French Foreign Minister Jean-Yves Le Drian. 171102071159524 The alliance, made up of Niger, Burkina Faso, Chad, Mali and Mauri...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>🌍Second G5 Sahel donors Conference under way in Mauritania | Al Jazeera English - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vuK07X7ognQ</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECmnf9VgXS7CPVdJMuAwbGwqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgwkOgB</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:42:40 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vuK07X7ognQ" target="_blank"&gt;🌍Second G5 Sahel donors Conference under way in Mauritania | Al Jazeera English&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heads of state from the 5 Sahel countries in Weste Africa are meeting international donors in Mauritania. It's an attempt to raise billions of dollars for a region that has seen years of violence. Al Jazeera's Nicolas Haque reports from the capital Nouakchott. - Subscribe to our channel: http://aje.io/AJSubscribe - Follow us on Twitter: https://twitter.com/AJEnglish - Find us on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/aljazeera - Check our website: https://www.aljazeera.com/ #Mauritania #G5Sahel #G5SahelConference&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.youtube.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Want To Reduce Migration? Spend Money On Climate Change, Not Border Security - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/freylindsay/2018/11/30/want-to-reduce-migration-spend-money-on-climate-change-not-border-security/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEOJ-XejuhZ6-UpSITKWcTcqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMMGBAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:51:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/freylindsay/2018/11/30/want-to-reduce-migration-spend-money-on-climate-change-not-border-security/" target="_blank"&gt;Want To Reduce Migration? Spend Money On Climate Change, Not Border Security&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Illegal migrants from Niger stand next to their tents on May 14, 2014 near the fruit market in the Algerian town of Boufarik. The Sahel-Sahara region has been plagued by jihadist violence and severe food shortages. (Credit: FAROUK BATICHE/AFP/Getty Images) The UN Global Compact for safe, orderly and regular Migration which has created so much trouble over the past few months contains an important new recognition. Among its various declarations, the compact recognizes “that societies are undergoing demographic, economic, social and environmental changes.” This is one of the first signs that ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>French says its forces kill at least 30 extremists in Mali - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/43aad4ea35db43a6bc7e4a866ca49dc1</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO3QoIUMeCSMwrjIYbbqveIqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 21:59:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/43aad4ea35db43a6bc7e4a866ca49dc1" target="_blank"&gt;French says its forces kill at least 30 extremists in Mali&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BAMAKO, Mali (AP) — France's anti-terrorism forces in Mali have killed at least 30 al-Qaida-linked extremists in central Mali, including the possible death of a chief jihadi leader, France's armed forces ministry said Friday. The ministry said in a statement that the attack overnight Thursday into Friday combined air strikes, Reaper drones, helicopter assaults and ground engagement by French soldiers. Chief jihadist leader Hamadoun Kouffa and other main leaders of the Katibat Macina jihadist group are probably among the dead, Armed Forces Minister Florence Parly said on Twitter. Kouffa is t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>UN: Number of hungry children at 10-year high in Africa's Sahel - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/number-hungry-children-10-year-high-africa-sahel-181116175332100.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELfvl4WiYjNIcypnd3B1iqsqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:35:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/number-hungry-children-10-year-high-africa-sahel-181116175332100.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN: Number of hungry children at 10-year high in Africa's Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of hungry children in West Africa's Sahel region has reached a 10-year high in 2018 due to a lack of rain, conflict and increasing food prices, a United Nations agency said on Friday. More than 1.3m children under the age of five suffered from severe malnutrition this year in the six worst hit countries in the Sahel, a biogeographic transitional zone between the south of the Sahara desert and the north of the Sudanian Savanah. This accounts for a 50 percent increase over 2017, said the UN children's agency, UNICEF. "Each year in the Sahel, many children suffer from severe acute m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>French and West African presidents launch Sahel force - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-sahel-idUSKBN19N0CS</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDDv8tbcKnOxjfkMjwqINK8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 19:18:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-sahel-idUSKBN19N0CS" target="_blank"&gt;French and West African presidents launch Sahel force&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Tiemoko Diallo BAMAKO (Reuters) - African powers launched a new multinational military force to tackle Islamist militants in the Sahel on Sunday, which French President Emmanuel Macron told a regional summit should be fully operational by the autumn despite its current budget shortfall. Some observers see the initiative of the G5 Sahel bloc - Mali, Mauritania, Burkina Faso, Niger and Chad - as forming the basis of an eventual exit strategy for around 4,000 French troops now deployed to the volatile region. But Macron said Paris had no plans to withdraw them. Islamist militant groups, som...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Jihadists, Insurgents Plundering State Arsenals Across Sahel - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/jihadists-insurgents-plundering-state-arsenals-across-sahel/3604404.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJmxt3-bJ-m6rhxB-AQyj1QqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 15:25:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/jihadists-insurgents-plundering-state-arsenals-across-sahel/3604404.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jihadists, Insurgents Plundering State Arsenals Across Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new report, the most extensive on illicit weapon flows in the Sahel in several years, confirms arms looted from huge Libyan stockpiles after the ouster of Colonel Moammar Gadhafi have fueled Islamist insurgencies in North and West Africa since 2012. But jihadists and Tuareg fighters have diversified their supply chains and have added new sources as the outflow from Libya has decreased, due partly to interdiction efforts and a rising internal demand in Libya for weapons as the conflict there looks set to escalate. Jihadists and other Islamist insurgents have plundered arms from inadequatel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Troops killed in ambush on joint Niger-US patrol - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/troops-killed-ambush-joint-niger-patrol-171005041922809.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMH46Oo9ui8NJ7Q68yLH2PUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 08:29:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/10/troops-killed-ambush-joint-niger-patrol-171005041922809.html" target="_blank"&gt;Troops killed in ambush on joint Niger-US patrol&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five Nigerien and three US special forces were killed and others wounded in an ambush on a joint patrol in southwest Niger. The attack, which occurred on Wednesday night, marks the first US combat casualties in Niger, where Washington provides training and security assistance in the fight against armed groups in the Sahel region. "We can confirm reports that a joint US and Nigerien patrol came under hostile fire in southwest Niger," a spokesperson of the US Africa Command told Radio France International (RFI) by telephone. According to RFI, the ambush took place after fighters from Mali att...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Gunmen kill five Niger soldiers as Mali insurgency spreads - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-niger-security-idUSKBN1331MV?il=0</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH7e3dnrignQpMesw9W7fggqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 13:32:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-niger-security-idUSKBN1331MV?il=0" target="_blank"&gt;Gunmen kill five Niger soldiers as Mali insurgency spreads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NIAMEY (Reuters) - Heavily armed gunmen riding motor bikes and other vehicles raided a village and killed five soldiers in Niger near the border with Mali early on Tuesday, the interior ministry said, amid signs of a growing Islamist insurgency in the region. Dozens of attackers entered Banigabou, about 20 km (12 miles) from the frontier before dawn - gunshots rang out for two hours, said residents. The ministry did not name the raiders, though Islamist militants based in Mali's desert north have been pushing south toward its capital and over borders in the fragile Sahel region into Niger a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>EU commits 50 million euros to combat militants in West Africa - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-security-sahel-idUSKBN18W2GV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEP3jv5R2QS5iIfM5CFBOixoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 18:59:11 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-security-sahel-idUSKBN18W2GV" target="_blank"&gt;EU commits 50 million euros to combat militants in West Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAKAR (Reuters) - The European Union committed 50 million euros ($56 million) on Monday to help the countries of West Africa's Sahel region set up a multinational force to combat Islamist militant groups. The vast, arid zone has in recent years become a breeding ground for jihadist groups - some linked to al Qaeda and Islamic State - that European nations, particularly France, fear could threaten Europe if left unchecked. In a statement released during the visit to Mali of its foreign policy chief Federica Mogherini, the European Union said its support would help the so-called G5 Sahel coun...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Militants kill 15 Niger soldiers in patrol ambush - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-niger-security-idUSKBN1622QY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHHhWB85EeXTwA9ahus0gXoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 22:45:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-niger-security-idUSKBN1622QY" target="_blank"&gt;Militants kill 15 Niger soldiers in patrol ambush&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NIAMEY (Reuters) - Militants ambushed an army patrol in Niger on Thursday, killing 15 soldiers and wounding 19, the Defense Ministry said, occurring in an area near the border with Mali where violent Islamists have been seeking to expand their reach. "A search operation is underway to neutralize the terrorists," the ministry statement said of the attack just outside the town of Tiloa. Militants and allied criminal gangs have long exploited the areas around the vast, desert border between Mali and Niger to launch attacks, even after a French-led military intervention pushed insurgent groups ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>U.S. wary of French push for U.N. to back Sahel force: diplomats - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-security-sahel-un-idUSKBN18Z2R7</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEF9O-QO0Y43nfLyrlyl6H-wqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 20:13:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-security-sahel-un-idUSKBN18Z2R7" target="_blank"&gt;U.S. wary of French push for U.N. to back Sahel force: diplomats&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Michelle Nichols UNITED NATIONS (Reuters) - The United States is wary of a French push for the U.N. Security Council to authorize a West African force to combat terrorism and trafficking in the Sahel region because it does not want the world body to help fund it, diplomats said on Thursday. France circulated a draft Security Council resolution on Tuesday to the 15-member body that would approve the force using "all necessary means" and ask U.N. chief Antonio Guterres to report on options for U.N. support to the operation. Closed-door negotiations began on Wednesday, and diplomats said th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>France Turns to Armed Drones in Fight Against Sahel Militants - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/france-turns-to-armed-drones-in-fight-against-sahel-militants/4016980.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFPmOeu7ib5L_b-m3366v3AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 02:04:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/france-turns-to-armed-drones-in-fight-against-sahel-militants/4016980.html" target="_blank"&gt;France Turns to Armed Drones in Fight Against Sahel Militants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France has decided to arm its surveillance drones in West Africa as part of counter-terrorism operations against Islamist militants, Defense Minister Florence Parly said on Tuesday. French President Emmanuel Macron has made fighting Islamist militants his primary foreign policy objective and the move to armed drones fits into a more aggressive policy at a time when it looks increasingly unlikely Paris will be able to withdraw from the region in the medium to long-term. France has six Reapers France currently has five unarmed Reaper reconnaissance drones positioned in Niger's capital Niamey ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Africa and the West must collaborate in order to eliminate terrorism, says Macron - The Telegraph</title><link>http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/07/02/africa-west-must-collaborate-order-eliminate-terrorism-says/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECG1wRU7SfOluYTWQ4J_-EwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 18:23:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2017/07/02/africa-west-must-collaborate-order-eliminate-terrorism-says/" target="_blank"&gt;Africa and the West must collaborate in order to eliminate terrorism, says Macron&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France and African states must work together to "eradicate terrorists, thugs and murderers" in the vast Sahel region, Emmanuel Macron said on Sunday. The French President, meeting in Mali with leaders from the five regional countries involved in the new force, threw his weight behind a new multinational military force set up to fight jihadists. He said France would provide military support for operations as well as 70 tactical vehicles and communications, operational and protective equipment. "We cannot hide behind words, and must take action," he said at a summit of the leaders of Mali, Ma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>France, Germany Tighten Defense Cooperation in Africa's Sahel - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/france-germany-tighten-defense-cooperation-in-africa-sahel-/3967218.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAxW2qO3NpNDLoR2axG9ekcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 01:30:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/france-germany-tighten-defense-cooperation-in-africa-sahel-/3967218.html" target="_blank"&gt;France, Germany Tighten Defense Cooperation in Africa's Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Germany on Monday lent support to France's push to make operational a new multinational military force that will tackle Islamist militants in Africa's Sahel region and urged other powers to contribute funds at an Autumn donor conference. On a joint visit to Niger's capital, Niamey, German Defense Minister Ursula von der Leyen and her French counterpart, Florence Parly, said the Sahel force was West Africa's best hope for defeating the militants. Some observers see the G5 Sahel force — comprised of troops from Mali, Mauritania, Burkina Faso, Niger and Chad — as forming the basis of an eventu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>France Urges UN Backing of West Africa Force to Tackle Terrorism, Trafficking - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/france-urges-un-backing-west-africa-force-tackle-terrorism-trafficking/3890240.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDWzp7_DgV_O7hfQkW6mrYMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 08:27:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/france-urges-un-backing-west-africa-force-tackle-terrorism-trafficking/3890240.html" target="_blank"&gt;France Urges UN Backing of West Africa Force to Tackle Terrorism, Trafficking&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France on Tuesday proposed that the United Nations Security Council back a West African force to combat terrorism, drug and human trafficking by "eradicating the actions" of Islamist militants and organized crime groups in the Sahel region. The vast, arid zone has in recent years become a breeding ground for jihadist groups - some linked to al Qaeda and Islamic State - that European nations, particularly France, fear could threaten Europe if left unchecked. "We cannot afford to let the Sahel region become a new safe haven for terrorists across the world," French U.N. Ambassador Francois Del...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>West Africa seeking 50 million euros from EU for anti-Islamist force - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-security-sahel-idUSKBN18U0JI</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEADkmYliiWEr0oPL33zgWWMqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 13:25:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-security-sahel-idUSKBN18U0JI" target="_blank"&gt;West Africa seeking 50 million euros from EU for anti-Islamist force&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BAMAKO (Reuters) - The countries of West Africa's Sahel region are requesting 50 million euros ($56 million) from the European Union to help set up a multinational force to take on Islamist militant groups, Mali's military chief said on Saturday. The vast, arid zone has in recent years become a breeding ground for jihadist groups - some linked to al Qaeda and Islamic State - that European nations, particularly France, fear could menace Europe if left unchecked. Chad, Niger, Burkina Faso, Mali and Mauritania - the so-called G5 Sahel countries - have proposed a regional task force designed to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>France Softens Proposed UN Backing for Sahel Force to Appease US - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/france-softens-proposed-un-backing-for-sahel-force-to-appease-us/3909432.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFdprAcNDoytbQn-7a6Vc3AqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 01:36:08 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/france-softens-proposed-un-backing-for-sahel-force-to-appease-us/3909432.html" target="_blank"&gt;France Softens Proposed UN Backing for Sahel Force to Appease US&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations Security Council is set to vote on Wednesday on a draft resolution to back a West African force to combat terrorism and arms, drug and human trafficking in the Sahel region after France weakened the language in a bid to appease the United States. The vast, arid region has in recent years become a breeding ground for jihadist groups - some linked to al-Qaida and Islamic State - that European nations, particularly France, fear could threaten Europe if left unchecked. Last year, the Sahel nations - Niger, Mali, Chad, Burkina Faso and Mauritania - proposed establishing specia...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>West African and French leaders launch Sahel force - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/west-african-france-leaders-launch-sahel-force-170702140016920.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDz2U94cIQtbXz2xfzTyNDUqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 06:38:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/west-african-france-leaders-launch-sahel-force-170702140016920.html" target="_blank"&gt;West African and French leaders launch Sahel force&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five African countries have launched a new multinational force to fight armed groups in the Sahel region, which France's President Emmanuel Macron told a summit in Mali should be fully operational "in a matter of weeks". The new regional anti-terror force is set to include as many as 5,000 soldiers, with one battalion from each of the so-called G5 Sahel countries: Mali, Mauritania, Burkina Faso, Niger and Chad. "Our enemies are cowards, but they have determination. They want to destroy us," Macron said on Sunday, in a regional summit with the G5-Sahel leaders in the Malian capital, Bamako. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Macron in Mali for talks with leaders of Africa's Sahel - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/macron-mali-talks-leaders-africa-sahel-170702100325671.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHuGNugfXFrJUyQ5mAHKXcMqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 11:44:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/07/macron-mali-talks-leaders-africa-sahel-170702100325671.html" target="_blank"&gt;Macron in Mali for talks with leaders of Africa's Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron has arrived in Mali for talks with the leaders of five countries across Africa's Sahel region to support a new 5,000-strong multinational force to fight armed groups in the area. The five African countries, which make up so called G5 Sahel, have pledged to to fight al-Qaeda-linked groups and others in the region who have alarmed the international community after launching deadly attacks in recents months on areas that were once considered relatively safe. "Every day we must combat terrorists, thugs, murderers ... who we must steadfastly and with determinatio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>UN: Number of Hungry Children in Africa's Sahel Hits 10-year High - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-number-of-hungry-children-in-africa-s-sahel-hits-10-year-high/4662016.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEET_KLieuBOLKWnq99oo88MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 19:28:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-number-of-hungry-children-in-africa-s-sahel-hits-10-year-high/4662016.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN: Number of Hungry Children in Africa's Sahel Hits 10-year High&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of hungry children in West Africa's Sahel region reached a 10-year high in 2018 because of poor rains, conflict and high food prices, the United Nations said Friday. More than 1.3 million children under age 5 suffered from severe malnutrition this year in the six worst-hit countries in the semi-arid belt below the Sahara — a 50 percent increase from 2017, the U.N. children's agency UNICEF said. "When children suffer from severe acute malnutrition, they are more vulnerable to illnesses such as malaria and waterborne diseases," Marie-Pierre Poirier, UNICEF regional director for Wes...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>New French President Reaffirms Commitment to Fight Terrorism in Sahel - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3867200.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC94nsQFik5fcO-qM_YgStMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 16:02:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3867200.html" target="_blank"&gt;New French President Reaffirms Commitment to Fight Terrorism in Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;During his election campaign, France’s new president Emmanuel Macron promised he would visit French troops in Mali. Just days into his term, he made Mali his second foreign visit, and his first to Africa. In choosing Mali as his second foreign trip, just a week into his presidency, Emmanuel Macron was sending a clear message that he is determined to continue the fight against terrorism. France sent troops into Mali in 2013, in a military intervention that pushed the extremists from their strongholds, but hasn’t stopped the wave of killings, kidnappings and attacks there by Islamic militants...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>France must work with African allies to combat terrorism in the region, says Emmanuel Macron - The Independent</title><link>http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/politics/macron-france-africa-allies-combat-terrorism-mali-a7819331.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPfdZLemRxoijMQX_fJv4UwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 14:05:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/politics/macron-france-africa-allies-combat-terrorism-mali-a7819331.html" target="_blank"&gt;France must work with African allies to combat terrorism in the region, says Emmanuel Macron&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France and its African partners must work together to wipe out Islamist militants in the volatile Sahel region, President Emmanuel Macron said at the opening of a summit in Mali's capital Bamako on Sunday. At the meeting, leaders of the G5 Sahel bloc - Mali, Burkina Faso, Mauritania, Niger and Chad - were expected to launch a new multi-national force aimed at combating Islamist militants and illegal activity in the vast region. "Every day we must combat terrorists, thugs, murderers ... who we must steadfastly and with determination eradicate together," said Macron, who was making his second...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>France says backs West African cooperation against Islamists - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-africa-idUSKBN178283</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGpybsqFirzJYCrx7AL1X9IqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 01:50:30 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-africa-idUSKBN178283" target="_blank"&gt;France says backs West African cooperation against Islamists&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By John Irish NOUAKCHOTT (Reuters) - France backs efforts by West African states to boost security in their Sahel region, including a plan for a 5,000-strong multinational force to combat Islamist fighters, its foreign minister said on Thursday. Jean-Marc Ayrault said the G5 Sahel states - Mali, Mauritania, Chad, Burkina Faso and Niger - must improve their counter-terrorism capacity. "The countries of the G5 have decided to enter a new phase ... with the creation of a common force to protect their borders," Ayrault said after meeting Mauritanian President Mohamed Ould Abdel Aziz. "The secon...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Macron vows to step up French fight against Islamists in Africa - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-mali-idUSKCN18F0DV</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOK0bfPY_2If_Mll1HrXct0qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 19:50:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-mali-idUSKCN18F0DV" target="_blank"&gt;Macron vows to step up French fight against Islamists in Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Marine Pennetier GAO, Mali (Reuters) - France will step up the fight against resurgent Islamist militants in north and west Africa and will work more closely with Germany to help the tinderbox region, President Emmanuel Macron said on his first trip outside Europe on Friday. Visiting Mali days after taking office, Macron vowed to keep French troops in the Sahel region until there was "no more Islamist terrorism" there. He said operations would be escalated in response to signs that militant groups were regrouping and uniting. "It is vital today that we speed up. Our armed forces are givi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>At least 18 killed in restaurant attack in Burkina Faso - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/86148904-80b9-11e7-a4ce-15b2513cb3ff</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEByemVXnNou1qQKJ_NOIqNwqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 14:11:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/86148904-80b9-11e7-a4ce-15b2513cb3ff" target="_blank"&gt;At least 18 killed in restaurant attack in Burkina Faso&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suspected Islamist militants killed at least 18 people in a “terrorist attack” on a Turkish restaurant in the Burkina Faso capital Ouagadougou, the government said. No one has claimed responsibility for the raid on the Aziz Istanbul restaurant on Sunday night, which lasted for hours. But, like other countries in west Africa, Burkina Faso has suffered several attacks by jihadis during the past few years. The attack began at about 9pm when two gunmen started shooting after arriving at the restaurant on motorbike, local media quoted witnesses as saying. Video footage from the scene showed scor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Researchers: Climate Change May Turn Africa's Arid Sahel Green - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/researchers-say-climate-change-may-turn-africa-arid-sahel-green/3930013.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN9sX7DuUkzaNSjanPPSQ_MqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 23:31:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/researchers-say-climate-change-may-turn-africa-arid-sahel-green/3930013.html" target="_blank"&gt;Researchers: Climate Change May Turn Africa's Arid Sahel Green&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Africa's driest regions — the Sahel — could turn greener if the planet warms more than 2 degrees Celsius and triggers more frequent heavy rainfall, scientists said on Wednesday. The Sahel stretches coast to coast from Mauritania and Mali in the west to Sudan and Eritrea in the east, and skirts the southern edge of the Sahara desert. It is home to more than 100 million people. The region has seen worsening extreme weather — including more frequent droughts — in recent years. But if greenhouse gas emissions continue unabated, the resulting global warming — of more than 2 degrees Celsiu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>France says '20 fighters killed' in northern Mali - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/05/france-20-fighters-northern-mali-170501042340404.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBlIS7_dv6LoCXyFIhHzCnoqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 06:46:26 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/05/france-20-fighters-northern-mali-170501042340404.html" target="_blank"&gt;France says '20 fighters killed' in northern Mali&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;France says it has killed about 20 suspected fighters in a forest near Mali's border with Burkina Faso. French Mirage fighter jets bombed several suspected arms depots in the Foulsare Forest, southwest of the northern Malian city of Gao, late on Saturday, a French counterterrorism unit said in a statement on Sunday. Troops from Operation Barkhane, whose mission is to target fighters operating in the Sahel region of the Sahara Desert, said they also discovered large amounts of arms, ammunition, rocket launchers and explosives. It however, did not identify the groups that were targeted. A Fre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Could this 'miracle' grain from Africa become the next quinoa? - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/2017/09/29/africa/pierre-thiam-fonio/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFesDwL825zlIxNVOXbMGo8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 14:40:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/2017/09/29/africa/pierre-thiam-fonio/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Could this 'miracle' grain from Africa become the next quinoa?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a child, Pierre Thiam didn't think there was anything extraordinary about fonio; a tiny-grained cereal he often ate on summer vacations at his grandparents'. Decades later he sees it as the "miracle" grain that could replace quinoa and transform the economy of the Sahel. Fonio has been grown for over 5,000 years and is possibly the oldest cultivated cereal in Africa. The gluten-free grain, native to Thiam's birth country, Senegal, has been touted as the next quinoa. "It is nutritious, particularly rich in methionine and cysteine, two amino acids that are deficient in most other major gra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>UN Security Council Backs W. Africa Force to Fight Sahel Militants - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/un-security-council-backs-west-africa-force-to-fight-sahel-militants/3910976.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED3GxRvp0oB0xgfEEx1B5M8qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:24:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/un-security-council-backs-west-africa-force-to-fight-sahel-militants/3910976.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Security Council Backs W. Africa Force to Fight Sahel Militants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United Nations Security Council on Wednesday unanimously backed a West African force to combat militant groups as well as arms, drug and human trafficking in the Sahel region after diplomats said France softened the resolution's language to secure the support of the United States. The vast, arid region has in recent years become a breeding ground for jihadist groups - some linked to al Qaeda and the Islamic State - that European countries, particularly France, fear could threaten Europe if left unchecked. Last year, the nations of the Sahel - Niger, Mali, Chad, Burkina Faso and Mauritan...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>France softens proposed U.N. backing for Sahel force to appease U.S. - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-security-sahel-un-idUSKBN19B321</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKJlNUq4AvUJzpQDkVGIVV8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 20:49:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-africa-security-sahel-un-idUSKBN19B321" target="_blank"&gt;France softens proposed U.N. backing for Sahel force to appease U.S.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Michelle Nichols UNITED NATIONS (Reuters) - The United Nations Security Council is set to vote on Wednesday on a draft resolution to back a West African force to combat terrorism and arms, drug and human trafficking in the Sahel region after France weakened the language in a bid to appease the United States. The vast, arid region has in recent years become a breeding ground for jihadist groups - some linked to al Qaeda and Islamic State - that European nations, particularly France, fear could threaten Europe if left unchecked. Last year, the Sahel nations - Niger, Mali, Chad, Burkina Fas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Heading to Sahel, France's Macron scrambles for exit strategy - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-sahel-idUSKBN19L0FM</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJ7t2cdL4x_d6Z_tPispw3MqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 05:11:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-sahel-idUSKBN19L0FM" target="_blank"&gt;Heading to Sahel, France's Macron scrambles for exit strategy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By John Irish and Emma Farge PARIS/DAKAR (Reuters) - President Emmanuel Macron heads to Mali on Sunday to throw France's weight behind a new West African military force he hopes will lay the basis for an exit strategy for its own troops; but its prospects for success look slim. Mali is hosting a heads of state summit with Niger, Chad, Burkina Faso and Mauritania - known as the G5 Sahel - who could ultimately deploy thousands of troops into the vast, arid Sahel region that remains a breeding ground for militants and traffickers that Paris considers a threat to Europe. Four years after interv...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Is climate change to blame in Freetown? - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/climate-change-blame-freetown-170817133120465.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDLhh4GUW6gK1WouXV7_gu4qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 06:27:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/08/climate-change-blame-freetown-170817133120465.html" target="_blank"&gt;Is climate change to blame in Freetown?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deadly landslide in Freetown, Sierra Leone on Monday morning was undoubtedly partly the result of deforestation. During the rainy season, Sierra Leone is one of the wettest places on earth, statistically. And from that point of view, it is a surprise that such disasters don’t happen more often. It looks as though the changing climate may make the future risk even greater as more frequent and more violent rainy season events such as this are a measurable consequence. In tropical Africa, much of the seasonal rain comes from thunderstorms and often these cluster together, creating mesoscal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Heading to Sahel, France's Macron Scrambles for Exit Strategy - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/heading-to-sahel-france-macron-scrambles-for-exit-strategy-/3924048.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELOpswilV4V3qewBXT2Pbj4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 02:00:28 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/heading-to-sahel-france-macron-scrambles-for-exit-strategy-/3924048.html" target="_blank"&gt;Heading to Sahel, France's Macron Scrambles for Exit Strategy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Emmanuel Macron heads to Mali on Sunday to throw France's weight behind a new West African military force he hopes will lay the basis for an exit strategy for its own troops; but its prospects for success look slim. Mali is hosting a heads of state summit with Niger, Chad, Burkina Faso and Mauritania - known as the G5 Sahel - who could ultimately deploy thousands of troops into the vast, arid Sahel region that remains a breeding ground for militants and traffickers that Paris considers a threat to Europe. Four years after intervening in its former colony to ward off a jihadist off...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>UK troops sent to Africa’s jihadist belt to fight extremism and migration in British ‘pivot to Sahel' - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/06/uk-troops-sent-africas-jihadist-belt-fight-extremism-migration/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECpeRWtm1Uu0Pdz7ru-b01MqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/06/uk-troops-sent-africas-jihadist-belt-fight-extremism-migration/" target="_blank"&gt;UK troops sent to Africa’s jihadist belt to fight extremism and migration in British ‘pivot to Sahel'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The French military vehicle broke down in the unforgiving desert of northern Mali, 80 miles from the nearest base. Jihadists, bandits and armed villagers all criss-cross the arid plains, and attacks targeting French counter-terrorism forces are common. This time, however, following a commitment made by Prime Minister Theresa May to President Emmanuel Macron in January, an RAF Chinook airlifted the dust-whipped vehicle and its personnel to safety. The RAF deployed three helicopters and 120 personnel to Gao, northern Mali, in July, but their presence marks the tip of a much broader British “p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Burkinabe Farmer Wins 'Alternative Nobel' for Drought-fighting Technique - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/burkinabe-farmer-wins-alternative-nobel-for-drought-fighting-technique/4585941.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECZ3ugGhLudrJqPeIChqBjEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 03:35:32 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/burkinabe-farmer-wins-alternative-nobel-for-drought-fighting-technique/4585941.html" target="_blank"&gt;Burkinabe Farmer Wins 'Alternative Nobel' for Drought-fighting Technique&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A farmer from Burkina Faso who popularized an ancient farming technique to reverse desertification is among the winners of Sweden's "alternative Nobel prize," announced on Monday. Yacouba Sawadogo shared this year's award with three Saudi human rights activists and an Australian agronomist. The 3 million Swedish crown ($341,800) prize honors people who find solutions to global problems. Sawadogo is known for turning barren land into forest using "zai" - pits dug in hardened soil that concentrate water and nutrients, allowing crops to withstand drought. The technique has been used to restore...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>US Stepping Up Armed Drone Efforts in Niger - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/us-stepping-up-armed-drone-efforts-in-niger-/4545073.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEI1cURMgpOVZ-opsnbtwDQoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 23:09:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/us-stepping-up-armed-drone-efforts-in-niger-/4545073.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Stepping Up Armed Drone Efforts in Niger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Air Force is months away from completing the construction of an air base in Niger for armed drones that will target militant groups operating in the region, a U.S military official told VOA. "To date, the Air Force has spent approximately $86.5 million on the construction project at Nigerien Air Base 201," Auburn Davis, a spokesperson for U.S. Air Force Europe and Air Force Africa, told VOA. "The total estimated construction cost, including FY19 planned projects, is $98.5million," Davis added. She said that the base, which is located in Agadez city in northern Niger, is the biggest...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Leaders Urge Global Support for Women, Girls in Africa's Sahel - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/leaders-urge-global-support-for-women-girls-in-africa-s-sahel/4477152.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPLwLZGYwWjtYwYGcJXXAPcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 22:05:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/leaders-urge-global-support-for-women-girls-in-africa-s-sahel/4477152.html" target="_blank"&gt;Leaders Urge Global Support for Women, Girls in Africa's Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several high-level women are calling for more international support focused on helping women and girls in Africa's Sahel region respond to the impact of conflict, terrorism and underdevelopment. The foreign minister of Sweden, the U.N. deputy secretary-general, and the African Union's special envoy on women, peace and security just wrapped up a joint visit to Niger and Chad where they met with women from all areas of society. "The countries we visited and the Sahel region are located between hope and despair," Swedish Foreign Minister Margot Wallström told a special meeting of the U.N. Secu...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Can AU Tackle Security Challenges in the Sahel? - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/can-au-tackle-security-challenges-in-the-sahel-/4476948.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB-rqIaI9nduxhva0LBKKO0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/can-au-tackle-security-challenges-in-the-sahel-/4476948.html" target="_blank"&gt;Can AU Tackle Security Challenges in the Sahel?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;African leaders meeting in Mauritania last week pledged to redouble efforts aimed at curtailing and defeating extremist groups on the continent, especially in the Sahel region. The pledge followed a rash of attacks by jihadi terrorist groups in two Sahel countries, including an attack that killed 10 Nigerien soldiers in the country's southeast and an attack on the headquarters of the regional anti-jihadist G5 Sahel Force in Sevare and two other attacks in Mali. But some experts are warning that there is not much the African Union can do to enhance the capabilities of the G5 force that was e...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Africa's Sahel Armed Groups Not Just Islamist Militants - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/africa-s-sahel-armed-groups-not-just-islamist-militants/4464617.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE5Nwf5PxQKpQCdRiMLmdB4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw6pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 11:24:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/africa-s-sahel-armed-groups-not-just-islamist-militants/4464617.html" target="_blank"&gt;Africa's Sahel Armed Groups Not Just Islamist Militants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamist militants have been a major problem in Mali since at least 2012, when armed jihadists briefly took over the northern half of the country. But not all the young men who join armed groups in the region — including Islamist ones — are motivated simply by religion. According to researchers, many join armed groups for reasons that are practical, which if addressed could provide some solutions to conflict. The threat from armed Islamist groups in the vast Sahel region seems to be worsening on some fronts. A still image taken from a video shot on June 29, 2018, shows damaged buildings ins...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>3 killed in attack on West African counterterror force's HQ - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/b51545124ff74d3da6bed30d389aeda9</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMe6_oJ2tnX9QD2uvPWc7U8qGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 23:13:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/b51545124ff74d3da6bed30d389aeda9" target="_blank"&gt;3 killed in attack on West African counterterror force's HQ&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;BAMAKO, Mali (AP) — A car packed with explosives detonated at the headquarters of a new, five-nation West African counterterror force in Mali, setting off a gun battle that killed two soldiers, a civilian and two attackers, officials told The Associated Press on Friday. The attack highlighted the brazenness of the extremist threat in a part of the world that made headlines in October with the killing of four U.S. service members in an ambush in neighboring Niger. Force commander Gen. Didier Dacko confirmed Friday's attack by phone from Niger, saying it began with the car attack. Residents s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>At least six dead in Mali after attack on regional anti-terror force base - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/29/mali-people-dead-after-attack-on-g5-sahel-anti-terror-taskforce-base</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFSz9G0QSCa_wd7-elXyBHoqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 16:56:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/29/mali-people-dead-after-attack-on-g5-sahel-anti-terror-taskforce-base" target="_blank"&gt;At least six dead in Mali after attack on regional anti-terror force base&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamist militants have attacked the Malian headquarters of a regional anti-terror taskforce, killing six people and leaving many injured, according to a provisional toll. A suicide bomber tried to penetrate the base at Sévaré in central Mali, according to a security source. A local orange seller, Haoussa Haidara, said “there was a huge blast” followed by exchanges of gunfire. Gunshots could still be heard an hour later. It is the first attack on the headquarters of the joint G5 force, set up in 2017 to combat jihadist insurgents and criminal groups in the vast, unstable Sahel region of Afr...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Mali: Car bombing targeting French troops kills civilians - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/mali-car-bombing-targeting-french-troops-kills-civilians-180701150834395.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEfF562eY9jLrLC6mgkT-mMqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 16:11:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/07/mali-car-bombing-targeting-french-troops-kills-civilians-180701150834395.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mali: Car bombing targeting French troops kills civilians&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A car bomb attack targeting a military patrol in northern Mali has killed at least two civilians and wounded several French soldiers, according to Mali's defence ministry. Patrik Steiger, France's army spokesman, confirmed that civilians had been killed in Sunday's bombing near the town of Bourem in the Gao region. He said the explosion took place near three French vehicles during a joint patrol with Malian troops. The blast, which came two days after a deadly attack on the Mali headquarters of a five-nation regional force known as G5 Sahel, underscores the fragile security situation in the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Mali: G5 force headquarters targeted in deadly attack - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/06/mali-g5-force-headquarters-targeted-deadly-attack-180629175547728.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBWVD7KDVtQOtN7gBSB_u8cqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 18:42:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/06/mali-g5-force-headquarters-targeted-deadly-attack-180629175547728.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mali: G5 force headquarters targeted in deadly attack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least two soldiers have been killed and several others wounded in an attack by unidentified fighters on the headquarters of an African military taskforce in central Mali. The assault on Friday on the G5 Sahel taskforce - a security mission composed of Mali, Niger, Burkina Faso, Chad and Mauritania - in the town of Sevare was perpetrated by an unknown number of assailants who used rockets and a vehicle rigged with explosives to attack the compound, a spokesperson for the Malian defence ministry said. Diaran Kone, a spokesman for the Malian army, said two members of the army and two "terro...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>6 killed in attack on EU-funded anti-terror force in Mali implicated in ‘summary executions’ - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/431320-mali-g5-sahel-attack-executions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKUHNvycf5eFFEQImGPh_wkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 00:46:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/431320-mali-g5-sahel-attack-executions/" target="_blank"&gt;6 killed in attack on EU-funded anti-terror force in Mali implicated in ‘summary executions’&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least six soldiers were killed in a suicide bombing of the G5 Sahel anti-terrorist force in Mali. The attack came just days after the UN accused the force of the “summary and arbitrary execution” of civilians. A suicide bomber exploded a vehicle in front of the G5 Sahel joint task force compound in Mali’s central town of Sevare on Friday. The explosion was followed by an attack from militants. “The attackers fired rockets at the headquarters and some of them infiltrated the compound. There was an exchange of fire,” Mali’s defense ministry spokesman Boubacar Diallo told Reuters. At least ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>African leaders talk security with French president - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/7e1ff937fc8c4c25af8ca8625d9c832d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKAebG1-JvZxKiXXxeVJTqsqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 22:20:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/7e1ff937fc8c4c25af8ca8625d9c832d" target="_blank"&gt;African leaders talk security with French president&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOUAKCHOTT, Mauritania (AP) — African heads of state have pledged to coordinate efforts to improve the continent's security and defeat jihadist organizations, particularly in Nigeria and the Sahel region, during talks Monday at the 31st African Union summit held in Mauritania's capital. French President Emmanuel Macron arrived in Nouakchott Monday to discuss the battle against Islamic extremism and ways to finance counterterrorism and peacekeeping operations. Mauritanian President Mohamed Ould Abdel Aziz met Macron at the airport, and praised the French president for his "work for the devel...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Funds Slow to Come to Anti-Jihadist Sahel Force, says Niger - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/funds-slow-to-come-to-anti-jihadist-sahel-force-says-niger/4443844.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIfJkNb4EyoQcsd1MhI1SN0qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 17:06:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/funds-slow-to-come-to-anti-jihadist-sahel-force-says-niger/4443844.html" target="_blank"&gt;Funds Slow to Come to Anti-Jihadist Sahel Force, says Niger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A joint military force to fight jihadists and organized crime in the Sahel has chalked up successes but promised funding is slow to materialize, the foreign minister of Niger said on Monday. "The strength of the G-5 Sahel force has become a reality even if not all the funding has been disbursed," said Kalla Ankourao, whose country is assuming the rotating presidency of the group. The force also includes Burkina Faso, Chad, Mali and Mauritania. Originally intended to become fully operational in mid-2018, the G-5 Sahel force operates alongside France's 4,000 troops in the troubled "tri-border...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>UN Says 6 Million Struggling to Get Food in Africa's Sahel - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/sahel-malnutrition-/4436537.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPMBODNK6jaAZOrJHOzM0mcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 02:15:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/sahel-malnutrition-/4436537.html" target="_blank"&gt;UN Says 6 Million Struggling to Get Food in Africa's Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.N. humanitarian chief warned Tuesday that nearly 6 million people are struggling to get food in West Africa's Sahel region and severe malnutrition is threatening the lives of 1.6 million children. Mark Lowcock said in a statement that these levels haven't been seen since a crisis in 2012 "and the most critical months are still ahead.'' He said the rapid deterioration in recent months in Burkina Faso, Chad, Mali, Mauritania, Niger and Senegal "reveals an urgent need for more donor support.'' He said U.N. plans to respond to the crisis in the six countries are only 26 percent funded and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>France's Macron Urges Donors to Quickly Finance Sahel Force - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/france-s-macron-urges-donors-to-quickly-finance-sahel-force/4424050.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEE7ejoEKNb1HuNdyknvCZ6UqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 18:38:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/france-s-macron-urges-donors-to-quickly-finance-sahel-force/4424050.html" target="_blank"&gt;France's Macron Urges Donors to Quickly Finance Sahel Force&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron called on international donors to quickly make financing available for the Sahel regional counterterror force. In a news conference in Paris with visiting Niger President Mahamadou Issoufou, Macron said money "now needs to be disbursed" to allow the five-nation regional force, known as the G5 Sahel, to keep functioning. He said the European Union started financing the force last week and will provide equipment in coming weeks. He called on other donors like Saudi Arabia to meet their financial commitments. Issoufou expressed his concerns over the financial s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>On Mali Visit, UN Chief Asks Donors to Back G5 Sahel Force - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/mali-visit-un-chief-antonio-guterres-asks-donors-back-g5-sahel-force/4415162.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH138B5i7HUIPd1EYwv87zUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 21:40:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/mali-visit-un-chief-antonio-guterres-asks-donors-back-g5-sahel-force/4415162.html" target="_blank"&gt;On Mali Visit, UN Chief Asks Donors to Back G5 Sahel Force&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.N. Secretary-General Antonio Guterres appealed to donors Tuesday to provide more predictable support to the G5 Sahel force fighting to contain West African jihadists. He spoke while on a visit to Mali, the country worst affected by Islamist militants. A conference in February of about 50 countries including the United States, Japan and Norway pledged 414 million euros ($509 million) for the G5 Sahel force, made up of troops from Mali, Niger, Chad, Burkina Faso and Mauritania. But the force has been planned for years, yet has only got off the ground in the past few months as little of the ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Longtime Jihadist Leads Group that Claimed Niger Attack - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/longtime-jijadist-leads-group-claimed-niger-attack/4388470.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIuA9jX35DD8sRHmUiYnB2EqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 19:15:58 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/longtime-jijadist-leads-group-claimed-niger-attack/4388470.html" target="_blank"&gt;Longtime Jihadist Leads Group that Claimed Niger Attack&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not much is known about the Islamic State in the Greater Sahara, the group that claimed responsibility for killing four U.S. and four Nigerien soldiers in western Niger last October. However, the group's leader, Adnan Abu Walid al-Sahrawi, is a well-known figure in regional jihadist circles. Al-Sahrawi "is a longtime veteran of the West African subregion with deep networks in Mali," according to Jacob Zenn, fellow of African and Eurasian Affairs for the Jamestown Foundation in Washington and a consultant on countering violent extremism. "He is able to manage groups of multiple ethnicities t...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Al-Qaida Branch Threatens Attacks on Western Companies in Africa - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/al-qaida-threatens-africa/4385820.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED5O81LC7Nrj5c4BU-wx_cgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 01:45:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/al-qaida-threatens-africa/4385820.html" target="_blank"&gt;Al-Qaida Branch Threatens Attacks on Western Companies in Africa&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An al-Qaida affiliate threatened attacks on Western companies' operations across North and West Africa on Tuesday, calling them "legitimate targets" and urging Muslims to boycott them. Al-Qaida in the Islamic Maghreb (AQIM) has launched raids on installations in the past, in particular in Algeria where it carried out a major assault on a gas plant in 2013 that killed dozens of workers. Its fighters have also carried out high-profile attacks on hotels frequented by foreigners in Mali, Burkina Faso and Ivory Coast. "This statement calls to boycott all Western companies and foundations ... tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Sahara desert is 10 percent bigger than 100 years ago - RT</title><link>https://www.rt.com/news/422856-sahara-desert-expansion-climate-change/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECAzQ5XR2r3IQnAlxoWiufMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAownP3cAjDQkhww_oMo</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 12:42:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.rt.com/news/422856-sahara-desert-expansion-climate-change/" target="_blank"&gt;Sahara desert is 10 percent bigger than 100 years ago&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;RT&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Climate change is partly to blame for a startling increase in the size of the Sahara Desert over the past one hundred years. According to a new study, the world’s largest desert has expanded by 10 percent since 1920. READ MORE: Countdown to Day Zero: Why is Cape Town running out of water? (VIDEOS) Researchers from the University of Maryland studied rainfall data to measure boundary changes of the desert and found that higher summer temperatures coupled with dry winters are increasing the overall aridity of the land. The expansion of the desert also spells trouble for humans and ecosystems i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.rt.com">RT</source></item><item><title>World’s largest desert has grown even larger due to climate change - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/environment/sahara-worlds-largest-desert-climate-change-growth-global-warming-sahel-a8280361.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEM2-MhTTjXLV3-7oZYJuUoUqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 17:21:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/environment/sahara-worlds-largest-desert-climate-change-growth-global-warming-sahel-a8280361.html" target="_blank"&gt;World’s largest desert has grown even larger due to climate change&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Sahara Desert has grown significantly over the past century, and climate change is largely to blame, according to a new study. Analysing data collected since 1923, a research team examined the different factors that contributed to changes in rainfall in the Sahara region. They found the desert, already around the size of the US, had expanded by about 10 per cent over the period covered by this data. These results have implications for those living in the border region of the Sahara known as the Sahel, but the scientists noted that climate change-driven desertification is not a phenomeno...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Int'l Donors Pledge More Than $500M for West Africa's Sahel - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/international-donors-pledge-more-than-half-a-billion-dollars-for-west-africa-sahel-region/4268139.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED4C4R5vDlWsCxaT98aor64qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 20:03:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/international-donors-pledge-more-than-half-a-billion-dollars-for-west-africa-sahel-region/4268139.html" target="_blank"&gt;Int'l Donors Pledge More Than $500M for West Africa's Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Union and other international donors pledged more than half-a-billion dollars Friday to support a multi-national military operation in Africa’s vast Sahel region, which has fallen prey to smugglers, human traffickers and terrorists in recent years. Speaking after an international meeting on the Sahel in Brussels, European Union foreign policy chief Federica Mogherini said the pledges far exceeded initial expectations. She said they mirrored the strong international support for the so-called G-5 Sahel — a regional development and security initiative headed by five Sahelian natio...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Burkina Faso: Army headquarters and French embassy attacked - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/03/blast-rocks-burkina-faso-ouagadougou-reports-180302110142186.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJmCV1IR5dWM6X_uHrtaPY0qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 11:33:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/03/blast-rocks-burkina-faso-ouagadougou-reports-180302110142186.html" target="_blank"&gt;Burkina Faso: Army headquarters and French embassy attacked&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 16 people, including eight gunmen, have been killed in coordinated attacks on the French embassy and army headquarters in Burkina Faso's capital, Ouagadougou. Witnesses say masked attackers used guns and explosives during the Friday's assault. At least eight assailants and eight security personnel were killed, the military said. Officials also said that more than 80 people, including civilians, were wounded. The national police force confirmed that Friday's attacks occurred in an area near the prime minister's office and the United Nations roundabout. An attack also occurred at the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Sahel support 414 mn - Mogherini (3) - Agenzia Ansa</title><link>http://www.ansa.it/english/news/business/2018/02/23/sahel-support-414-mn-mogherini-3_c296b844-a139-4636-9d1b-eeaec2bf276c.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECSQcrODX5fHejVCldY3WjsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsP-hCTCXv5cCMJSC0QU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:15:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.ansa.it/english/news/business/2018/02/23/sahel-support-414-mn-mogherini-3_c296b844-a139-4636-9d1b-eeaec2bf276c.html" target="_blank"&gt;Sahel support 414 mn - Mogherini (3)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Agenzia Ansa&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;(ANSA) - Brussels, February 23 - European Union High Representative for Foreign Affairs Federica Mogherini said after a conference on security and development in the Sahel Friday that the EU and other partners were putting a total of 414 million euros into the African area. "Today we announced a supplementary support for the joint force of the Sahel of 50 million euros extra which will be added to the 50 already put in," she said. "The total support for this region is 414 million euros thanks to investments not only by the EU but akso by other partners," said Mogherini. She said the c...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.ansa.it">Agenzia Ansa</source></item><item><title>Explosive Device Kills 2 French Soldiers in Mali - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/explosive-device-kills-two-french-soldiers-in-mali/4264624.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENMqjxbKPyJoeVNSW5jxCUcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 20:21:14 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/explosive-device-kills-two-french-soldiers-in-mali/4264624.html" target="_blank"&gt;Explosive Device Kills 2 French Soldiers in Mali&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two members of a French counterterrorism force in Mali were killed Wednesday when an improvised explosive device hit their armored vehicle in a border region with Niger, authorities said. French President Emmanuel Macron's office said a soldier and an officer were killed in the explosion. A statement by Defense Minister Florence Parly said those killed were part of a "vast operation'' patrolling the border region with Niger. It did not specify the locality. The minister identified the victims as Emilien Mougin and Timothee Dernoncourt, from an armored regiment based in Valence but members o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Observers Call for Deeper Diplomatic Engagement in the Sahel - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/observers-call-for-deeper-diplomatic-engagement-sahel/4248234.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDRR_wPiGoMYjKDRm2xFlKEqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 21:04:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/observers-call-for-deeper-diplomatic-engagement-sahel/4248234.html" target="_blank"&gt;Observers Call for Deeper Diplomatic Engagement in the Sahel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A draft of a Pentagon report on the attack in Niger that killed four American soldiers, four Nigerien soldiers and an Nigerien interpreter last October calls for a smaller, more cautious U.S. military presence in West Africa, according to sources who spoke to The New York Times. That could emphasize the need for deeper diplomatic and political engagement in the Sahel, given ongoing security challenges and difficulties in funding and coordinating a regional task force. Militant groups Details about who is responsible for the October 4 attack have been difficult to confirm. However, U.S. and ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>IS Offshoot Claims 2017 Niger Attack on US Forces - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/islamic-state-offshoot-claims-twenty-seventeen-niger-attack-united-states-forces/4206936.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDoL9XGx9MXU_4x5UfATbMcqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 00:30:23 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/islamic-state-offshoot-claims-twenty-seventeen-niger-attack-united-states-forces/4206936.html" target="_blank"&gt;IS Offshoot Claims 2017 Niger Attack on US Forces&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Islamic State offshoot is claiming it carried out the October attack in Niger that killed four U.S. soldiers and four Nigerien troops and sparked questions about U.S. military involvement in West Africa's vast Sahel region. The Mauritanian Nouakchott News Agency reported Friday that Abu al-Walid al-Sahrawi with the self-professed IS affiliate claimed responsibility for the October 4 ambush about 200 kilometers (120 miles) north of Niger's capital, Niamey. The news agency has carried messages from the affiliate before, according to the SITE Intelligence Group, which monitors jihadist webs...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Italy PM plans to shift military forces from Iraq to Niger - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-defence-niger/italy-pm-plans-to-shift-military-forces-from-iraq-to-niger-idUSKBN1EI0E2</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPOMXcRvNv7XB4YPkDFIQQkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 15:00:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-defence-niger/italy-pm-plans-to-shift-military-forces-from-iraq-to-niger-idUSKBN1EI0E2" target="_blank"&gt;Italy PM plans to shift military forces from Iraq to Niger&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROME (Reuters) - Italian Prime Minister Paolo Gentiloni said on Sunday he would propose to parliament transferring some of the country's troops stationed in Iraq to Niger to fight people smuggling and terrorism. Gentiloni said Italy's 1,400-strong military presence in Iraq could now be reduced after victories against Islamic militants and instead deployed in the Sahel region of West Africa. "We have to continue to work, concentrating our attention and energies on the threat of people trafficking and terrorism in the Sahel," he said aboard the Italian ship Etna used in the European Union's "...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item></channel></rss>