<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Remand - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqJAgKIh5DQkFTRUFvS0wyMHZNRE5uY21KdE9CSUNaVzRvQUFQAQ?hl=en-NG&amp;gl=NG&amp;ceid=NG:en</link><language>en-NG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 14:01:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>Court remands Deji Adeyanju in prison till 2019 - Daily Post Nigeria</title><link>http://dailypost.ng/2018/11/29/police-remand-deji-adeyanju-prison-till-2019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiTGh0dHA6Ly9kYWlseXBvc3QubmcvMjAxOC8xMS8yOS9wb2xpY2UtcmVtYW5kLWRlamktYWRleWFuanUtcHJpc29uLXRpbGwtMjAxOS_SAZQBaHR0cHM6Ly9kYWlseXBvc3QtbmcuY2RuLmFtcHByb2plY3Qub3JnL3YvZGFpbHlwb3N0Lm5nLzIwMTgvMTEvMjkvcG9saWNlLXJlbWFuZC1kZWppLWFkZXlhbmp1LXByaXNvbi10aWxsLTIwMTkvYW1wLz9hbXBfanNfdj0wLjEjd2Vidmlldz0xJmNhcD1zd2lwZQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://dailypost.ng/2018/11/29/police-remand-deji-adeyanju-prison-till-2019/" target="_blank"&gt;Court remands Deji Adeyanju in prison till 2019&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Daily Post Nigeria&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following his arrest by the Nigeria Police Force, human rights activist and co-convener of 'our mumu don do' crusade, Prince Deji Adeyanju has been remande.&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://dailypost.ng">Daily Post Nigeria</source></item><item><title>Stop Granting Reckless Remand Orders To Police, CJN Warns Judges - SaharaReporters.com</title><link>http://saharareporters.com/2018/11/27/stop-granting-reckless-remand-orders-police-cjn-warns-judges</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiYmh0dHA6Ly9zYWhhcmFyZXBvcnRlcnMuY29tLzIwMTgvMTEvMjcvc3RvcC1ncmFudGluZy1yZWNrbGVzcy1yZW1hbmQtb3JkZXJzLXBvbGljZS1jam4td2FybnMtanVkZ2Vz0gEA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://saharareporters.com/2018/11/27/stop-granting-reckless-remand-orders-police-cjn-warns-judges" target="_blank"&gt;Stop Granting Reckless Remand Orders To Police, CJN Warns Judges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;SaharaReporters.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chief Justice of Nigeria (CJN), Justice Walter Onnoghen, yesterday warned judges in the country to refrain from issuing what he described as “reckless” ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://saharareporters.com">SaharaReporters.com</source><media:content url="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/nDYH3T_Rzub3_Rb7UndREnxdSDmtLURdNw9Nwip6ua5jlNO5w60Zm6X9HgOA2BQnY0zQKv01hP_0k-2fWQomKRH3HiMPjTdktUsxZJ2TztIatlsBoIFPXt2KF3QYnQJdeRuA3V405yrrECSWscAkPLC_DD_c3-ILoTdNweZL2JnmjX4=-w150-h150-c" medium="image" width="150" height="150"/></item><item><title>Sex-for-Marks: CPC speaks on remand of OAU lecturer, charges VC on sexual harassment - Daily Post Nigeria</title><link>http://dailypost.ng/2018/11/23/sex-marks-cpc-speaks-remand-oau-lecturer-charges-vc-sexual-harassment/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CBMiZWh0dHA6Ly9kYWlseXBvc3QubmcvMjAxOC8xMS8yMy9zZXgtbWFya3MtY3BjLXNwZWFrcy1yZW1hbmQtb2F1LWxlY3R1cmVyLWNoYXJnZXMtdmMtc2V4dWFsLWhhcmFzc21lbnQv0gGtAWh0dHBzOi8vZGFpbHlwb3N0LW5nLmNkbi5hbXBwcm9qZWN0Lm9yZy92L2RhaWx5cG9zdC5uZy8yMDE4LzExLzIzL3NleC1tYXJrcy1jcGMtc3BlYWtzLXJlbWFuZC1vYXUtbGVjdHVyZXItY2hhcmdlcy12Yy1zZXh1YWwtaGFyYXNzbWVudC9hbXAvP2FtcF9qc192PTAuMSN3ZWJ2aWV3PTEmY2FwPXN3aXBl</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://dailypost.ng/2018/11/23/sex-marks-cpc-speaks-remand-oau-lecturer-charges-vc-sexual-harassment/" target="_blank"&gt;Sex-for-Marks: CPC speaks on remand of OAU lecturer, charges VC on sexual harassment&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Daily Post Nigeria&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Consumer Protection Council (CPC) has commended the on-going prosecution of the dismissed lecturer of the Obafemi Awolowo University (OAU), ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://dailypost.ng">Daily Post Nigeria</source></item><item><title>Huawei CFO accused of fraud by US authorities - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/118d3154-fa56-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMbK1Ww8Fj4I01QZoskutpkqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gw0tp6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 01:18:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/118d3154-fa56-11e8-8b7c-6fa24bd5409c" target="_blank"&gt;Huawei CFO accused of fraud by US authorities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;US authorities are seeking the extradition of Huawei’s chief financial officer on an allegation of fraud, claiming that Meng Wanzhou lied to American banks about the relationship between the Chinese telecoms group and a company called Skycom in order to circumvent sanctions on Iran. The details of the US case against Ms Meng — the daughter of Ren Zhengfei, founder of Huawei — were laid out during a bail hearing on Friday in a court in Vancouver, where she was arrested last weekend while in transit from Hong Kong to Mexico. The hearing was held over until Monday after a day-long tussle betwe...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Indian court remands British businessman accused in AgustaWestland 'copter deal - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-agustawestland/indian-court-remands-british-businessman-accused-in-agustawestland-copter-deal-idUSKBN1O41LG</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEA03Gm_E2MNOk1GvTPIA8nwqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 12:57:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-india-agustawestland/indian-court-remands-british-businessman-accused-in-agustawestland-copter-deal-idUSKBN1O41LG" target="_blank"&gt;Indian court remands British businessman accused in AgustaWestland 'copter deal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Indian court on Wednesday remanded to custody a British businessman accused of paying bribes to Indian officials to win a helicopter deal for Anglo-Italian firm AgustaWestland, following a rare extradition. The case threatens strong repercussions for India's opposition Congress party, as Prime Minister Narendra Modi's ruling party called the extradition of Christian Michel a victory in its fight against graft. "Who knows what secrets will tumble out once he starts talking?" Modi said at a rally in western Rajasthan which is electing a new state assembly. Modi is seeking to embarrass Cong...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Syrian aid worker who swam refugees to safety freed from Greek jail - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/syrian-aid-worker-sarah-mardini-refugees-freed-greece</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK5MDkW_3v0vCF8aeHTvRGMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:08:54 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/05/syrian-aid-worker-sarah-mardini-refugees-freed-greece" target="_blank"&gt;Syrian aid worker who swam refugees to safety freed from Greek jail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;After 107 days of incarceration, Sarah Mardini – the Syrian human rights worker who saved 18 refugees in 2015 by swimming their waterlogged dinghy to the shores of Lesbos with her Olympian sister – has been freed from Greece’s toughest jail. The 23-year-old was released late on Wednesday from the high-security Koryallos prison in Athens, where she was being held in pre-trial detention on charges of people-smuggling. She was allowed to walk free after her lawyers posted €5,000 (£4,450) in bail. Related: Arrest of Syrian 'hero swimmer' puts Lesbos refugees back in spotlight Sean Binder, a 24-...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Amnesty International calls for Thailand to release Australian refugee footballer - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/amnesty-international-calls-for-release-australian-refugee/10582628</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMrE3HdcbihtlNqGNJkxwxMqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 08:44:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-04/amnesty-international-calls-for-release-australian-refugee/10582628" target="_blank"&gt;Amnesty International calls for Thailand to release Australian refugee footballer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amnesty International Australia has called for the release of a Melbourne-based refugee and football player from a detention centre in Thailand, after he was detained at the request of Bahrain. Hakeem Ali AlAraibi — a Bahraini national — was detained at Bangkok Airport a week ago and remains in custody despite being cleared to return home after the Red Notice used to detain him was lifted. While Thai officials said on Monday he may be released on Tuesday, documents obtained by rights groups showed Mr AlAraibi would be remanded for 12 more days. Bahraini officials have formally requested tha...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Nissan panel puts off selection of nominee to succeed Ghosn: source - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nissan-ghosn/japanese-prosecutors-to-arrest-ghosn-on-fresh-claim-prolonging-custody-sankei-idUSKBN1O301S</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMLSHn2faQFlb1ZZtvtPwFwqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 03:46:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nissan-ghosn/japanese-prosecutors-to-arrest-ghosn-on-fresh-claim-prolonging-custody-sankei-idUSKBN1O301S" target="_blank"&gt;Nissan panel puts off selection of nominee to succeed Ghosn: source&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Nissan Motor Co (7201.T: Quote, Profile, Research, Stock Buzz) panel on Tuesday failed to nominate a successor to Carlos Ghosn as chairman in the wake of his arrest and dismissal for alleged financial misconduct last month, a source familiar with the situation told Reuters. Ghosn could remain in detention until the end of the year as Tokyo prosecutors plan to rearrest him on a fresh claim of understating his income, the Sankei newspaper has reported. Nissan has tasked a three-member panel of external directors with the selection of a new chairman. The panel includes Masakazu Toyoda - a fo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Four Catalan leaders facing trial in Spain go on hunger strike - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/catalan-leaders-facing-trial-spain-hunger-strike</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECC364cOz6LN1NxdZERsqIgqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDZ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 11:51:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/catalan-leaders-facing-trial-spain-hunger-strike" target="_blank"&gt;Four Catalan leaders facing trial in Spain go on hunger strike&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four of the Catalan leaders facing trial over last year’s failed push for regional independence have gone on a hunger strike, claiming they are being treated unfairly by the Spanish justice system. On Saturday, JordiSànchez, the former head of the powerful grassroots group Catalan National Assembly, and Jordi Turull, a former Catalan government spokesman, announced they were embarking on the strike at Lledoners prison. The pair accuse Spain’s constitutional court of deliberately blocking their numerous appeals to prevent their cases progressing to the European court of human rights. “We ask...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Bourke Street 'trolley man' in custody after alleged burglary - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/bourke-street-trolley-man-michael-rogers-in-custody/10573260</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDopo6yg9amzdnuHwJlsluEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 08:09:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-30/bourke-street-trolley-man-michael-rogers-in-custody/10573260" target="_blank"&gt;Bourke Street 'trolley man' in custody after alleged burglary&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Melbourne man referred to as "trolley man" after his attempt to help police in this month's Bourke Street terrorist attack is now in custody. Police say Michael Rogers has been charged and detained over an alleged burglary in East Melbourne two days ago. The 46-year-old has been charged with burglary offences and theft. An online fundraising campaign raised more than $150,000 for Mr Rogers after he won widespread praise for attempting to fend off Islamic-State inspired terrorist Hassan Khalif Shire Ali by ramming him with a shopping trolley in Bourke Street. He was remanded in custody and...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Erdogan extends crackdown despite plaudits over Khashoggi response - Financial Times</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/e55681a6-f2fa-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENTfJhxQj7lo5gag7-qESDUqFwgEKg8IACoHCAow-4fWBzD4z0gwwtp6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/e55681a6-f2fa-11e8-ae55-df4bf40f9d0d" target="_blank"&gt;Erdogan extends crackdown despite plaudits over Khashoggi response&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;When police boarded Osman Kavala’s flight and summoned him to the front of the plane, he assumed that he had dropped his ID card. But the Turkish businessman and philanthropist was taken to a police station, then to jail. More than one year on, he remains behind bars, waiting for an indictment that details the allegations against him. “It seems quite unbelievable that he has been deprived of his freedom for so long,” said his wife, Ayse Bugra Kavala. Recep Tayyip Erdogan, the Turkish president, has won international plaudits for his dogged pursuit of the case of Jamal Khashoggi — the Saudi ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.ft.com">Financial Times</source></item><item><title>Japan court OKs extending custody of ex-Nissan chairman - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/e97401b0d26b43d1973f89191990baad</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEB3dHbI_nK_qlOA6IYYLLG4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 13:41:38 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/e97401b0d26b43d1973f89191990baad" target="_blank"&gt;Japan court OKs extending custody of ex-Nissan chairman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A Japanese court on Friday approved a 10-day extension of the detention of former Nissan chairman Carlos Ghosn. The Tokyo District Court said it approved a request from prosecutors to keep Ghosn until Dec. 10 for a further investigation of his suspected financial irregularities. Ghosn, 64, was arrested Nov. 19 by Tokyo prosecutors on suspicion he falsified financial statements and underreported his income and benefits. His first 10 days in custody expires at the end of Friday. The court said it also approved a 10-day detention extension for another former Nissan executive, Greg...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>US Marshal killed outside Tucson house, suspect detained - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/7d7210715a864d9fa083b3474ac18257</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHhmvRjiHl8MLVFk055EHV4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwu4lR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 21:19:59 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/7d7210715a864d9fa083b3474ac18257" target="_blank"&gt;US Marshal killed outside Tucson house, suspect detained&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — A deputy U.S. marshal serving a fugitive arrest warrant against a man accused of stalking a female police sergeant after she seized a handgun and ammunition from him last year has been shot and killed outside a Tucson house. The suspect had recently visited Tucson Police Department, where he confronted the sergeant in person, then filed an online complaint about last year's seizure of his weapon, demanding that she and other officers be "arrested" and warning against the possibility of a "shootout at the OK Corral," authorities said. Chase White, 41, was shot while serving th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>The man on a mission to get New Zealand's Māori out of prison - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/30/the-man-on-a-mission-to-get-new-zealands-maori-out-of-prison</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMLA3KMiWQ8CtBuV1iya1igqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 23:40:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/30/the-man-on-a-mission-to-get-new-zealands-maori-out-of-prison" target="_blank"&gt;The man on a mission to get New Zealand's Māori out of prison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kelvin Davis describes himself as a member of “the most incarcerated tribe in the world”. The former teacher grew up in New Zealand’s deprived Northland region and has seen childhood friends, schoolmates and relatives locked away. Appointed the country’s corrections minister in 2017, he is now on a mission to empty the nation’s prisons of Māori inmates. And after just eight months with Davis in the job, the overall prison population has dropped by 8%. New Zealand has one of the highest incarceration rates in the OECD, and in March the country’s prison population hit a record 10,820 people –...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Japanese prosecutors vow to hold Ghosn as long as needed - The Associated Press</title><link>https://www.apnews.com/b740b935c9ed40d1b3905b62f12e9f5e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBq0yvPaaNIYGuNDNoxQUTgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwm4pR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 13:03:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.apnews.com/b740b935c9ed40d1b3905b62f12e9f5e" target="_blank"&gt;Japanese prosecutors vow to hold Ghosn as long as needed&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Japanese prosecutors said Thursday they will detain former Nissan chairman Carlos Ghosn for as long as is needed to finish their investigation into suspicions of financial irregularities, as the Renault-Nissan-Mitsubishi alliance reaffirmed its partnership. Shin Kukimoto, deputy chief prosecutor for the Tokyo District Public Prosecutors' Office, defended its handling of Ghosn, who was arrested on Nov. 19 along with another Nissan executive, Greg Kelly. "We are not detaining (Ghosn) for an unnecessarily long time," Kukimoto told reporters. "We only take necessary steps as needed...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Austria arrests suspected spy after court ruling - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-austria-spy-arrest/austria-arrests-suspected-spy-after-court-ruling-idUSKCN1NZ2KR</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECmTAVeKpVqzA2UgJpXiov8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 20:35:35 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-austria-spy-arrest/austria-arrests-suspected-spy-after-court-ruling-idUSKCN1NZ2KR" target="_blank"&gt;Austria arrests suspected spy after court ruling&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An Austrian army colonel suspected of spying for Russia for 26 years was arrested on Friday after a court reversed a decision that there was no need to detain him pending trial. The case is embarrassing for Austria, which has some of the closest relations with Russia in the European Union. Moscow denies any involvement in the case, which was made public this month and was uncovered after a tip-off from Britain. "He has already been arrested," the prosecutors' office in Salzburg, where the recently retired colonel lives, said in a statement. A court in Salzburg initially dismissed the prosec...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Austere Japan detention quarters contrast with Ghosn's globe-trotting lifestyle - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nissan-ghosn-detention/austere-japan-detention-quarters-contrast-with-ghosns-globe-trotting-lifestyle-idUSKCN1NR1CY</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELKiDJSHLFcPOsMW726UhkgqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMJSCDg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 12:37:01 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-nissan-ghosn-detention/austere-japan-detention-quarters-contrast-with-ghosns-globe-trotting-lifestyle-idUSKCN1NR1CY" target="_blank"&gt;Austere Japan detention quarters contrast with Ghosn's globe-trotting lifestyle&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese prosecutors have confirmed that Nissan's arrested chairman, Carlos Ghosn, is being held in the spartan Tokyo Detention Center, its many rules and restrictions making for a stark contrast with his comfortable, globe-trotting lifestyle. Ghosn is most probably being held in a small 4.8-sq-m (52-sq-ft) room with a toilet at one end, say experts familiar with the facility. Many of its rooms have traditional straw tatami mats and a futon to sleep in. Others are Western-style with beds, said a Reuters reporter who has visited there. Detainees are allowed to shower on set days, although no...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Jeremy Brabrooke: Murderer on run from open prison spotted in church - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/jeremy-brabrooke-murderer-church-spotted-hampshire-prison-hmp-ford-sussex-police-a8641521.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFiaiXqx1zG0E2zfaalLnboqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 16:35:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/jeremy-brabrooke-murderer-church-spotted-hampshire-prison-hmp-ford-sussex-police-a8641521.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jeremy Brabrooke: Murderer on run from open prison spotted in church&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A convicted murderer who has been on the run from an open prison for more than five days has been spotted at a church in Hampshire. Jeremy Brabrooke has been on the run since he absconded from Ford Prison in West Sussex last Wednesday. Sussex Police have now released security camera footage of the last time he was sighted later that day on a visit St Faith’s Church in Havant, Hampshire. Read more - Murderer on run from prison in Northern Ireland - Prisoner hung himself after two days in jail - Prisoner back in custody after being accidentally released from jail The 56-year-old was sentenced...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Fifa ethics judge arrested in Malaysia on suspicion of corruption - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/nov/21/fifa-ethics-committee-judge-arrested-suspicion-corruption</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEq-oQrdTLuIOEeyT8zjeAMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTCtvRU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/football/2018/nov/21/fifa-ethics-committee-judge-arrested-suspicion-corruption" target="_blank"&gt;Fifa ethics judge arrested in Malaysia on suspicion of corruption&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Fifa ethics committee judge was arrested in Malaysia on suspicion of corruption and resigned on Wednesday as director of an arbitration service. Sundra Rajoo’s lawyer told the Associated Press his client had been detained by the Malaysian anti-corruption commission after returning from Fifa business in Zurich the previous evening. The lawyer, Cheow Wee, said a court refused a request for a seven-day remand order against Rajoo, and that he was later released unconditionally. “The judge agreed with our position that he [Rajoo] has diplomatic immunity and privileges,” Cheow said. “He cannot ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Prisoner who killed himself 'told staff voices were telling him to do so' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/17/prisoner-who-killed-himself-told-staff-voices-were-telling-him-to-do-so</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEADrsSJunZ80tgT8MjaP1_0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 18:03:19 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/17/prisoner-who-killed-himself-told-staff-voices-were-telling-him-to-do-so" target="_blank"&gt;Prisoner who killed himself 'told staff voices were telling him to do so'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mentally ill prisoner who killed himself after spending two days in jail had told staff he was finding it hard to ignore the “voices” telling him to do so, a report has found. Michael Berry, 27, was deemed to be “high risk” when he was remanded at HMP Bedford in March 2017, appearing “distressed, hopeless, teary and prone to acting impulsively”, the report notes. Berry was in a “fragile” state and detoxifying from heroin and crack cocaine use. The report, by the prisons and probation ombudsman, says an officer who completed Berry’s initial reception screening told the investigator he did ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Bourke St killer was on bail for driving offences - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-16/bourke-street-attacker-had-bail-extended/10504532</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEK_zDdHpNw7-Oy1w_mveKTEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 01:48:24 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-16/bourke-street-attacker-had-bail-extended/10504532" target="_blank"&gt;Bourke St killer was on bail for driving offences&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Nino Bucci, ABC Investigations Bourke Street attacker Hassan Ali had his bail extended only weeks before the deadly rampage, despite a long history of failing to appear in court. Hassan Ali, 30, was charged on three separate occasions with minor driving offences dating back to February last year, and failed to attend court to answer any of them, law enforcement sources confirmed. His bail was forfeited for the first time in August last year, and then again six months later, before he was served with a warrant in October that extended his bail for another three months, according to court ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Russian accused of online fraud and wanted by the United States arrested in Bulgaria - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/10/world/russian-hacker-wanted-by-the-united-states-arrested-in-bulgaria/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDdXfJyrvfNm3q-XGbF2DQsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 07:03:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/10/world/russian-hacker-wanted-by-the-united-states-arrested-in-bulgaria/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Russian accused of online fraud and wanted by the United States arrested in Bulgaria&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Russian citizen accused of online fraud involving millions of dollars has been arrested in Varna, Bulgaria, on a warrant issued by the United States and is awaiting extradition proceedings, according to a statement by the Varna District Court issued Thursday. A US Justice Department spokeswoman declined to comment on the arrest. "As a matter of longstanding policy, the US Department of Justice generally does not comment on extradition-related matters until a defendant is in the United States. There is nothing public at this time," US Justice Department spokeswoman Nicole Navas Oxman told ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>'McMafia' case: woman who spent £16m at Harrods granted bail - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/nov/08/mcmafia-case-woman-spent-16m-harrods-granted-bail</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEL5S7-9zG1xCYfE0pDDPI4MqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 18:02:13 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/nov/08/mcmafia-case-woman-spent-16m-harrods-granted-bail" target="_blank"&gt;'McMafia' case: woman who spent £16m at Harrods granted bail&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A woman who spent £16m in Harrods and is subject to the UK’s first McMafia-style “dirty money” investigation has been released on bail after nine days in custody following a request for her extradition to Azerbaijan. Zamira Hajiyeva was arrested by the Metropolitan police last week at the request of authorities in Azerbaijan, where she is wanted on two charges of embezzlement. Her husband, Jahangir Hajiyev, was jailed in 2016 for defrauding Azerbaijan’s national bank out of up to 5bn manat (£2.2bn). Hajiyeva was released on bail on Thursday after a high court judge dismissed a request by th...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Canberra woman staged crime scene before making false rape claim to police - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-06/canberra-woman-admits-to-falsifying-rape-claim/10470888</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFpOV2i2nTSnG2z-pjba7-YqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 09:07:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-11-06/canberra-woman-admits-to-falsifying-rape-claim/10470888" target="_blank"&gt;Canberra woman staged crime scene before making false rape claim to police&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Elizabeth Byrne A Canberra woman who accused her former partner of rape nearly five years ago has admitted she made up the claim, which saw him spend months behind bars. As a five-day hearing into the matter began in the ACT Magistrates Court, Sarah-Jane Parkinson, 28, unexpectedly pleaded guilty to making the false claim in March 2014 and even staging a crime scene. Parkinson, a former police worker, also pleaded guilty to possessing a prohibited weapon after she was found with capsicum spray. The original allegations were made against Parkinson's former partner while he was a prison of...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Australia police say Melbourne attacker was known to authorities - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/australia-police-melbourne-attacker-authorities-181110063533043.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELf0h4uW0UCoIU75NVvpO3YqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 06:58:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/11/australia-police-melbourne-attacker-authorities-181110063533043.html" target="_blank"&gt;Australia police say Melbourne attacker was known to authorities&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australian police said on Saturday a man who fatally stabbed a person and injured two others in central Melbourne "held radicalised views" that prompted him to carry out the attack. The perpetrator, Hassain Khalif Shire Ali, 30, had his passport canceled in 2015 after it was learned he planned to travel to Syria, police said. The attack occurred on Friday when Shire Ali got out of a pickup vehicle, which he then set on fire, and stabbed three men, one of whom died at the scene. The attack on Bourke Street horrified hundreds of onlookers during the afternoon rush hour in Australia's second-b...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Spain prosecutor seeks long jail terms for Catalan pro-independence leaders - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spain-politics-catalonia/spain-prosecutor-seeks-long-jail-terms-for-catalan-pro-independence-leaders-idUSKCN1N712K</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDXvoxN3NuEK8mnKgW2dH3AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 11:52:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spain-politics-catalonia/spain-prosecutor-seeks-long-jail-terms-for-catalan-pro-independence-leaders-idUSKCN1N712K" target="_blank"&gt;Spain prosecutor seeks long jail terms for Catalan pro-independence leaders&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spain's public prosecutor on Friday sought jail terms of up to 25 years for nine leaders of Catalonia's independence movement, filing charges of rebellion and misuse of public funds over a failed secession bid that they spearheaded last year. But the State Attorney - a separate government-appointed body also prosecuting in the case - said rebellion charges should be dropped in favor of the lesser offence of sedition and that it would seek maximum sentences of 12 years. Madrid imposed direct rule on the wealthy northeastern region in October 2017 after it declared its independence on the bas...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Government failing in duty of care to prisoners as jail sentences lead to poorer health, MPs warn - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/prisoners-health-illness-jail-social-care-committee-mps-report-westminster-a8610761.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBVW2YHwXm6PIopXJZFK-hoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:02:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/prisoners-health-illness-jail-social-care-committee-mps-report-westminster-a8610761.html" target="_blank"&gt;Government failing in duty of care to prisoners as jail sentences lead to poorer health, MPs warn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government is failing in its duty of care towards prisoners, as going to jail has become not only a deprivation of liberty but a “sentence to poorer health or healthcare”, MPs have warned. A new report by a parliamentary committee found increasingly “unsafe and unsanitary” prison conditions following budget reductions and a loss of prison officers were limiting prisoners’ access to healthcare and their ability to lead healthy lives. The Health and Social Care Select Committee warned record levels of violence and self-harm, a poor quality diet and limited time out of cells due to staff s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>Pipe bomb suspect Cesar Sayoc planned 'terrorist attack' since July, DOJ says - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/31/politics/pipe-bomb-suspect-doj-letter/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEO5Agg5wIArAw_20SKGtuLoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMJrUpgU</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 05:40:47 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/31/politics/pipe-bomb-suspect-doj-letter/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Pipe bomb suspect Cesar Sayoc planned 'terrorist attack' since July, DOJ says&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man accused of sending pipe bombs to prominent Democrats had been planning to send the explosive devices for months, the Department of Justice says. In a letter sent Tuesday, Geoffrey S. Berman, the US Attorney for the Southern District of New York, said the FBI searched suspect Cesar Sayoc's laptop and found documents containing the victims' addresses and return labels similar to those used on the intercepted packages. "Metadata from the electronic devices indicates that the defendant started planning the attack as early as July 2018," Berman wrote in a letter to Magistrate Judge Edwin G...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Defense: Protester intended radioactive substance for self - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/61077f6f3a3e4cffb8220c7e48ddc63d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHoZPuhdIE6id7HmPQYW1YgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9Cgwv7tQ</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 23:14:09 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/61077f6f3a3e4cffb8220c7e48ddc63d" target="_blank"&gt;Defense: Protester intended radioactive substance for self&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — An attorney for a Wisconsin political activist accused of trying to buy a lethal dose of a radioactive substance online said Monday his client intended to use it to kill himself because he has cancer. Federal public defender Joseph Bugni argued that a criminal complaint filed last week against Jeremy Ryan, 30, of the Town of Madison, does not state specifically what material was being sought, so prosecutors had failed to show probable cause. But U.S. Magistrate Judge Stephen Crocker found probable cause that Ryan had committed a federal offense and ordered him to remain...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>Young black Portuguese men take police brutality case to court - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/young-black-portuguese-men-police-brutality-case-court-181026215738680.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJeXQsRgtOBHj5y2aqD4q34qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw87UI</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 08:25:36 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/young-black-portuguese-men-police-brutality-case-court-181026215738680.html" target="_blank"&gt;Young black Portuguese men take police brutality case to court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eighteen months ago, they were defendants, accused of storming a police station. But since that case was overturned last year, Flavio Almada, Celso Lopes, Rui Moniz, Miguel Reis, Paulo Veiga and Bruno Lopes have been testifying not as the accused, but as victims in an unprecedented trial that has put 17 officers of the PSP - Portugal's public police force - in the dock. The new case, currently being heard in court, rejects the version of events previously offered by the police officers, and charges them with physical assault, aggravated kidnapping, inhumane treatment and inciting racially-m...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Man arrested for trying to steal Magna Carta - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/26/police-arrest-man-for-trying-to-steal-magna-carta-salisbury-wi</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH02kMUKdfymGeCXFqeJRZ8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 10:27:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/26/police-arrest-man-for-trying-to-steal-magna-carta-salisbury-wi" target="_blank"&gt;Man arrested for trying to steal Magna Carta&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man has been arrested on suspicion of trying to steal a Magna Carta from Salisbury Cathedral. Wiltshire police said the 45-year-old was arrested on Thursday after alarms were triggered by an attempt to smash the glass box in which the artefact was displayed. A man matching witnesses’ descriptions was arrested on suspicion of attempted theft, possession of an offensive weapon and criminal damage. Police said he remained in custody. The document was not damaged in the incident. Magna Carta, one of the most significant documents in British history, is a peace treaty that was sealed by King J...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Madagascar pre-trial detainees face 'life-threatening conditions' - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/madagascar-pre-trial-detainees-face-life-threatening-conditions-181022155950931.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECxyX2rn1ooqiyjrt0Fj4SkqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 07:23:39 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/10/madagascar-pre-trial-detainees-face-life-threatening-conditions-181022155950931.html" target="_blank"&gt;Madagascar pre-trial detainees face 'life-threatening conditions'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 52 people died in Madagascar's prisons last year while awaiting trial due to "appalling prison conditions", according to Amnesty International. In a report published on Tuesday, the global rights group also said that thousands of people who have not been found guilty of any crime were subject to "life-threatening prison conditions", including severe overcrowding and poor hygiene as well as lack of food and medical care. The main causes of death was respiratory problems and cardiovascular diseases, Amnesty said, citing prison authorities. The report was based on visits to nine pris...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>'Lady in the lake' murder case referred to court of appeal - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/26/lady-in-the-lake-accused-could-receive-posthumous-pardon</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBCw2HQTxJi5SITndGtEE3sqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:14:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/26/lady-in-the-lake-accused-could-receive-posthumous-pardon" target="_blank"&gt;'Lady in the lake' murder case referred to court of appeal&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man who hanged himself in prison after being convicted of murdering his wife and dumping her body in Coniston Water in the Lake District could receive a posthumous pardon after the case was referred to the court of appeal. The Criminal Cases Review Commission (CCRC) has recommended that judges review the trial of Gordon Park, who was found guilty in 2005 of killing his wife, Carol, a mother of three. It was one of the UK’s longest murder inquiries. Carol Park had gone missing in the summer of 1976 from the family home near Barrow-in-Furness, Cumbria. Her body, trussed and weighted down, w...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Peruvian judge frees opposition leader Fujimori from prison - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-peru-fujimori-keiko/peruvian-judge-frees-opposition-leader-fujimori-from-prison-idUSKCN1MS2DM</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiECqL_wxs3HpsPyVI1r4FcqoqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 16:06:25 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-peru-fujimori-keiko/peruvian-judge-frees-opposition-leader-fujimori-from-prison-idUSKCN1MS2DM" target="_blank"&gt;Peruvian judge frees opposition leader Fujimori from prison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Peruvian judge late on Wednesday freed conservative opposition leader Keiko Fujimori from jail where she spent the past week pending charges in a money laundering probe. Judge Cesar Sahuanay said there was no legal basis for jailing Fujimori and 19 others before trial in connection with alleged payments from Odebrecht, a Brazilian construction group at the center of the region's biggest ever graft probe. Fujimori, the daughter of former autocrat Alberto Fujimori, called her arrest political persecution. She denied prosecutors' allegations that she was the head of a criminal group within h...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>VIP paedophile accuser 'Nick' appears in court over claims he lied to the police - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/20/vip-paedophile-accuser-nick-appears-court-claims-lied-police/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEBN6Ag0T7G9oV2S5rMXsKeEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 15:29:41 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/20/vip-paedophile-accuser-nick-appears-court-claims-lied-police/" target="_blank"&gt;VIP paedophile accuser 'Nick' appears in court over claims he lied to the police&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man known as "Nick" whose allegations sparked the VIP sex abuse probe has appeared in court charged with lying to police and fraudulently receiving £22,000 in compensation. The 50-year-old - whose real identity cannot be revealed for legal reasons - is accused of 12 counts of perverting the course of justice and one count of fraud. He appeared at Newcastle Magistrates' Court on Saturday morning. His claims about the existence of a VIP Westminster paedophile ring led to Operation Midland, which saw the homes of figures including Lord Bramall and the late ex-home secretary Lord Brittan ra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>David Gauke: priority must be protecting women when placing transgender prisoners - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/oct/19/david-gauke-priority-should-be-protecting-women-when-placing-transgender-inmates-karen-white</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENtVvIrnKLoIIynmPWdYjy8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 13:30:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/oct/19/david-gauke-priority-should-be-protecting-women-when-placing-transgender-inmates-karen-white" target="_blank"&gt;David Gauke: priority must be protecting women when placing transgender prisoners&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protecting women in custody should be prioritised when placing transgender prisoners, the justice secretary has told the Guardian, criticising the safeguarding failures that led to Karen White being transferred to a female prison. David Gauke said cases of prisoners presenting themselves as transgender needed to be handled sensitively but added that White should never have been put in a women’s jail. He insisted the case was not the result of wider systemic failings. White, a convicted paedophile, entered the UK prison system as transgender on remand for grievous bodily harm, burglary, mult...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Man whose allegations sparked Westminster abuse inquiry in court - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/20/man-whose-allegations-sparked-westminster-abuse-inquiry-charged</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKfjOfezzSrBfK0A63SGvwMqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 12:26:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/20/man-whose-allegations-sparked-westminster-abuse-inquiry-charged" target="_blank"&gt;Man whose allegations sparked Westminster abuse inquiry in court&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man known as “Nick” whose allegations sparked the Westminster VIP sex abuse inquiry has appeared in court charged with lying to police and fraudulently receiving £22,000 in compensation. The 50-year-old – whose real identity cannot be revealed for legal reasons – is accused of 12 counts of perverting the course of justice and one count of fraud. He appeared at Newcastle magistrates court on Saturday morning. His claims about the existence of a paedophile ring in Westminster led to Operation Midland, during which the homes of figures including Lord Bramall and the late home secretary Lor...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Myanmar newspaper journalists held after handing themselves in to police - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-journalists/myanmar-newspaper-journalists-held-after-handing-themselves-in-to-police-idUSKCN1MK1N6</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJVVlsDrpqbCLtWVg_mDprYqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 09:45:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-myanmar-journalists/myanmar-newspaper-journalists-held-after-handing-themselves-in-to-police-idUSKCN1MK1N6" target="_blank"&gt;Myanmar newspaper journalists held after handing themselves in to police&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three senior journalists at Myanmar's largest private newspaper were remanded in custody after handing themselves in to police on Wednesday, facing accusations of causing "fear or alarm" following a complaint from the Yangon regional government. One of the men, Eleven Media Group's editor-in-chief Kyaw Zaw Linn, had earlier told Reuters that police raided the paper's offices at about 7 p.m. on Tuesday, but he and two other journalists sought by the authorities were not there. "The office informed me that they came because of an article in the journal," he said, shortly before entering a pol...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Fugitive Peruvian judge captured in Spain - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-peru-corruption/fugitive-peruvian-judge-captured-in-spain-idUSKCN1MT2DF</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELqTWgf78WnJ30907K4T_5AqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 22:35:34 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-peru-corruption/fugitive-peruvian-judge-captured-in-spain-idUSKCN1MT2DF" target="_blank"&gt;Fugitive Peruvian judge captured in Spain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fugitive Peruvian Supreme Court justice accused of leading a criminal group that infiltrated the country's judicial system was captured in Madrid on Friday and held on remand by Spanish authorities. Judge Cesar Hinostroza's escape to Spain through normal border exit points has embarrassed Peruvian President Martin Vizcarra, who has made fighting graft the top priority in his seven-month-old government. "He's now with Spanish police, foreign affairs agents and Peru's police attache," Vizcarra said on local broadcaster RPP. Hinostroza was taken to Spain's High Court, where a judge opened ex...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Suspect Says He Didn't Mean to Kill Bulgarian Journalist - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/suspect-says-he-didn-t-mean-to-kill-bulgarian-journalist/4620706.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEPJAznWaVNfNm5I5ELBDKnsqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw-pwi</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 16:30:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/suspect-says-he-didn-t-mean-to-kill-bulgarian-journalist/4620706.html" target="_blank"&gt;Suspect Says He Didn't Mean to Kill Bulgarian Journalist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 21-year-old suspect in the rape and slaying of a Bulgarian television journalist said Friday that he killed Viktoria Marinova, but didn't mean to. Handcuffed and surrounded by police officers, Severin Krassimirov spoke to reporters inside a courtroom where he appeared for a custody hearing. “I regret it so much. I cannot believe I did it,” Krassimirov said of Marinova's killing. The young man's defense lawyer had asked for the hearing to be held behind closed doors, but the court in Ruse denied the request. The lawyer joined Krassimirov after he had spoken to the media and told him to rem...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>New York man charged with threatening senators over Kavanaugh vote - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/politics/brett-kavanaugh-senators-threat/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMrzS_DiTh3FBFXhujpw9PUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 23:39:45 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/politics/brett-kavanaugh-senators-threat/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;New York man charged with threatening senators over Kavanaugh vote&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A New York man was arrested and charged Friday by federal prosecutors with threatening to assault and murder two US senators in retaliation for their support of Justice Brett Kavanaugh's confirmation to the Supreme Court. The man, Ronald DeRisi, left more than 10 threatening and "expletive-laced" voicemails for the two senators beginning September 27, according to the complaint unsealed Friday by prosecutors in the US Attorney's Office for the Eastern District of New York. In one message, DeRisi said he had a "present" for one of the senators, the complaint says, adding: "It's a nine millim...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Bulgaria indicts suspect accused of the rape and murder of a television journalist - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/19/bulgaria-indicts-suspect-accused-rape-murder-television-journalist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHoLPRfiRroWMKp-_XjP3qcqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 13:13:57 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/19/bulgaria-indicts-suspect-accused-rape-murder-television-journalist/" target="_blank"&gt;Bulgaria indicts suspect accused of the rape and murder of a television journalist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bulgarian prosecutors on Friday indicted a man accused of the rape and murder of a television journalist and the court hearing the case ordered him to remain in custody pending trial. Severin Krasimirov, 20, was handcuffed and under heavy guard when he appeared before the regional court in the northern town of Ruse. He told journalists that he had approached journalist Viktoria Marinova and hit her in the face. "Yes, I am guilty. I am sorry, I can't believe I did this," he said. Prosecutors called for him to be tried for Marinova's rape and murder. According to media reports, he had already...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>'Saddest case I have investigated': Ombudsman's scathing report on incarcerated woman - ABC News</title><link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-16/victorian-ombudsman-saddest-case-woman-with-disability-prison/10382072</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENcsKiOD5ox606vp3FOtrnEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 05:32:53 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-10-16/victorian-ombudsman-saddest-case-woman-with-disability-prison/10382072" target="_blank"&gt;'Saddest case I have investigated': Ombudsman's scathing report on incarcerated woman&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Dan Harrison A woman with a development disorder screamed with distress and lost almost half her body weight while she was locked up in solitary confinement for up to 23 hours a day, the ombudsman has found. The woman, who was given the pseudonym Rebecca to protect her and her family's privacy, was held in a Victorian prison for 18 months because there was no suitable alternative accommodation for her. Ms Glass found the woman's treatment breached Victoria's human rights laws and international standards on the rights of people with disabilities. "Rebecca remained in prison simply because...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Transgender prisoner born a male who sexually assaulted female inmates after being jailed for rape is sentenced to life - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/11/transgender-prisoner-born-male-sexually-assaulted-female-inmates/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFAQrS2UV4dAU1gsjG9zPAYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 12:07:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/11/transgender-prisoner-born-male-sexually-assaulted-female-inmates/" target="_blank"&gt;Transgender prisoner born a male who sexually assaulted female inmates after being jailed for rape is sentenced to life&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A "predatory and highly manipulative" rapist and paedophile has been jailed for life after a court heard how she used a transgender persona to attack female prisoners. Karen White, 52, who was born a man, used the guise of wanting to change sex to convince the authorities to place her in a women’s prison where she sexually assaulted two female inmates. White carried out the attacks at New Hall women's prison in Wakefield, West Yorkshire, while being held on remand accused of a knife attack on a neighbour and raping two women. Leeds Crown Court heard how she used her "transgender persona" to...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Police apologise to family of man wrongly put in jail for the murder of his son - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/12/police-apologise-family-man-wrongly-put-jail-murder-son/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGLX0oudseX0rENygCGFm8oqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 10:52:07 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/12/police-apologise-family-man-wrongly-put-jail-murder-son/" target="_blank"&gt;Police apologise to family of man wrongly put in jail for the murder of his son&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police have apologised to the family of a man who was wrongly arrested for murdering his own son, but who died just days before seeing the real killer jailed. Freddie Stacey, 66, spent 16 weeks on remand in Durham jail in 2004 after being wrongly accused of beating his son, Scott Pritchard to death. The real killer, women's football coach, Karen Tunmore, 36, was finally brought to justice earlier this month when she admitted attacking Mr Pritchard with a baseball bat over a minor debt. Tragically Mr Stacey suffered a heart attack days before the case came to court and died before he was abl...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Immigration detention staff 'thought suicidal man had toothache' - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/11/immigration-detention-staff-foreign-national-held-prison-toothache</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN4WViO9iXpEyO4ZFeAaH30qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 10:48:43 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/11/immigration-detention-staff-foreign-national-held-prison-toothache" target="_blank"&gt;Immigration detention staff 'thought suicidal man had toothache'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An immigration detainee killed himself two days after staff determined in a three-minute meeting that his distress was down to toothache, despite him telling them he wanted to die after being held for nearly a year, a custody watchdog has said. The 28-year-old Polish national was remanded in prison custody on charges of assault and criminal damage, but due to his offending history was transferred to an immigration removal centre (IRC) – understood to be Harmondsworth – pending deportation. He became increasingly distressed as it was unclear to him why he had been detained for so long, the P...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Supreme Court Poised To Overturn Ninth Circuit Ruling Granting Bond Hearings To Criminal Aliens - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/wlf/2018/10/15/supreme-court-poised-to-overturn-ninth-circuit-ruling-granting-bond-hearings-to-criminal-aliens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiENNv5OctkCskapX5he_uTm4qFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/wlf/2018/10/15/supreme-court-poised-to-overturn-ninth-circuit-ruling-granting-bond-hearings-to-criminal-aliens/" target="_blank"&gt;Supreme Court Poised To Overturn Ninth Circuit Ruling Granting Bond Hearings To Criminal Aliens&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A summer day in front of the US Supreme Court Building in Washington, DC. The October 10 Supreme Court oral argument in Nielsen v. Preap demonstrated that the justices continue to be sharply, ideologically divided over the federal government’s authority to detain criminal aliens pending completion of removal proceedings. But contrary to some early post-argument commentary, the oral argument left little doubt about the likely outcome: Chief Justice Roberts, Justice Thomas, Justice Alito, Justice Gorsuch, and Justice Kavanaugh will vote to overturn the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Transgender prisoner who sexually assaulted inmates jailed for life - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/11/transgender-prisoner-who-sexually-assaulted-inmates-jailed-for-life</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHe_aa1dAsU9-G7mYLFd550qFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 11:52:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/11/transgender-prisoner-who-sexually-assaulted-inmates-jailed-for-life" target="_blank"&gt;Transgender prisoner who sexually assaulted inmates jailed for life&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A “predatory and controlling” rapist has been jailed for life after she attacked vulnerable women in female prisons. Karen White, 52, who was described as being a danger to women and children, admitted sexually assaulting women in a female prison and raping another two women outside jail. White was on remand for multiple rapes and other sexual offences against women when she transferred to New Hall prison in Wakefield. White, who is currently transitioning, was jailed for two counts of rape, two sexual assaults and one offence of wounding. The Ministry of Justice has since apologised for mo...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Boy, 16, charged with attempted murder and rape of girl, 10, in Devon - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/08/boy-16-charged-with-attempted-and-of-girl-10-in-devon</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEAvgbAqPPpMdpTzK2RBbq2AqFwgEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDJ4PsF</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 07:46:55 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/08/boy-16-charged-with-attempted-and-of-girl-10-in-devon" target="_blank"&gt;Boy, 16, charged with attempted murder and rape of girl, 10, in Devon&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 16-year-old boy has been charged with the attempted murder and rape of a 10-year-old girl in Exmouth, Devon, police have said. The boy appeared before Exeter youth court on Monday. The alleged attack took place on 4 October in the Marley Road area of the seaside town. He was remanded in detention and will appear before a district judge on Thursday. During the 10-minute hearing the boy spoke only to confirm he understood the court proceedings. Devon and Cornwall police have issued a statement warning that people should not identify the boy or the alleged victim on social media. The alleged...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Rwandan opposition party leader feared dead amid reports he escaped from prison - CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/08/africa/rwanda-opposition-leader-escaped-jail-feared-dead-intl/index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDjDUgLb0y95mSAZ_Mf6z0kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPvTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 18:48:03 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/08/africa/rwanda-opposition-leader-escaped-jail-feared-dead-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Rwandan opposition party leader feared dead amid reports he escaped from prison&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The jailed vice president of Rwanda's opposition FDU-Inkingi party escaped from prison on Sunday, according to the country's correctional service. Boniface Twagirimana was missing from a routine headcount at the prison Monday, local media reported, quoting a Rwanda Correctional Service spokesperson. The spokesperson said that Twagirimana and another prisoner had managed to escape by jumping over the complex's fence and said that an investigation had been launched. But members of the FDU -- an unregistered political party -- are calling "foul play" and fear that Twagirimana's life could be i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>Rapist vaults over dock and flees court after guilty verdict - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/04/rapist-flees-court-after-guilty-verdict-bradley-tout</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHMN_h3kOQzWRsx94inykzwqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 12:04:05 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/oct/04/rapist-flees-court-after-guilty-verdict-bradley-tout" target="_blank"&gt;Rapist vaults over dock and flees court after guilty verdict&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A rapist is on the run after leaping out of a courtroom dock moments after being found guilty of a sexual attack on a 16-year-old girl. Bradley Tout, 20, managed to evade private security staff as he fled from Worcester crown court at the end of his trial. He forced his way out of the courtroom and into the main atrium before bursting through double doors and on to the street. Addressing the jury after the escape on Wednesday, the judge, Nicolas Cartwright, said: “Well, I’ve never seen anything like that happen before.” Tout was jailed for seven and a half years in his absence on Thursday. ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Police in the dock for giving people the chance to spend Halloween in Fred West's cell - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/25/police-dock-giving-people-chance-spend-halloween-fred-wests/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEG2ORcwLC4JEn6iriPO0VQEqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 22:33:16 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/25/police-dock-giving-people-chance-spend-halloween-fred-wests/" target="_blank"&gt;Police in the dock for giving people the chance to spend Halloween in Fred West's cell&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A police force has been criticised for cashing in on serial killer Fred West’s notoriety by charging people to spend Hallowe’en in his former cell. West Midlands Police are promoting a ghost-hunting evening at the Steelhouse Lane cells in Birmingham, where West was housed before being transferred to HMP Winson Green in 1994. In its advertising, the force boasted the event provided a “unique opportunity” to spend the night at the notorious Victorian lock-up, adding: “These cells were occupied by none other than the original Peaky Blinders, Fred West and many more. Be there if you dare.” For ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Westminster crash suspect Salih Khater to face trial next year for alleged terror attack outside Parliament - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/westmnister-crash-trial-date-salih-khater-terror-attack-parliament-square-car-latest-date-a8559111.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIJr6CBQR5TJO095DCvcPBYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/westmnister-crash-trial-date-salih-khater-terror-attack-parliament-square-car-latest-date-a8559111.html" target="_blank"&gt;Westminster crash suspect Salih Khater to face trial next year for alleged terror attack outside Parliament&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man accused of attempting to launch a terror attack outside the Houses of Parliament is to go on trial next year. Salih Khater allegedly ploughed his silver Ford Fiesta into cyclists and pedestrians before swerving towards police officers and crashing into a security barrier last month. The 29-year-old appeared at the Old Bailey charged with two counts of attempted murder. - Read more Salih Khater appears in court over attempted murder outside Parliament The charges state he tried to kill people at the junction of Parliament Square and Abingdon Street, and police officers in Abingdon Stre...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>It’s no wonder prisons are in crisis. Inmates are humans, too - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/sep/25/prisons-crisis-inmates-humans-strikes-uk-us</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDBExWQAv5zhqGg-cFa9iSMqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 12:00:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/sep/25/prisons-crisis-inmates-humans-strikes-uk-us" target="_blank"&gt;It’s no wonder prisons are in crisis. Inmates are humans, too&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last couple of months have been a crucial time for the prison system. The mass walkout by prison officers in England and Wales a fortnight ago, which was quickly called off by the Prison Officers Association after talks with the prisons minister Rory Stewart, was just one cause for serious concern. Related: Government admits role in Birmingham prison failure Sparked by worries about conditions, including violence, the action came hard on the heels of a damning report from the prison inspectorate into the privately run Birmingham prison in August, which concluded that it was in “an appal...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Man at center of Nobel sex scandal remanded pending verdict - The Associated Press</title><link>https://apnews.com/97dfc31094db41389020bdff2d0b4664</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJJEYXzs6nyum4WKAFJ4fqUqGAgEKg8IACoHCAowhO7OATDh9CgwvaadAg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 11:58:31 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/97dfc31094db41389020bdff2d0b4664" target="_blank"&gt;Man at center of Nobel sex scandal remanded pending verdict&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Associated Press&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — The man at the center of a sex abuse and financial crimes scandal that is tarnishing the academy awarding the Nobel Literature Prize was remanded in custody Monday, pending the verdict in his trial. Jean-Claude Arnault, a major cultural figure in Sweden and the husband of Swedish Academy member Katarina Frostenson, was on trial for two counts of rape of a woman that allegedly took place in 2011. The accusations against him triggered a crisis within the prestigious academy, with seven members quitting and the body announcing that no prize will be awarded this year....&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://apnews.com">The Associated Press</source></item><item><title>German court releases Iraqi suspect in Chemnitz stabbing - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-protests-suspects/german-court-releases-iraqi-suspect-in-chemnitz-stabbing-idUSKCN1LY1VD</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEOm-iFXZQlFBO7gf_wJigbIqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:59:27 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-protests-suspects/german-court-releases-iraqi-suspect-in-chemnitz-stabbing-idUSKCN1LY1VD" target="_blank"&gt;German court releases Iraqi suspect in Chemnitz stabbing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A German court on Tuesday released an Iraqi asylum seeker detained last month over the fatal stabbing of a Cuban-German man that set off violent protests by far-right radicals, his lawyer and a prosecutor said. A Syrian man who was also detained over the stabbing of the man remains in custody, the prosecutor said. A third suspect is still on the run and prosecutors think he and the Syrian were involved in killing the 35-year-old carpenter, in the eastern city of Chemnitz, the prosecutor said. The Iraqi's lawyer complained about his client's detention. "Today's revocation of the arrest warra...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>A cell became his cemetery - CNN</title><link>http://www.cnn.com/interactive/2018/08/us/ice-detention-stewart-georgia/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEC7RxGGMBQPlnXWSM3yY2OwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowocv1CjCSptoCMPrTpgU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 15:23:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/interactive/2018/08/us/ice-detention-stewart-georgia/" target="_blank"&gt;A cell became his cemetery&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;CNN&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is part of "Inside America's Hidden Border," a series about one of the largest immigrant detention centers in the US. Read about a fight against the odds, the women who wait and the view outside the gates. Miguel Montilla was in the law library when the banging started. Over and over he heard it -- the sound of a man screaming as he pounded the wall of the cell next door. When a guard came by, Montilla listened. The man in Cell 102 said he was suffering from psychosis. "I hear voices talking to me," he said. "And they're bothering the shit out of me." Montilla climbed on a toilet and s...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.cnn.com">CNN</source></item><item><title>You've Served Your Time. Now Here's Your Bill. - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-prison-strike-labor-criminal-justice_us_5b9bf1a1e4b013b0977a7d74</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEIj2orRGZOlpSq-QzE1K9pEqFggEKg0IACoGCAowxYgCMIBNMJeP1AM</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 13:00:06 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/opinion-prison-strike-labor-criminal-justice_us_5b9bf1a1e4b013b0977a7d74" target="_blank"&gt;You've Served Your Time. Now Here's Your Bill.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last Sunday, on the anniversary of the Attica prison riot, a nationwide prison strike ended. Billed as likely the largest prison work stoppage in the country’s history, it started on Aug. 21, the anniversary of the assassination of Black Panther Party field marshal and prison activist George Jackson. For two weeks, inmates in 17 states planned to refuse their work assignments. Because of the lack of transparency in the prison system, it’s not clear how many incarcerated people actually joined the strike. No matter how many people participated in the collective action, the strike succeeded i...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.huffingtonpost.com">HuffPost</source></item><item><title>'They threw my baby in the trash': Majority of women in US House unite on bill protecting pregnant prisoners from 'shameful' conditions - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/pregnant-women-prison-jail-us-house-prisoners-birth-karen-bass-mia-love-a8535326.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGK3nBdG_9NbevK55vSY4V0qFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 15:28:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/pregnant-women-prison-jail-us-house-prisoners-birth-karen-bass-mia-love-a8535326.html" target="_blank"&gt;'They threw my baby in the trash': Majority of women in US House unite on bill protecting pregnant prisoners from 'shameful' conditions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of all of the heartbreaking things that have happened to Pamela Winn in her lifetime, nothing compares to the moment she learned she had lost her baby while haemorrhaging in a jail cell in Clayton County, Georgia. “I’m laying there, I’m bleeding, I’m shackled to a bed, I’ve got these two men down between my legs that I don’t know from Adam, and they’re there saying that they threw my baby in the trash,” she told The Independent of the moment, more than 10 years ago, when the doctors told her she had miscarried. “It’s not something I will ever forget. Ever.” It’s exactly the kind of experien...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>New California Law Terminates Bail And Risks Public Safety While Texas Seeks Reform - Forbes</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/chuckdevore/2018/09/10/new-california-law-terminates-bail-and-risks-public-safety-while-texas-seeks-reform/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFblmRcZCxsuCgScVFQ5hVsqFQgEKg0IACoGCAowrqkBMKBFMI_CEg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 21:58:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/chuckdevore/2018/09/10/new-california-law-terminates-bail-and-risks-public-safety-while-texas-seeks-reform/" target="_blank"&gt;New California Law Terminates Bail And Risks Public Safety While Texas Seeks Reform&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cash bail has its critics; make it better, don’t end it. With California Governor Jerry Brown’s signature on Senate Bill 10, the cash bail system, with 15 centuries of history, was ended in the Golden State. Bail’s demise will cause unneeded waves in California’s increasingly turbulent criminal justice system. When a person is accused of a crime, they are brought before a judge, informed of the charges against them, and may have bail set. The purpose of bail is to increase the chances that the accused will return to court for trial if released from jail. Cash bail has become unpopular in ma...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.forbes.com">Forbes</source></item><item><title>Protest by prison staff over violence and safety concerns called off after government seeks court injunction - The Independent</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/prison-staff-protest-violence-safety-concerns-court-injunction-government-stewart-justice-department-a8537661.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEJXalvQkpjYu-3DSeA8Z9UYqFggEKg4IACoGCAowzdp7ML-3CTCtyxU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:57:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/prison-staff-protest-violence-safety-concerns-court-injunction-government-stewart-justice-department-a8537661.html" target="_blank"&gt;Protest by prison staff over violence and safety concerns called off after government seeks court injunction&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Independent&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A protest by prison staff over violence and safety concerns has been called off by their union following an agreement with prisons minister Rory Stewart. The Prison Officers Association (POA) ordered its members to demonstrate outside prisons in England and Wales from 7am over “unprecedented” levels of violence. The union decided to take industrial action after the government was issued an official warning on Thursday over the deteriorating jails for the fourth time in nine months. Read more - Third of prison officers who quit leave within a year of starting - Number of prison officers resi...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.independent.co.uk">The Independent</source></item><item><title>White people make up largest proportion of British terror arrests - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/sep/13/white-people-make-up-largest-proportion-of-terror-arrests-figures-show</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELTIvtW12oTbWM4YsOpzP1wqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 14:33:33 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/sep/13/white-people-make-up-largest-proportion-of-terror-arrests-figures-show" target="_blank"&gt;White people make up largest proportion of British terror arrests&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;White people make up the largest proportion of arrested terrorism suspects for the first time in 13 years, official British figures show. There were 351 arrests for terrorism-related activity in the year to 30 June, a fall of 22% compared with the 449 arrests in the previous year, Home Office statistics show. The proportion of suspects recorded as white by the arresting officer increased by four percentage points to 38% in the period, while those deemed to be from an Asian background fell by seven percentage points to 37%. The proportion recorded as black fell by two points to 9%. It is the...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>US policewoman arrested after shooting black neighbour - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-10/texas-police-officer-arrested-after-shooting-black-neighbour/10222706</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKovihtiS95IxYozpcxzCWEqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 08:22:22 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-10/texas-police-officer-arrested-after-shooting-black-neighbour/10222706" target="_blank"&gt;US policewoman arrested after shooting black neighbour&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A white policewoman was arrested on Sunday (local time) over the off-duty shooting of her black neighbour in his flat in the United States last week. According to a police statement, Amber Guyger, 30, shot and killed her 26-year-old neighbour, Botham Jean, on Thursday after returning in uniform from work to the South Side Flats in Dallas, Texas, where they both had apartments. She reported the shooting to police and told officers who responded she had mistaken Mr Jean's apartment for her own. Officer Guyger was taken into custody and booked into the Kaufman County Jail, the Texas Department...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Prison guards vow to fight 'war of attrition' over privatisation plans - ABC News</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-10/sa-prison-guards-strike-over-privatisation-no-show-for-court/10221450</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEN8fLFXqCr7zKhyge5tAu8wqFggEKg4IACoGCAow3vI9MPeaCDDciw4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 02:10:00 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-09-10/sa-prison-guards-strike-over-privatisation-no-show-for-court/10221450" target="_blank"&gt;Prison guards vow to fight 'war of attrition' over privatisation plans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Court cases are being adjourned or held without the defendant present as South Australian prison guards strike over the State Government's plans to privatise the Adelaide Remand Centre. The strike means that all eight publicly run prisons across the state have been locked down today as guards walk off the job. But the lockdown is also impacting on the state's justice system, preventing prisoners from being brought to court or into video-link suites inside prisons for their case hearings. A Courts Administration Authority spokeswoman said matters would "still be listed as usual so there can ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.abc.net.au">ABC News</source></item><item><title>Texas police officer faces manslaughter charge over 'wrong flat' fatal shooting of neighbour - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/10/texas-police-officer-faces-manslaughter-charge-wrong-flat-fatal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEH17NjsasW8aQkDIBAln4-IqFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 08:18:44 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/10/texas-police-officer-faces-manslaughter-charge-wrong-flat-fatal/" target="_blank"&gt;Texas police officer faces manslaughter charge over 'wrong flat' fatal shooting of neighbour&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;An American police officer who says she mistook her neighbour's apartment for her own when she fatally shot him has been arrested on a manslaughter charge. Amber Guyger was booked into the Kaufman County Jail, in Dallas, Texas, after being taken into custody on Sunday over the off-duty shooting. She was later released on bond, having posting a £232,000 ($300,000) bail, according to reports. Ms Guyger fatally shot 26-year-old Botham Jean at the victim's apartment, having mistakenly entered the flat thinking it was her own. The 30-year-old, who has been on the force for four years, now faces ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Transgender person accused of rape is remanded into female prison and sexually assaults inmates within days - The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/06/transgender-person-accused-rape-remanded-female-prison-sexually/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHSBTu0OCEy10r9Cn1DQkA8qFggEKg4IACoGCAowm6R6MMKqCTCfrxU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 17:55:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/09/06/transgender-person-accused-rape-remanded-female-prison-sexually/" target="_blank"&gt;Transgender person accused of rape is remanded into female prison and sexually assaults inmates within days&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prison service has apologised after a transgender inmate, charged with raping a woman sexually assaulted four fellow inmates just days after being remanded into an all female jail. Convicted paedophile, Karen White, who was born Stephen Wood, was undergoing gender reassignment, but had not undergone full surgery, when she was accused of repeatedly raping woman in 2016. The 52-year-old, who had been previously been jailed in 2001 for a sex attack on a child, told the authorities she identified as a woman and was remanded into HMP New Hall near Wakefield, West Yorkshire. But within days o...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.telegraph.co.uk">The Telegraph</source></item><item><title>Cambodia opposition figure Kem Sokha under house arrest - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/cambodia-opposition-figure-kem-sokha-house-arrest-180910052227527.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHpWbTC5vWwWWMUi60TMJDAqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 13:39:21 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/09/cambodia-opposition-figure-kem-sokha-house-arrest-180910052227527.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cambodia opposition figure Kem Sokha under house arrest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cambodian opposition leader Kem Sokha has been released on bail and placed under house arrest after spending more than a year in prison on widely decried treason charges. The decision to grant bail to the president of the now-dissolved Cambodian National Rescue Party (CNRP) was made after considering his health conditions and "legal assurance that the accused would not flee from court proceedings", the government said in a statement on Monday. Hundreds of supporters gathered outside his home in the capital, Phnom Penh, following his release in the early hours of Monday. Kem Sokha was arrest...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Cardiff man appears in court on terrorism and explosives charges - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/sep/01/cardiff-man-appears-in-court-on-terrorism-and-explosives-charges</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFBxSMnEdvtUmFAhVNnV9CQqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 15:19:49 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2018/sep/01/cardiff-man-appears-in-court-on-terrorism-and-explosives-charges" target="_blank"&gt;Cardiff man appears in court on terrorism and explosives charges&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man accused of making high explosives at his home in Cardiff has appeared in court, charged with terrorism and explosives offences. Police found explosive substances in the fridge and shed during a raid at the home of Edward John Harris, 27, on Wednesday. Harris is also accused of possessing manuals for making explosives. Harris, of Ely in Cardiff, appeared at Westminster magistrates court on Saturday and spoke only to confirm his name, date of birth, address and that his nationality is “white British”. The hearing lasted less than 20 minutes. He is charged with four counts of making or p...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Buying your way out of jail is wrong. It's time to end America's bail system - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/aug/30/abolish-bail-bonds-cash-bail</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHSNaZVp1FQNribc0baBUGoqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTC9vBU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2018/aug/30/abolish-bail-bonds-cash-bail" target="_blank"&gt;Buying your way out of jail is wrong. It's time to end America's bail system&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beginning this summer, you will not see bail bond advertisements on Google or Facebook. In May, the tech giants announced they will no longer permit the bail bond industry to broadcast ads on their platforms. They stated that enabling an exploitative industry that preys on low-income communities and people of color is a breach of their terms of service. Currently, the majority of people held in American jails are awaiting trial The commercial bail industry and its big insurance backers hover over the American criminal justice system, siphoning wealth and opportunity from poor communities. T...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Uganda: Court frees jailed opposition MP Bobi Wine - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/08/uganda-court-frees-jailed-opposition-mp-bobi-wine-180827065231995.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEHM5axkMW9U_hTVY3S1eI94qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 10:13:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2018/08/uganda-court-frees-jailed-opposition-mp-bobi-wine-180827065231995.html" target="_blank"&gt;Uganda: Court frees jailed opposition MP Bobi Wine&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert Kyagulanyi, a musician-turned-MP whose arrest prompted protests in Uganda, has been granted bail by a court in the northern city of Gulu. The opposition lawmaker and 11 others were freed on a 'non-cash' bail on Monday. The court did not approve the bail application of more than ten other suspects charged alongside the MP. Kyagulanyi, who is better known by his stage name, Bobi Wine, is charged with treason. They were arraigned over their alleged role in the pelting with stones of the President Yoweri Museveni's convoy after a local election rally. Military prosecutors on Friday dropp...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item></channel></rss>