<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><channel><generator>NFE/5.0</generator><title>Blaise Compaoré - Latest - Google News</title><link>https://news.google.com/topics/CAAqIggKIhxDQkFTRHdvSkwyMHZNREZ4WkdOa0VnSmxiaWdBUAE?hl=en-NG&amp;gl=NG&amp;ceid=NG:en</link><language>en-NG</language><webMaster>news-webmaster@google.com</webMaster><copyright>2018 Google Inc.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 12:48:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><description>Google News</description><item><title>French court approves extradition of brother of ex-Burkina Faso president - Reuters</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-burkina-france-justice/french-court-approves-extradition-of-brother-of-ex-burkina-faso-president-idUSKBN1O41XO</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEp_VC6_2pgkmsuiV4nFwtkqFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:47:12 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-burkina-france-justice/french-court-approves-extradition-of-brother-of-ex-burkina-faso-president-idUSKBN1O41XO" target="_blank"&gt;French court approves extradition of brother of ex-Burkina Faso president&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Paris court of appeal on Wednesday approved an extradition request by Burkina Faso's government for the brother of ex-Burkinabe president Blaise Compaore, a court spokeswoman said on Wednesday. Police detained Francois Compaore at Charles de Gaulle airport in Paris in October 2017 on an international arrest warrant related to the 1998 murder of Norbert Zongo, who published Burkina Faso's Independent newspaper. The killing of Zongo, who had been investigating the murder of a driver who worked for Francois Compaore, became a symbol of repression during Blaise Compaore's 27-year rule, which ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>General Denies Leading Burkina Faso Coup - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/general-denies-leading-burkina-faso-coup/4674080.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFKnP0_21cQ3M-9zZn6D3HMqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 14:47:04 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/general-denies-leading-burkina-faso-coup/4674080.html" target="_blank"&gt;General Denies Leading Burkina Faso Coup&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A general denied leading a deadly 2015 coup attempt in the West African state of Burkina Faso, in his first trial testimony on Monday. "I neither ordered, nor planned, nor organized, nor executed what some people are calling a coup d’état on September 16, 2015," Gilbert Diendere told a military court in the capital Ouagadougou. "I just faced up to a given situation on the advice of mediators and by agreement with the military hierarchy," said Diendere, who appeared in the packed courtroom in a red beret and military fatigues. Diendere is the former head of the elite Presidential Security Re...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Pan-Africa festival of film projects a renewed sense of optimism - The Guardian</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/feb/27/pan-africa-festival-of-film-projects-a-renewed-sense-of-optimism</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEGleitKQG8hUMD1sqlxd3BIqFggEKg4IACoGCAowl6p7MN-zCTDlkko</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 06:00:02 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/feb/27/pan-africa-festival-of-film-projects-a-renewed-sense-of-optimism" target="_blank"&gt;Pan-Africa festival of film projects a renewed sense of optimism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;The audience were taking no chances: as the sky brightened over the city in the morning, they lined up outside Ciné Burkina in scarves and horn-rimmed glasses, keen to be the first to catch Frontières. The film is the poignant tale of the multiple dangers faced by four African women trying to get across west Africa to Lagos by bus – including rape, extortion, hijacking and road accidents – and their developing friendship along the way. Most of those attending had crossed borders themselves to be there, albeit less hazardous ones than the Frontières characters, so it was a fitting start for ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.theguardian.com">The Guardian</source></item><item><title>Burkina Faso mining lost $1 billion to graft in decade: parliament - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-burkina-mining-corruption-idUSKCN12Q2QO</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFpmoZqGWXiYK8vQbYY3Ux8qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 20:14:17 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-burkina-mining-corruption-idUSKCN12Q2QO" target="_blank"&gt;Burkina Faso mining lost $1 billion to graft in decade: parliament&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OUAGADOUGOU (Reuters) - Burkina Faso lost nearly a billion dollars to corruption and mismanagement in the mining sector in the decade leading up to the fall of Blaise Compaore and the year after he was forced out, according to a parliamentary inquiry. The committee announced its findings late on Tuesday after a three-month investigation and called for charges to be brought against three ex-ministers as well as the former president's brother, Francois Compaore. None of the ex-officials named in the report, who are living in exile in neighboring Ivory Coast, could be reached for comment. The ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Suspects in arms depot raid claim torture, humiliation - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/suspects-arms-depot-raid-claim-torture-humiliation-170402062622610.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEEV_XXcWZN_QG__IBcO6cC8qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 07:55:52 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/04/suspects-arms-depot-raid-claim-torture-humiliation-170402062622610.html" target="_blank"&gt;Suspects in arms depot raid claim torture, humiliation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 20 Burkinabe soldiers on trial at a military tribunal over a failed raid on an arms depot last year have said they were tortured to extract their confessions. Almost all of them said they had suffered beatings, humiliation and food deprivation at the police camp where they were held after their arrest following the raid in January 2016, for which they have been on trial since Tuesday. "When I was arrested on January 25, 2016, I was abused by police officers from 2:00pm to 4:00pm," Sergeant Ollo Stanislas Poda said on Saturday. "I was beaten with a wet rope, threatened with an [automat...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Trial of Burkina Faso's Ex-leader, Ministers Begins After Delays - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/3843968.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiELcWAqZJboorX3qaY6OPAgoqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 01:27:29 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/3843968.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trial of Burkina Faso's Ex-leader, Ministers Begins After Delays&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A trial of Burkina Faso's former leader Blaise Compaore and his cabinet began Monday after delays, with the court dismissing calls from the defense to cancel the proceedings. Compaore, who fled during a popular revolt in 2014 as he sought to extend his 27-year rule of the West African country, is being tried in absentia. The former Western ally currently resides in exile in neighboring Ivory Coast, where he has since acquired citizenship and which refuses to extradite him. Along with around 30 former ministers, Compaore faces assassination charges for allegedly authorizing the use of force ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Burkina Faso: Coup attempt thwarted, says government - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/10/burkina-faso-coup-attempt-thwarted-government-161021154201818.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEFv0J7sA4mr29W0FwslcN34qFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 05:11:48 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2016/10/burkina-faso-coup-attempt-thwarted-government-161021154201818.html" target="_blank"&gt;Burkina Faso: Coup attempt thwarted, says government&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;Security officials in Burkina Faso said they had foiled another coup plot in the West African nation and blamed it on former presidential guards. The government said on Friday that it thwarted a "vast conspiracy" by forces loyal to ousted leader Blaise Compaore that aimed to seize power. About 30 men from the former president's security unit plotted to free prisoners who were part of a September 2015 coup attempt and then attack the presidential palace, said Interior Minister Simon Compaore. A local news website, Koaci.com, quoted the minister as saying the coup plotters also intended to ta...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Trial Delayed for Burkina Faso's Former President - VOA News</title><link>http://www.voanews.com/a/compaore-trial-burkina-faso/3828179.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEDxyMam5WPpWXb8VC5ZI3ZgqFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 16:18:42 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/a/compaore-trial-burkina-faso/3828179.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trial Delayed for Burkina Faso's Former President&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Burkina Faso court has postponed the start of the trial of ex-president Blaise Compaoré and his former Cabinet. The accused are being tried for their alleged role in the violent crackdown on the 2014 uprising that ultimately ended Compaoré’s nearly three decades in power. The much-anticipated trial of former president Blaise Compaoré and almost his entire former Cabinet was supposed to start Thursday. But instead, it was adjourned before it even began. According to sources within the Ministry of Justice, there was a scheduling conflict. The Lawyers' Association of Burkina Faso is holding ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item><item><title>Burkina Faso replaces army chief after series of attacks - Reuters</title><link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-burkina-security-idUSKBN14H1TL</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEKT-KgIzO1n9zx3U4Vkw8X4qFggEKg0IACoGCAowt6AMMLAmMLT5lwM</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 22:26:15 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/us-burkina-security-idUSKBN14H1TL" target="_blank"&gt;Burkina Faso replaces army chief after series of attacks&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Reuters&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;OUAGADOUGOU (Reuters) - Burkina Faso President Roch Marc Christian Kabore replaced army chief of staff Pingrenoma Zagre on Wednesday, the government said in a statement, after a string of deadly militant attacks, including against the security forces. The statement did not provide a reason for Zagre's replacement by Sadou Oumarou, formerly the inspector general of the armed forces, but military sources said the decision was prompted by the incidents. Attacks in Burkina Faso were relatively rare before an attack by al Qaeda-linked fighters on a hotel in the capital, Ouagadougou, that killed ...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.reuters.com">Reuters</source></item><item><title>Trial of ex-leader Blaise Compaore under way - Al Jazeera English</title><link>http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/05/trial-leader-blaise-compaore-170515111857706.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiED8tMsy8qpDiwnYRpIzE4_MqFAgEKgwIACoFCAowhgIwkDgw0O8B</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 12:22:51 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2017/05/trial-leader-blaise-compaore-170515111857706.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trial of ex-leader Blaise Compaore under way&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Al Jazeera English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;A closely-watched trial of Burkina Faso's Blaise Compaore, former president, and members of his cabinet is under way in the capital, Ouagadougou. Compaore, who fled to neighbouring Ivory Coast during a popular revolt in 2014 against his attempts to change the constitution and extend his 27-year-rule, is being tried in absentia. Along with 34 ex-government ministers, Compaore faces assassination charges for allegedly authorising the use of force against unarmed protesters during the uprising that toppled him, killing at least 24 people. READ MORE: Coup attempt thwarted, says Burkina Faso's g...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="http://www.aljazeera.com">Al Jazeera English</source></item><item><title>Security, Youth High on Macron's Agenda in Burkina Faso - VOA News</title><link>https://www.voanews.com/a/macron-meets-with-burkina-leader/4139761.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CAIiEMGUgJmM3ohvRhuLIRbYbv4qFwgEKg8IACoHCAowqc_1ATCe_xQw2pwi</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:58:50 GMT</pubDate><description>&lt;a href="https://www.voanews.com/a/macron-meets-with-burkina-leader/4139761.html" target="_blank"&gt;Security, Youth High on Macron's Agenda in Burkina Faso&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;VOA News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron met with university students in Burkina Faso Tuesday, as he kicked off a three-day trip to West Africa. He is the first French president in three decades to visit Burkina Faso. President Emmanuel Macron spent three hours on Tuesday at the University of Ouagadougou, discussing migration, climate change and terrorism with a room full of students. In his remarks, the French president said he would pursue equal partnership with African nations, breaking with the more paternalistic relationship of old, a relationship between France and its former colonies known a...&lt;/p&gt;</description><source url="https://www.voanews.com">VOA News</source></item></channel></rss>